<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Aha - I have it... yes I have got some annoying cold/cough/nasal cavity filled with thick green goo type bug which is threatening my smoking habit. Why? Well if I smoked now my lungs would be coughed up before my very eyes together with my enitre lower intestinal tract bolting for the back exit door...  Yes colds are great to reinforce the idea that smoking is bad for you and very expensive.... so why am I sitting here taunting myself with the idea that a "quick puff" couldn't do any harm? Those bastards at Marlboro and their secret addictive chemicals is the reason why!  So I have taken medical advice and stuffed a really hot curry down my neck so that the cold can be "sweated out". Sounds like a lovely process eh? My eyeballs feel like they are bulging now - I BLOODYWELL HATE BEING ILL!!!  On the limo front I have got my orders from HQ and have got a Hen Party this saturday night - lets hope they get so pissed that they lose any inhibitions and want a good servicing from their newly adopted limo driver who has got a bunged up nose, sweats like a pig, has bulging eyes and whose lungs and lower intestinal tract are flopping about his person.... Colds eh? I love 'em......   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well its called confessions of a limo driver and at the moment I confess to feeling bloody tired. I got home at 4am - which is early believe it or not... I had a job to take a bunch of South African potato farmers to a club called ZULU's - which seems quite appropriate seeing as they were all Afrikanas!  So after a long day and night I hit a sodding road cone knocked over by some pissed up motorist at 3.30 am this morning causing some damage to the Chevrolet Wagon I was driving - I hope I dont get docked any money cause I had no way of missing it.  Its now been confirmed - I am addicted to RED BULL. Its a fantastic way of keeping yourself alert on these long evenings out and helps to keep you out of Accident and Emergency.  I had some tosser last night flashing his lights at me and brake testing me - if I had an empty vehicle I would have rammed the bastard off the road and give his tiny brain a good kicking. It still amazes me how some people assume that they own the road and that it gives them the right to try and dominate every other road user into submission and move out of their way or compensate for their lack of vision in anticipating slower moving traffic - they obviously can't see further than the alcoholic stupour they are driving in.  So I awoke and the dim memory of seeing 2 of my cats looking suspicious hanging round the sideboard last night when I got in is reinforced by my parents moaning about a half dead - half alive mouse chased to an inch of its life by Rosie and Jelly ( the 2 usual suspect cats ). The little devils had it cornered last night and just sat there pretending to be admiring the view of the sideboard - devious creatures.... I love 'em!  I am getting concerned now as my dad is bitching about a small piece of carpet which has vanished - hmmm Rosie Jelly and Doophus will have to calm down before I get kicked out.... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>