<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Well, what can I say? I'm starting a blogger... is that what they call it? Anyways, I call this entry as my introduction... since this is my first entry... I have to tell you something about myself. My name is Gloreina G. Peregrino-Montevirgen... yes... I'm married!!! I am an Engineering graduate from some school somewhere in Manila and I'm a frustrated doctor.... a very long story that you will get bored with.. so.. never mind... :)       Anyways.. where was I? Oh yeah... me.. my least favourite topic.... what can I say about myself? I'm a nature lover.. I love reading books... watching movies... listening to that radio, hiking, swimming and meeting new people.. I can talk almost about anything under the sun and really like expressing myself through art. I'm most of the time... well... people say.. happy-go-lucky... but that's something I just put up in front. I suffer from manic deppression... meaning when I get deppressed, I become WHACKO.. yeah... somewhat of a morbid type of whacko... I spent a year of my life in that dark period and well.. I'm trying to get away from that... but well, one step each day.. as you could say...      People... I'm afraid of them... they just don't know it.. I want to be friends with them but I also have this wall that I can't seem to put down... I love helping people... it's in my blood you could say but there are just some people who takes advantage of your kindness... and I'm a sucker for that.. People says that I have no air of mystery... Yeah right... they do not know my secrets... the ones that I dare not tell anybody... My thoughts always roams about something I cannot disclose.. This is actually the nearest thing I ever came in revealing it.       Let's change the topic... I'm blabbing... I'm currently working as a call center agent in peoplesupport.. a call center office in Makati.. you guys would probably know about it... oh well... my mind is drifting again... I do this most of the time...can't seem to focus on one subject... I guess I better end this now... I'll just wite again..  
     

    
</post>


<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       hah... I can finally breathe easily... just today I got a message that I'm already a regular employee at my office...it's about time... I have worked really hard for this job and also to stay in it. For 6 months, I have worked my butt off... taking calls and well, sacrificing... for the sake of my baby. That's the reasin I'm still here in this office. For my baby. She's my life. I don't think I'll be able to survive without her. I want to give her everything I can have and I would do everything for her. I sometimes regret that because of this work, I don't have much time for her. When I get home, I would be able to see her amile, kiss her abit, hug her once or twice before falling off to sleep due to exhaustion. When I wake up, she's already asleep and all I can do is look at her, stroke her... sigh...         Now, I'm not so sure that I will be able to stay long on this job.. I'm hoping that I wil be able to do so... you know.. stay... but no one really knows your future... For now, I'm happy to say that I'm getting there.. slowly but surely... and I'm happy to be where I am today. :)  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>