<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG school starts 2 morrow!!!!!!!!!!!!! that's soo kool i mean y not start ur 8th school, i mean thhere is soo much 2 learn and get lost in! HAHA not i love school yeah but starting ur 8th school AAAHHHHHH i mean that 2!! i can't wate 2 c all of my fiends again but most of um i have all ready seen in band camp and @ the dance so yeah i don't know what they joy is any more!! exept that i am single! any 1 is u read this then comment on it please and thank u          ~Me~  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i am single right know and that's good 4 what has been going on recentlly w/ every thing and just about every body. the dance last night was sooooo much fun. and my cat is liking my leg.eeeeeeewwwwwwwww o well i love her so it's ok.      ~Sierra~  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok so like krista is mad @ me i guess. i mean it is soo dumb y she is i mean all i did was comment 2 a couple of her things. i mean WHAT THE HECK THAT'S  Y THEY MAD THIS. o well she'll get over it  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey there every 1 i feel like such a dork right know because i have my glasses on. HAHA lol i am like REALLY bored right know and can't wate untill 2 morrow. because i have church, then gater fest (a peparally really), then a dance. 2 bad that Brett was A.grounded. B. not allowed 2 cum because it would really have been great going w/ him. well n2m else just that i had a  blast @ molly's house.!!!!  it was soo funny. well i gtg ttyl  lyl  bye                 ~Sierra~  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey there Kari had a good idea i will do what she did and if u dont' know what i am i am talking about i will show u.   Molly- we had tons of fun talking on the phone 4 hours, band exhabtion, and movies. Allyson- hanging out and movies Kari- comeca , mission trip (ALL WAYS REMEMBER THE BAFFALO!!!) , and WOF and OOF, (expeacally when we went and did those "little" kids rides. LOL and we got a chance 2 talk. and the camping trip Krista- the same as kari's comeca mission trip, camping trip, and the WOF OOF. Brett- comeca, movies, and my band exhabtion, Dana- park, and band camp (WE R SOOO BAND NERDS!!!!!!!!!) HAHA lol  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey there every 1 i'm good now he still hasn't called me but i'm good because he emailed me. and were cool now. i still miss him like crazy but sum day i will get over it but not now but sum day. I CAN'T WATE TELL HAPPANING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! i mean the experiace of it and the resalt. and Brett is going HAHA lol i am soo tired and hiper right know. o well  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG THIS IS LIKE SOOOOO BUGGING ME!!! i mean if people say that they r gunna call then they should!!!!!!!! ok know that that is off of my ches. what am i doing 2 day?? OOOO i remember i am going 2 a friend's church's lake thing or another and i hope that i don't loose my glasses because i am gunna be @ a lake so i have 2 take out my contacts. o well i'll live. OMG I AM FREAKING OUT!!! jk i mean high school starts in like 6 days. do i have my stuff ready 2 go?? no. am i scared 2 start a new school HELLO THIS IS MY 7 OR 8 SCHOOL'S SENCE KINDERGARDEN. am i pms'n?? dont' have a clue. did i really just right that HELL YEAH!! am i bored?? yeah am i hiper OOO YEAH!!!! what pop have i had ......um......MOUNTAIN DEW and id remember. i am just gunna end this before i say sum'n that i will regret.                                       LOVE YEAH ALL OF YEAH!!      ~Sierra~  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey there every 1 how r u? i'm fine just watting 4 a phone call.....cough........o well maybe sumtime he will call me. gtg lyl bye  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        hello there 2 every 1. WOW that was lame but o well ur'll live wont u. HAHA on u. i plan 2 right here a ton so right back 2 me.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>