<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, ok it's now sunday at 9:38 pm the thought of another week of work comes to mind making me relize how much i appreciate the weekend even thought it's just as busy as the work week. this weekend we had a birthday bbq for everyone in my sunday school class we had 17 people not including kids all in a 2 bedroom moblie home(kinda like packing as many sardines as possible into a small tin can) ,but to my surprise it worked. As another birthday comes and the candles are lit the hope that the fire department won't show up also comes to mind as much as i love fire trucks they have a tendency to ruin cakes. Wow that makes me feel old i need to relize that i'm only gonna be 27 but at this stage in life i have already gone through alot of the muck on this world that i don't wish upon my worst enemy, and besides your only as old as you feel right...Besides i still have one thing that means the world to me my kids and my future wife and the knowledge that no matter what happens in life all i have to do is cry out to god and he will carry me through it all...I shall continue to keep you up to date on all the happenings in life just continue to check back....LOTS OF LOVE TO THOSE WHO CARE 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello and thank you for taking the time to visit my blog. To begin I am 27 years old (on 8/18/04) am I divorced father of three wonderful children whom I love with all my heart and soul. My oldest son Nick is soon to be 8 and his hobbies include looking for creepy crawlies just like every other boy you may know. Kassandra is the next in line she is daddies princess at 6yrs old she's pretty much like any other little girl bent on making boys fall before her feet while looking sweet and innocent. Then there's Tyler 4 the youngest of the group and the cohort to Nickolas anywhere nick goes so goes Tyler. As for dad well i'm into drawing fantasy art, golf, and reading the Holy Bible as I try to follow gods commands for my life. Now as I said I am a divorcee I have to mention the one woman that has come into my life and helped restore order to an otherwise stressful life Amber my fiancee as of 6/18/04 wedding planned for summer of 05. Amber is the spark in life that has opened my eyes to life after divorce she has brought to me what it's like to be truely happy in an otherwise dark world.I lOVE YOU AMBER AND KIDS 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>