<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When you wake up in the morning, they are not so bad. In the middle of the night, it's a different story...  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're a Winter. You very much enjoy your time alone but do like other people's company sometimes. You just need your space. You have a few priviledged friends who saw past your colder exterior to find the true you. You can have pretty bad mood swings (though you hate to admit it) so you could be soft one second then storming around the next! But over all, you're a very pleasant person once people take the time to get to know you. You're a good friend for in-depth talks. You're very talanted when it comes to creative things.   urlLink   What season are you? (pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizzilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Congrats! Your a Pure Angel! Angels, as far as most of them go, are all compatabile creatures, but Pure ones simply are symbols of God. Pure Angels always appear when a child is born, when a rainbow is seen, or when someone shares their first kiss. They never grow old, an can appear in the shape of a naked woman with white, bold wings. Pure angels are the carriers of god, and show their love to everyone in the world.   urlLink   What Kind of ANGEL are you? (For Girls only) This Quiz has amazingly Beautiful Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizzilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your a Unicorn! Unicorns are pure, innocent, magestic creatures that have a spiraling white horn growing out of their forehead, and a white graceful, horses body. Unicorns represent the sign of purity, innocence, freindship, healing, rejeventation, and truth. Your horn is rare prized, but you tend to be naive, lured by a childs cry. Unicorns are reare, beautiful ans shy mythical creatures, and you are lucky to be one.   urlLink   What Mythical Beast are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizzilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm only putting this one in because of the awesome picture:     You're Element is Water. You are soft and serene at most times but like Wind, you're scary when you're mad. You proabaly have a talent is singing and even your speaking voice is lovely. You have an innocent type of beauty that makes you look younger than you are and you like close relationships with people.   urlLink  What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)    brought to you by   urlLink  Quizilla     urlLink     
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So I went to the airport yesterday. I saw all these people, they were going to all these places. I wished I was going somewhere, even for a little while but I'm not, I'm here & it bites! I would go away with my friends but their idea of a good holiday is going somewhere to sit on a beach somewhere all day (im asian...I don't need to tan :), going out every night drinking themselves into liver failure and going home with random men, not my style at all. I just want to go somewhere..where I can do a bit of shopping, maybe see some art, climb a tree/mountain &amp; just generally hang out. Grrrr!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...........................  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mood: It was angry....it is now relieved & a little less stressed =)   Listening to: The Corrs....umm now B2K      My Dad is leaving the country on Friday to open a business abroad...So I asked for Friday off work....I'm not going to see my dad for 6 months....& yet it took four hours for anyone to get back to me....Grrrrr ....Just because they CAN take four hours, they do...*shakes head* People on power trips need to have their brains re-connected or at least get them taken out of their butts! Anyway, I did something about it &amp; hopefully will see results in a few days...in the meantime I have Friday off, my first day off in about 8 months...I get to sleep in!! I have not had the chances to sleep in for about 4 months so yay for me *cheers alone* Other than that, a rather uneventful day :)      Rune thought: I wonder how long I can keep my kitty in the bank before it dies?  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mood: Tired...kind of grumpy (due to the tiredness methinks)   Listening to: umm...Whitney Houston :)      Doing this & playing Rune at the same time is pretty hard, I'm guessing it is a skill I will develop rapidly ;) Apart from tired, I'm feeling pretty good :) Work is annoying me at the mo, being a temp is kinda handy as I only have to give an hours notice if I want to leave...which I'm thinking I want to..I guess why I'm STILL there (after 8 months) is because it is my comfort zone...I know the work, the people, the politics....It's getting harder being there, people are not happy :( I may just go on a impulse..My agency will find me something, they always do (cos they are Angels) My diet is going great, im eating well & me &amp; my mate are walking round a lake everyday after work.....just gotta keep at it :)      Rune Report: Today was a good day in terms of levels, got to level 20 agility &amp; ranging, level 30 for mining, still working on smithing (got it to level 20 while typing this)....so much to work on...not to good in terms of hanging out with friends, they were not much at all :(   I dont like how my Rune chica bends down when she is smithing :/  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       .....If this will work  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I guess I should keep it simple. I do have a tendency to talk and talk (or should that be type &amp; type?) I'm not sure who will get to see this....just testing the blog thing out :)  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>