<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is that sort of day that I am not sure what direction I am exactly going in at the moment. My day started at 5:30am: I awake out of a deep sleep on a leather black sofa which I find to be very comfortable these past few weeks. I married a twice divorcee African American man with 2 children and lately it seems that we both are trying to find some sort of medium to this thing society called the American Dream or dreamly life of marriage with 2 teenage boys from a previous marriage. I awake and find a blank Television screen staring back at me. I was watching before I doze off to sleep while watching several movies with my teenage stepson called "The Perfect Score, School of Rock, and Dorm Daze. Before I drifed off to a deep sleep I remember glancing over at J.. and notice that he was staring at the screen blankly at the television when the movie Dorm Daze was featuring a clip with a women with bare tits kissing on another chick. I said nothing. I fell asleep. At 5:45am I began to make my coffee and smoked a cigarette in the front of my computer. While waiting for the coffee to perk, I sat in front of my laptop attempting to logon but to no avail the dam thing was not logging on. The information highway was clogged at that time of the morning. I gave up. I walked up the stairs to my sleeping husband around 6:30am C.. who was sound asleep. I called his name as I entered the room and said Good Morning C... He said Good Morning D.., I am still sleeping I need my rest. I did not give a rat ass that I was waking my husband. I was craving some immediate mental attention and needed to talk about mindless shit. I had a cup of coffee in my hand that I was willing to share with C. I said to C, I thought you had to be somewhere at 7am so I thought I would awake you for some quality time. He grunted and groan before sitting on the edge of the bed. D..I don't need to be anywhere until 10am, I am going back to sleep. I got very pissed off that he did not want to get up and hang out with me early in the morning and simply chat. He swallowd a few sips of coffee and asked what time is it. I don't know because we don't have a clock nearby. I did not care what time it was considering he has not been home in the evenings, he has been very busy working late night shifts. I spoke to him about my agenda for the day and I wanted him to tell me about his.  Fastforward an hour: Before he showered he suggested sex which lasted a good 5 minute before he came. He looked at me and said that he thought we would be making love. I said to C.., that is not making love that was simply a 5 minute fuck but that is OK. I really did not have the energy nor time to get pissed off from the act. I conveyed to him that there is a difference between Sex, Fucking and making love. We started our day and I am too tire right now to keep typing about my thoughts. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>