<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Feeling really happy tonight ...Doing my last night of night shift. Going to day shift next month. Next 5 days would be off for me ..Yet to make any plans yet.. Hope to meet up with a few of my friends again ..Eugene being one of them. Haven't had the opportunity to meet up with him since I've got into this new job.  Its rather cold at work place as I work in the server room. Have to find many ways to keep warm. I don't usually feel cold easily as those closer to me should know... But Itz really DARN COLD there ....Guess itz kept that way to ensure that the computers are working at optimum levels and not overheated.  Felt a little sick before coming to work. Don't know is it because I'm not used to working in the night shift. Think I'm getting a bit heaty down inside. But luckily, the next 5 days would be off for me ..So it ain't all that bad ... Wonder what i'll be up to the next 5 days .. Most of my friends would be busy doing their stuff, as it is the weekdays afterall.. Kinda surprised that some of them are actually helping me to count the days to my off days for me ...Touched :0)  Dad went to see the doctor again tonight. He's been having a bad stomach the past few nights. Hope he'll be alright soon.  Yah ok...Thats all for tonight ...Lets see what tomorrow brings .!!  DiLloN 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a rather fun day. Went out to meet Chin Chai this morning. I've not been able to meet up with him for about a year and a half already, as he was away in australia doing his degree. Its kinda amazing actually, that one year could just fly by like that ...Anyway, realised that he wanted to become an insurance agent with AIA. Its really weird, the paths we decide to take in the end after our education ...Some become dentist, some doctors, some going into network marketing, some becoming teachers, and ....you get the picture...Anyway, decided to ask him to recommend me a couple of insurance schemes that I could take up ..  After that. he had to head back to office, so I decided to go down to city hall as I had an appointment with Anthony in the evening for dinner. As it was only 2.45pm, I decided that I could catch a movie whilst waiting... Found myself watching Twin Effects II ..There were quite a few special effects, but I found that movie's storyline just average. Luckily it was only $6.50 ...  The movie ended at around 5pm, just in time to take a slow walk down to cityhall mrt to meet Anthony for dinner. We decided to go to Marina's food court for dinner. A change from the one at suntec, however it was closed for renovation. We ended up eating at Millenia's food court. We sat and chatted there for quite awhile about the 'birds and bees' ...after which we took a walk around Millenia. As we walked, we found ourselves at Riz Carlton Hotel. The decor inside that hotel was "WOW"..... even the toilets had hand towels ...A rare opportunity to use the toilets of such a posh hotel. ..hehe ...From there, we proceeded for home ...  After reaching home, I felt rather bored ...so I decided to try my luck to get Frank out for supper ....Managed to get him out to a coffee shop beside S11(our usual haunt for supper).  Decided to call it a day finally....Feeling rather tired now ...wonder how tomorrow would be like .. I'll proberly leave it till tommorrow ...for itz experience ........  DiLloN   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a very tiring day for me. Played scrabble online with Jaccob till 4am this morning. Ended up waking up at 10.30am in the morning. Before I knew it, lunch was round the corner. Didn't even have time to eat the bread that I bought from Carrefour yesterday night. It was really mind boggling to play scrabble so early into the morning when your brain juices ain't functioning at optimum levels. Remind me never to do that again ...  Had to rush home after lunch as the painters were coming by to paint the front door of my house. Ended up spending the afternoon watching LOTR III at home. As it was a three hour plus movie, by the time it ended, I had to go with my family to Hougang Mall for dinner with my extended family.  Oh if you did not know, we had been doing this for the last couple of years already ..Dinner at Hougang Mall on Sunday evenings. It is becoming sort of a family tradition. I had a bowl of homemade noodles and I was lucky as the noodles were pipping hot when it was served. At least it managed to keep me warm, as I was sitting right under the airconditioner. Darn cold ...  Came back with a new padlock for our gate, as the old one was starting to give us problems .. Mum also bought a new tshirt and before long we were back at home again ...hopefully tomorrow would be more eventful ...  DiLloN 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>