<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I'd like to take this time to share with you 1 of my techniques on going to sleep, when you just can't stop tossing & turning. Here lately I've been doing just that; Jenn has to go to sleep around 10pm or so (she actually has to get up for work, hehe) so I usually go to bed too. Everything was going fine until about 3 or 4 days ago. Now I just wind up laying there & rolling around until 11, 12, or like last night, 1. So here is what I do in times like these. (CAUTION: Extreme Geekness Ahead) Do you remember the scene in  urlLink "The Empire Strikes Back"  where Yoda is on Luke Skywalker's back &amp; they're running through the woods? Ok, Luke is asking all these questions & finally Yoda says, "No more will I teach you today. Clear your mind of questions......mmmmmm........mmmmmmm..."Then Luke puts him down on the ground &amp; he starts playing with his stick. Ok, that's the scene I think of to go to sleep. I just follow Yoda's advice, clear my mind of questions & whatever else that's running through there &amp; try to relax. It definitely helps. If you think I'm full of crap &amp; Yoda is stupid, you better watch it, because you know he could kick your ass. Cheers. Phil P.S. The most important part of the quote is the "mmmmmm.....mmmmmmm.." 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I really have nothing to blog about today, so I figured I'd introduce you to my hometown of  urlLink Henderson . It's in West TN, about 75 miles east of Memphis & about 30 miles north of the MS state line. It had only 1 traffic light growing up, but now it has a couple, with plans for more! Yeah progress is a bitch. Anyways, you can click on the link for the hometown newspaper, &amp; read all about the rash of burglaries that is terrorizing the western part of the county.  After that, you can blow your brains out because you were so goddamn bored that you actually clicked on the link.  Have a nice day.  Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, we just watched a real winner.  Smokey & the Bandit III.  This is one of the crappiest movies I own, have rented, watched, seen, suffered through,you name it.......What the hell happened?  The 1st one was great, then the 2nd one started the sucking slide, & then.....oh Jesus.  I guess Burt Reynolds had 3 movies in his contract & tried to get out of it, because he made a 2 minute appearance at the end of this one.  God, this shit sucked.  Cheers.   Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, as you have noticed I didn't post yesterday.  That may have something to do with the fact that I was slightly intoxicated on Tuesday night/Wednesday morning.  Never, ever go to Eric's house & drink beer &amp; then let him pour you a "shot" of Southern Comfort.  Needless to say I was finished for the night.  I don't think I can drink like the old days; getting old really sucks I guess.  That was my only real talent too...great, now I really am worthless.  Anyways, I gotta finish scrubbing the bathtub & toliet now.  Cheers.   Phil  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, Jenn eats the last piece of chocolate pie last night, then she eats the last ice cream sandwich, while we're watching Smokey & the Bandit II (it sucks, compared to the first one, by the way).   So I'm left with no sweets.  WTF?  So we went to Walmart awhile ago, & we were gonna get the Turtle Brownies, like we took to her parents' house the other night.  Sadly they were out of them, so we got Double Fudge ones.  Sounds good right?  Except SOMEBODY forgot to look at what size pan they go in, & we got the small version instead of the 13" x 9" size.  Now I'll blow through those in a heartbeat!  I mean, for crying out loud, what do I keep her around for?!  She's supposed to know these little food dimensions, but nooooooo.....I gotta find them, buy them, & eat them too!  Next thing you know she'll want to me to bake them also.  Jeez......married life is rough.  Cheers.   Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Steve is probably the most underrated musician around.  I discover more & more good stuff of his everyday; & I'm not talking just "Valerie" &amp; "Higher Love".  These were giant hits back in  the 80's!  Of course his Spencer Davis Group, Blind Faith, & Traffic stuff are good too.....but in the 80's he took the title.  I mean come on "Back in the High Life Again" won 2 Grammys, 1 of those was album of the year!  The Grammys aren't exactly geared towards talent (look at them now, "OutKast wins album of the year?"  gag me with a fucking spoon), but at least they used to be.  Oh well.  Long live Steve.  Cheers.                 Phil I hope he's not dead or something. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I finally drug myself outta bed this morning.  I was sitting on the edge of the bed, looking at my feet when I noticed something dark on the floor.  Having just awakened & not having my glasses on (I'm blind as a bat) I couldn't make out what it was.  I bent down & hovered my face right over it &amp; guess what......it was a good ol' friendly neighborhood roach!  So, I went & got some paper towels &amp; disposed of his carcass.  I'm sure I breathed in some of his death fumes, & now I'll get some South American cockroach disease; but ...hey....it'll be something to talk about, anyways.  Cheers.    Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, we get ever closer to a total family, internet, geek reunion.  Now Jenn has entered the fray with her own blog.  Just click the title for a trip to the lair of the white worm.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's another good blog of useless ramblings.  The 1 & only Mr. Spud has started a site.  He'll be posting audio clips of Sweetbread soon, so don't worry folks.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, to kind of piggyback on what Kid_Lysol was saying on his blog about the music industry, I also think that music today sucks!!!!  I keep the ol' XM dialed on channel 8.  That's the 80's channel for all of you still stuck with the FM; you're all at the mercy of the local radio channels & their master (ClearChannel).  Now, I have heard rumors that ClearChannel owns a stake in XM, & maybe it's true, but...whatever, they still play good stuff.  I mean right now I'm listening to "Devil Inside" by INXS, & before that it was "Maneater" by Hall &amp; Oates.  I mean, come on, you can't hear that on the radio.....(at least not in Augusta).  Speaking of Hall & Oates, I knew a guy in the Air Force named Harry, who told me that (oh, update...Pet Shop Boys just came on...sorry) his uncle was driving in Colorado &amp; got rear ended.  When he got out of the car, John Oates got out of the other one, & was pissed off.  Apparently John is really, really short.  So he threatened Harry's uncle, the uncle threatened him, etc....The cops finally showed up & they got it settled, &amp; nobody at the county jail had to listen to "Possession Obsession" over & over.  That's my story for the day.  Oh yeah, my job hunting this morning went as you'd expect.  That's why I'm sitting here writing this crap.  Cheers.                   Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For all of you out there wanting to read a good blog, full of ramblings, try Kid_Lysol & his Silent Parade page.  It'll blow your mind, man........ 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I just finished eating my 2 biscuit breakfast.  Now I gotta go brush the hair off my teeth, & comb my shaggy mop of hair.  I'm supposed to be at the Augusta Jobshop around 10am.  The chick there wants me to fill out an application & talk with her about what kind of jobs they have available.  So, if any past indicators of my job huntin' experiences in this  town apply, ......it'll be a total waste of my time.   I guess I gotta do something though, I'm about to go bananas.  If I had a damn job, we'd be rolling in it; but......I don't....so......we're not.  ARGHHH!!!  Only a few more months to go before I can forget the stench of this hole called Augusta.  Cheers.               Phil    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So much for the weekend. It pretty much flew by with little accomplished. Slept in twice, cooked brownies and a pie... ate at the Twisted Chicken and my parents' house. My how time flies... I've really noticed it now that I'm a little older. I started college 6 years ago.  6 years!  I've already finished my first year of teaching. I'm no longer a newbie. People look at me like I'm supposed to know what I'm doing! And then I realize... I  do  know what I'm doing! I'm not a kid anymore... where did the time go? I think that I may finally realize the truth in the statement "youth is wasted on the young." And I'm not even that old yet. What happens when I reach 30? 40? 70? Aches and pains... not able to move around as well... my own kids looking at me like I'm crazy... yikes.  If only we could extend those tender years when we saw the magic of wishing on a star, and still got excited at the prospect of a visit from Santa. When we stared in awe at the money the Tooth Fairy left and the Easter basket that was empty the night before. If I knew then what I know now... I'd savor every minute. We're in such a big hurry to grow up, and then when we do... all we want is to be a kid again.  But maybe if we keep that kid in our hearts and look to life with excitement, wondering what will come around the next corner... we never really have to grow up.  Maybe.  :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, I hate having just 1 posting......so here's #2.  We're about to leave for Jenn's parent's house.  We're eating a roast, & we're taking brownies for dessert.  I'm not really hungry because we already stuffed our faces today....but hey....gotta keep my fat streak going.  Cheers.     Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, Eric told me about Travis having a blog, & Jenn made me make one of my own, so I guess you could say that we just jumped on the Travis bandwagon.  (Sorry, man)  So, here it is; my own blog filled with the most mind numbing, useless, crap.  It's basically gonna be filled with whatever garbage my poor excuse for a brain can dream up.  I'll try to update it regularly, but it'll be hard, what with my busy schedule during the week & all.  Cheers.                                                                                                     Phil  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I picked up the book Jenn is reading lately (although it is just like all the other ones she's read since we met). It's a nice little  urlLink Harlequin  called "Fool for Love". I was thumbing through while she was blogging. I wanted to see exactly what the female mind needs to ingest for reading stimulation (wink...wink) Yes, I already knew the answer, but I wanted to see for myself ok? It's basically a shitty story that some chick makes up that surrounds all the graphic sex scenes. So I guess women read through about 20 pages of crap, then 10 pages of hot, dirty action...then 20 more pages of fluff, etc...That's all well & good, but as I brought up to Jenn, these are the things that your moms &amp; grandmas read. It's actually disturbing; especially when you think back to a time where you were in their presence & they were reading. You think it's a nice day, birds are singing, blue skies, not a care in the world...but across the room your granny is reading about "mounds of love pudding, &amp; steamy bulges". Now true, they've been around the block, & if they have kids &amp; grandkids, then of course they've taken the one-eyed snake to the optometrist a few times. But, when you realize it you wish you weren't as curious &amp; left the book alone. I feel really funky, like I need to go take a bath. Cheers. Phil 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, as you have seen on  urlLink Jenn's  & Mr. urlLink Spud's  websites we won the $50 at the Limelite last night. The best part of it was the usual teams didn't get jack shit! Oh well, the fat nasty chicks on their teams need to lay off the beer calories anyways. That's all I am going to say on winning; but I would like to touch on the current crisis of the week around here, & that is the public smoking ban. I think that the government &amp; public(as usual) has its priorities mixed up. Smoke fumes are noxious, true, but something is even more offensive than that & needs to be banned. Yes, I am talking about the dreaded disease of many towns with military installations. All of the local  urlLink GIs  that invade the bars &amp; fill up the taxi cabs on the weekends are very hard on my delicate senses. Not only do they smoke (air pollution), scream & yell (noise pollution), but they attempt to be funny (brain pollution). Someone needs to tell them that if you act gay, I won't think you're cool, I'll think you're gay. Oh well though, they are hardcore killing machines, &amp; if they wanna let off some of the stress of rigorous combat at Ft. Gordon, who am I to complain. Cheers. Phil 
     
    
</post>


<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This weekend passed by like a rocket.  We didn't do much (which was just fine with me), but now it's time to go to bed, and I have to get up and go to school tomorrow.  Phillip reminded me this evening that we hadn't made the trip to Wal-Mart that I needed to take.  I needed to go and buy prizes for my kids.  So we finished our cups of coffee and took the truck over to Wally World.  I headed straight for the toy section.  I asked my students what kinds of prizes they wanted me to have, and they told me.  Holy Crap.  Yu-Gi-Oh.  Bratz.  Hot Wheels.  Light up yo- yo.  Transformers.  Did you know how expensive toys have gotten?  I walked out of Wal-Mart with one bag.  And I payed over $50 for it.  As we were walking out to the truck, Phillip brought up an interesting point.  He remembered that as a kid, he didn't get things like these.  He wasn't so easily bought.  I remembered as well... I don't ever remember having to be bribed to behave.  And that's really what it is, no matter what the text books say.  Extrinsic motivation.  Working for something that you want.  Are we babying children these days?  Or have families changed so much that children are being exposed to the harshness of life to early... and they can't handle it?  Then again... I am in SpEd.  Is it just that  these  kids can't handle life?  Do they get away with more at home?    Or are they a product of their parents?  Were their parents this troubled and no one noticed?  Agh.  My head hurts.  peace out, yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We won!  We actually won!  We went to trivia night, played the game, and actually won the $50 bar tab with only 3 players.  Philaces, Mr. Spud, and I pretty much sucked for most of the game.  But we managed to pull it out by... not betting much at the end.  We only bet 5 pts.  So when we got the question wrong, it was ok!  This may be our strategy from now on.  We also found out that we can save the bar tab and use it whenever we want to, and that we can buy food, drinks and merchandise as well.  We also got a free t-shirt, and Mr. Spud got a poster of a girl when he bought a St. Pauli's.  All in all, not a bad night at all!  Life is good.  peace out, yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok.  So not that long ago, my husband, Phil,  urlLink awoke to find a roach  right next to our bed.  Today, we've found  two .  And I'm not talking about little bugs... I'm talking the kind that could probably take the trash out to the dumpster for us.  Big suckers that'll look you square in the eye and say, " Now  what are you going to do?"     Now, Phil and I keep a pretty clean house.  We take the trash out daily, don't leave dirty dishes in the sink, and sweep and vacuum on a regular basis.  We even put all of the food up in tupperware and in the fridge right after we eat dinner.  So what's the deal?  Why are we being attacked by probably my least favorite insect of all time?  Beats the hell out of me.   Both of the roaches today have been in the bedroom, too.  And I  know  we don't eat in there.  I can't even figure out how they are getting in.  I see no cracks of any size, let alone one big enough for the first monster we saw today.  And I do know that roaches can fit through holes of about any size.  But I see no holes!  So where are they hiding?  Maybe we need to call the  urlLink Orkin Man .  Before we start seeing  urlLink other friends .  It is my firm belief that all bugs in the house are evil.  And they will face the wrath of the Raid can.  But it would be better if they never showed their ugly muggs to begin with.  Any other ideas on keeping the creepy crawlies out?   peace out, yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes being a teacher sucks.  When exactly am I supposed to make my copies for my students?  After school, of course.  And when is everyone else supposed to make theirs?  Well, after school, of course.  That makes for major congestion at the copier.  At one of my schools the copies are made for us.  We have to turn in what we want copied... with a three day turn around.  So if you need something quick... you're out of luck.  At the other school, you get to make your own copies.  But we only get 300 a semester. (You blow through them quickly when you have to make 3 copies of education plans that are written for each SpEd student... and each plan is at least 10 pages long.)  But I guess I have the best of both worlds... I get copies at both schools... so if I can wait and don't need something right away, then I can turn them in.  But if I need them tomorrow, I can make them myself.  One day, every child will have a laptop and we won't have to make copies at all... we'll have the kids upload the pages.  Of course, "one day" is about 50 years away, but hey... I can hope, right?  Don't crush my dreams!  peace out, yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know, people ask me all the time, "So how's married life?"  And I always answer, "It's good!  I'm enjoying it!"  But we all know that's just a polite answer.  In the south, when someone asks you, "how are you?", most of the time all they want in response is a "Good, you?"  The answer I really want to give is, "It's absolutely wonderful.  In the actual relationship, not much changed after the wedding.  We get along the same... do about the same things... treat each other the same way that we did before we got married.  But it's very comforting to know that for the rest of our lives, we'll have each other.  Deep down inside I know that I just married someone that loves me no matter what.  He wants for me all of the things that I want for myself, and vice versa.  From now until one of us dies, we'll be together.  A support when things are crappy.  Someone to be proud of you when you accomplish a goal.  Someone who didn't have to love you, but does anyway.  And though from day to day, not much is different from the way we were before we got married... that commitment is still there.  "A lot of people tell me, 'Oh, you just got married.  You'll feel differently after a year.  The honeymoon stage will be over.'  Well, maybe for them.  How do they know?  Are they that unhappy in their marriages?  I know that 50% of all marriages end in divorce.  Do they have to bring it up when they talk to me?  Oh, they don't say it directly.  They say, 'The honeymoon stage will be over.'  I'll just say I hope not.  If this is a 'honeymoon stage', it's gonna be a really long one.  "I do know this.  When we said till death do us part, we meant it.  I don't think either one of us will give up that easy.  Especially not once we have kids.  "I know you're thinking, 'this kid doesn't know her elbow from her butt.'  But a  commitment  is a  commitment.       "So married life is good.  I'm enjoying it."  Think they'd stick around long enough to hear all that?  peace out yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If per chance you wander on to this site and you don't know me, let me introduce you to my internet family!  There's  urlLink Philaces , my husband, lost in his Black Hole;  urlLink Mr. Spud , my brother, playing in his Guitar Sandbox, and our friend  urlLink Kid_Lysol , marching in his Silent Parade.  If you get a chance, check them out!  peace out, yo! :) jenn 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Being a teacher, as I am, I've learned a few things about the dynamics of families.  Especially the families near the poverty level.  I work in two schools... one in a small town where everyone lives in a trailor park, and the other in a very large school in a somewhat urban community. (Believe it or not, these two schools are only 7.5 miles apart.)  There are many families at these schools near the poverty level.  A teacher friend of my told me that often when families are that poor the parents don't talk to the children.  When I first heard that statement, I think I glazed right over it and didn't think about it really.  "Aw, that's sad.  Anyway..."  But now I'm seeing the effects.  Let's really think about this.  These parents don't talk to thier children.  Now, they are under pressure to try to provide.  And often they are tired at the end of the day.  If they have jobs, it's often manual labor.  But they don't talk to their children!  EVER.  They fuss ("get outa there!"), they yell ("Boy, you better sit DOWN!"), but they don't talk.  No "how was your day?" or "let me read you a story" or "look at the pretty bug!"... can you imagine?  Can you imagine what life would be like if for the first 4 years of your life... no one talked to you?  And we wonder why these kids have learning problems.  No one talks to you at home, and then... THEN you go to school.  And all they do is talk.  And they want you to answer questions.  And they want you to play nicely with your classmates.  They (the teachers) expect that your parents have talked to you.  They think you understand what they're saying to you... when they ask you what you want for lunch, you have no idea what's going on.  This is beyond my comprehension.  But then again, I've never lived near the poverty level.  peace out, yo! jenn 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, yes. I too must join in. Not to be outdone by the boys, I've created my own little space on the wild, wild web. I probably won't be posting quite as much as you guys do, but hey... I'll do my best.  Now... about this whole music thing. I'm thinking that ultimately, music is in the ear of the listener. If you think it's music, and you like it, then more power to ya. So the guy with the mohawk and the skateboard likes to listen to Marilyn Manson, and the girl with the pink sweater and the feather boa on her purse likes to listen to Britney Spears. I like old sappy love songs. Phil likes Phil Collins and Led Zepplin. Mr. Spud likes christian rock and Creed.  And the main thing is... none of it will go away. Unless, of course, no one is listening.  Peace out, yo!  :) 
      
</post>


</Blog>