<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I would update my day as usual but nothing happened, I cleaned a lot which is depressing, i went online a lot, I did do this survey thing that Alexa did and poor Lex, when I said that dirty thoughts about they waynes world girl was in my head, she thought I was talking about Bugs Bunny in a lady dress, cha, no man, I was talking about Stacy/Cindy his exgirlfriend who is creepy but has a rather funny character  anyway, I bet your pretty shocked about the bugs Bunny thing so heres the quote that will fill you in  Garth-"Hey Wayne, have you ever found it arousing when Bugs Bunny dressed as a girl bunny pretending to be a girl" Wayne-"Uhhhh....No"           ( long periods of laughter )  so, here I am, on the computer at midnite almost, congratulations to Alexa, probably the only person who actually read my quiz thing, lol, yeah I know its long!!!!!             Zang                                                                        Zang                                                        Zang                               Zang                                                                          Zang            Zang                      Zang 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      x ] Spell your first name backwards - Mas [ x ] The story behind your Blog user name - I got bored [ x ] Are you a lesbian/homosexual - Im a lesbian, I like women, hahaha [x ] Wallet - its brown leather and its got Ryan Paul and me on the Comet for a picture x ] Hairbrush - comb, its black [ x ] Toothbrush - NY KNICKS style [ x ] Jewelry worn daily - NONE an occasional St Christopher necklace [ x ] Pillow cover - green with red stuff (CHRISTMAS) [ x ] Blanket - a blue fleece one x ] Coffee cup - Bugs Bunny [ x ] Sunglasses - I have some that are Men In Black style [ x ] Underwear - I wear boxers [ x ] Shoes - just my awesome new Adidas blue ones [ x ] CD in stereo right now - Simon and Garfunkel, Hendrix, and Best of Broadway, Im soo glad I listen to one type of music x ] Tattoos - Woodstock, on my ass [ x ] What you are wearing now - clothes, my fame tshirt and my cargo shorts and boxers of course x ] In my head - brains and mucous and dirty dirty thoughts with the girl from Waynes World [ x ] Wishing - TO GO TO CHINA [ x ] After this - i'm gonna be bored (Im copying Lex's lol) [ x ] Talking to - Alexa, Chachoo [ x ] Eating - my insides?? [ x ] If you could get away with it and murder anyone, who would it be? - omg I was waiting for this one but theres 2 many presently, I could go for mon frere, Sam Bondi just because hes an asswipe and thinks hes a child prodigy, which he isnt at all [ x ] Person you wish you could see right now - Mary and Alexa cuz theyve been making me laugh a lot lately [ x ] Is next to you - now why would you want me to express my thoughts with someone next to me (no one anyway) [ x ] Some of your favorite movies - WAYNES WORLD, Zoolander, WAYNES WORLD 2, for serious x ] Something you're looking forward to in the upcoming month - finishing the Hobbit [ x ] The last thing you ate - like 6 leftover fortune cookies lol [ x ] Something that you are deathly afraid of - snakes, Old people, and opening soda cans under your fingernail [ x ] Do you like candles - when they smell good (agreed) [ x ] Do you like hot wax - sorta, mostly when it makes ur hands numb [ x ] Do you like incense - incest, I tihnk I bought that at a store once, lol, its good shit, especially the 60s song Incense and Peppermints [ x ] Do you like the taste of blood -  not really cuz it stings bc of level of acidities in your hand [ x ] Do you believe in love - too much so (agreed) [ x ] Do you believe in soul mates - sorta [ x ] Do you believe in love at first sight- maybe at like 6th site [ x ] Do you believe in Heaven - Id liek to believe but I dont know [ x ] Do you believe in forgiveness - Yeah, its not a believing matter, it just has to happen [ x ] Do you believe in Jesus - Suzie~ Im a C Im a C-H-R-I-S-T-I-A-N lol [ x ] Who is your worst enemy - annoying people from school [ x ] If you could have any animal for a pet, what would it be- evil ferret by far[ x ] What is the latest you've ever stayed up - umm, just not going to sleep (agreed) [ x ] Ever been to Belgium - Ive been to France, Ive seen that hot girls underpants [ x ] Can you eat with chopsticks- YES [ x ] What's your favorite coin - ??? i may be insane, but i dont have a fav. coin! (AGREED) [ x ] What are 3 cities you wouldn't mind relocating to- umm..NYC(agreed), someplace on the Kerguellin Islands (polar opposite of Averill Park), and Greenwich in England [ x ] What are some of your favorite pig out foods- JAX and chips[ x ] What's something that you wish people would understand - me (agreed) [ x ] What's something you wish you could understand better- peoples treatment of others [ x ] Anyone you miss that you haven't seen in a long time - MY CLI people [ x ] What's one thing you want to make happen for tomorrow - nothing cuz Im going to Saras for the day [ x ] my father thinks i am: awesome, I would say crazy like Lex but its kind of the other way around [ x ] my mother thinks i am: freaky, note the sanity difference between parentals [ x ] my sibling thinks i am: annoying, they can fuck themselves hard tho [ x ] my grandma thinks i am: needy [ x ] my boyfriend/girlfriend thinks I am- umm..? [ x ] your three best qualities - hilarity, intelligence, caring (really popular qualities [ x ] three worst qualities - my self respect, my attitude, my difference in attitude among family/peers [ x ] things you are often complimented for- intelligence, sheer handsomeness lol [ x ] you get embarrassed when - easily [ x ] makes you happy - being/talking to friends  [ x ] upsets you - family matters (not the show) [ x ] you keep a diary - well i write in this [ x ] you have a secret you have not shared with anyone - not really, I have nothing to hide [ x ] you fold your underwear - Only after having sex in them...? of course I do fucktard [ x ] you talk in your sleep - damn straight [ x ] you bite your fingernails - nope [ x ] you believe in love - already told you deuschbag [ x ] movie you rented = 50 First Dates and BAD SANTA [ x ] movie you bought =Last I think was 50 First Dates  x ] song you listened to = not presently but I am a Rock by S&G [ x ] song you've downloaded = my comp sucks to much [ x ] CD you listened to prior to the current one = Best of Broadway  [ x ] person you've called =Sara about tomorrow [ x ] person that's called you = Paul about tomorrow[ x ] TV show you've watched = OLYMPICS and Oliver Beene [ x ] you wish you could live somewhere else = no, i love living in hicksville..ARE YOU DURANGED?!(agreed) [ x ] others find you attractive = not really, once in a while [ x ] you want more piercings = Id have to have them [ x ] you want more tattoos = maybe [ x ] you drink = nope [ x ] you do drugs = never and neither of which i intend to do (agreed) [ x ] you like cleaning = does anyone? (agreed) [ x ] you like roller coasters = UH HUH [ x ] you write in cursive or print = both, wierd I know [ x ] ever cried over a boy/girl = I think not really, maybe way back in like 6th grade where it was really lame [ x ] ever lied to someone = if I said havent gone a day without lying Id be lying to you [ x ] ever been in a fist fight = sorta, it was a little fist a little shoving [ x ] ever been arrested =god I hope not cuz I would have been drunk or high at the time in order to have been name] Sam [nicknames] Sam lol and Seamus and Moose and Dumbass (my personal fav.)[home] hicksville [birthday] Oct. 2 [sign] Libra [eye color] green hair] brown [bf/gf]:P(AGREED) [school colours] blue + gold [mascot] because i am the head of the school spirit at my school...wtf do i care[clothing style] just what I want, its mediocre anyway [pets] None [label] label-maker [movie] Waynes World [color crayon] robins egg blue [kind of pens] umm writing pens [flowers] Roses cuz of the outkast song [cereal] i like bagels [candies] hard candy [ice cream flavor] cookie dough [skittle flavor] n/a [color m & m] n/a [pizza topping] sausage &amp; pepperoni [salad dressing] none [hangout] treehouse [saying] gringo chicken [quote] hmmm..i'm quite fond of "Somewhere in the darkest corner of your darkest dream, there is a place where all that is lost can be found. And there in that darkest corner, crouched in the cold, you will find me... and you will find yourself" Davey Havok, im too lazy too type so lexs sounds good [teacher] bagetta & frey [day] any day that isnt a hobbit day [month] october (YES!) [season] fall (YES) [number] 15 [holidays] ummm, I guess Christmas but its too short [shoes] Adidas [store] SPENCERS, omg, a laugh everytime [fast food place] I  [restuarants] Applebee's or lakeview [rugrats character] that show got old fast (agreed) I dont know, I liked Chuckie even tho Angelica was such a biznotch [simpsons character] omg omg omg omg, the nerdy scientist by far then in 2nd the comic store owner, worst episode ever! GLOIVEN! [teletubby] PO, lol, I just burst out laughing [radio station] 88.3, 92.3, 95.5, 96.3, 98.3, 99.5, 100.3, 102.3, 103.1, 103.9, 104.9 cuz I liek pretty much everything [font] COMIC SANS MS, im such a crazy font person [person to talk to online] no one should take offence but Kendra for the laughs and Alexa for the constant agreeance wth everything I say lol [band] HARRY AND THE POTTERS or SIMN AND GARFUNKEL [subject] English with Bagetta, nothing else tho, no other englishes either [food] pizza I guess [color] Orange ( you know that Black is the new white) [boxers or briefs?] boxers [plaid or striped?] striped but only vertically cuz apparently that makes me look better [scream or scream2 or scream3?] cuz I could judge that seeing as Ive seen none of them [urban legend or the faculty?] didnt see either [salt or pepper?] SALT but pepper got me thru my global final with a 94 so I dont care, I dont like pepper tho, it makes me sick [rare, medium, or welldone?] medium well which is what my mom always ordered me, IM SUCH A TOOL [m & m's-regular, peanut, peanut-butter, or almond?] some of those arent even MMs flavors, I prefer the newer cruchy MMs [hershey's-hugs or kisses] xoxo I dont care xoxo [chocolate or vanilla?] Im a big vanilla fan but both are really good [bleh or blah?] blah (agreed) do ppl even say bleh, omg select chorus, so Miss Baratto, if the bluhs are over there and the blahs are over here, where do the blees go, omg, best time of my life [okay, ok, or o.k.?] I prefer Hokay, so! from The End of the World on Ebaums [sex, drugs, or rocknroll?] Rock n' Roll, maybe a little sex, maybe the drugs might spice up the sex lol, jp [shake or stir?] shake it like a polaroid picture [bright colors or dark colors?] bright [beavis and butthead, king of the hill, or daria?]King of the Hill [adidas, nike, fila, or reebok?] Adidas is the only one that hasnt been scandaled for sweatshop labor [big red, juicy fruit, or doublemint?] big red. I love you CLI ppl (insider-that was the name of my group (BIG RED)) [sunshine or rain?] SUNSHINE [rain or snow?] I HEART SNOW, especially when it cancels school [silver or gold?] sold or gilver, lol, gold [skaters or jocks?] LABEL MAKERS BITCH [preps or freaks?] goddamn! but freaks rock (AGREED) [cds or cassettes?] cds, cassettes are so 1994, for shiz [shampoo+conditioner in one or separate?] I guess separate cuz Im gonna trust Lexs judgement [winnie the Pooh] yes WInnie the Pooh [whole clinton-lewinsky thing] omg like I should judge the decisions of an ex president (but I bet he was like, for once could u see it from my point of view... Iwas horny)  [supermodels] only Amanda Beard, SCHWING! [clowns] creepy [are you left handed or right handed?] right [are you smart?] Yes, Im the best of 2 worlds, street and book smart [whats your middle name?] well they say danger is my middle name, no its Jon [how many personalities do you have?] I lost count at around 122 [how many piercings do you have?] how many goddamn times with the piercings [are you superstitious?] sorta, not really [do you read your horoscope?] when i'm bored (agreed) [what languages do you know?] english, french, Polish, Czech, and some Spanish and Italian [do you like cotton candy?] good stuff [what instruments can you play?] I play Saxophones, Piano, some Dulcimer, I know little drum rhthyms, some guitar, and a little bit of the recorder (so grade school) [what words do you overuse?] lol, I dont even know, most of my linguo is gibberish [how many pillows do you have?] own or on my bed, own:idk, on my bed:2 [do you like to dance?] a little, it helps to have a choreography [do you like to sing?] all the live long day, I sand somewhere from west side story a bajillion times today [how many cds do you have?] a 100 maybe [Do you like to talk on the phone?] yeah but only if its 2 way conversation [how many times have you moved houses?] I was born in an apartment and then I moved here ( I was born in a hospital but for when I was like 1mth to 9 I lived in an apartment building [what do you think of chain letters?] I hate them [do you like where you live?] not particularly [is your room messy?] my half is clean, Michaels, not soo clean [do you like your writing?] no, I hate writing unless its free spirited [do you like to fingerpaint?] omg, yeah, in like Kindergarten, I dont get to do much of anything artwise anymore [do you sleep with a stuffed animal?] who says the animals stuffed, rar, lol, no I dont I sleep with myself [do you sleep with socks on?] only if its rediculously cold [are you ticklish?] yeah but its kind of fading out [are you shy?] nope, I am when Im around jerkfaces [do you talk to yourself?] yep, and the tv (AGREED) [is your house 1, 2, or 3 stories?] 3 basement, 1st floor 2nd floor [do you have a basement or an attic?] both..kinda (agreed) [did you go to preschool?] yeah [are you a morning person?] Im an everything person (if that were physically possible [who has the sexiest voice in the world?]idk, I love sweden accents [who has the most annoying voice in the world?] idk, that guy from Hairspray I think [do you believe in God?] YES [do you believe in aliens?] yeah [do you believe in ghosts?] yeah [do you believe in bigfoot?] not unless it is Alexa's late gerbil [do you believe in the loch ness monster?] Yeah [whats your favorite feature (on yourself)?] my nose maybe, I dont particularly care [what do you do when you're nervous?] have a leg spasm, I kid you not [whos your role model?] any highly acclaimed Hollywood Actor [what celebrities do you look like?] I look like no one really but Ill look like myself when Im a celebrity [what celebrities do you act like?] any one thats crazy cool like Jack Black [son?] I had an abortion that would have been my son, lol, jk, yeah [daughter?] I guess [have you ever thought you were gonna die?] when we were robbed, kinda pathetic tho, that was when I was like 9 [wheres the farthest place you ever traveled?] Florida [where do you wanna go?] CHINA FOR PETES SAKE! [would you rather burn to death or freeze to death?] freeze I guess, I dont like the thought of either [can money buy happiness?] money can do a lot of shit [do you think guys or girls have it easier?] neither, the world is a crazy place [would you eat a bowl of live crickets for $40,000?] I guess so cuz Crickets are small and easier to consume [if you had a band what would you name it?] Samsonite and the Suitcases (Idk, thats all I got in creativity mode right now) [what do you wanna be when you grow up?] I want to be an actor or a singer, I know its a long shot but thats what I really want [gonna go to college?] yes indeedy [where do you want to live?] I kinda want to be like Jonny Depp and live in Paris [who do you love?] I love everyone except for the deuschbags [who do you hate?] Sam Bondi but I think I answered this one a couple times lol x. my best friend thinks I am = retarded x. a compliment you got that made you blush = I dont think Ive blushed from a compliment, more likely an embarassment x. makes you happy = People who know how to raise my spirits x. upsets you = people who are rude, we all are but whatever x. song that was stuck in your head= Somewhere from West Side Story x. CD you listened to = wow, I dont remember, take that x. person you were thinking of = well I definitely am thinking about Lex cuz Im reading all her responses to this as well x. you wish you could live somewhere else = YES! x. you believe in online dating = only if thats your means of talking, I hate LDR x. others find you attractive = not really  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today I was all like wooo, I started by waking up painfully to the sound of parental units sneezing and coughing really loud, whatever, then I helped my dad go to the dump to drop off random crap, then I came back to then go out again to see Collateral, that was a really good movie I thoroughly enjoyed Jada Pinkett Smith, she was actually really good, I thought it was a breakthrough performance for her, then I went to Church and sat there trying to harmonize with the hymns so there can be a little more excitement, THEN, I came home and had nachos for dinner, after this I came upstairs and went online forever writing emails and talking to people about China, Im still very worried that i wont be able to go because of prices, Dad told me not to worry about that just yet, I imagine Im gonna have to get a job soon. Then I went downstairs to watch the end of the olympics for swimming, nooooo, jk jk, I then decided I would try and watch Waynes World the whole way thru but I decided to update this in case I fell asleep so here I am, WOOHOO!  Wei ut dehr mahn  (that was me saying way out there man)  Zang! Yes, I know Cantonese 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Id just like to clarify that I do tend to use irrational levels of capital letters and incorrect uses of parenthesis, wow, Im lame, I noticed QUITE a few lol  ZANG! hey, I might learn cantonese in China 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, today was really cool. I basically woke up and I think I just shaved and shit with this new shaving cream and it makes your face numb, real cool, then I went down stairs to watch the very end of the price is right, it was boring, then i went upstairs and I went online to talk to cashin and Feeney, we chilled and had some funny, convos "Dont be someone your not, be yourself, thats whats really cool" I listened to a little more S& G, not a surprise, then Ben decided to be nice and he burned me Michaels Harry and the Potters CD, fun fun fun, I think after that I cleaned the hallway closet for Ma mere, then I ate spaghetti and meatballs, and THEN, the happiest moment of my life (sort of) occurred, I was invited to go to China for 17 days (ppl 2 ppl) I was really excited cuz Paul, Kendo, and Laurlaur all went to Aussie land and it was my turn to have a little fun, I get to play national champions of china in pingpong, cook chinese food, have teatime with locals, teach kids english, go to the great wall, and learn Kung Fu and Tai Chi, Im like, woooo, I acted so strangely after finding out, I knew that I would have to do some major sucking up in order to get in on this trip. So, were all set for going to the meeting in september, I CANT WAIT, I hope its not too expensive, after all that, what did I do? OLYMPICS, I also came up here to type emails to some freaks and geeks (Mary and Paul), btw, Im starting to think I should rename myself Peter that way it can be Peter Paul and Mary) how cool would that be? idk, but so I watched more olympics, I got really tired but then I watched a LITTLE, emphasize that one, a little Waynes World  Waynes World Waynes World Party Time Excellent  in closing a waynes world quote  Garth: "That woman who plays the bass, she makes me feel kinda funny, like when we used to climb the rope in gym class"   ZaNg! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I dont think I actually did much for the rest of the day, I did more random cleaning which is lame and I dont know why I do it, then I started to wacth 50 first dates but the I had to go down eat dinner with the folks, actually, my mom showed me how to make a grilled cheese sandwich, I now know that I will be the next Chef Guy that yells bam, except, I wont at all because cooking sucks unless its like a real meal. so, after dinner I watched Jeopardy and yet again I totally kicked ass and took names against the teenagers in the tournament, I was like OH SNAP! but then after that what else could I do but watch the olympics, I watched michael phelps get a gold, along with Amanda Beard, and Carly Patterson, oh, and the Piersol guy. Definitely more gymnastics and swimming but thats the way uh huh uh huh I like it, wow, LAME! but it was fun, they did do really well, and Amanda Beard is a total babe. so basically all that leads me up to this point and I think Im gonna go downstairs and finish watching 50 first dates, YAHOO  Random Waynes World Quote:  Miss Hornee: Garth, Im gonna be Frank with you  Garth: Oh, well can I still be Garth?  haha, yes! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I definitely forgot to update this yesterday so Ill just tell you about yesterday then I will update this again tonite, so, wow, Michael just put 40 blueberries in his mouth, is there some Gradess gene where everyone is retarded. Anyway, so yesterday, my dad wanted to go see a movie but I didnt feel like getting off my ass so I suggested renting movies, we rented Along Came polly which was awesome bc of the blind ferret, which, depressingly enuff, made my life, we also saw Bad Santa which was totally not in season but it was fucking Hilarious, with a capital H, my problem was, Billy Bob Thornton is such a bad actor and everything, but how did he make babies with Angelina Jolie, Angelina is way up on my babe list, those lips are killer, shes fucking bitchin, then again, so is Jennifer Garner, shes my favorite chick, omg, the best is Pam Anderson, actually not at all cuz she has Hepatitus C, I dont know how that manifests itself but it is a major turnoff desite the big bongo drum boobies!, lol, so then after watching movies we basically at that point watched Jeopardy and ate chicken, I HAD CHICKEN IN ALL THREE MEALS THAT DAY, heres the low down, down low, no doubt on the chicken meals  *Breakfast-leftover chicken pizza from Olive Garden *Lunch-Crispy chicken sandwich Mickey D's (barf with mayo) *Dinner-Barbecue Chicken, ma meres, delonkshous  which brings me to my next point, I make up a lot of random words and I dont know quite how to spell them, ohs wells  so, after jeopardy I think I watched more olympics because its my life, so far its been kind of cool even tho its just been swimming and gymnastics, Im really looking forward to running relays and all the other track and field stuff. Wow, I just started singing that Dont stop believing, hold onto that feeling! omg, Im definitely listening to Harry and the Potters, YES!!!!!! so I watched the olympics/ cleaned until about 1 in the morning which at that point I attempted to fall asleep, phew, thats a day in the life of the man!  Keep it real guys 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From the past to the present, music has brought us together, and we will continue to stomp into the future  oh man, I didnt say that a bajillion times today :), anyway, so my day was cool, I woke up and immediately went shopping with the parentals to Sams Club and I loved taste testing all the stuff, then I went for school supplies, which in turn was fun, just not at all, then I went to get a pair of sneaks, oh man, I got this awesome pair thats blue and then I came home and watched more olympics, then I definitely watched WAYNES WORLD 2 until we left for the Olive Garden which was good eating, then I went to Moxies to get some Ice cream, then I am done by watching Michael Phelps win gold in the 200 butterfly, awesome, and Amanda Beard is a babe and I saw her on the 200 medley, oh man shes a babe, shes such a babe that if she were a president she would be baberaham lincoln, yeah thats a waynes world quote, good stuff, well Im gonna go watch more, Catch yas on the flipside! IM OUTIE  Poopity 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG, today was sooo awesome (not really) a litttle heads up, sarcasm is my life. Anywayseewhosers, new one, I basically woke up and was like I have to finish my summer homework today before I literally go back into my rage mentality. So I finish the book and finish writing the 1st draft of my essay EXCEPT for the quote I wanted, I WAITED 5 FUCKING HOURS FOR A QUOTE I ENDED UP USING FROM A SONG, how refuckingtarted unbefuckinglievable is that. So I finished walking down that road, I was sooo glad to be like literally done, all I need is Dianes editing skills cuz shes a news editor so shes my hero when it comes to writing. So, for lunch at 4 I had nachos and watched Synchronized Diving, US CAME IN FIFTH, wtf, it was a rip off but I was glad the greeks finally won something, I tend to root for the teams of which the games take place, I definitely want to see the 200M freestyle cuz Michael Phelps and I think Kaitlyn Sandeno are doing it. ANYWAY, so after doing all that shit, I tried to memorize everything I do for the Hobbit which isnt much but Im glad I dont have to do much cuz Im lazy and that would be soo much more stressful, ALL IS GROOVY, btw, I forgot that Ive been listening to Simon and Garfunkel for like 5 hours, but then I went to rehearsal and that was boring, but Sam Bondi farted on stage TWICE, that is like Gods way of saying your awesome Sam. I was sooo excited. Then Mary Coofey and I went to Cumbys and we got PIXIE STIX and went psycho, in Austin Powers talk we "went mental on account of the pixie stix", awesome, then after my awesome cameo was done, I filled out my bio and it definitely says Randomosity forever folks and egg yolks, Alexa helped it too be funny. I was excited. Wow, how many times can I say excited in a journal entry. I WAS SOO BORED however after that wating for ma mere, I definitely left my umbrella in the lobby on the counter. I found out Im going to the Olive Garden tomorrow, Ive kind of resisted going there for a while cuz its like Tex Mex is to Taco Bell as Olive Garden is like Americanized Italian and I was afraid it was going to be lame, OMG, I just decided I want to listen to Christmas music, ok, well Im outie   ZANG! Thank you Waynes World, just thank you 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow, I created one of these because Im in boredness withdrawal after being at Sara's forever partying down for Jin-Jin. Anyways, my first question is how can you have soo many normal fonts such as Courier or Arial and then writes Wingdings, why even bother putting that in there do you want me to go   fuck a duck   why write something so lame like that in Wingdings. Anyways, I guess Im supposed to tell you about today. Well, today I got my 5th abortion, wow, jk, Im a fucking guy, but who would put that in here. ANYWAY, today I went to my sister Sara's house for Jinas(+ the accent) graduation. I was ther for about 12 hours swimming in pools hot tubs and I saw my biology teacher there, I gave her a daquiri. We played Spud, watched Wayne's World which was awesome. And we talked a lot. BTW, this would be Lexa Rae and Sara Carly. Then I ended up being there for about 10 hours which is psychotic considering it was supposed to be a brunch. Mrs. A worked rediculously vigorously hard on that scrumtrillescent food. Then I went home and watched the Olympics, is it just me or is Gymnastics rediculously boring, its all the same thing over and over again, everyone has to do the one event until they switch to the next. I really liiked watching my so far favorite swimmers, Kaitlyn Sandeno and Michael Phelps get medals. Its literally amazing. So then I came up here and decided to do something with my life so to speak.      Ha, The END  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>