<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ("v")
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Peter & Tina are sittin in d park doin nuttin, bt jus gazin in2 d sky, while all deir frens are havin fun wit deir beloved half.  Tina: I'm so bored. Jus wish I have a boifren nw 2 spend time wit.  Peter: I guess we're d oni leftovers. We're d oni person hu isn't wit a date nw.  (both sighed &amp; silence 4 a while)  Tina: I think I hav a gd idea. Let’s ply a game.  Peter: Eh? Wat game?  Tina: Erm…It's quite simple. U’ll b my boifren for 100 days & I'll b ur galfren for 100 days. Wat do u think?  Peter: Wokey..Anyway I dun hav any plan 4 d nxt few months.  Tina: U sounded like u aren't looking forward 2 it at all. Cheer up. 2day will b our 1st day &amp; our 1st date. Where shld we go?!  Peter: Wat abt a movie? I heard tat der is a really great movie in theater nw.  Tina: Seems like I dun hav any beta idea dan dis. Lets move.  (went 2 watch deir movie & send ech other hm)  Day 2: Peter &amp; Tina went 2 a concert 2gether & Peter bought Tina a keychain wit a star.  Day 3: Dey went shppin 2gether 4 a fren's birthday present. Shared an ice-cream 2gether &amp; hugged ech other 4 d 1st time.  Day 7: Peter drove Tina up on2 a mountain & dey watch d sunset 2gether. Wen d nite came &amp; d moon glowed, dey sat on d grass, gazin at d stars 2gether. A meteor passed by. Tina mumbled sumthing.  Day 25: Spend time at a themepark & gt on2 rollercoasters &amp; ate hotdogs & cotton candy. Peter &amp; Tina gt in d haunted house & Tina grabbed sum1's hand instead obe Peter's hand by accident. Dey luffed 2gether 4 a while.  Day 67: Dey drove pass a circus &amp; decided 2 gt in 2 watch d shw. D midget asked Tina 2 ply a part as his assistant in d magic show. Went around 2 see other entertainments around after d shw. Came 2 a fortune teller & she jus said "Treasure evry moment frm nw on" &amp; a drop of tear rolled dwn d fortune teller's cheek.  Day 84: Tina suggested tat dey go 2 the beach. D beach wasn't so crowded tat day. Dey hav deir 1st kiss wit ech other jus as d sun was settin.  Day 99: Dey decided 2 hav a simple day & is deciding 2 have a walk around d city. Dey sat dwn on2 a bench.  1:23 pm Tina: I'm thirsty. Lets rest 4 a while 1st.  Peter: Wait here while I go buy sum drinks. Wat wld u like?  Tina: Erm...Apple juice will b jus fine.  1:43 pm Tina waitin 4 abt 20minutes &amp; Peter haven’t return. Den sum1 walked up 2 her.  Stranger: Is ur name Tina?  Tina: Yes, & may I help u?  Stranger: Jus nw dwn der on d strt a drunk driver has crashed in2 a guy. I think itsur fren.  Tina ran ova 2 d spot wit d stranger &amp; sees Peter lyin on d floor wit blood ova his face & her apple juice still in his hands. D ambulance came &amp; she wen 2 d hospital wit Peter. Tina sat outside d emergency room 4 five & a half hours. D doctor came out, &amp; he sighed.  11:51 pm Doctor: I'm sorry, bt we did d best we cld. He is still breathing nw bt God wld take him away frm us very soon. We found dis letter inside his pocket.D doctor hand over d letter 2 Tina & she goes in2 d room 2 see Peter. He look weak bt peaceful. Tina read d letter &amp; den she burst in2 tears. Here is wat d letter said.  "Tina, our 100 days is almost over. I had fun wit u durin all dese days. Although u maybe greedy sumtimes & less totful, bt dese all brought happiness in2 my life. I have realize tat u are a reali cute girl &amp; blamed myslf 4 nva taken d time 2 noein tat. I hav nuttin much 2 ask 4, bt I just wish tat we can extend d day. I wan 2 b ur boifren eva & wish tat u can b bside mi all d time. Tina, I love u."  11:58 Tina: (sobbing) Peter, did u noe wat was d wish I made on d nite der was a meteor. I asked God 2 let us last 4eva. We were suppose 2 last 100 days so Peter! U cnt leave mi! I LOVE YOU, bt can u cum back 2 mi nw? I luv u, Peter. I luv u.  As d clock struck twelve, Peter's heart stopped beatin.  It was 100 days.  NOTE*Tell d guy or girl tat u luv dem b4 it’s too late. U nva noe wats goin 2 happen 2mrw. U nva noe hu will b leavin u &amp; nva return. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Y cn+ ppl b mOr3 und3r$+andin?! Y mu$ ppl b sO unr3a$Onabl3...i nid 2 cOp3 wi+ my mOth3r'$ naggin, my fr3ns, my lOv3 lif3, my $+udi3$...i'm $uff3rin frm d3pr3$$iOn & y3t, nObOdi nO3$ hw i f33l, i'm g3++in mOr3 & mOr3 3mO+iOnal th3$3 da3$, $um+im3$, i 3v3n cry my$lf 2 $lp & nObOdi nO3$...nObOdi car3...nObOdi bO+h3r...i nid sum1 2 tOk 2...b+, i jus dunnO3 wa+ 2 say...i f33l lik3 sl33pin & nva wak3 up. My mum wan$ mi 2 cum hm & h3lp h3r 3vryday &amp; $h3 wan+$ mi 2 do w3ll in my $tudi3$ @ d $am3 +im3... wa+ am i 2 dO?! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hw great eh?! She sold d thingy w/o tellin us, we took d thingy together, and nw, she gt d $$$ & nva even split wit us?! Is dis reasonable?! Is dis fair?! U sold it &amp; nva split?! & she still dare say she told us le...wat d heck!!! &amp; wen i ask abt it, she still can tell mi abt it?! Dun she feel guilty at all?! Is she cold blooded?! I think she has gt "hide" (animal's skin)  P.S ::: nVm, we dun 1 tt kiNda dirty $$$ ... :::     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       a millioN wOrdz wOuld nOt briNg yOu baCk, i knOw cOz i've tRied ; nEitHer wOuld a millioN teArs, i knOw, cOz i'vE criEd. (>.      .:. B.B : y dOez eVery1 thinKs tHat im lyiN tO em ?! y aM i alwaYx da oNe to be blamed ?! y dOex eVery1 seEm to be sOoo violeNt ??? it jUz scaRex mi ~ nO1 caRex bOut hw i reaLi feeLs insidE. *sObx* LiFe sUx !!! U're alwaYx usiN violeNt agaiNest mi, jUz cOz u nOe tt weN u dO, i'd jUz kip ma mOuth shUt and say nUthin ... y aM i tOleratin all tHis ? u nOe besT i did diz cOz i cHerisH wad we haB nOw aNd nOt cOz oBe ppL or lyiN or ur sO-called tRust !!! (>.      (uNknOwn) : i stOod up 4 eVeryoNe dEr ... aNd wHen i neEded heLp da mOst, hu's reaLi deR ??? ... i HATE u gUyx ... i haTe mysElf fOr tRustiN u gUyx !!! duN alwayx veNt ur aNger on mi, im nO loNger da lil' gaL nxt dOor, stOp treatiN mi lyK oNe !!! i haTe u i hate u i hate u !!! tOld ya lOadx oBe time, i'll trUst, i'll learN ta trUst ! - jUz gimmE time ... all i nId isH time tO prOve ma wOrtH ... !!!       (>.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh...nw in sch, so sian, D.K ridin moi blog arhx?! hehex...dun luff at my blog lahx...idiot!!! ltr u wan go where?! we go Pat toh and mum mum ok?! hehex...oops...d bell jus rang, wen is d exam gonna finish?! Do finish le, bewi sian de lehx...early noe dun do so fast...    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        D.K & G.G (freNdxXx^2004) 
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG!!! She's havin her period and yet she goes swimming?! Can u blieve it?! Yucks!!! Den dos guys all swim in d pool!!! Yucks!!! U guys...eEeEeEeEeEWwWwWwWw!!! Yucks, imagine swimmin in a pool contaminated wit menstration...eEeEeEwWwWw!!! i dun wana tok abt it le!!! Thinkin obe it oni lemme hav goosebumps... ^~^~^~^~^~^~^~^~^~^  G.G, nOw isH ma tUrn ta repOrt ... (>.   ::: EeeeEeeeEeewWw ... yUcky !!!~ weL, canNot briNg mYsElf tO da actuaL situatiOn wHere faraH saW wiB heR owN eYex tt "sHe" wipe heR "blOod" frm da wHite cHair !!! eEe ... !!!~ lOlx ... oMg !!! weL, thinKin bOut it jUz maKes mi feEls ... eEeeEee !!!~ aNd i osO caNnOt imagine tt sHe weNt dOwn da poOl &amp; cOntaminate da watEr wiB heR ... Ah-HEm ... MENSES !!! woOhOo!!! *duN waNa thinK bOut it!!!~*       
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wOw...tt fat ass tadae so xing fu sia...go  hong  wit so mani obe our class bois...wonder which 1 she likes...lOlx...i mus go destroy her relationship like she did to ppl's...bloody  p** c**** b**  ... gggrrr...sicko!!! Nvm, ppl nobodi 1 den can hong, so gib u chance lahx...dunnoe hw ta lOOk at ur size arhx?! think ppl will like ya eh?!  1 glance at d mirror d mirror oso will breaK!!!  and as 4 u, it will be mani mani pieces!!! Think ppl tok 2 u oni means like u arhx?! Dun BHB liao lorx...noe ur own limits!!! dun go too far!!! Den evrytime oni noe hw ta copi ppl, say ppl's hair style no nice, in d end?! u oso go cut wat...wats d diff?! Ppl buy wat, u oso will say "I wan"...sick!!! Den moi piku or anibodi else gt swts oni, u will oso will say "I wan", and wen u gt, u kip it to urslf... selfish C**** B**  !!!   ^unsatisfied^   urlLink g3rl^gal_scorpio88@hotmail.com^  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>