<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       August 19,    Well, as you all have read I had metioned that i was going out , with this great guy named, Morgan Tolbin. I decided to just be friends with him. Which all my friends think that I' am a idiot for doing that, I don't though. Some of is stupid friends told me something that really hurt my feelings. They made a comment to me, that I was no Hillary. If you don't know who she is , she is his ex-girlfriend.   That really hurt me. If you have seen Morgan you would also know how HOT he is. He is well built with huge muscles...Chelsey..(sorry inside joke.) If you know me you would know we didn't look good together. I just didn't feel pretty with him. I tired to explain it to soem of my friends, but they just don't seem to understand. All they see is a hot guy, and a stupid dection. Man, it's like I can't seem to find me a good boyfriend. A guy I can just hang out with and have a really good time with. It seems like they are all taken, or they are friends with me. If you also knwo me you know I love all my friends and would NEVER date them. Sometimes I regret being me. Sometimes I love beign me. %-)  
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       August 21, Last night my best friend Chelsey stayed over.. We had so much fun... We pranked called my idiot of a friend Tyler... We were going to roll his house , but we never got the chance (damn it) We probably stay up until 3 am... chated on line with my friend Matt.. and just goofed around for the rest of the night .... we also took pictures.. so now people will get to see what i look like.. Chelsey if your reading this.. we need to do it again... and we need to roll Tyler's house...lol %-)  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       August 17, omg..... today during english we were doing diagram sentences..... which i hate with a passion.... well it was my turn to go up to the board and do one.... well i did the whole thing right except for one small thing... i placed a word in the wrong place.... and my teacher told me which word it was... and it needed to be placed on a leg? what is a leg? i had know clue.... i was a wierd shaped line that was soppose to be in the shape of a leg.... well i didnt look like no damn leg.... man i was mad...... and then i also had to go up and do correcting the sentences.. were u go up to the board and correct like missed spelled words.. i had to read the sentence aloud for everyone to hear... and there was the lst name of a guy which was updike.... well when i read it out loud i said up dick..omg how imbarrassing. %-)  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       August 6, i was working at the fair ..... and my neighbor tyler... whom im totally in love with.... was soppose to come and get me..... b/c he had a mototcross race that night and i wanted to see him.... well, when i first got there i saw him an he'd said he would come get me closer to the race time... so i was like okay.... well it was about nine and the races started at seven so i was really pissed off..... then i saw him again ...... but this time he was with a girl!!!!!!!! well about nine-thirty i got to take a break... so me and my friends brtiney, matt, chad, and some of their friends.. went to go look for him.. well when we found him.. i asked him who was that girl... he said he had got back with his ex- girlfriend... the dumb thing about this ordeal... is he knows that im crazy about him....so for the next half hour i had to watch him flirt and make out with her..... until i got fed up with it and said i was leaving..... All my friends could also see i was almost in tears and said that was a good idea... when we started to leave.. tyler asked why we leaving... i told him if he didn't know .... he was as stupid as i thought.... he had a confussed look on his face.. so i guess he is stupid... but the cool thing was... my friend chad... who everyone thinks is a total babe... grabbed me and pushed me up against tylers truck adn kissed me .... and held hands with me the rest of the night to make tyler jealous... i must have worked b/c he came up to me and said whats going on why are u holding hands with that dude... i was like u can do but i cant... he got so mad he throw his helmet down and cracked it.... he was like whatever u were never mine... all i said was ur right i was never yours........ but things have cooled down and were trying to be friends again....but its hard... but im cool with it b/c i dating morgan... one of the sweetest guys i know.. and handsome too.....%-)  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        August 17, Today at school..which rocked by the way...b/c im now going out with Morgan Tolbin...hottie.... well...anyways.. during gym.. . there was a purse in the locker room...and some very suspious looking girls around it...so i thought the girls might have steel it...so i put it in my locker.. where they couldnt... then after gym..i annoucced to everyone i had a purse in my locker and if they were missin gone i had it... well, no one cam efor so i told everyone i would take it to the office...when the bell rung for next period... i first walkrd upstairs to get my books and as i was walking down to the office...a chunky girl walked up to me.. and said thank god you found my purse... so without thinking i gave it to her.... b/c how did she not know it wasnt mine... later, on in the day... i got called down to the commons office were the vice principle wanted to see me... i thought it might have been for the dress code or something... then he told me about a purse which was stolen..... oh crap... i gave someone a purse that didnt belong to them....damn it.....so i felt bad that whole entire day... but let me tell you if i see that girl ...... im definatly giving her a piece of my mind....    
    
</post>


</Blog>