<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well well well.. Looks like i dun have any improvement wit this blog..haha sorry guys i've been quite busy.. err... doin that stupid Graph Comm.. yes, i can vividly imagine all ur faces, "HUH! Jo do Graph Comm sia! wah.. " k either that or "HUH got graph comm to do ah?????!"

hahahaha.. relax.. i wasn't jus doin tt s**t .. went to pay my bill.. i mean sch fees haha.. download some stuff.. Like that hit "I like that" by Houston feat Chingy (damn i love that song), "Lean Back" by Terror squad and some other hiphop songs.. helo i'm hintin to y'all to dwld these songs la.. hehe especially Amanda since she's been wantin new songs to revamp her playlist i guess.. haha.. got some other songs.. but can't recall the titles.. oh ya if ur into a bit of hardcore (not porn) then maybe u wud lik 40oz by D12

I'm meetin my old fen from pri sch later and i dun think i'll know how he looks now haha.. passin him my social studies note.. YES! givin away all that bull!! Like salvation army.. no wait tt army take stuff not give stuff.. ah wateva! yesterday met hazwan to give away my A maths stuff and help him out a bit but ermm.. hehe i kinda forgot almost everythin bout A math.. sorry wan!

OK guess i need to wrap this all up cos i'm meetin Irfan later YAY! poor kid.. he's so tired nowadays.. cos of sch and O levels prep.. geesh it brings back memories.. Take good care of yourself k!  Anythin call me, babe! i'll be here eager to help..


By the way, check out hoobastank's new vid called Same Direction (my latest fave).. the vid feature Kanye West, Joel from Good Charlotte and... jet jet jet.. CHESTER from linkin park! haah!! have a listen, the song rocks..

     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this thing rite here may not be appropriate for cat-haters...

most ppl know how i LOVE cats and kittens and this mornin as i was walkin to e bus stop to see my baby go to sch (no, i dun hav kids *lik DUH*) i heard a little kitten meowing.. i kinda ignored it cos i thought i was hallucinating.. see, sometimes i hear things when my eyelids are threatening to close my eyes and hypnotise me to sleep.. so when i was on my way back home, i saw a small, scrawny lil kitten cryin out wit its tiny, tired voice so helplessly sittin on the staircase landing.. it looked so vulnerable and seemed to be callin out for its mom or smth..  so sad... all alone.. and i looked around to see if there's any adult cat that looked lik the kitten but there wasn't any..

can u imagine that lil kitten, its a male by the way, waitin and callin out for its mom and she never came.. so i went home and bring out some milk and went back down to feed this poor thing and when i decided to leave it FOLLOWED me.. aiyoh... how? i tot to myself.. i cant bear to leave it behind but i can't bring it home either.. do u know how many cats i hav? i may not hav 7 lik kamariah hehe but i hav 4... very cute ones..  so i guessed i kinda left him there.. jus hoping that his mom will return and he wud grow up to be a stronger cat and be independent..

its afternoon now and its raining badly.. how i wish all the cats at s'pore HDB blocks are safe and sheltered.. 

     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i got a question for u guys..
how do I include audio in my blog and post pics on it?

     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey yo  
 this is my first time settin up this thing and i hope no one would critisize it haha.. Here's a newbie at bloggin. I woke up this morning and a sudden ambigious decision to blog hit me. *BAM* and so i'm now sittin here with no purpose to blog emotions or make a diary entry.. 
  
 Well here's something I would like to share with those of u who think that they have a crappy love life.. 
  
 Love's a bitch  
 All relationships end 
 What happens now when that person's gone? 
 The one whom you thought you could always count on 
 You fall in love and they fall out 
 Love is a bitch.. All relationships end 
  
 How do I let go of the love that means so much to me? 
 How do I go on when you're part of me? 
 I'm dying inside each time I see you 
 Don't lose side of me cos you're all I see.....  
 (lyrical content by Rufio) 

     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WARGH! i hate mugging unless its pretentious.. I've been tryin to lean back and chill but thoughts of failing keeps drifting across my head.. Failiure's certainly not flattering.. (that New Found Glory song is stuck playin over in my mind damnit) I feel so poor in terms of intellect.. I think we'll jus move on and talk bout today's dilemma on movies.. Btw Irfan's gonna have his English oral for his O levels tmr.. GOOD LUCK aite! I'm sure u'll do fine and ace it! Jon wants to watch Alien Vs Predator but shalu wants to watch Secret Window.. and there's a new choice now- Bourne Supremacy ahaha which one sia? Eh now I'm hungry talkin bout supremacy.. supreme pizza.. stuff crust.. YUM! Well i hav a date today and we're watchin AVP at 3pm.. and I'm not even sure bout the Sentosa outing we're havin on Wed.. another dilemma- watch on tues or wed? sentosa or wild wild wet? hey it kinda rhyme! k fine.. well anythin u guys watchin or goin to jus post a comment or we can meet up tmr after (%$#*&amp;@!!) Medisoc test... Since someone called me a music commentator I would lik to recommend u guys to take a listen to 'Caught up' by Usher, its one of the tracks in Confessions, 'The Sun' by Maroon5 and Spongebob Squarepants interlude... haha kiddin bout the last one lah

     

    
</post>


</Blog>