<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I,once a believer,devited to God.   Committed foreverto service of the Lord.   Praying, a believer,filled up with faith;   lost it one daybut wasn't too late;   I got it back soon,forgot what was past.   Filled with faith againbut just didn't last.   Then a believer,paying homage to Satan;   devoted to His cause,no more at a loss.   Betrayed by the Satan,cried out in my pain;   called out to God,His devotee again.   Praying to Him,praying day in and out;didn't get my miracleand so I did pout.   A Satanist's lifewas the life I was living:Asked Him for helpbut He wasn't too giving.   Cursing the Satan,got back to the Lord,once more devoted to Almighty God.   Was hurt bad one day,was hurt in the heart;retraced my footstepsand once more did star   tthe worship of Satan,the pursuit of evil,hatred for mankind and love for the Devil.   Doubted Him onceand got back to God;was connected to Satanbut severed that cord.   Today I am in the pursuit of "good","pure" thoughts in mind,like a child of God should.   It's difficult for me 'causethere's still some confusion thereas to whether I'll be God'sor whether He and Satan'll share....   to be continued...  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "A man is incomplete until he is married. After that, he is finished," Zsa Zsa Gabor had poignantly said in one of her interviews. Being married nine times, Hollywood's celebrity sex symbol with her known penchant for jewellery and furs, would know better. Although many would not agree with what the Hollywood actor had to say about the institution of marriage, for many married pros the real strength lies in the test of trust and honesty. And increasingly, many Indian professionals are finding themselves on a sticky wicket as their marriages arranged by folks and concerned elders are falling apart, with rising incidence of infidelity. As eager parents exercise effective communication in setting up their children's lives, many young professionals are now sharing mind space with unknown people in the orbit of arranged marriages. With little time for life after work, many pros find themselves in a situation where they are dependent on others to get their personal life rocking. And often, many professionals find themselves having to spend their lives with total strangers with whom they have very little in common. A union solemnized by practical considerations and familial commitments rather than matters of the heart often finds itself running out of steam in sometime, resulting in a quest for emotional and mental connect. And the hunt for mental bonding often blurs the divide between the mind and the heart and, increasingly pros are finding themselves in the infidelity zone. "My doctor sister had an arranged marriage with a lecturer in Delhi University around 5 years back. Belonging to different backgrounds, they were unable to connect emotionally. While my sister plunged herself in her work at the clinic and hospital, her husband started seeing a fellow academician. Finally, they separated after 2 years of efforts and goading from respective families trying to make their marriage work," Meeta Choudhury, a 27-year-old graphic designer, said.    With no real chemistry to add zing to the relationship, professionals in arranged marriages often find themselves reeling under the after effect of a lack of proper communication. Not being able to connect on the same wavelength often makes pros seek gratification outside marriage, ultimately leading to a tryst with promiscuity.   urlLink   To make a marriage work, it is imperative to be on the same wavelength. As workplace gets competitive, India Inc. has been witness to a lot of young pros spending long hours at work. In such a scenario, with little or no emotional bonding with one's partner, it is not uncommon to strike a relation of convenience with a colleague or fellow worker. And often, many pros citing work commitment as an excuse stay away from home to spend time elsewhere. Disha Gurung, a senior HR manager with a leading beverages company in Delhi, had an arranged marriage last year. Well-placed in her career and job, the 29-year-old small town girl from Dehradun is yet to understand her lawyer husband completely. While he likes partying and action flicks, she is one for cozy dinners and mush movies. "Being in an arranged marriage does come with its own rules, as I am learning. Although I have been spared the spanner of infidelity so far, it is not possible to predict the future. Sometimes I get a little jittery when he spends long hours in the office. Moreover, there are also informal meetings, casual parties, increased interaction with colleagues - all these factors are there. And infidelity can happen in situations where you are attracted to your attractive colleague, with whom you can discuss strategy," Gurung said. However, her husband Amit feels that "people who have had love marriages have also crossed limits and experimented. Arranged marriages, at least, ensure greater moral responsibility and accountability as honouring parental choices is important. Also because families are involved, many pros maybe having an affair on the sly, but will not take any extremist step."    Love quotient is an important parameter that make or mar most arranged marriages. And it is this hunt for elusive "love" that makes most dabble with unconventional behaviour and seeking sexual and mental gratification outside marriage. Caught in a loveless union, most pros often spend long hours at the workplace. Also justifying an affair at the workplace becomes easy for pros in arranged marriages by simply stating that "My wife/husband does not understand me" or "We have nothing in common but kids".   urlLink   "In the end it is all about accountability. My wife who works as a financial specialist with an MNC bank, had an affair with her boss, a year after our marriage and it never even hit me that there was something amiss. Long hours at work, stuck on the phone, text messaging galore - now when I look back in hindsight, it all fits like a jigsaw puzzle. When I confronted her, she said that she did not connect with me and found him stimulating. Needless to say, we got divorced in a month's time," Harmeet Raheja, a software solutions expert, said. While Raheja took the extreme step, advertising professional Tania Nath remained trapped in a bad marriage to investment banker Ashok Shrivastava for a long time. An alliance that the family officiated, the client servicing executive realised her husband's philandering ways 2 years after her marriage. Initially, she dismissed it as simple office interactions that bordered on friendship. But weekend getaways, absences at family occasions and forgetting anniversaries became more common. "Initially, I kept telling myself that I was over reacting because he had seemed so charming and nice in the beginning. But slowly, over the years I realised that it was all a charade as he did not want to upset the apple cart by letting his family know. Me remained the dutiful wife, while his attraction lay elsewhere. Last year, I knew that I had enough and decided to file for divorce," Tania said. Even as workplace competition mounts, and pros have to do the constant balancing act between domestic frontier and personal desires, there are those who believe that an affair is not to be remembered, whether arranged or not. "One time infidelity should be forgiven, I feel. Anyone can digress and it is but natural to sin. And temptation anyways is not easy to handle, especially if there is complete emotional and mental, connect with someone. Of course, arranged marriages does make it a little difficult for people to shed their inhibitions completely and let their guard down. If there is already such an arrangement outside marriage, an affair is but natural. Of course I would never do it," Anil Vaid, a insurance advisor married for 4 years, said.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       There's safety in numbers. This was perhaps the guiding principle that brought thousands of women working in dance bars across the city out in the open on Friday to protest "police harassment".   urlLink   Away from the strobe lights, the girls were exposed to the public's gaze and did their best to hide behind dupattas. Dressed mostly in kurti-salwars and platform heels, many carrying mobiles, the bar girls ranged from teenagers to mothers with grown-up children. Most were reluctant to talk about their backgrounds and backed away from the mikes and cameras. Although they were around to air their grievances, they were clearly being herded around by the bar owners. They had come to Azad Maidan to declare that they wanted to earn their livelihood in peace.    But how free are women employed as bar girls? Stories of economic hardship and exploitation abound, as was portrayed in Madhu Bhandarkar's critically acclaimed film Chandni Bar. In fact, Bhandarkar, who interviewed around 200 bar girls before writing his script, believes that most bar girls have been lured into the trade with false promises of marriage or jobs in cities.    Take the case of Ravina (name changed), a resident of a transit camp in Goregaon, who had to join the profession to keep the home fires burning. Her jobless father is grateful that his "pretty daughter" has landed a "well-paying job" in a local bar. According to Bhandarkar, "Some bar girls are forced into the trade by unemployed fathers or husbands. There are several lower-middle-class girls who dance in bars to pay for their education." Manjit Singh Sethi, who owns the Karishma bar in Dadar, reveals that "some of them are housewives and do it out of economic compulsion. They have the usual problems back home-drunkard husbands, jobless fathers and huge families, including siblings, who survive on their money."    However, for every Ravina, there is also a Purvi who has willingly joined the profession. Eighteen year-old Purvi (name changed) stopped scrubbing floors and washing utensils after a neighbour offered her a "money-making job". The next time she visited her former employer she had a smartly madeup face and said she was making Rs 1,000 daily, as against the Rs 3,000 she made earlier after a month of sweat and toil. The lure of money-bar girls earn between Rs 500 and Rs 6,000 a night in tips from customers-is obviously strong, but many of the girls prefer to keep their employment a "wellguarded secret" from people they know. Purvi's family, for instance, believes that she is a "night cook in a big hotel". In another case, a bar dancer from Malad, who also owns a hosiery stall in Andheri, tells her friends that she works as a night nurse in a private nursing home in Malad.    One of the common refrains for bar girls is that they "go to a call centre at night". According to a bar owner from Andheri: "We send Tata Sumos to pick up the girls from their residences at around 6 pm. They are dropped back home in the wee hours. Most of the girls tell their neighbours and friends that they work in a call centre." Bar owners reportedly allow the girls to take most of their tips home. "We also provide them with free food, cold drinks and transportation to and from their residence. They are also provided protection and we also fight court cases on their behalf," says Sethi. "Bar dancers are different from prostitutes," he claims. "We do not allow our customers to misbehave with them or molest them. They are performers who just dance for money."    But sources in the Mumbai police claim that several bar girls have doubled up as prostitutes. In May 2002, when the social service branch of the Mumbai police raided the WWF bar in Nehru Nagar, it allegedly found 164 bar girls soliciting customers.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The first step towards weekly meeting on saturday's of SIES friends kick started yesterday with bang from BIG SPOT, bowling ally. All of us had a great time bowling & flexing our Muscles. The night saw a great dinner at 'Only Parathas', Khar, with really good panner tikka, yummy hara kababs &amp; delecious & tummy full PARATHAS. The night saw the end with some great music at our vey own disc, Mumbai Auto. It was fun guys &amp; look forward for great time ahead. King of Good Times!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       We all are meeting on 21st Aug 2004 at our same place, probably this time we would go out for a movie. Meet you guys at the very same "Katta", at same time. Those buddies who dont know the venue can call anyone of us (Vish, Sat, Kartiks or Sardar)  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        From very relaible sources, I came to know that Yogita got married. Well great news!!!     Congratulations Yogita from all of US!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       We salute you Major Saab! You’ve saved India the blushes. You’ve proven that the Indian army still produces the finest gentlemen. Secretly, every single Indian was scared that the Olympic contingent might return with nothing to show. Aapney izzat rakh li. Rajyavardhan Singh Rathore, we salute you! Congratulations Major Saab...!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Leander Paes and Mahesh Bhupathi overcame an injury scare and world number one singles player Roger Federer to advance to the quarterfinals of the men's doubles tennis at the Olympic Games here on Tuesday.    A bleeding nose for Paes early in the second set threatened to derail the 'Indian Express' but the multiple Grand Slam champion quickly recovered from the injury to power the 'Indian Express' to a 6-2 7-6 (9/7) victory past Federer and his Swiss partner Yves Allegro in the second round. The defeat meant the end of Olympic medal hopes for Federer who suffered a shock second round exit in the singles to unseeded Tomas Berdych of the Czech Republic earlier in the day. The loss was Federer's second in three matches following his first round ouster by another Czech, Dominic Hrbaty, at the Cincinnati Master two weeks ago that ended the Wimbledon champion's 23-match winning streak. Paes and Bhupathi now play fourth seeds Wayne Black and Kevin Ullyett of Zimbabwe in the last-eight round. The fifth seeded Indians targeted Yves Allegro who proved to be the weak link in the Swiss camp. They broke him in the third game to go up 2-1 up before Paes was forced to call the trainer. But once Paes, who was laid down by a brain lesion and was forced out of action for six months last year, recovered from the set back, the duo broke Allegro once more to power their way in the second set. The second half of the match, however, proved to be tougher for the Indians as Allegro tightened his serve and Federer began to dominate.   In fact, Paes and Bhupathi were forced to save two break points in the second game on the latter's serve.   At times, when the situation got tight, the Indians had to revive their famous chest butts to see them through. Fortunately, the two had some vociferous support from the sparse crowd that included the members of the shooting contingent, Anjali Vedpathak Bhagwat and Suma Shirur. The Swiss led for the first time in the match when they went up 2-1 and the Indians were always trailing. Serving to stay in the set, Paes' serve came under pressure at 15-40 but the former world number one doubles pair held their nerves to hold serve and push it into tie-breaker. Into the tie-breaker they were once again 1-3 down but once again pounced on Allegro's serve to level it 3-3. They went up 6-4 on Bhupathi's serve for two match points but the Bangalorean committed his first double fault to fritter it away. On 8-7, however, Bhupathi produced his trademark service return winner to deliver the knockout punch.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Probably at this moment of glory when Maj. Rathod has brought pride to the nation, we should also not forget the thrashing of South Africans by our Indian hockey players. The match started with the Indian players calling for "Bole Sonihal, sasriakal"   When they went 1 down I switched off the TV as I sensed yet another defeat & went out to meet Vish. But I was wrong &amp; there was something else instore.   It was a match of nerves, India looked rusted, though the piston started firing at the end & there was true Indian spirit fighting which cruised them to victory &amp; the best being wiping their deficit goals.   Great job done boys!!!   Keep it up. We are with you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dear Friends,  As part of our community friendship & to be in touch with each other, this is a small effort towards our global vision we had envisioned during our college days. I urge you to continously contribute to this effort &amp; help our users to get on what's happening around us. Happy Connectivity!!! Enjoy this effort.  Satish Nair   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>