<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had work today from 1 till 5... I know it's only four hours, but it seemed like forever! Luckily, I started off my shift with a double espresso. Boy if that doesn't wake you up, I don't know what will (except being plunged into a pool of icy water... that works too). So I'm home now and all is well. Haha. I am such a homebody... when it comes the time for me to move out of the house I will be pacing around my new place, mumbling strange things and talking to people who don't exist. Maybe I should just build myself a little house in the backyard. Then if my prince charming comes around, we can just live there... And I will never have to leave home. And I can always drink coffee with  half and half  in it (not coffeemate, mind you... now the thought of that stuff makes me quite nauseated). As you can read, I am somewhat and quite a bit scatterbrained today. So these thoughts are sort of streaming along as I go... nothing really connects them except for the fact that I'm tired. So write me soon... for I need some real human contact. Living in this 67th demention can get a little overwhelming sometimes. "See" ya, b 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... my name is Daisy Smith (although my nickname is "Beth" after the girl in  Little Women , one of my fave movies) and I am 24 years old. I live in the UK, and love it. Except for when it rains for days on end... anyways... I live at home with my mom, dad, two older brothers, two younger brothers, and two dogs. I love eating bagels, and drinking coffee...lots of coffee... and I love making fun of and/or mocking my lovely jubly aunty "julie". She lives in the US and has really completely turned into an American... she has even taken up their accent... on accident! anyways, this blog is mainly me talking to my aunt, of whom I really do like. see you later alligator ;) -B 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after our trip, i wasn't feeling so well... after four days of not enough sleep, too much theological information, not enough caffine, and not eating enough (i.e. eating at weird times, not having my normal food...). By Sunday morning I had a bad headache, and by the end of church, I felt horrible... a bad, bad migraine... i had taken some super 'should-work' prescriptions (legal... we talked it over with my doctor... don't worry)... it nothing worked. so to the ER my mother took me... lllllllllloooooooooonnnnnnggggggggggggg day, including meds, iv's, rice kri$pie$, and warm blankets in a freezing room... don't feel bad for me. I'm just complaining... we are so blessed to get treatment like this. Anyways, I've been "recovering" for the past 2 days and so.  But it is well with my soul. I'm good. and more than me, HE is good. Here, read this, it has really blessed me:  MORNING and EVENING Charles Spurgeon Morning of May 31, 2004  "The king also himself passed over the brook Kidron." --2 Samuel 15:23 David passed that gloomy brook when flying with his mourning company from his traitor son. The man after God's own heart was not exempt from trouble, nay, his life was full of it. He was both the Lord's Anointed, and the Lord's Afflicted. Why then should we expect to escape? At sorrow's gates the noblest of our race have waited with ashes on their heads, wherefore then should we complain as though some strange thing had happened unto us?  The KING of kings himself was not favoured with a more cheerful or royal road. He passed over the filthy ditch of Kidron, through which the filth of Jerusalem flowed. God had one Son without sin, but not a single child without the rod. It is a great joy to believe that Jesus has been tempted in all points like as we are. What is our Kidron this morning? Is it a faithless friend, a sad bereavement, a slanderous reproach, a dark foreboding? The King has passed over all these. Is it bodily pain, poverty, persecution, or contempt? Over each of these Kidrons the King has gone before us. "In all our afflictions He was afflicted." The idea of strangeness in our trials must be banished at once and for ever, for He who is the Head of all saints, knows by experience the grief which we think so peculiar. All the citizens of Zion must be free of the Honourable Company of Mourners, of which the Prince Immanuel is Head and Captain.  Notwithstanding the abasement of David, he yet returned in triumph to his city, and David's Lord arose victorious from the grave; let us then be of good courage, for we also shall win the day. We shall yet with joy draw water out of the wells of salvation, though now for a season we have to pass by the noxious streams of sin and sorrow. Courage, soldiers of the Cross, the King himself triumphed after going over Kidron, and so shall you. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey J, Sorry about all this stupid blog confusion... remember when I was changing my email and IM like every second?  oh well... I hope this is here to stay...    btw   - murphy  does  have quite a law, doesn't he? 
    
</post>


</Blog>