<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Poetry is not really my thing and it never was. But it seems that everyone around me thinks I am. To me poems have ro rhym, but that is not enteirly true. Poems don't have to rhym they can be anyhting they can be just your explination of love or life or you feelings towards someone, and sometimes that does not rhym cuz if it did you would be using word that are not relavant to what you are saying you are just looking for rhyming words.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       These feelings I have a burried deep with in me and i cannot explain them, not now not ever because to explain them would not do them justice, words cannot come close to the amount of love I have for you. Every day I wonder why god has blessed me with such an awesome gift and why, why you chose me I will never understand. What is it that you see in me? How can it be that you see me perfectly and I see nothing near perfect? How can it be that out of all the beautiful gorgeous girls out there, you chose me? But I've come to realize that I sould not be questioning why but thatnking god that you did in the first place. So now I say thank you, thank you for choosing me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Highschool a place and time of our live that is sure to be full of problems and issues. Most of us this past year have been separated from our friends, I know I have. And it took me time to cope with that but I have somewhat and I realize that there is nothing I can do but stay intouch with those friends I keep close to my heart. Make sure that you stay friends with them and it's not the end of the world you will no doubt make new friends throughout highschool so there is really nothing to worry about. or so we think......  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       No matter where life takes us we shall forever remain friends. No matter the paths we take throughout highschool or the careers we choos for university. Our bond of friendship will always bring us together again. Forever firends.         
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Where ever the journey of life takes us, we shall for ever remain friends. No matter the distance between us or the differences in our lives our bond of friendship will always bring us together again.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    the guys, andrew, mehdi and georgie!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Georgie!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I think thats jamie caitlin and lindsey yupp yupp thats them.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    awwww... Kaitlyn and *spez*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Evil child that Katie lol&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Throw your hand in the air and wave em' round like you jus dont care!!! ooo ooo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Theo!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Anton, the model???&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ally again!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    hana makin a funny face as usual! lol&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    the boys!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Monique, Kathren, Jess, Chantel, and Sarah&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ally eating!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    LMAO! jess and the ever wacky sarah!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    look tara and kara!!! its the ara's! lol&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    ooo! ok this picture is a bit more clear you can actually see people!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    LOOK! It's 8B!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Group shot!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Here we are watching a movie, "what women want"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    And of course the lovely kitchen ladies! Holly, Kristen, Natalie, and Meg!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is a few of us watchin Beau at our grade six graduation, wow he was small and had a very high voice.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A weird picture of my party!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    and yet another weird picture of my party, I seem to have a lot of those.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       What is love? Is it that feeling you get when ever you see that special someone pass you by and your heart skips a beat? Is it the way your legs turn to jello when ever they kiss you or hold you or hug you? Or is it that feeling of sheer happiness that you get when ever you talk to see hold or have anything to do with envolving that one person that you would give your life for, that one person that you would do absolutely anything for, that one person that you want to spend the rest of your life with? No amount of words can describe love it is impossible. Love is not just a word it is a feeling it is a way of life witout love would you want to live? No because love is what makes life worth living. Love is a magical feelinf that makes you want to change the world so that the person you love is forever happy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    LMFAO!!! this jus goes to prove how cocky men are!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    another group picture&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    And the ever gorgeous 8C&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    And our handsome 8C boys&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Group shot!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Our FI picnic unfortunately u can't really see anybody to clearly oh well.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    and the lovely ladies from left to right, natalie,  lindsey, caitlin, and jamie and of course theres me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is Monique my bestest bud (one of many!!!!!)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mehdi and me don't we look sweet&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    And the ever gorgeous Meg!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My PAR-TAY!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    LOOK! the Krystle's or Krystal's&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me and Jalyssa ain't I gorgeous i mean isnt she gorgeous? lol&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    People at grad! ' 04&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    More Grad pics! From left to right Abby, Holly, and Me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    MUHAHAHAHAHA!!! I got it to work!!!! YAY!!! oh ya this is me and Arianna at grad.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ally and Me at grad!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A metaphore is just a saying that people make difficult so that you have to find the real meaning behind it. Why can't they just say it plain andd simple? Why do they have to go all metaphoric on us?!?!?!?  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Be different, be weird, be true, be you!!!   What is life? Is it a great big test of courage, strength, power, love. No one really knows but throughout our lives we all try to find the answer to the question...What is the meaning of life? And the answer is simple, the meaning of life is what you make it to be.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>