<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Perfect temperature, sunny, and blues skies. What does that mean? Beach time. My friend Eleanor and I took in the sun and the waves on the north shore of Long Island. Truth be told, I haven't been to the beach much this entire summer. I guess that would explain my pasty stomach. I seriously think I blinded a few small children when I took my shirt off. My paleness aside, my time at the beach was very enjoyable. We even saw a very large lady that floating on/wrestling with (from the looks of it, either one could accurately describe what was going on) an inflatable whale.  Although it made me feel like a horrible person, I couldn't help but laugh at the sight of her jumping on the whale only to slide off and plunk back into the water.  By the way, it was Eleanor that pointed her out so clearly she is the worst person out of the two of us. We spent the greater part of the day at the beach and I am happy to report that I am now less pale than before.  After cleaning up, Cory and I drove Eleanor to the train station.  As we were waiting for the 7:19 train, we noticed a man walking up the tracks on the opposite end of the platform.  Obviously, walking in the train tracks is not the brightest of all ideas.  Last time I checked, a diesel LIRR train was a lot bigger than the average person.  A head-on encounter with one would not be pleasant.  But hey, I'm a med student...what do I know? Anyway, after many failed attempts, this guy managed to jump up and hoist himself up onto the opposite platform.  He walked down half the length of the platform and walks down the side access stairs.  For a little while, he just stands at the bottom of the stairs facing one of the platform supports.  I really thought he was going to whip it out and start peeing against it.  Luckily, we were spared the sight.  Instead, he mangages to get through the chain fencing that blocks off the tracks, walks under the platform, and hits the ground.  On all fours, he starts rummaging through the gravel.  He would pick stuff up and examine it with the greatest of care.  Maybe this guy was onto something.  Maybe there were precious gems or, dare I say, gold to be found underneath the platform at the Stony Brook train station?  Uh...I don't think so.  Once people started asking him if he was ok, he stopped his search and left.  The guy was probably coked out and was looking for drugs he dropped the night before as he walked by the train station.  Cocaine's one hell of a drug... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi. My name is Luis and I am a friendster-holic...  I am obsessed with it. Soon after signing up for it, I came to the realization that friendster could serve as a tool of procrastination and I immediately fell in love. Why spend time learning about the reabsorption of water in the Loop of Henle or about the coagulation cascade when you could be browsing the profiles of absolute strangers? Then, in a stroke of genius (fine...maybe it wasn't. Just go with it...), I discovered that friendster could be made even more fun if I wrote random messages to people. So now whenever I am bored or tired of studying, I browse profiles on friendster and write people random messages. Before I go on, I have something to share. I found this link as I was browsing profiles earlier today ( urlLink http://www.banterist.com/archivefiles/000169.html ). It is definitely worth checking out. I think I fall somewhere in between THE FRIENDSTER and THE FAUX-CANDID but without the familiarity with the whorehouses of Costa Rica.  So back to my obsession with friendster. If you think I message just anyone, think again. I only write to people who I find have something interesting in their profile to comment on. Interesting can be either a good thing or a bad thing and can itself lead to a friendly or not-so-friendly message. That's the beauty of the internet...you can say things to people in a message that you would never have the balls to say to them in person. I especially like to go after people who write that they want to meet "everybody" or "anybody". C'mon now, that has to be the biggest lie ever. I refuse to believe that. Do you know how many wackjobs there are out there? I know that I personally have no desire to meet "everybody"...and I'm a pretty social guy. "Everyone" or "anyone" includes the type of person that will kill and mutilate their mother or that will have an affair with their husband's pet monkey and I'd just rather stay away from them. Trust me, these people exist...just watch the 11 o'clock news...or Jerry Springer.  An example of someone I would have rather not met was the body scrub lady that accosted me today at Garden State Plaza. I went to my dad's body shop (where they fix cars, not where they sell beauty products) to wash my car. Afterwards, I decided to stop by the mall to pick up some things that I needed. After stops at Banana Republic and Sephora, I made a final stop at The Body Shop (the beauty product place). As I was walking out, I was approached by a fairly attractive woman. So in typical male fashion, I stopped to hear her out. BIG MISTAKE. "Have you heard of the Dead Sea?", she asks. I didn't even get a chance to answer when she had already pulled me off to her cart. That's right kids, she was based out of one of those carts in the mall. That should have served as an indication of things to come. She got me to put down my bags and proceeded to pour body scrub on my hands. She had me scrub my hands, rinse, and then poured moisturizing lotion on them. Although pleasant feeling, the whole process left my hands smelling a little too girly...even for my tastes (which can be pretty girly at times). She then informs me that the body scrub usually sells for $75 but that she was going to give it to me for $50. Although I am the kind of guy that would buy body scrub, I have absolutely no idea what would have tipped her off to that fact. I was wearing flip flops, an old pair of shorts, and a beat up t-shirt. And I was all dirty from having spent an hour and a half washing my car. Clearly, I was not a prime candidate for buying overpriced body scrub. This lady was obviously dilusional. I told her that I didn't have the money to buy her body scrub. She then asked me how much I had spent on my other purchases. I told her (highballed it, of course) and she said that I should consider the body scrub purchase as an investment in my skin which I will have for the rest of my life as opposed to the polo shirts I bought which I "would only wear a few times and then toss." I assured her that a wear my clothing more than just a few times and made up some excuse about being late to something to get away from her. In the end, I kind of felt bad that she wasted her time with me rather than devoting her energies to the two ladies that came up to her cart near the end of our encounter. Then again, she should have known better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No matter how much people bitch and moan about the French, I would still argue that they play a valuable role in my life. For example, a good French wine has been the source of much personal enjoyment on many occassions. Recently, the French have had a big impact in my everyday speech.  Ladies and gentlemen...I introduce the term, bourgie (pronounced boo-jee...or something like that. Do I look like Merriam-Webster?). It is derived from the word "bourgeois" and was coined by the one and only M.W. Robertson. Don't worry, he's not really "one and only", just a friend of mine from college. Anyway, Mark came up with this term to describe the kind of girl that I seem to be attracted to. In a nutshell, bourgie is used to describe a woman who is well educated, worldly, cultured, well put together, and has a sense of fashion. Kind of like a female metrosexual, if that makes any sense what-so-ever. Since it's introduction a few weeks back, I have incorporated the term bourgie into my vocabulary as much as possible. I am also encouraging others to do the same. So go out there and spread the word...literally. I'm hoping it will become the next big thing since "shock and awe".  Yesterday, I went outlet shopping at Woodbury Commons with my housemate Cory and my friend Erin. After deciding that Erin was in fact bourgie, Cory and I took on the task of identifying other bourgie girls. It kept us very busy, let me tell you. There were a lot of bourgie-looking girls...so many that it was hard to keep track of at times. I think they should change the name of the place from Woodbury Commons to BourgieLand.  On a side note, I received a random message on friendster from a girl in the Philippines today. I was excited but to my disappointment, Hallmark does not make a greeting card for this kind of occassion. She wants to know if I can be her friend. I always hear stories from my female friends about messages that they get from random guys in random asian countries, although many of these guys seem to reside in the Philippines. I always wondered what it would feel like to get a message of this nature. I guess now I know...my life has not been changed significantly because of it. At least the message I got wasn't sketchy like the one's my friends get sometimes. Anyway, I hate to sound mean but I don't think a friendship is going to work out. I can't even be friends with some people that live in New York. Plus, I already have a lot of friends...or at least that is what I'd like to believe. Being friends with someone in the Philippines sounds like too much work. I'd rather just sit here and watch late night Olympic coverage. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Girls are mean.  That has been the great lesson learned in the last few weeks.  Many of you would probably tell me that I am making a crazy generalization.  I assure you I am not.  Okay...so maybe my sample size isn't very big (only two, which would never stand up to scroutiny in the scientific world) but I am still reserving myself to right to apply my findings to the entire female gender.  So you might be asking, "what is this all based on?"  Well, let me tell you...  Our first example is AM.  I met AM a while back on friendster.  First we started exchanging emails and then we upgraded to AIM.  Things were going really well and we decided to meet up.  On a side note, never go on a first date to the Met.  Making conversation to get to know the other person, viewing art, and making intelligent comments on art are all tasks that individually require a lot of energy and thought.  They should never all be mixed...especially in a date kind of setting.  Needless to say, the date didn't go so well.  She was also a fan of modern art, which didn't help the situation seeing as I'd rather shoot myself in the foot than spend hours looking at modern art.  Regardless of how not well the date went, I still thought AM was a nice girl.  So when she said "we should hang out again", I totally agreed thinking it would be nice to be friends with her.  Apparently, she was not thinking the same thing.  I called her a couple of times afterwards to see if she wanted to hang out and she never answered the phone.  She emailed me once saying that she was really busy but that she would let me know when she had time to hang out.  Then, all of a sudden, she disappeared from IM.  I thought that was a little strange and after some investigating, I figured out that she had blocked me from her IM.  Did she think I wasn't going to figure it out?  C'mon...I know I'm not always the sharpest tool in the shed but you have to be kind of smart to be in medical school.  Seriously...  Case number two is C.  C was this amazing girl that I had the pleasure of dating for about three weeks.  She was smart, talented, funny, and cute.  After all of our dates, C would write me emails telling me what a great time she had.  I thought things were going well and started falling for her in a way I hadn't fallen for anyone in a while.  Everything was great until last week.  We were supposed to hang out last Sunday and I waited around for her to call me...but she never did.  I called her a couple of times and she never answered.  I thought C might have gotten mad at me for drunk dialing her at 2:45 a.m. (I know, I'm smoooove) so I sent her an email on Monday apologizing and asking if we could hang out at some other point in the week.  I didn't get a response until the end of the day when she sent me an email saying that the reason why she hadn't called me was that one of her exes had "popped back onto the radar screen" and that the situation had been going on since before she met me.  In my opinion, that would have been valuable information...three weeks prior!  Anyway, she said she hoped we could stay friends so I emailed her back saying that I would love to be friends and that we should definitely hang out sometime.  Let's just say that I haven't heard from her since.  Ladies and gentlemen, I think I was dooped again.  I guess I just wish girls would be upfront about things.  I wish they would just say something along the lines of "I never want to talk to you/see you ever again" rather than say "lets hang out again" or "I hope we can be friends" when they don't mean it.  I know it would probably suck a lot to hear that at first but in the end, it saves you from feeling pathetic later on when you actually try to be friends with these girls and you get no response.  I hope this didn't come off as a woman bashing blog entry, 'cause it isn't...ok, maybe just a little bit.  Truth be told, I like women.  My mom's a woman...that helps... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So after many months of reading other people's blogs, I decided to go ahead and start writing my own. One blog that I now read pretty religiously is written by this girl, Alexis ( urlLink http://www.lex.zogblaster.com/ ). I highly recommend you check it out. Her blog is hilarious and witty. No one should ever expect anything like that from me. Seriously folks...there's a reason why I'm in medical school and not writing the next big series of books since the Harry Potter series. If I can pull off an 8th grade level of writing, I consider myself extremely successful...  Although I should have written about this a week ago, I'm gonna go ahead and write about it now since it's been on my mind ever since. Two weeks ago, I had the pleasure of serving jury duty. Like most people, I was not thrilled about the prospect of having to sit in a room with a bunch of strangers for hours and hours on end. I was hoping that there would be some cute girls in the crowd to help pass the time. Walking around New York everyday, you see tons of attractive people all over the place. I think it's a pretty well known fact that there are more attractive people in New York than in most other places on the planet. So you'd think that a random sampling of the population of New York County would yield a group of fairly attractive people. Well...I thought wrong. There were only about 7 people (guys and girls) who I would consider attractive out of about 150. Being "hot" must be some kind of exemption to jury duty. It keeps you from being summoned in the first place and then, if the system makes a mistake and you get a summons anyway, you are dismissed within the first two hours of being there. The jury duty lady read off all the reasons why people should NOT be in jury duty and one by one all the attractive people got up and left. All that was left was a group of awkward looking people...not ugly...just awkward. I was very glad I had my iPod... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>