<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past 2 months I've worked in the music business.  Here's what I've learned:  1)  The people that work in this business (at my record label, anyway) truly love music.  Depite the glamor, the sex, the free tickets, the ability (gift) to make a decent living in "entertainment," and even the envy of friends, when all's said and done, these people love the music.  Even the people who don't know much about it.  Accountants, business people, whoever.  They love music.  This was one of my biggest and most pleasant surprises.  2)  I love music too much to work here full-time.  To watch the stuff being made, and to be stuck (as an 'MBA') doing the bean counting, is very frustrating.  Things that I love drive me crazy, plain and simple.  Girls, music, whatever.  My nails are bloody and gross--a clear biproduct of 2 things: 1) my propensity to devour my "nails" into a bare and bloody pulp; 2) working in the music business.  Not the relaxing revelation ("wow, and you call THIS...WORK?!) that I had hoped for.  (FWIHH)  3) "Urban Music," is run by a group of disorganized (if music-loving), unorthodox people, who do all kinds of things that we over in the pop side of the biz "dont want to know anything about."  This is freightening.  However, perhaps that helps to keep it authentic.  Street teams, payoffs, illegal sign postings (for which we budget)--only scratch the surface.  4)  For the most part, new rock music sucks.  It all sounds like Truman and AFI and Hoobistank (sp) with the whiny singer and the heavy guitar.  The whiny singer can work.  Sunny Day Real Estate, Blink 182, and even Eminem are proof.  But I liked music trends better when everyone wanted to sound like Eddie Vedder, not a fucking 14-year old girl.  5)  Hip hop is a legitimate and good art form.  Some of the beats are great.  Between the beats, the lyrics, the samples, even just the attitude--there is a lot to like in hip hop music.  I hated it before coming out here.  The best new music, is (and I am shocked to hear myself say this) rap music.  It is new, fresh, interesting, and catchy.  Edgy.  Rock is stuffy and old.  Except for that Rise Against song Give it All.  6)  The people here are, for the most part, so good.  My boss has been so nice to me, even though there wasn't much for me to do.  Tonight, we are off to drinks to celebrate my last day.   Rachel, Carla, Myra, Glen, Jeff H., and Berman.  In weeks to come, we will deal with the following: 1) the outrageous number of girls with whom i have become "involved" since arriving in LA 2) going back to business school 3) the ex girlfriend coming to visit over the next couple days 4) my (in)ability to keep this BLOG  Hopefully, it will get better between now and then.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>