<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am so frustrated.  I just have to write this down because if I don't get it out of my system I am going to scream at someone who doesn't deserve it and then I'll feel even worse.  *sigh*  Married life is usually the best.  I mean, I love my husband all to pieces and he's a great guy.  Lately, however, it has been a different story altogether.  And I don't know how to fix it.  I'm starting to get so mad.  I know that's not the correct reaction, but I can't help it!  I am at the end of my rope and I can't take anymore.  I really can't.  For the last two weeks, he has been going through such HUUUGE mood swings, that I just can't cope anymore.  For the last two days, he's gone from literally yelling at me to bringing me flowers back to yelling at me.  And the yelling?  It's over stupid little crap.  Like I didn't have my checkbook with me yesterday.  Hello!  Both of us put our checkbooks away because we were having trouble with the account.  Remember?  SO don't yell at me for something that is beyond my control.  Today, I'm driving someone else's vehicle.  Mind you, it's not even my own, but all the same I get yelled at when it leaks the last little bit of gas it had in it out and I ran out on my way back to work after lunch.  And yeah, I forgot that you can't close the door all the way, so I got locked out, but that's the first time he's actually had to go out of his way to help me since I've been driving this trash heap.  Yell at me for 'not having my head screwed on straight' when really the problem is that you are stressed out and you won't talk to anyone about it and so I get to catch the brunt of your bad temper.  I don't think so.  And he'd better not come home expecting anything in the bedroom.  Because as much as I understand that guys need sex, I also understand that for them to get any they need to attend to the needs of the woman they intend to get it from and that is definitley not happening lately.  Oh, I could just scream!  Doesn't help to cry.  Tried that already.  All that happens is my eyes get red and my face gets wet.  I prayed about it, but I just don't seem to be getting any answers.  The only people I'm comfortable talking to about all of this I can't talk to because a) they are my parents and don't need to be in the middle of this melodrama or b) my best friend is still single and doesn't have proper perspective on the situation.  SO here I am, pounding out my frustrations on a keyboard when all I really want is to be loved and appreciated by my husband.  Not yelled at for being stupid or unorganized or selfish.  All of which may be true on some level, but I don't need that from him.  God, help me not to lose my mind.  I think I might if this doesn't let up sometime soon.    Tata for now.  Must go clean house while am furious.  Maybe I'll actually get something done and prove that I'm not disorganized or stupid.  bleah 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>