<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       ooWwwWWww   i broke my nose...   NOT COOL!   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well howdy. after that nasty little shot by my fellow blogger, I have decided to do my blog... Firstly, I would like to give a pat on the back to whoever invented bubble wrap. I mean, talk about multi-purpose. It starts off keeping our breakable items safe in their box, and then faithfully fulfills my need to hurt something. Each 'pop' that I hear is like a shriek of terror...not that I'm one to hurt things, but ya'll must admit that sometimes it feels good to vent. Now, I would also like to have a little chat with whomever made pizza pops. If you were cool enough to make something as tasty as a pizza pop, why could you not take the time to make sure the yummy filling doesnt burst out the other end? C'mon man! Or lady... I am the victim of a cast beating. Fortionatly, my bruise can only be seen under certain lighting, and you have to run your hand over my arm to feel the bump, but it is still a sad affair. But I do believe it is subsiding... But that is all. Good day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Okay, so being the faithful blogger I am, I decided to check in with blog life.  Today, officially the coolest thing ever is walking out in a downpour, for serious. And puddle hopping, too. And I love the new Taking Back Sunday CD, it's hot.  But I have to stop saying 'that's hot' or 'it's hot', I've been pretty good today, but yesterday was horrendous.  I sounded like Paris Hilton...And after my late night mini supper I'm still kind of hungry. Wow, do I talk about food enough in my posts?! And me=so psyched. I finallly get to work again, and have money. More than $24.60. Even though my first two shifts won't count because I'll be working them off for my Mom...but I'll get to work with Quinn so that should be entertaining.  And Chelby likes Plain White T's!! Wahoo for her. We're such music buddies.  La dee da...Oasis in my brain....at least it's better than Keisha Chante who has deceptivly mind entrancing songs.  And my broken brother is officially a woman beater. Who "casts" people.  Mmm...short post. But thats okay I suppose, it's better than none...not naming names...My neighbour always has the light on in his loft deal, and it's high up, so he can peer into my computer window, and it's a sad story because I ripped the blind off of the window. A ha. I'm out kids.   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        You know what I love? E-bay. It doesn't get a whole lot cooler than that to me. And you know what I found out today? That Chris Carrabba used to sing for Further Seems Forever. I suppose I should've known, but I'm oblivious to these sorts of things. This blogging thing just keeps getting wierder for me. It feels like I'm talking to myself, but people are listening and I don't know it. Do do do do do do. Honestly I could kill for some 5 cent candies right about now. I am such a deep thinker. Well hopefully this is entertaining Miss.Binkley herself because this post is for her, since I'm apparantly the worst blogging buddy. But what are you going to do? And I say, just make a post of mindless information. Which is about as deep as I am at most times, which is unfortunate, yes? I'm addicted to the smell of coconut sex wax. And I want my MTV.  Sorry I won't pull a Mark Knopfler. Or will I? And I want to have Alexandre Despatie's babies. Sorry again. I think I'm going to go for bed, because my night time humour isn't really funny to anyone else but myself. Good night planet Earth.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       by the way...I learnt how to be as cool as I am from Chris.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       pssst... life is better again... :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      *sigh* How come things gotta change and such? I mean...how come emotions and feelings have to change? Why can't we just be stangnant and un-evolving (is that a word...)?  How come I ask questions of people who are not there... 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hey Kids:   So here's my first official post, since my first was kinda sad, so I'll just forget about that. I could delete it, but I'm just too lazy and who knows what you'd be missing. Well I don't know who is all going to read this except me and Chelby, but I'll still make an effort to post because I'm a team player, yes? It is soo nice and sunny out and I want to lie outside and tan my ghostly self, but the grass is too damn long, which isn't the greatest because then the insects will come after me. I am so hungry. I know some people never eat breakfast, but I am not one of those people. I always eat breakfast, and today, I have found no breakfast. Boo erns for me...So today is finally the start of hockey. Not good kind, just camps, which are boring to watch, but I get to go in and talk to the concession lady so I can have money again. But then the season starts soon, which is cool. And now since I can't go camping on the September long, hockey is what I'll look forward to. Since school isn't really something I enjoy, except for being able to see my friends again. Blog, blog, blog. I'm not used to this kinda thing so I don't know what to write. Chelby has cool posts of goodness, and mine so far isn't the greatest. Hers details events and happenings, mine is random ramblings. But let me tell you something: I hate my brother. Anyhow, more on that later as that progresses. Like King Charley, who knows what I'm talking about eh? eh?! Ooh well that's it for now. Bye bye boys and girls.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alrighty...back again. I must agree with Mel. Who is going to read this other then me and her? I've gotta apologize for what I'm going to be showing ya'll next, but it made me laugh, so i decided to enlighten everyone out there. Aaaand GO.   What do you call a woman with a sinking ship on her head?               Mandy Lifeboats Hahahahahaha...Well, I thought it was clever at least... But alas, that is all for now. Plus, I really ought to be watching the Olympics... Ta Ta  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I wish I could bowl. I want my own bowling ball one day. It will be shiny and new. I will love it. In the side of its shiny-newness, will be my name, masterfully engraved. Mine. Mine alone. Is that wierd? Should someone like me who only bowls a couple times a year wanna bowl so bad? Or want their own bowling ball? Why oh why oh why...       So me and Mel went for a friendly midnight stroll to 7-11 yesterday. How come night time strolls are so much more fun then daytime strolls? It's crazyness, no? OooooOooh! And we also discovered that 7-11 is the nighttime hang out for pretty boys...in MY town at least. Haha. Joke.  So I was checking out the Something Corporate website the other day, and I came across something i found midly amusing. Here goes. 
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      pleeeease work  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        ahoy!     welcome to our blog! my names chelby and over there's mel :) we're just new here so please, no yelling while we figure this crazyness out...     see ya'll soon...        
     
    
</post>


</Blog>