<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      quite the title, but I seriously hate looking for work.  I have been lots of places on the expansive internet to try and find the perfect job. I have been mostly looking for graphic design and/or photography jobs. Unfortunately, a vast majority requite that the sucessful candidate have a 4 year degree in graphic design. I almost have to laugh at the requirement. What most students learn in 4 years, I have in one.. and not at a school, but through work... A lot of what is taught is design principles and learning how to accurately determine what is the concept that the customer (or employer) wants and then doing it... a student learns lots of interesting techniques that they may or may not EVER use on the job...  I am by no means saying that getting a degree is bad, I am just wishing that prospective employers would be open to people who don't have a degree but are just as capable of performing the job required.  anyway... I am frustrated and am trying so hard to let God be in control of this whole thing...  NEWSFLASH: Debbie talked with her mom yesterday after we got her a new phone.. . She said "Whatever you decide to do, your father and I will support you. You are an adult and we trust you.. BUT you had better make sure that you know that you know that you know that this is the path that God wants for you and you had better be able to look everyone in the eye and tell them that this is what God wants and that you have peace about it" Or something along those lines... pretty surprising move for her..I'll keep praying and we'll see what happens when it happens.. 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I applied for a job working an offset press overnights a couple days ago. I had an awesome interview and I felt amazing about it. It was doing something I had gone to school for and missed working with offset presses. A big plus was the $20 an hour that they were going to pay. Well, the second guy that I was going to interview with decided that I didn't have enough recent experience.... I haven't worked a press in a few years, but it's like riding a friggin bike! Anyway... bad day at work yesterday.. I left work early on Tuesday and got yelled at because of it... well, I didn't know how much work was really in the store! NO ONE COMMUNICATES AT THAT DAMN PLACE!! THAT made me so mad. *sigh* I need a new job  Anyone know of any good internet places to search for jobs besides Monster, Career Builder, or HotJobs?  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after seeing Brent's blogspot, I figured that it was time to start my own. Welcome me to your family. Today, I just get off work and all I am doing is sitting here at Kinkos and publishing my blog. Seeing Debbie later and going to have a wonderful time... soon, I will post my history and where I have been. Not tonight though. I would take too much time. Ask Brent, he knows..  I will say a little about myself. I am 27, opinionated, somewhat cynical, and I am going to kick ass for Jesus. I am an untrained youth pastor and that dream will become a reality soon for me. Like Brent, I went to North Central as well. I believe that I desipsed it as much as he did. We worked together for a couple years on the Northern Light when I was the editor. He and I, along with a few freedom fighters, produced light in a dark world that resides at 14th and Chicago. May the legacy continue. I have a beautiful and stunning woman of God for a girlfriend, I am attending a new church (sorry, Brent. I gotta do what I feel is right), and I hate my job.. but a new one comes along soon.. I KNOW it will..  for now, let this be just a taste of what is to come. May we all share in the glory that is truth, may we defend it till our last breath, and may we all benefit from the sharing of true knowledge that can help shape our wisdom..  ta ta for now  
    
</post>


</Blog>