<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so my daughter, Emma, started crawling this past weekend. So we baby-proofed the house all weekend. Our dog's (Belle's) food &amp; water bowls (shiny silver) are near the kitchen and Emma's play area. My daughter is like a racoon: anything shiny must be touched! My wife and I watch as Emma crawls her way over to the dog bowl full of fresh dog food. We repeatedly say "no" as she crawls over there (she's only 8 1/2 months old, so she doesn't comprehend). We let her touch the food bowl, then pull her hand away, slap it (Extremely) gently, say "no" again, then move her back to her play area. She immediately crawls back for the food bowl. (This is what Paul would refer to as the "sin" nature in Romans...even appearing before the age of 1!).  So I start to notice Emma is drooling a lot...almost like spit up, but not that much. I discount it as drool (which is happening a lot since she's teething, too) and watch her crawl back toward the dog bowl. She's drooling and then crawling through it which is really grossing me out. I pick her up and ask my lovely wife (Allison) to wipe off her hands and face. Allison then sees a big 'ol piece of dog food in Emma's mouth! YUCK!!!!!!! My wonderful wife sticks her fingers in Emma's mouth and pulls out the slimy, slightly dissolved dog food and throws it away.  So, Emma had been munching on some dog food for about 4 minutes before we even found out! And she kept crawling back to the bowl! I guess she likes dog food. Maybe that will save us some money in the long run! :)  Thought I'd share my lovely pre-dinner event with the world.  Kids are exciting.  And kinda gross, too....sometimes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    My daughter crawled for the first time yesterday.  We will now be chasing her until she's 18.  Let the good times roll!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      From my last post, I mentioned a  urlLink game  I am addicted to.  After hours of random testing, I finally figured out the correct sequence!  (it's the small things in life)    1) Square (robot)   2) Sun (orange sphere)   3) Ladder   4) Mountains   5) Egg   6) Pipe   7) Fan   8) Gear   9) Wind (cyclone) 10) Dish 11) Circle / Jet thingy 12) TV screeen / monitor  What a great finish to another truly productive day at work! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I must say I was extremely productive at work today! About half the office was out, so there wasn't much going on, especially since my boss wasn't there. So a few co-workers and I were talking about good CDs we had. I then mentioned that I would like a copy of a co-worker's CD. The other 2 perked right up and asked if we had a burner in the office, which we do. I then spent about 4 hours ripping and burning 8 CDs and making 2 or 3 copies of each CD. Can a blog be used as evidence in a court of law? If so, may I mention that I'm a frequent liar, especially about gross acts of copyright infringement? :)  Anyway, I ended up with some good rap CDs I was mildly interested in (Nelly & 50 Cent). I also ended up with some Godsmach CDs. I couldn't tell you what they sing, but all I know is that it kind of scares me. So I won't be listening to them. But I did score Coldplay and the Jets albums. I would like to recommend everyone getting those 2 albums (whether you prefer to pay or pirate is up to you). The Jets album stinking  rocks  from start to finish. Good stuff.  I just thought I'd let ya' know about my super productive day at work. I finished up the day playing a really weird but wildly entertaining  urlLink game  on the internet.  If you figure out how to maximize all the pieces, please let me know...it's driving me nuts!  Peace out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      People tell me I talk a lot.  Which is very true. I recently saw a friend's  urlLink blog  and decided that the blog was my natural calling!  I hope to not spend every entry talking about my "b e a utiful" daughter Emma, but I can't promise anything, as she is a countinual fountain of new tricks and stories.  I'm off to watch the Olympics!  Women's gymnastics!  Exciting stuff. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Larger than life&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>