<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LOL!!! oh blinking dramatic does that sound eh?   What I mean is I have opened the door to my little forum on Delphi.   urlLink http://forums.delphiforums.com/willowisp/start    I will not stand by and not share, I  feel I have to do this, sort of cathartic know what I mean?  Anyway, anyone who thinks they can just waltz in and start bashing or trolling is in for some challenges.  I have been on Delphi long enough to know that there are some serious shit stirrers, and I will not have that happen.      A sheep I am not. LOL!  
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Fall is almost here, you know what that means. BACK TO SCHOOL YEEEEEHAW!!  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hallelujah I made it through the visit.  Of course she was here 45 mins earlier than she said she would be. So there we were at 8:15 just dressed when she showed up. Oh well she sat and had coffee with us while the kids ate their cereal.    We gave her a full tour of the new church which totally blew her mind. Central would fit into our foyer. lmbo~     Dinner at the China Emerald was ok, I found some veggies and salad I could eat so I hope I didn't blow my diet for this week.  But on a good note we are done with the visit until Xmas so I can get down to serious dietting.    Mum, went on and on about how bad a dog would be but I tried to ignore her. I want my puppy!!!   
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          My mother in law is coming in less than 15 hours and I am not even freaking. Ok I am freaking but I am not ready. I need to vac the family room and clean the upstairs bathroom. I just can't get into it this time. Maybe it was the horrible Broccoli reaction I had from my lunch. OMG I am in so much pain from the stupid green junk. That will teach me.  I do have a great little parent moment to share. Caleb my oldest was at a friend's house last night while the parents were out. He only had a small bowl of icecream because he knew that his father and I would be upset if he had, had a huge one!!! To me this shows great control and shows that he listens, and can be trusted. Today it is a bowl of icecream, in a few years it will be a beer at a party.  
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Time for bed, yes all my energy is used up for another day. It seems I owe hubby some good lovin' since he was able to let my MIL down easy about next weekend. Whew! As well she has agreed to go to a Chinese all you can eat on Sunday for the kids. Lets just home they have a great salad bar. I am not paying Jenny Craig money so I can just screw around on food I don't even like.  I am so sad, Ziggy's family is having a huge garage sale Saturday morning, the only neighbor I liked on this street is moving. I hope we are next. 
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         We were out doing errands to day and hubby and I got coffee, the kids wanted some water to go with their donuts so we asked for a couple of cups.  "I am sorry, we only SELL bottled water" was the gals comment. We drive up to pay for our stuff and hubby asks again if he could just have a cup of tap water for the kids. She sticks to her story that they can't do that they only SELL water. If we were inside the store she could give us tap water.  Hubby got all snarky and told them he would not be back to this location. That everyone other one in the city doesn't have a problem giving a kid a cup of water. It really pissed me off since we were not just asking for water we were dropping at least 5$ there for other stuff. Grrrrr  
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My husband just doesn't get why I am on here again. He needs a hobby that is for sure. Other than doing the laundry I mean. I have never in my life seen someone so obessed with laundry. It has to be washed. It can be piled up in the laundry room all clean but it has to be clean. I think it would be fine if he put the stinking ( not anymore ) stuff away.  He just sits and watches me. Drives me batty.
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He talks about them all day long, everyone he sees he has tocomment on them. His big fun is to bump me and make them bounce.  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ok, my youngest is totally obessed with boobs. I kid you not.   Posted by  urlLink Hello  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Oh my gosh!!! I think just figured this dang thing out, techie I am not, just a tired old woman. LOL!!!  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, ok just one my MIL.
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         What do you think it is that makes otherwise private people jump into the net and tell their lives to total strangers? Do you think it is our ingrained need to reach out? Or maybe for some a need to show off? Heck I don't even know why I am doing this, I saw a friend had one and thought why not me too. LOL!  
</post>


</Blog>