<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, I'm on my friends' brother's computer and I'm making yet Another Post just to take up some more space. My friends are behind me right now screwing around playing basketball with a tennis ball, and I'm sucking on a popsicle stick typing away mindlessly until I get bore 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This post is to take up space on this blog.  Stfu. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've been thinking of a letter to write to this girl I like a whole lot at school.   She seems like a nice girl.. but I just don't know what to say to her when I finally work up my guts and finally put it down on the line. I've been thinking of writing a poem or a lovenote or something. But I suck at that kind of stuff. I've been getting my friends to tell her the stuff that I need to tell her, but I can't just use my friends as messenger boys. I've also been using  her  friends that I like her, and that's the way the thing is getting started.. I can feel my heart sink to the bottom of my stomach when she passes me in the hallway.. I sit behind her in study hall, drawing detailed sketches of the back of her head. Her locker is about 20 lockers down from me, and she's friends with the girl that's in the locker next to mine. I danced with her in 5th grade one time.      I just don't know what to say.  
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's yet another morning in my cramped computer space. I feel a little drowsy today. Mainly because I had a bit too much Nyquill. That stuff can knock you out, man.      I'm gonna be posting a hell lot of crap on here today, because somehow my Steam isin't working. Those of you who know what Steam is can now feel my pain and sorrow.      No, I'm not gothic.      So I guess I'ma look for more funny pictures and save them on my computer for future reference.      P's.  
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey guys, me again, yet another post. Today I killed the entire Counter-Terrorist team in one whole round. I rockzors.      I found some really cool pictures on the internet, but I need friggin' Hello BlogBot to post pictures directly on the blog.. damnit damnit damnit.. (walk away mumbling angirly)   
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay. I did ALL I could to get rid of these goddamned pop ups, but they never go away. It's like a stray cat that stays in the back alley of your apartment, meowing and meowing the WHOLE NIGHT. So eventually you end up throwing a shoe or a brick down the windowsill at any moving object down below.. and then end up missing.. and it's still there.. Anyways..      I turned on Spyware Blaster, a new spyware remover I downloaded off of Kazza. Works like a charm, but when I turn it off the spyware comes back. Not to mention the lag I experience on Counter-Strike because of all this goddamned spyware.  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey guys.      Gawd am I tired. It's bad enough that I couldn't sleep last night and ended up watching Kids in The Hall for 3 hours. I stayed up until like.. 4 in the morning getting the theme song stuck in my head (hey, it's a pretty kickass tune). And then to make matters worse, I wake up at 10:30!! Wtf!? I only slept like.. 6 hours!? It's madness!!      Anyways I was just about to turn Steam on before I posted on my blog.       Keep on tranglin',   Endiment  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey doodes! My name's Jon. But my nickname online (and in Counter-Strike) is Shinobi. Welcome to the first post on my new blog!      ...      Erm. Not much to talk about, eh? Due to the lack of creativity I'll rant on and on and on. Starting now!      Hello Viklas! Your mother is the speed limit. Aspirin can sometimes cause cancer in women and small animals. Please use extreme caution with lawn gnomes.       Your Tylenol,   Shinobi  
    
</post>


</Blog>