<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok..i decided dat thr is no such thing as 'an eye for an eye'...i will let DM find out bout the hypocrite attitude of TIAK SHIT..so i just keep my mouth shut n prove to the DM dat i can perform better thn the HEad, the Vice and the rest of the ExCo..even though i m an ExCo now..i will still stay the same prefect as i m..still wun catch people for smuggling food n so on.. I can DO it...cos  i have u as my support..  damn bored now....someone entertain me pls......................... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's practically a fun yet boring yet fruitless day for meh..woke up, heard tuition teacher sick, not coming..so on the com n started playing game..haha..thn eat breakfast n carry on playing till dinner time..play LOD, SimSafari, GB...haha..so fun yet boring.. But yet..i nvr even touch on my studies loh..wasted one whole weekend..gonna chiong during weekdays liao..haiz......ok..now go bathe liao..bye bye.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Ncc training...guess whu came? u guess la...gues...dat fooker blardy sheety 'Senior Spec' IZAP COLD!!! Damn shit loh..came n took the part a whom i m training to train the orienteers C&amp;C loh..its like..why must people going for orienteering competition be training their voice? for wad? He purposely one loh..some more still go pump the part b..come on la IZAP, we r the specs liao la..u just siam aside la..coem n extra for wad? call ur self senior spec..i pui* anyhow pump people..tink i forgot wad happen izzit? pump me..n cannot even tink of an reason y u pump..thn anyhow cock sum excuse up..stupid la..ok..u're stupid, IZAP COLD!!! Go suck up to BOB la!!! Alrite..after trainin, Sir Jeremy actually wanted to treat the 5 of us to Marche..but Jeremy need to go for tuition n some fellow not present..so not full force..thn in the end we only went Cineleisure to eat PAstamania...n the coffeebean..after dat go home liao..quite sian la..haha..but Sir promise dat he's gonna treat next time..rite? I hope the next time he treat, we also promoted liao loh..still dunno wad post i m... Alrite..now its like i damn bored la..dunno wad to do..see show or play com or just sit here n breathe........S.I.A.N. . . =P 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So its like today i show Toh, n he said dat its isn't fair that he haven went thru my proposal of the prefects thingy..so when i next see him during recess..he told me i have lotsa suggestions..very good..n dat they are very sharp..haha..as i said..i can pia my way out one..just U wait n see..tiak..although i may seem to slack b4 i was exco..but now..i m given the golden chance to prove myself..n get u out...u better watch out..u better watch out..Raynard Ang is coming..to ..town... =) Ok..tomolo Sir gonna treat us to food liao..cos he's promotion coming..haha..wonder when's my promotion in NCC...damn slow leh...feakin slow loh..more thn half a year liao..... Alrite..gtg bathe liao...ythn later enjoy myself playing com..hehe..no more tests liao.......yeah!!! n mayb late in the nite..call someone..dunno can or not.. =P 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alrite man!! Tink mayb DM's on my side or wad..haha..went to se him today..he asked me wads the reason i tink i was called here..i replied dat the HEad Puifat n Vice Shit dun like me..*haha* HE was like..so shocked loh..first time people replied such n ans when kanna sacked..so he told the Head n Vice..made me an ExCo, a Senior Puifat..haha..n i m given the chance to voice my opinions liao..haha..now i can slowly slowly removed..the TIAK shit..n those i tink not up to standard liao.....or those abusing power...u'll wait n SEE!!! Anyway..tomolo having meeting personally wif DM, want me to show him the problems n solutions of anything..i gonna tell him everything..n i mean EVERYTHING!!! haha.. By the way..I'm damn happy today loh..no bout kanna promoted..but sumthing else..haha..finally..nvm..hehe =P 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oKie, bascially i dunno how i feel now..just heard that tomolo i gotta see the DM, MR R2D2...was called out today wif some other sec2 prefects by Boss Head Prefect..But yet, he tried to beg wif the 2 people dat complained bout me, to forgive me..( did i hear wrongly? forgive me? WTF had i done? ) Ok,let me roughly say bout wad happen...Dat B|00dY sNg TiAk just do not like my face..i noe it..when leonard n me were late for duty becos we wee kept longer by teacher to tok bout the test coming..he tailed me all the way to the other side of the canteen...only me..ONLY ME!!! y? dunno..ask me bout wad time izzit, which i ans u dun have watch meh? Thn he said i was late for duty, but still dun care when i told him the reason, so i ans dat i din noe dat prefects can fail their tests but heck bout it..dats weird loh.. So now, i m happy dat if i were to be sacked from prefects, i can stop facing that TIAK shit, but yet, its gonna affect my testamonial....i m damn confused..but if i were to remained, i have to be dog to that shit again..which i find it damn humilating..how?!?!?!?!?
     

    
</post>


</Blog>