<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm watching the Olympics and the local station does an advertisement for it's news program, 6 o'clock, 11 o'clock, best news team, award winning, blah, blah, blah. Then they said something that made me take notice. They said something to the effect that they have realized that if you tell people the facts, (hold on to your hats, people), they will know the truth. I sat there blinking at the TV...Tell people the facts and they will know the truth. They made a commercial to tell me this!? Now I'm wondering if they thought I was to ignorant to figure that one out on my own, or did THEY just figure that one out and flet they had to tell me about it. I'm just picturing a busy news room, the clicking of keyboards, telephones ringing, a low din of conversations, people consulting others on stories and leads. Over in the corner a cub reporter staring at some copy suddenly looks as if a light has just gone off in his head. He stand on his desk and in a loud voice announces to the news room "People, listen! If you tell people the facts...They will know the truth!". The room goes quiet. You can see everyone mouthing the words this cub reporters had just spoken, trying to wrap their heads around this new concept. "If you tell people the facts, they will know the truth." Suddenly a man in a starched shirt and tie stands and barks, "By god this man is right!...Doug, call a meeting. We have to let people know about this! Team, my office in 5 minutes. Bring everything you got on this concept, we might just have something here!" The news room begins to bustle again. Fade to black. Well, I'm glad to see that my local news now understands that if they tell me the facts, I'll know the truth. I guess they can stop the "Let's just tell them enough to scare the crap out of them." or the "Yea, we're a news department, but we have our own agenda." tactics they had been using. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep hearing people talk about freedom. About living free. They want to be free to do what they want, when they want, to whom they want. Kudos. But why does it have to be at the expense of MY freedom? Why is that? What have I done to them? I just want to live my life the way I see fit. They want to eat in a smoke-free restaurant, great, find one, frequent that establishment, tell all your friends. Can't find one? Talk to a restaurant owner. Maybe they'll change. Or better yet, if you think that there are so many people out there that want to eat their meals in a smoke-free environment, start your own! You'll have your cake and eat it too! Smoke-free! Don't go bitching to your local elected officials and force everyone to bow down to your way of life through threat of fines, imprisonment or loss of property at the point of a gun.   So Tired   That's just one example, I'll write about many more. I feel I must do this because I'm getting so tired. I read the news, listen to people talk, and see what our Kulture has become. I don't want to be living in this world of Socialist vs. Moralist, of Left vs. Right, of Liberal vs. Conservative. They're both wrong. They don't care about you, they care about control, absolute and total. I think there is an alternative, a Sub-Kulture, where you have more than freedom, you have liberty. And hey, I won't force it on you. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>