<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Analytical Reject 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Forty Six and Two Theory-There are three totally different kinds of humans on the Earth, meaning that they perceive the One reality in three different ways, interpreted differently. The first kind of human has a chromosome composition of 42+2. They comprise a unity consciousness that does not see anything outside themselves as being separate from themselves. To them, there is only one energy - one life, one beingness that moves everywhere. Anything happening anywhere is within them, as well. They are like cells in the body. They are all connected to a single consciousness that moves through all of them. These are the aboriginals in Australia. There might be a few African tribes left like this. Then, there is our level, comprising 44+2 chromosomes. We are a disharmonic level of consciousness that is used as a steppingstone from the 42+2 level to the next level, 46+2...These two additional chromosomes change everything.   The human genome - the complete set of human genes - is composed of twenty three separate pairs of chromosomes. Twenty-two, of which, are numbered in order of size, from the largest (1), to the smallest (22). The remaining pair consists of the sex chromosomes. Therefore, we have 44+2 chromosomes.   According to the teachings of Drunvalo Melchizedek, who is the founder of the flower of life teachings, and the originator of this theory, there are three grids for human consciousness around planet Earth, which correspond directly with the chromosomes in the human body. The first one is forty-two plus two, the second is forty-four plus two (our current evolutionary position), and a third which consists of forty-six plus two chromosomes. The third grid contains "Christ" consciousness.   As anyone with a bit of education and half an ounce of intelligence will tell you, the current number of chromosomes (23) is of no significance at all. Many species, including our closest species among the apes, have even more chromosomes, and many have fewer.   Although like with any religion or philosophy the validity of the facts at face value may look false, but it does stimulate the mind, and Melchizedek definitely has an interesting theory behind consciousness. He also has some very interesting information about sacred geometry and how it relates to you personally. If you haven’t already, read Nothing in This Book Is True, But It's Exactly How Things Are, by Bob Frissell. In the book, Bob tells the story of Druvalos teachings, and reveals sacred geometry to you in an easy to understand way.   With many other theories and philosophies, it is important to use them as a way to explore a temporary belief system (coined by Robert Anton Wilson), also known as a reality tunnel, which stimulates the mind, and allowed themselves to explore a new way of thinking about consciousness and reality itself.   Beliefs are often crippling to the mind, you should try and explore anything and everything. Even if you encounter success with a particular meditation, such as the MERKABA, or ritual magic, once you start to develop your own dogma, your mind is dead. Temporary belief systems, temporary egos, or temporary reality tunnels (one in the same) are the way to go, because belief systems create the kind of complacency where ignorance thrives. This is the way to the true forty six and two state of emotional evolution.  
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       today has just started & there is nothing that i want more for it too end. all of these randomized thoughts are creating a  distraction for the future to dissect. my future and past have merge to create a tomorrow. nothing will stand in the way of it. invention of a great mortality is just another acronym. today has just started and there is nothing i want more for it too just end.......  
    
</post>


</Blog>