<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The title is just an excuse to post funny  urlLink pictures  of the pope. Whatever you think of him, you have to admit:  urlLink the man  is dead funny. Look what he got caught doing. That  urlLink poor sob  is always trying to promote Catholicism.       
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yesterday I visited a dutch   weblog   which I visit quite often. One of the posts was about how great the eighties were. Well, let me tell you: the eighties sucked harder than a baby on a breast. We didn't have internet for starters. Most of us didn't even have a pc yet. No mobile phones, no digital cameras, no mini-discs, no cd-roms. But we did have: the Berlin wall, Thatcher, a black Michael Jackson, a pope who could still talk understandably, etc... And this: Eighties hairdos     and Duran Duran (with wicked eighties hairdos):    Please leave your opinion or views in the comments.    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Actually I had a dream. Last night.       I was organising a birthday party and I decided to get Led Zeppelin to play at the party. Wut? Yes Led Zeppelin.    So I sent them a letter asking if they were up for a gig in Belgium. The next week those buggers show up at my door, all of them. Just to tell me they were interested but they charge 150.000 dollars per concert. Wut? Yes 150.000 dollars. That pretty much ruined my dream.       Then I woke up with a dry mouth and smog in my head.             
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       with the following keywords: auction your mother. This is what came up.    I say: let's auction her at a starting price of € 1,75. Place bids in the comments!  
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Since it's "en vogue" I feel I should post on this topic.  Most people come out looking  urlLink great , but sometimes it goes  urlLink wrong .    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A simple little  urlLink game  involving five cubes. The goal is to click the red square and move it around without touching sides or the blue cubes. A score of more than 18 seconds is considered phenomenal.  (Thx to Markie Mark &amp; his funky bush of hair).   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        A Dutch website dedicated to selling some candy you'll never see me eat. How about you? Would you give it a try?    urlLink  Strange freakin' candy    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        A new version of the worm that spread from infected Microsoft Web servers in June has been identified and is using instant messages and infected Web sites in Russia, Uruguay, and the United States to spread itself, according to one security company.    Researchers at PivX Solutions of Newport Beach, California, have intercepted new malicious code closely resembling that from widespread   attacks in June attributed to a worm named "Scob" or "Download.ject." The new attacks use mass-distributed instant messages to lure Internet users to Web sites that distribute malicious code similar to Download.ject  
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I've been a naughty boy. I have been out last night and I had a   teenie-weenie bit too much to drink.     And now I'm at work with a teenie-weenie bit of a hangover. The thirst is the worst part,   not so much the headache. I tried smoking a cigarette earlier but I couldn't finish it. My mouth feels like an ashtray right now. Work and hangovers don't go well together...      What should be my punishment? Tell me in the comments.          
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're probably asking yourself why I chose this name. No, I don't want to auction my mother. I love my mother dearly.    I want to auction yours. You can make good money auctioning mothers. Back in 98 I made my first sale, eventhough the product wasn't premium quality, I made a few euros. I kept her picture.         
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        A new blog is born. Welcome to it.   
    
</post>


</Blog>