<Blog>


<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Its Friday..! Had a voracious lunch (alone!) and proceeded straight to the Basketball court. ( BAD IDEA) I played for 45 minutes and in that time out of around 50 shots to the hoop...I managed to score only around 7-8 times.... My form was that pathetic...it was kinda frustrating cause I was hopin to have a nice time....anyway.. to add insult to injury when I came back I decided to confront something that I should have done about a week ago.    Before I tell you more..its FLASHBACK time.....(yoohoo)     When I had reached Bangalore, I was kinda alone. Agreed I had friends but they were guys...ok there are things u can do with guys but its always nice to be in a relationship with someone of the opp. sex. So here i was settling down and having a rocking time boozing and gettin used to this beautiful city..and then due to some magical twist of fate, I get an SMS from someone. Delving deeper into the matter I realised she was a girl.(thankfully!) I had called her up one day and had a decent conversation... :-) couldnt believe my luck.. the fact that she was 7 years my junior was just a minor deterrant...(apparently she liked my voice..!) I used to have a lovely time talking with her @ nights and things were kinda cool... until 3 weeks ago... There was this big misunderstanding (cause of me) as a result of which we didnt talk for a week. I did break the ice and tried to get things back to what they were.. somehow things didnt revert back to normal ) .          END OF FLASHBACK        welcome back folks!    hehe...ok so I proceeded to give her a call ( Remember in the beginning I Said Bad Idea? ,multiply it by 1000...this was that bad! but I didnt know it then..did I?) ..     She was having lunch...in college...First of all   she was surprised on hearing my name.. I guess   she wanted everyone around her to know that the Asswipe had called...so she was like "Rohan.....is this Rohan?!"      I  then proceeded to ask her a casual question. There was COLD deathly silence on the other end.     I repeated the question like 4 times (silly me)    An then at that exact moment..It hit me..The truth finally dawned upon me...(in black and white) I realised that it was truely over.. I killed the connection,sent her a thank u sms/greeting and closed the chapter.     Now that im reflecting on this incident, I cannot but help remember my mental state at that point.. inspite of the noetic emotive katharsis I had mixed feelings  ..    :-)+:-( =:-        Agreed my emotional feelings were at an all time low...I had sunk to such depths that I havent seen in a long time...and that too for someone who I considered just a friend .... Now you might feel that these are negative,antagonistic feelings..wheres the :-)..... hold ur horses mate..:D    Now ive always believed in the law of averages and the fact that emotionally life kinda follows a sine wave pattern...and since I was at the lowest point of the negative kind...things are bound to improve soon...(see I know im a die hard Optimist!) ...as I am surrounded by pitch darkness all around me I see the proverbial light at the end of the tunnel ....So I decided to move on...    This was a pretty bad day for me...and things definitely cant get any worse than that............ or can they????        Only time will tell :)                           
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       fridays fast approaching , i can sense it....nearby shhhh.... not a sound my dear friend ..!  As I peer into the darkness of the void, the impending gloom is consorting with my rabid mind ....  the pathos of poignance is verily the poignance of pathos,  the foul odour of the dark betrayal,  verily, friday cometh knocking......     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>