<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    swimming in the dark&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    pawikan 3&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    pawikan 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    pawikan&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hardly update this online journal.  you can find a better updated journal by the same blogger at  urlLink www.livejournal.com/users/t1moune .   I'm soooooooo sleepy.  good night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm no model-material but I must say I love posing for  pictures .  Hehe.  That is why I am trying out BLOGSPOT with it's new photoblogging system through  urlLink hello.com , which makes it so easy to include photos in one's blog.  I'll try this out for a few days or weeks and see if I will be a satisfied customer (well, unpaying customer,that is).  === i love that i was able to  sleep  from 2am to 2pm last "night".  I miss that I can sleep for 10-12 hours a night!  Eversince I started working again, I still haven't gotten used to sleeping early.  My body clock really dictates that I sleep at around 2am.  But then, that would mean that I only get around 5-6 hrs of sleep if I want to arrive on time for work.  For some people, that would be more than enough but if I really listen to my body, ideally the amount of sleep i need is 10 hours.  That would mean I won't be cranky the whole day, I'd have enough oxygen in my brain to afford to go jogging at the end of my workday, my skin will not be breaking out with zits or what-have-yous, and i can survive the day without having to go on a food  and diet coke binge.  Really, if I had enough dough to spend on shopping and gimmicks, I 'd put off having to work again for a few more months.  hehehe... Don't get me wrong, though.  Working at  urlLink Jescom  has its own share of perks.  One is, I get to work for social development through the propagation of faith (I work for the Catechists' Foundation of the Philippines under the Jesuit Communications), I was given the opportunity to take on a leadership position (with no one working under me... hahaha) considering the limited length of stay that I could commit to, I am in familiar teritory (the Ateneo, the Katipunan area, JesCom, etc), my co-workers are kind and easy to get along with, among other things...dot..dot..dot...  ====   RSS Reader.   I totally support  urlLink Carlo 's take on the rss reader!  If you view blogs by going to individual websites, give this a try.  It's so convenient to use, you'll thank us for sharing it with you.  :)    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    me at guimbal&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    me. at the backstage between concerts at the wvsucc, iloilo. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ey. m trying this out.  if i like it, I'll switch to blogspot from my current provider or client or whatever you call it... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>