<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       …While the moonlight shine in your face      Your eyes can reflect your soul.      In that deep brown of your eyes      I can see for a second your mind,      Your thoughts, you feelings…      I can see your happiness and your sadness,      I can see the most frightening evil nightmares,      And those beautiful pink dreams…      I can see all the beauty of the world and      I feel small…      I can see all this just for a second, and then…      You blink, as you close your eyes you close your mind…    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hj lembreim de ir buskar uns desenhs k tinha guardad algures no fundo de uma gaveta e digitalizalos, pus me a brincar no Photo shop e isto foi u k saiu. Dêm uma olhadela aos: "eye"; "Punk in motion" e "Punk" deixem os vossos comentários... =P  
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    eye&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Punk in motion&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Punk&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          A adolescência é aquele periodo na vida de alguem, durante o qual este se recusa a acreditar que um dia será tao estupido ou mais que os seus próprios pais.      
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I’m lying down in my bed,Over me a strange light,It seems to shine in light blue deep pink…It looks so fragile, looks like my mind…I wake up, I was dreaming. Then I remember you, I remember about the times that we were at schoolYou used to seat next to me… I’ve been remembering those times a lot lately,Now we are long away one from another, I feel melancholic,I miss those times…The only way to reach you and those memories is just by feeling melancholic… We are grown up now Things are different, everything is much more serious now…I don’t know if can stand it.Today it’s a dark evil deep night, I’m felling weightless, that light is coming again… I’m going away. I’m dieing in my own existence, or …maybe not…     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Now I’m sited in my chair at school,I just think about you,The teacher is a fool,I just want to be near you,I can’t stand this much longer… I’m getting anger, I MISS YOUI say fuck off to the fool and I get off the school. Now I’m sited near youI feel like if the world was mine,And you……You… you just shine,I’m yours and you’re mine,Things are in the right way,We kiss and go away.     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         ...Se pensasse no que faço, nada fazia,Faço o que não penso,Não penso no que faço,Não digo o que faço,Não faço o que digo......Se pensasse no que digo, nada dizia,Digo o que penso,Não penso no que digo,Não digo o que faço...     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                                        Today it's a strange night,           Full is the moon, blued is the moonlight, shining are the stars dark is the sky, seeking is my mind, Seeking for you…                                               …Were have you been?...           In these nights, only in these nights, I can get that feeling; feel you as if you were here…                         Feeling the heat that your body drains, feeling the sweet voice that your mouth speaks, feeling your heart beating as if it was mine… I almost can see you, but it was only a shadow, just another shadow, and you are not here with me…   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Evil deep dark nights It’s their time,  The Thoughts…  They need to get out of your mind, Your mind it’s their nest… Were they born, Were they get shape Were they grow  The Thoughts…  Your mind drains power to then, Your mind feeds them, Your eyes reflect their will Your brain is controlled by them  The Thoughts…  They are nothing without you But You’re nothing without them  The Thoughts!...     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Someday you will wake up And you won’t see your shadow, Someday you will wake up And you won’t feel your body Someday you will wake up And you will know the meaning of FLY Someday you will wake up And you will see everybody you left behind  Then you will look to you life and you‘ll see that you had been a puppet in the others hands… Then you will look behind and you’ll see that you had a miserable life… And then as you realize that you had been smashed like a bug you will bleed for revenge… You will want to cut the strings that had controlled you for a whole lifetime. You will want to break free…  So don’t let the others control you! Be your self no matter what they may think, no matter what they may say, no matter what they may do!   Be your self everyday, Enjoying your life: As you want, As you plan, As you do…      
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Someday you will wake up, and you wont see your shadow Someday you will wake up, and you wont feel your body Someday you will wake up, and you will know the meaning of FLY Someday you will wake up, and you will see everybody you left behind   --»Devido a este Post ter sido colocado provisoriamente(Nao me lembrava deste pensamento na sua totalidade) apaguei a segunda parte do mesmo. O pensamento original esta a ser publicado com o titulo: "Some Day"      
    
</post>


</Blog>