<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay!!!!! I just received a phone call from KU inviting me for a job interview on Wednesday!!! It is for the Public Service Supervisor position at Watson Library. This is very good news because I have been trying to get an interview with KU libraries for almost two years. Not to mention, a new job might get me out of this cubicle. The only thing is, this job pays less than the one I have now. So, this poses a dilemma; an extra $200 a month, or a job I might enjoy? I think maybe I'll just focus on the interview for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I've been reading the 5th Harry Potter book (I know, I know it's been out for awhile and I'm behind, but you see I'm poor so I waited for it to come out on paperback before I bought it) and Robbie has been referring to the book as the crack pipe because I can't seem to put it down. Disclaimer: I'm only on chapter 13, so nobody (Brett) respond to this and spoil anything for me.  Anyway, it's Friday and I'm at work on what might be the slowest day to date. I've been trying to read in secret for the past 30 minutes. I spread some papers on my desk so that it might appear to passersby that I am doing actual work. But, I'm not sure if I look very convincing since I'm sure I look like I'm just staring at my lap. So, I decided to lay off for awhile and get on the internet only to find that the internet was DOWN. The horror! The horror! A Friday without the internet? How will I make it through the day? Obviously, it's back now.  Today is the annual staff picnic. It's scheduled from 11-2 and I plan on exploiting the three hour window to it's full extent. We also were allowed to wear jeans today since it's the big picnic day. I guess that's supposed to give it a "laid back" feel. I'll tell you what would make it more laid back...beer. Now that would be entertaining. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired of posting comments anonymously and Brett told me that he has one now, so I figured that in order to keep up I should just start my own blog. So, this is it. I have no idea what I'm doing at this point, but I did manage to pick out a "look" from about 8 pre-selected choices and now I'm typing in a little window that resembles an email. Am I doing okay so far?  I'm at work at the moment. I hate my job. I figure I might as well get that out of the way right now because I foresee many ramblings about life in the cube. For example, just a few minutes ago I overheard the following conversation between two of my co-workers...  "I'm sorry, my bad." "You're what?" "My bad." "You're bat?" "No, my bad. It means, my fault." "Oh! I guess I don't know what that means."  See what I have to deal with?  Anyway, I'm going to end this first post now because I have very important work to attend to, such as rinsing out my coffee cup and figuring out how to get through the next 36 minutes before lunch. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>