<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy all.  If you refer to my last post, you noticed that I rambled on about my two buddies Ryan and Bryon. Potentially this past weekend was to be great, as long as Ryan the flake came through. Rye and I were to meet Bry in Pamona at 1 in the afternoon. I am driving the 2 hour drive, when at 12:15 I get a call from Ryan. Bastard lives 4-5 hours away and he hasn't left yet. Was I surprised? NO. Was I pissed off? Not really. I arrive at Bryon's house at 12:50 because I am a reliable friend who is always on time. We contemplate taking bets on if the bastard is going to come or not. Not really wanting to lose my money, I decide against it.        Ryan shows up at around 6:00. He is lost 3 miles down the road in San Dimas. San Dimas High School Football rules! Anyway. We pick his ass up, and decide that we are going to go to one of Bryon's friends birthday dinner at 7. Ryan is a vegetarian. He doesn't even eat things that are made with eggs. Bryon and I are avid carnivores who will eat anything smaller than us. Where do we go for dinner? Outback. Hilarious. With the smell of sweet cooked animal in the air, Ryan is obviously perturbed. He starts arguing with mega bitch waitress about his salad. I don't know what her problem was, my guess she needs to get it in the butt. Anyway. Out of respect to Ryan I get a dish with Chicken. I figure its less offensive then cow. Bryon gets a steak salad. Bitchy waitress takes a couple hours to do just about anything so we head out to Dave and Busters for more drinks at around 10ish.   Dave and Busters are assholes about I.D. You cant get into the place without an I.D. which doesnt even make sense since they ask you for it at the bar again. Needless to say, one girl we were with forgot her's so her and her boyfriend didn't get to go. Assholes.  We continue to get our drink on and play stupid games. We play this virtual reality battletech game. Pretty sick.  Our pool table finally comes up. We decide to play girls against guys using slop. Big mistake. Those girls were so damn lucky, we lost the first 2 games pretty fast. One of the cocky girls we were with decided that it would be a good idea to start playing for something. Ryan offers to take off all his clothes and run naked. Not a surprise. We all come to the conclusion that there will be some clothes coming off, details to be hashed out later.   Now guys don't need alot of motivation when it comes to competition. You throw some boobies into any equation, and a guy becomes 10 times better at anything. We destroy the girls in 2 games. They do not live up to their bargain. Guess they werent very slutty. Damn.  We came home at around 3:30am and went to bed a little bit after that. Just like old times with 2 of my closest friends.   Seriously, I can go on forever but I'm guessing that only 2 or 3 people have even read this much. I will keep Sunday short. Went and saw "Without a Paddle", ATE at the star of India. Chilled with Ryan until he left this morning. Good times, Good friends. I'm glad everything turned out alright.
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend has the potential of being a great one. If all goes to plan, my buddy Ryan will drive his ass to San Diego where we will likely destroy my one month of sobriety. Saturday we will drive to Pamona, where Bryon is going to Med school. I met Bryon and Ryan in Japan in 2000, and we all became really close friends. Being away from friends and family in a far away land is not easy, but these two cats made up for it. We haven't all hung out together since, shit... November 2000. I say that this weekend has "potential" because Ryan is the biggest flake. He is sporadic to say the least, but no matter how many times the guy lets you down, you can't help but love the guy. He is a free spirit who has been abducted by aliens numerous times. He is actually one of the choosen one's who has a special relationship with the little green men. I know what your thinking.... The guy is a nut! All I can say is your probably right, but I have no reason not to believe him. Maybe he will put in a good word for me when the little bastards take over.          I'm off to go search for a used  urlLink Dashboard Confesional  CD. I forgot to pack it from Virginia, and I really want to listen to it. I wish I knew some people out here that listened to good music, I could just burn it. Suck fest. I have all my old DC, but I have been craving for the new Cd for quite some time now. Oh yeah, if you really want to listen to an incrediable album, check out  urlLink Further Seems Forever- The Moon is Down . This cd was when Chris Carabba of Dashboard was the lead singer and the band actualy sounded good. Maybe the new FTF will be good, somehow I doubt it.  urlLink Saves The Day- Stay what you are , rocks too. I'm out.
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here in San Diego, I live near a small community called  urlLink Hillcrest  , a little place that I like to call the gayest place on earth. It is a large area of the city composed of both rural areas and a large bustling business district. Along almost every house or business, large rainbow fags hang from windows. The people of Hillcrest are a proud people, who believe that anyone that sets foot on their sacred community has a 90% chance of being a homosexual. I have never really had anything against fudge packers and carpet munchers. I always figured that if a guy was gay then that is just the way he is, as long as he doesn't set foot in my military, and as long as my future children aren't gay, then I am totally cool with them.  The thing is.... I am a raging  urlLink Metrosexual . Sometimes people, gay men especially.... think that because of my appearance, I am gay.  Doesn't really bother me, because the people who matter the most know the truth.  However, lately I have started to really get fed up with all the looks, stares, and smiles I have been getting from the people of Hillcrest.  I feel like a really hot girl that is being gauked at all the time. I feel dirty. I feel like a piece of meat.        For instance: I'm running my usual route,(which happens to go through the gayest place on earth) and a car stops right next to me, a drag queen sticks it's head out the window, and in a deep voice yells, "You work it sister!" I began to run faster and tried to shake the experience out of my head for fear of future nightmares. I turned around at my normal spot, a mile down the road and proceeded to run back the other way.  Somehow, as if the freak was stalking me... It yells at me again. I could not hear what it was saying, for I was running as fast as I could. I had 2 miles to go but I was picking up the pace. The look of this individual shook me, and since then I have gotten annoyed when gay guys hit on me.   My closest friend, Bryon said it best when he told me that I shouldn't be getting upset.  He is a bigger metrosexual then me, and explained that I really shouldn't be so surprised. Apparently my skin tight clothing looks ultra gay, and I am bringing it upon myself. Whatever the deal is, I feel violated anytime a guy gives me that dirty, I want to pop your can look. eww.  If Hillcrest didn't have all the convenience of cool places for a metrosexual such as myself to go too, I would just not go. If I need to go down to the store, I'm not going to drive the opposite way into ghetto mexicanville.  I have never been surronded by such silliness. I urge all of you to come visit me so I can take you to the gayest place on earth. 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can you say bandwagon? 
    
</post>


</Blog>