<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Finally! at last i have seen my sweet heart haha, i've missed Celia alot, 2 bad Pui San couldn't come along... we went out 2gether N it was so fun, alot of things 2 say to eachother of course haha..   later on that day we were planning 2 go to her home and then visit Pui San, but unluckily i wasn't feeling very well, so i went home... real bad luck...        
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        these past few dayyzz had been so boring... i didn't went 2 Rotterdam to chill...only tuesdaynight..that night i went out to Rotterdam for a little while 2 see my frend Wai San (aka Mandy) she had come from Belgium, so we chilled for a   while...   after that i went home, and i didn't went out anymore. i don't kknow why, i wasn't really in the mood for it i guess.. although i really wanted 2 see my hunny's again..;) i had missed them alot, we kept in touch by phone every day...        
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        back in Holland... the first thing i did when the door of the plane opened was switching on my phone, and the 1st sms i received was from my honey celia ;). that time, my sadness of being back here had turned into happiness, i was really looking forward 2 see my frenzz again...i also had missed them alot...          Everything has gone quite smoothly when i arrived at Amsterdam airport..there was some delay, and i had to wait for like 20 minutes for the lugagge, but the most important thing was that there were no ppl at the custom, so they didn't check anybody... i've been very lucky, wouldn't want to imagine how long it would take before they were done checking every corner of my luggage... that would have taken AAAGES before they were done!!          That day, the sun was shining bright and it was very hot.. it was a  wonderfull day! 2 bad it was just that day... cos it's quite chilly now and there r a lot of rainy dayzz.. (this is one of the reasons why i don't really like living here..)           When reached home, i unpacked my luggage and i managed 2 put all my clothes, shoes etc. in my closet. i'm have actually been pretty proud of myself haha :P...     then it was evening already (so fast!) and i went to zZZzZz...                  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         2d  ay is my last day in singapore..... i feel like crying...but there r no tears       i know i'm going 2 miss all the things here, the shopping, my lovely family ( ok, sometimes the aunts r sooooo damn annoying, but still..i know i will miss them alot...) , the food, and also clubbin here...( although i didn't went to clubs alot..wonder who's fault that is huh??!!... :P )          2 day i didn't do much... i went to my cousins house 2 see Izella, my cousins daughter... dunno how 2 call her...my cousins' daughter.....mmm... we were celebrating because she was 1 month old...           After that i went to Orchard with my cousins, we shopped for a while. Ofcourse i could't buy anything, cos i already had bought too many things.. :(.. that day i was really worrying about my luggage n stuff. i prayed that they'll let my pass...           After the 'shopping' we went home, i began 2 pack my stuff, while i did that, i realized for the 1st time that i actually had bought alot of things.. :P for a moment I wondered how my 10 pair of shoes, my jeans and all the clothes could fit into my closet..     N thats not all, i had 2 bring alot of food to... the kaya that my sweet grandmother made for us, the abolone, the mushrooms and etc... happily my dearest godmother me helped me pack ( what will i do without her!! )          but FINALLY, around 20.30 i finished packing, the closer i got 2 the departure time, the more i wanted 2 cry...           It was about 21.00 when my godfather arrived, and it was about time 2 go...      mindy, ena, grandma, my godmother and my godfather would bring me 2 the airport.      my other (! yeah i got 2! haha :P) godmother and my cous jas also wanted 2 bring me 2 the airport...     they would go with another car, but then my godmom was to tired 2 go, cos she just got back from Thailand ( she bought me a package of pork floss haha thx! ) so eventually jas didn't go cos there was no space anymore... but i was so happy that so many ppl wanted 2 bring me.. :)           there were no problems at the checkin, but the stupid security ruined my bag and my pen, cos they were having a conversation, they forgot to put my bag  in a basket...      About a half hour later, it was time to leave, we made some pics and then i finally went inside...and that moment , there were tears dripping off my face. i was surprised, cos i haven't cried for a long time already. I thought i had no more tears to cry, i thought that... i had already cried it all out before...                               but ok, back to what i was telling... well actually there isn't much to tell anymore. This was my last day               
     
    
</post>


</Blog>