<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend was an interesting one. There was a bachelor party (my friend got married not me). And on Sunday I got to just chill. Sometimes I wonder about life and why things happen. I guess that is why you have to sit back and just let it happen. This last year has been a long strange journey that has yet to come to a close. What turned out to a me living in Seattle for a few months before I moved to BC looks like it has turned into a year. It has been very frustrating along the way but I must admit I have met some people along this journey that have shaped my life in new and different ways that will forever impact me. I guess that is why you have to sit back and just enjoy the ride that is life. Back to my friends bachelor party, I can't believe one of my childhood friends is getting married. I mean I can't even balance a check book let alone commit myself to some thing like that. Oh well I guess some of us are not cut out for that type of thing. Any way  there shall be more on Monday (if anybody is even reading this thing). Well I hope everybody else had a good weekend, see ya'll later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend was an interesting one. There was a bachelor party (my friend got married not me). And on Sunday I got to just chill. Sometimes I wonder about life and why things happen. I guess that is why you have to sit back and just let it happen. This last year has been a long strange journey that has yet to come to a close. What turned out to a me living in Seattle for a few months before I moved to BC looks like it has turned into a year. It has been very frustrating along the way but I must admit I have met some people along this journey that have shaped my life in new and different ways that will forever impact me. I guess that is why you have to sit back and just enjoy the ride that is life. Back to my friends bachelor party, I can't believe one of my childhood friends is getting married. I mean I can't even balance a check book let alone commit myself to some thing like that. Oh well I guess some of us are not cut out for that type of thing. Any way  there shall be more on Monday (if anybody is even reading this thing). Well I hope everybody else had a good weekend, see ya'll later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember one night I was lost in Hong Kong, I came across this bar and settled in for a drink. It was then that I met her, it was then my eyes became open.  Observations From a Bar Stool    As the sun begins to plunge into the South China Sea Sweat trickles down the small of her back The dress she wears is clinging to her as she walks down the street The sweltering humidity of a Hong Kong Summer    Faded scuffed white heels compliment a tattered cotton dress Hair pulled back in a ponytail, face unadorned by make-up She is of a quiet simple beauty A gentle innocence defines her 19 year old face An innocence that has yet to be stolen by her new found profession  Walking to work she tip toes through the street Gracefully dodging the puddles left from the afternoon storm The soft glow from the neon lights of the bars is refracted in the pools of water she avoids  In an hour, the innocent face will be cloaked in cheap cosmetics Never the less her eyes she can not hide Her eyes show me a country still bearing the scars of its war torn past Ravaged first by Europe's greed Then by a bitter battle over political ideologies Finally her eyes show me a journey for a better life that has gone awry  Do you miss the village you grew up in? Do you miss the songs you sang with your sisters while working in the fields? Wipe the tears streaking down your cheek This is not the life you are to live  When the wind blows down the side of the rolling green mountains and across the rice fields It whispers your name Your wrong turns in life have brought you to this point Yet the die has not been cast  Your brothers and sisters are waiting for you at the village gate Go home my child Your mother is praying in the temple for your safe return Go home my child Your father is looking for you in the Market Go home my child Go home to Vietnam   Written By Jamison Whitfield Taylor Copyrighted 2004 All Rights Reserved 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever thought about that quiet kid in middle school that nobody would talk to or everyone would make fun of? Hmmmm. Sometimes I remember and I wonder.  Anyone Seen Billy Stevens?  Fresh dew on the grass, a fog lifting from the ground It all signals the start of a new day  A school bell ring echoing in the nearly vacant hallway Students push and hustle into their seats The teacher, taking role casually looks out into the classroom Calling “ Has anyone seen Billy Stevens?” No reply, absent he is marked  Of slight frame and stature Billy is Easily he can be overseen, overlooked and unnoticed  A failed child By a failed marriage  Failed by his Father A new bride and new family He does not care to be reminded of the failure Of his past  Failed by his Mother Traveling from man to man looking for affection Waging a constant war From inside a bottle  The bell sounds again The same process is repeated  The 2nd period teacher calling out “Any one seen Billy Stevens?” Again no response Again absent he is marked  Excelling at athletics and academics Billy did not Defined by dark baggy clothes and a timid nature Regularly the ridicule of the elite ones Seeming lost in a world that did not care A nameless faceless vessel Floating in the ocean of an overcrowded school population  The sunrise’s fog and mist turn to vapor The ringing of the bell begins the start of 3rd period Roll is once again taken Billy Stevens is once again marked absent  Other side of town Deputy Michael Andrews makes his rounds Down by the railroad bridge looking for transients His eyes are met by a pair of feet, dangling out in front of him  In the front right pocket of the body was a crumpled family photo A photo of what once was but will never be  By the start of 4th period the teacher did not have call “Has anyone seen Billy Stevens?”  Written By Jamison Witfield Taylor All Rights Reserved Copyrighted 2004   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well for my first Blog entry I will post a simple poem  The Dress   If one was to see it on a hanger One might think it to be any other strapless, rich navy denim dress  Yet when that strapless, rich navy denim dress Slid down the curves of her body My world was lit a blaze  Walking down the boardwalk On that star drenched August night I watched her Slice though the summer night air Crickle and crack of aged lumber below our feet The White Rock off in the distance  That dress hugging the turns of her body Much the same way a Jaguar hugs the road on a mountain pass  Her appearance is as sexual as is elegant Re-defying what it is to be a woman with every turn of her head  Tightly grasping my hand Leading me down to the beach Shapely rocks of the Northwest Coastline slip and slide under each step  Skipping stones into the darkness of night Light generated by a full moon casts down upon her Soft majestic black hair glistening in the light gently rests on her shoulders  Looking back at me with soft supple brown eyes Playfully beckoning me to come closer  Pulling her towards me Denim never quite felt like this  With the moon fully overhead it engulfs us in its radiant light Those brown eyes give off an unreal glimmer Her crimson colored lips move closer to mine  5,         4,            3  2,         1  Contact   It is then I realize I am completely at the whim Of the woman In the strapless, rich navy denim dress   Written By Jamison Witfield Taylor Copyrighted 2004 All Rights Reserved 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>