<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok. It's Saturday evening and I am inside on a computer writing in my blog. For the record, I am now the Queen of Pathetic. I have two cats curled up in a chair behind me, a girlfriend in bed asleep (she was in bed at 9) and I am debating about whether or not I should watch a movie or some lame-ass television.  Today I achieved a lot though. Moved a ton of furniture around, did every single stitch of laundry there was to do and finished reading a really good book. Yep, that was my day. Either I am getting really old or I am stuck in a rut. Who knows. If anyone has the answer, please feel free to let me know.  I received an email from a girl I went to college with today. We don't chat that much but it is nice to hear from her every once in a while. I caught her up to speed with my life and I find it funny about how many people are stunned when I mentioned that I have suffered through cancer this year. Am I taking this too lightly? I mean it was caught, treatment worked and my tests results are all positive, so I don't see the big deal. I mean, yes I was terrified and did my damnedest to hide that but, when the day was over, I knew that being positive was the best way to be because negativity was going to do nothing but add to the problem. Weird.  Ok, time to make a decision about the rest of my night. I think I will curl up on the couch, put a movie in and listen to the rain outside. Thank God it is raining....not just for the forest fires but because I miss the sound of the rain. So soothing.  Hugs y'all! A  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So after a crazy bad year in the life of me, it is about time that something goes the way it is supposed to.         Yesterday I met with my doctor to get some tests done to see how my cancer was doing.  Was it gone?  Did I still need treatment?  Was I going to suffer more depression?  The results came back and everything was GREAT!  I am so happy and finally feeling more positive than I was letting on.  After the radiation was over and the final check-ups were done, even though I was given positive news, I knew the next check-up (this one) was going to be the better deal.  Now that it has been done, I feel so much more confident that I have beaten it.  Yipee!      Tonight the plan is to celebrate with my girl, that is after we do all of the running around that we need to do.  Who knew renting a house could be so much work.      Well back to the grind so I can finish up with my day.  No need to explain how excited I am about that.      Hugs!   A  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well this is my first official blog. I don't know what to say, but hell, who is really going to read this anyway.      First things first...it's Friday, the weekend is literally hours away and I am hoping that it rains. Yes, I am hoping that it rains. Reason being - I have a ton of work to do inside and if it is nice outside I will have no motivation to do what I have to do, go outside and play. So yeah, I want rain.      Marn lost another baker yesterday and that bummed her out completely. Her boss, who can tend to be a little bit of jerk, said that she should have had more of a back-up of baking staff, but she did. For the small store she has, she had 5 bakers which is more than enough. One had to quit due to family issues, another one was leaving to go to school and then this new guy just decided that the work wasn't for him. So she has two bakers and she needs more. Anyone out there want to work in Victoria for $8/hour??      Poor thing :(      Things for me are all right. I am not doing much at work right now and I am not sure if that is because people just don't want to give me the work or if it is just because there really isn't much going on that I can do. Doesn't bother me much though because I can piss around, work on personal stuff and read the paper. Good times.      This weekend I get to patch holes, wash walls, vacuum, do laundry - I can sense your excitement....can you sense mine??      So yeah, that is about it for me. I will try to come up with more exciting things to write about, but really, I am not that exciting. I wish I were....it would give my life so much more punch!!      Hugs!   A  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>