<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow..isn't it wierd how you think you are really good friends with someone.  Then all of a sudden they are in a bad mood...so they decide to be rude.  I hate moody friends.  It's like what is the point of keeping them.  You never know from one day to the next if they are even going to like you.  One day they are the nicest person in the world.  The next you can't do a damn thing right.  Some of my friends are like that.  One in particular, and sometimes people decide to follow 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Woo Hoo tonight is girls night! Since the bf is out of town! I'm going to watch Princess Diaries 2 with my mom, two of my friends and their moms. Then the girls are spending the night here. We definately will have a good time. Maybe I'll tell them about this. They could start one too. Maybe we could do one of those team things. My boyfriend called from Canada yesterday evening, he is on vacation. We only talked for a little bit because it will be really expensive on his cell phone. He said he was having a good time. I'm happy for him, but I miss him!!     Maybe I'll have time to write about our fun time later tonight. Or I will just wait until tomorrow. I know how bad everyone wants to read this.....yeah right!!!   
      
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm not exactly sure what I'm supposed to write about on here. So I am just going to write about what I am thinking. I'm leaving for college in 8 days. I'm pretty scared because I have a great boyfriend that I have been dating for almost a year and two months. He is going to college about two hours away from me. We are both playing basketball so I'm not sure if we will be able to see each other much during the season. I am majoring in biology but I'm not sure what type of career I want to have.     Well I have been looking around this site and I can't find out how to look at other blogs. I guess I'm "blog illiterate." It doesn't really matter to me though. I don't mind if nobody reads this. I like being able to write about my feelings. I kind of actually feel like a dork for doing this. Oh well. Nobody will know!   
      
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        If somebody could get at me and let me know how to look at other people's blogs I would appreciate it.  I'm new at this and I am really lost!!!!!!!  Thanks   
      
</post>


</Blog>