<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching the television and I realized the huge amount of reality programs that tv has gotten. Whether its about rich bitches being stripped of their credit cards, to strangers being crammed in the house together for a big cash prize (though nowadays it seems natural that one guy and gurl in the house get close and fuck) anyway it seems that the idea behind reality shows has lost its meaning. Reality shows are supposed to relate in some factor to everyday civilan life hence the term reality, but these programs dont seem to have any of that, so Ive thought up of some, although they are not tv worthy, they fulfill the true meaning of reality.  1) Joe and his shitty life- join the life of Joe from the time he gets up to the shitty day he has at wrk, its lousy and he doesnt win money, the only thing he really wins is break time and a grease stain from the fries.  2)Uh Oh who's the father- pretty easy to understand, a random women is found in the streets, SURPRISE she doesnt know who the father is, but as the show progresses (with the help of DNA experts) we might and so might she, its really a lose lose situation cause whose taking the rap for the kid?  3)Whose going bankrupt- Another self explanitory show, follow Mike the liquidator and his crew as they break the bad news one man/women after another the fun never ends, well for the people being ruined the fun ends real quickly.   
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems to be more and more of a common thing nowadays that people have to be in a relationship, its quite odd I think it could be due a number of things tv programs and such not completly sure but its definately occurring more and more. This thought came to me today when i was on msn and this guy i knew at school popped online and was fuming and whining but he wouldnt say what for awhile. Finally he spilled his guts that he wanted a relationship with this Cynthia girl but she didnt feel the same way, I asked him why is this so important? To which he replied (word for word) "I dunno seems everyone else has some kinda fling or such going on" What the hell? he doesnt even like her, he just wants one cause everyone else apparently has one, what a shmuck. If anyone has any comments on this or feels this isnt outa the ordinary pls feel free to share, input is much appreciated. 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this is to be the first entry at Blog, although today was fairly slow and there isnt much to write, plans got shot down the toilet and as a result its kept me at home its amazing what boredom will drive a person to do, whether its washing ur mums car, or doing major unordinary things (tryin to make food from the cookbook) Oh ya i swear theres a salesmen infestestion around this neighbourhood all day long someones ringing by doorbell grrr, definatly have to do something about them. Well be back tomorrow with what I hope is to be much more exciting than this. Oh I almost forget, this Blog business takes a bit of wrk, if u find theres somethin fishy with the first entry its probaley cause i was trying to do something and messed up in the future there should be less of that as well. 
    
</post>


</Blog>