<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alrighty, then. As I slide ever more closer to middle-aged I have come across this blog-thing-o-matic. Not that I was really seeking it out. Simply put, I came across it while searching for something I never found. I’ve heard the term ‘blog’ thrown around here and there, but never really knew what the heck it was all about. I’m sure some “smarty” has written a ‘Blogging for Dummies’ book by now and I can find it at my local Davis Kidd Booksellers. Stereotypically of me I have no intentions of following any stinkin’ directions. Rather, I intend to learn the ropes as I go. I do this of my own volition, and will most kindly ignore any directions from the well-intended. One exception: I will try to adhere to any kind of netiquette that applies…momma didn’t raise no fool.             That “said,” allow me to opine a little about who I am and where I live. As you may have guessed by now I reside in the Mecca of all country-dom…Branson, Missouri! Sorry, Glenn, I’m kidding. I live in Nashville, Tennessee. The true home of country music. And I hate it. Not Nashville. I love Nashville. No finer mid-sized town can be found. I cannot stand country music. Which is sad because it is pouring out of every edifice you pass in this town. I haven’t always felt this way. Nor do I feel this way about all country music. I genuinely love the old country sound: Ernest Tubbs, Hank Williams, ‘Loretti’ Lynn, and the such. The junk they push off as country these days leaves me wanting more. The ‘pop’ sound of much of today’s country makes me feel as if I have just left a Tiffany concert at the local mall. If any of the local writers are reading, I implore you: “Please bring back some ‘twang.’ Sing about drinkin’ and cussin’ and most importantly, being down on luck.” I hear a train a’ coming…             Although it may read as such, I’m not really not all that cynical. I’m a nice guy just getting by the best I can. I love the city of Nashville, its people, and the opportunity it has to offer some really talented folks. So if you get a chance to drop by, do. Check in here from time to time to get my latest quip on Nashville and my latest adventures. Thanks for taking the time to read my words.             Oh, and one more thing…if you’re driving through Nashville and think everyone is driving way too fast and erratic, keep in mind: we’re not speeding, we’re qualifying (for NASCAR).  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>