<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow's back to the ol salt mines.  Have you ever wondered if that because you're so conservative in your thinking, that it actually holds you back?  Sue has mentioned in the past if I wanted to teach English in her school, that I could at anytime.  Who knows?  Perhaps if I weren't a broker, I would consider a 6 month trial?  Heck, why AREN'T I?????????????  Work sucks.  I'll tell you one thing.....100% commission isn't all what its cracked up to be.  At one point, it probably was.  But the uncertainty of $$$$, as in this month for example, and the asshole cheapskates who think nothing of throwing their money around ELSEwhere........argh.....too depressing to bitch about it now..........   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let's see:  another day off from the ol "Salt mines".  Who knows, I might just go in later today around 3:30 or 4:00.  Family's home and already on my case.   My neck's still killing me.  I thought that a few days of rest and more sleep would help, but not really.  Went out with T last night for a drink at Jaleo in Bethesda.  uneventful.......another "meet mkt"....afterwards, went to the Barnes&Noble to just relax.  GB, the chiropractor.....hmmm....wonder if I should give her a try?  People throughout the years have said that they do wonders.  But the regular doc will have nothing to do with them.....  What to do today........I should do something constructive, like clean up this pigsty of a room.  Just can't get motivated nowadays...............  feels like life is just flushing me along?  Haven't heard from EL in Toronto lately.  Always seems like I have to be the one to make the call.  BS in London wants nothing more to do with me, not even friendship.  WW in Tyson's is a lost cause, and CH in Centreville has been avoiding me.  GF transferred's B's IRA out to ETrade.  I've come to the conclusion that people do indeed "suck"   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       WoW!      The last time I kept a journal was waaaay back during my middle school years!  I used a cheapo spiral notebook that cost 99 cents. What was that, 1981???  How times have changed......  I figured that I would give this a shot.      Who would've known that after 4 1/2 years since leaving Trak, that times would still be rough?  Just my luck that when I envied those stock brokers all making over 100k a year, that when the opportunity came for me to join them, that we had the worst bear market in 30+ years!  Also, not to mention that the online brokerages and goddamn Arthur Levitt would decimate this profession.        Every post, I am going to remind myself to reminice about something that occured in the past.  That way, I can keep the memory alive.        This week was supposed to be one of the best, as I was looking forward to it with great anticipation.  Unfortunately, things happen and I understand it.  CG....don't push me away?  I know that you're going through some tough times right now as well.  But you know that out of all the people in this world, that I am one of the few that can understand.          
     

    
</post>


</Blog>