<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      random thoughts rolling around in my head. my horse. my cat. my betta. my job. my art. my  friends and family  my horse,  he brings me a freedom I've only ever dreamed of as a child. a girl's dream come true handed to me in a basket wrapped in ribbons and bows. a pet, yes, but not just any pet, a pet where I can taste what it's like to run with the wind. a pet that gives it his all willingly and out of choice not necessity. when I am one with my horse, I know who I truly am...he does not worry about the future, he remembers the past and lives in the moment...my horse  my cat, she is the most amusing damn thing I've ever seen. she brings a joy to my life as only a cat can. the epitome of I do what I want when I want. if she wants affection she comes to me apurrin', if she wants to play, she attacks my feet from under the chair or couch or blanket or door if she's behinding (hmmm...behinding new word of the day...an accidental combination of the words "hiding behind")one. simply playful  my betta, i watch  my betta in the mornings and evenings, he greets me in his little tank, I know he's watching me, he follows me, his pretty purple, red and blue colors reflecting the light of the morning sun, or artificial lamp light, i feed him and he is grateful....  my job, well my job, it's a job, a paycheck, money a constant headache within and without, I am surrounded by it, yet I cannot see it.....  my art, GOD my art, this talent that I possess, this gift that was bestowed on me and I'm letting it waste away. Why? I ask myself this often. I enjoy it. It is a doorway to another dimension on this earth and takes me far away from the stresses of daily living. Why don't I put pencil to paper more often? Where could it take me if I made it my ultimate goal? If I committed myself to every artistic whim, every request and every idea I've ever had, how many drawings and paintings would I have? How many would see and how many would want my art? Imagine.  There is a part of everyone in the mind of an artist, I as an artist, take it and translate it onto paper in a perfect vision and the people see themselve without ever knowing it and never ask why.  my best friends and family, those that are around me that I care deeply about. I would not be me without these wonderful people, they are my strength, they are a reflection of myself, they just are...     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        the horse is magnificent in all his glory and power not only does he possess the ability to mystify the human imagination but also to mirror the deepest emotions of his rider........we can learn a lot from the horse   
    
</post>


</Blog>