<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im back! ok now im in the library with adelina and the whole class hasn' t copied lit notes yet and its all my fault...ok whatever i dont care...i didn' t do my home econs homework yet leh...3 chapters...but yeah almost everyone probably didn' t do it yet too...i did my chinese compo last night for nothing cos i had no idea that we were going to have a test today! and of course its so obvious that im going to fail...i don' t feel well today...not even jan' s jokes can cheer me up...yesterday i went out shopping aagain with my mum and sister and brother...we went over to kinokuniya first and guess what? i bought the fruits basket 2nd vcd set!!!AND i also bought the last too coics of tokyo mewmew...i spent the whole night reading it so yeah (  smileys  )...but the ending really sucks cos aoyama gets to be with ichigo in the end and i sooo prefer shirogane lor! his heart must be utterly broken...*  sobsob  * anyway i already lent the books to alena and sammy and guess what again?alena just lent me the D.N.angel dvd this morning!!!YAY!so now i have to anime shows to watch but unfortunately i have no time at all!!!...from today to thursday i have to stay back for PM...WWWAAAAAAHHHHHH! so it means i'll only have time to watch it next week:( ...*  sighs  * ok...oh yeah i almost forgot, i also bought another dan brown book to read this week its called Angels and Demons...so i can read it during PM! YAY! ok...time to end now...i have to go downstairs to buy a notebook...so sayonara!(  bye in japanese  )  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi all! Finally i start to create another blog...it has been a long time...and i have ALOT of stuff to talk about so...i'll start off with my brand new CCA!( finally)   Im in PM(  production management)!   *applauds* haha...im so happy that im free from guitar and mr shi...though i guess i'll miss audrey,alena,chia hui and some other people...(  definitely not my seniors)   Right now im fitting in very well with PM and im going to do my first backstage duty on teacher's day! remember that i'll be at the left side of the stage! ok...now my academics life...so far im going well with my maths but i still suck at science...some more i can't believe that tomorrow's the science mock exam and instead of studying im on the net...im so going to fail...but adelina will definitely pass cos she's a very very very smart girl! hahas...okies now my friend life...so far me and addie are still the best of friends but i cant stand you know who anyomore...so yar...and of course i have been talking alot behind her back but who cares cos she's such a b****...unfortunately im not getting far with elisabeth...she seems to not even need me anymore...but never mind at least she still knows that im there...in class amira is still talking to herslef as always  (gg class...hahas  )  and beverley's irritating as always and the same goes to jan too...but cant resist jan's stupid jokes?! now luckily im not down for any tutorial yet...but i'll never know when i'llsuddenly be down for gepgraphy! oh yeah and chinese is as boring as always and my bloody chinese oral is coming up also...so sian...i dont think everyone will even bother to doit...many projects are due too...i dont really like my GY group cos you know who's in it...yuck...okay...i think enough's said...my dad's coming home soon so...ADIOS!  (which actually means bye)  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>