<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "The things that people in love do to each other they remember, and if they stay together it's not because they forget, it's because they forgive."    "When you're in love with someone it inspires you and gives you hope. You have faith that even if you can't be with them on earth, that if God wills, you will be with them one day in heaven."    Don't leave that person who loves u,for someone you like,because that someone you like,will leave you for someone,he loves.    I've been sitting here waiting for your call.I often wonder why I bother at all.Your probably talking to Amber or Chris.Maybe your eating or taking a piss.I'm bored to death but here I am.I often wonder if you give a damn.Even though it's getting late, you promised so I'll wait.Just as I'm feeling all alone, the silence is broken by the phone.I look out the window and see the sun.You finally called, so this poem is done!   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Boy had a good sleep! Slept at 12.30 woke up at 12.45. Anyway, watched cradle To the Grave after I woked up. Very interesting movie, lots of action and fighting scenes,but it is no ordinary fighting movie. This movie has taken martial arts to a whole new levelly-star-rating=) When to bed's yesterday to visit my cousin and when I was in the cab at the junction the cab took the "longest" way to the house and I was like,"Hey uncle u sure u going the right way?"    He said yah... This is a short cut!!   Well it turned out that his so called short cut cost me an extra $4. Man... That could have gotten me like 2 CD-RSI. Ah what the heck athlete I got there in one piece.      Here's something I found out...>>         Flirting is not rocket science. It is simply a common sense method of letting people know youre available without being tacky or obnoxious. AND if done properly, it is your best chance at snagging your future partner! So, get ready to demystify the art of flirting with these five fabulous flirting tips. Practice your new moves on the object of your desire this weekend    #1: Be SincereIf youre going to flirt, you need to be real about it. Anyone can spot a fake a mile away. If youre feeling insecure about your flirting skills, dont start with your secret crush since the 10th grade. Begin in a situation you are most comfortable with. If youre going to pay compliments to someone, be sincere about them. Really mean what you are saying and your results will be well worth the effort.    #2: SmileA smile is the simplest form of flattery. It shows that you are genuinely interested in the other person, and for that one single moment they are the only thing on your mind. Never underestimate the power of a smile.    #3: TouchTouch is an obvious sign of interest. Used correctly it can be a subtle way of getting a persons undivided attention. Rest a hand on their arm or on their knee when you are talking. Engage in activities that promote touch, such as dancing. Just be careful not to appear too flirtatious. The last thing you want to do is send the wrong signals.    #4: Hold Eye ContactHow do you make the object of your affection weak in the knees? Hold that meaningful gaze for just a few seconds longer than normal. Show them youre not one to turn away from something great!    #5: Be Interested In ThemWant to know if they are worthy of your undivided attention? Find out more by asking them open-ended questions about themselves. Show off your flirting skills by showing them you are actually listening to what they are saying. Bonus Tip:Dont forget to show your appreciation for the person spending time with you. Always thank the person you are with, and let them know if you had a good time with them. A little politeness goes a long way to making you the next catch of the day.     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Class pic  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Saturday morning woke up and didn't have the mood to go for my Mt class so I just went to my room and tried to study but I could not get anything into my head well I guess I m not a morning person. Got a lot of free time today and have to focus that time onto my books.      This morning there was a phone call for me on my hp which was my Mt classmate and he told me that he wanted to invite me for his birthday party next Saturday and I told him that I would go but now I have no idea on getting him a birthday present... Sigh Well he is 16 and I think I should go and find out what he likes first..         >> Every small positive change we make in ourselves repays us in confidence in the future  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>