<Blog>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    2003  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got into a rather long debate with a conservative tonight concerning Bush, Oil, and the War. Although the debate began about religious laws. According to him, without a God, without a religion, we have no morals. I guess that must mean that all the baby rapists in this world must be agnostic atheists. Sorry, doesn't add up. Long before I had faith, I knew right from wrong, it's called having a heart. So yes, that esceladed into the war. Lets see. Bush lied about nearly every single thing he told Congress during his State of the Union address. Lets review: He said that Saddam was giving the torrorists WMD, that's false, he said Iraq hasn't accounted for nearly 30,000 missiles, that is false, he said that Iraq purchased aluminum tubes used for WMD, that is false (they are used for M-81 rockets and are incompatible with any nuclear weapon), he said that Iraq could launch a nuclear attack at us within 45 minutes of being given the command, that is false - Iraq has never been able to launch missiles at us, he showed footage of a plane spraying faux anthrax, that is misleading - the plane was demolished in 1991. Bush on the captured "terrorists" at places like Abu Ghraib: "More than 3000 suspected terrorists have been arrested (by the US) in many countries. And many others have met a different fate. Lets put it that way. They are no longer a problem..." (state of the union message - Feb 4th 2003.  I would say that now I know who the Swift Vets role model is! Now, I really don't think that the information above can be contested. All of it, has been proven. But no, not good enough. He wants to use the good old "well Saddam was terrible to his people and you're saying we should of let him slide?@#" For the love of beef people, lets get one thing straight: I would esitmate that 98% of americans, for or against the war would agree that Saddam was a mad man (who else do I know that is mad?). Yes Saddam needed to be stopped, yes he was terrible. But I didn't see us rush into Nazi Germany because Hitler was an asshole to the Jew and Polish. No, we went in there because he was a militaristic threat! Furthermore, it wasn't a "we have no time to wait, we can't think about this any longer we have to act now" - ie: no preemptive war, that's suicide. But according to most conservative logic, it's OK because Saddam was a bad guy. It doesn't matter who lied, doesn't matter why we're there, doesn't matter how the focus has changed so many times our heads are spinning. No, all that matters is that "Bush did what Clinton didn't" in capturing Saddam and fighting terror. I find it funny though, because back when Clinton nearly captured Bin Laden after a surprise attack - the con's were bitching at him because "he's one man, not an entire nation! gripe gripe bitch bitch". Funny how a few years makes you change your mind on such big issues like war (right Swifties?).  So yes, back to what I was saying. I tried time and again to prove to this man that Bush sent us into war based on lies. He again counters about Saddam this, and Clinton that. What the hell does Clinton have to do with it?! I found an article by " urlLink The American Conservative " that had a very nice, very long explanation of the problem with invading Iraq. I was even nice enough to show it to him, since he kept claiming bias partisanship on the links I gave him (news flash: Facts don't always mean partisanship, especially when you look front page and you see BOTH names there). Of course that still wasn't good enough. So let me spell it out, again: By not only sending us all over creation, but also sending us into war without so much as a plan, hundreds of lives were lost. If we had actually planned things out, worked with real intelligence, and were discreet (instead of blasting "America plans secret attack on Bin Laden" on the news) about it - we could of had Bin Laden. But instead, we rush Congress into letting us go to war based on the fear that Iraq will nuke us (*cough* horse shit *cough*). Result: an up hill battle with an enemy we out number and out arm. It's like a retarted version of Viet Nam almost - another uphill battle because we weren't prepared. What do the neo cons say?  FDR... led us into World War II. Germany never attacked us: Japan did. From 1941-1945, 450,000 lives were lost, an average of 112,500 per year. Truman... finished that war and started one in Korea, North Korea never attacked us. From 1950-1953, 55,000 lives were lost,an average of 18,334 per year. John F. Kennedy...started the Vietnam conflict in 1962. Vietnam never attacked us. Johnson...turned Vietnam into a quagmire. From 1965-1975, 58,000 lives were lost, an average of 5,800 per year. Clinton...went to war in Bosnia without UN or French consent, Bosnia never attacked us. He was offered Osama bin Laden's head on a platter three times by Sudan and did nothing. Osama has attacked us on multiple occasions.   And again, the cons just can't get their facts or history straight.... I've offered evidence after evidence about how this war was one big hypocricy, but it just gets dodged and a Clinton comment is thrown back. If Clinton was really that bad, as the cons think he was, that must make GW Bush the living biblical devil!  Here is a history of this war in Bush's own words:  "The most important thing is for us to find Osama bin Laden. It is our number one priority and we will not rest until we find him." - G.W. Bush, 9/13/01  "I want justice...There's an old poster out West, as I recall, that said, 'Wanted: Dead or Alive,'" - G.W. Bush, 9/17/01, UPI  "...Secondly, he is not escaping us. This is a guy, who, three months ago, was in control of a county [sic]. Now he's maybe in control of a cave. He's on the run. Listen, a while ago I said to the American people, our objective is more than bin Laden. But one of the things for certain is we're going to get him running and keep him running, and bring him to justice. And that's what's happening. He's on the run, if he's running at all. So we don't know whether he's in cave with the door shut, or a cave with the door open -- we just don't know...." - Bush, in remarks in a Press Availablity with the Press Travel Pool, The Prairie Chapel Ranch, Crawford TX, 12/28/01, as reported on official White House site  "I don't know where bin Laden is. I have no idea and really don't care. It's not that important. It's not our priority." - G.W. Bush, 3/13/02  "I am truly not that concerned about him." - G.W. Bush, repsonding to a question about bin Laden's whereabouts, 3/13/02 (The New American, 4/8/02)  So its: Get Bin Laden! Get Hussain, he knows where Bin Laden is! Screw Bin Laden! Get the rogue terrorist groups - all of them! Reform, help, and provide for Iraq! Put in a president for them who hasn't been in Iraq for ages - this way he'll get us some nice oil deals!  Thanks for the lesson Bush, I now see what lives are being lost for: Your stupidity.  
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Too many times I see this political fanaticism comming from the strong right wingers. They love to preech their mantra of "just blame Clinton". I was astounded as to how much this happens when I first got involved with political debate. I will never understand how people can just keep voting and voting and voting for a single party. I could understand perhaps if this is just how things worked for them, and that the canidates they voted for always held what they wanted in a leader. But.. jeezus people! Don't get into this mentality of "My house votes (Political Party)". This causes so many problems, I swear. Wanna know what's partly to blame for Bush getting into office? A group of 12 Republicans outside the courtroom where the recount was held who were screaming and banging on doors and shouting "let us in! let us in! let us in!". Why? Of course so that their man could get put into office. Do people have any comprehension of fairness? Apparently not. If Bush was ellected into office legally without anything shady, I wouldn't complain about it. I wouldn't sit here and contest his election. While most of us know it, this country needs to open its eyes and grow a damn brain. These people just keep spurting off about whatever it is that the presidential ellection campaign uses as it's mantra. I think our first step in cleaning up America is to get Bush out of office. Honestly, I don't care who takes his place - anyone could do a better job, really. The second thing we gotta do, is whoever takes over, we need to make sure to get a fire up their ass and make sure they do the right thing. We have to make sure that we pay close attention to everything they do and when they step out of line - we gotta take to the streets and inform The People.We   can not   allow them to start up with conspiracies and such! The second thing we gotta do is pay attention to every election that goes on, no matter how small. Whether it's a judge, mayor, senator, or congressman - we  must  take this country back and help forge it into something that it should be! These morons that get into government offices are backed by political fanatics - and most of the time they're the ones with the money who want specific controll of how our country is run. This is how we got into this mess from the begining - the people with the money are the ones running, or the ones that are supporting.  This is a democracy - let our voices be heard!
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (if anyone is curious, the title is a play on words taken from the group "America Comming Together")   I checked my e-mail a bit ago and I was amazed at the timing of these news letters. I figured that I would update everyone on all these movements   Help Counter GOP Smear Campaign on TV    Moveon.org   The GOP has been airing a commercial on TV run by the "Swift boat veterans for Truth" that claim that John Kerry was a horrible soldier and that his medals and injuries were fake. They are saying that since he was a terrible soldier and is dishonest about his military record, he would be a bad commander in chief. Republican John McCain has said that the Swift Boat crew is nothing but a bunch of Bush-groupies. They are dishonest, and deffinately don't care about the Truth, just about Bush. Apparently they also attacked Mr. McCain when he ran against Bush for the Republican Presidential seat in 2000 (for those that don't remember). McCain, and others have asked Bush to denouse these claims by the Swift Boat crew and of course he has not agreed to do so (even after a petition was sent to him). So now the lovely folks at Moveon.org have decided to air an add to tell about how GW doesn't have a leg to stand on since he went AWOL while in the National Guard - and that Bush needs to tell the Swift Boat crew to stop their adds.  urlLink Moveon.org  says that they need $200,000 dollars to air this ad  today!  The group says about their new comercial  "Together, we can put it on TV in precisely the markets where the "Swift Boat" ad ran, making sure that no swing voters are misled by this smear campaign."   If you would like to see what this commercial will look like, you can check it out  urlLink here    It's time to call Bush to account for these dirty tricks. Together, we can do that on TVs across the country.      Report Shows How Bush Is Squeezing Middle Class    Misleader.org   Every day I get an e-mail from this group that tracks all of Bush's blunders. Usually I don't bother putting it in here because you can read it all for yourself by signing up for their daily e-mails  urlLink here . However, in the spirit of all the political e-mails that has filled my inbox in the last hour, I decided to plug them for once. Here is the first paragraph of todays "mislead":   "President Bush is now storming the country claiming his records show that he cares about America's middle class. On everything from taxes to health care to workers wages, the President says he has fought for average Americans. But a new comprehensive report shows that in almost every key economic area, he has actually gone to bat for his wealthiest contributors, at everyone else's expense. "   He says he's for the middle class, but he, and all of his friends, are not middle class, and he gives tax cuts to the rich? Something doesn't sound right there George.  To view the full report, click  urlLink here      Bush 'Faith-Based' Agenda Spreading In Federal Government, Report Finds Initiative Ignores Constitutional Principles And Civil Rights Protections, Says Americans United    Americans United For Seperation of Church and State   This is deffinately one of my favorite organizations.  urlLink Americans United  is a group that is on what you could call "theocrat watch". They keep a close eye on church and state issues and an even bigger eye on cults like the Christian Coalation that want to do nothing more than turn this nation into a Christian Theocracy. Just the thought of their selfishness and intollerance makes me want to puke.. AU reported today on the dangers on Bush's  urlLink faith based initaitives .  To check that out,  urlLink go here      George Bush: You're Fired    HRC.org   The  urlLink Human Rights Campaign  is probably my 2nd fav next to AU. They fight hard to make sure that the Gay, Lesbian, Bi-Sexual, Trans-Sexual (GLBT) community has the same rights as every other citizen in this country. Since the protester areas for the political conventions this year (both democratic and republican nationals) are way off away from the building that the convention is being held at - protestors aren't getting a fair deal here. But leave it to the wonderful folks of HRC to come up with a great idea: 4 trucks with the slogan "George Bush: You're Fired" running all around NYC and especially Madison Square Garden (where the Republican National Convention is being held). Check out their van add and help donate. Let's send  urlLink Bush a message   Well, that's all for this issue folks. I think now I'm gonna finally get some ice cream to nurse my sore throat.  special thanks to Jute Cat for helping fix the HTML problems
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I recieved my  urlLink stickers  from  urlLink Freepress.net . I ordered 25 for $5 and then I also got 5 for free. These stickers are great - I wish I had them when I went to HOPE. With my order, came a lovely pamphlet:    Ten Questions about Media to ask every candidate and elected official     WHY ASK THESE QUESTIONS?   Media provide information, the lifeblood of democracy. But today, paid TV ads have replaced political debate. Soundbite journalism and celebrity-obsessed news dominate the airwaves. Content is marinated in commercialism and local coverage is dwindling. In short, the public interest is being sidelined by giant media corporations' insatiable quest for bigger profits.  Asking political candidates and officials to state their positions on media brings these concerns into the public eye and onto the political agenda. Indeed, the future of our media — and our democracy — may depend upon how our elected officials address these ten media issues.   10 Questions for Every Candidate and Elected Official   1)  Consolidation  Do you support setting limits on media consolidation — through antitrust law and ownership protections — to prevent large companies from having too much control over what Americans see, hear and read?   Why to ask this : The United States has seen a massive wave of media consolidation over the past two decades. For example, Time Warner alone — in addition to its cable empire reaching 11 million subscribers — controls over 100 magazines, dozens of television networks and record companies, as well as major publishing, Internet, TV and movie production companies.  2)  Noncommercial Media  Do you support policies that would increase and preserve funding for public and noncommercial media, and eliminate commercial sponsorship of public radio and TV programs?   Why to ask this : Democratic discourse requires quality sources of information free from advertiser pressure. However, we provide less funding per capita for public broadcasting than most other industrialized countries — by a wide margin.  3)  Kids' Marketing  Do you support efforts to reduce commercialism and predatory marketing toward children, and to promote noncommercial educational TV programming for young children?   Why to ask this : Our children today are bombarded with advertising. Parents, teachers, and organizations dedicated to children's issues are growing increasingly concerned as evidence mounts connecting media exposure to a variety of health and behavior problems.  4)  Cable Rates  Will you promote consumer choice by setting limits on cable ownership and by supporting policies to encourage the development of competition in cable markets?   Why to ask this : Over the past 5 years, cable rates have risen over 40% nationwide. This is the direct result of government-granted monopolies and lack of competition. The government has stalled on setting reasonable cable ownership limits. Meanwhile, cable companies are increasing their profits as they eliminate communities' ability to negotiate public-interest-oriented cable agreements.  5)  Internet Freedom  Do you support open access rules that keep the Internet free and open, and that protect individual privacy from both government and corporations alike?   Why to ask this : The Internet exploded over the past decade in part because Internet Service Providers were required by law to allow access to all websites and users without discrimination. Big cable and telephone companies now want to restrict what users and providers can and cannot access, all in the name of profit.  6)  Campaign Coverage  Do you support requiring broadcasters to provide significant free airtime for candidates and public debates as a condition of receiving their government-granted licenses?   Why to ask this : The skyrocketing cost of buying ad time is a major reason candidates raise ever-higher sums of campaign money from wealthy special interests. This year, TV broadcasters — who hold licenses to use publicly-owned airwaves, free of charge — will rake in a record-setting $1.47 billion from political ads. At the same time, news coverage of campaigns, especially on radio and television, has plummeted.  7)  Community Media  Do you support giving more communities the ability to broadcast their own locally-based programming through an expanded low-power radio and television service?   Why to ask this : Many communities find themselves and their concerns misrepresented by major broadcasters. Citizens need to hear their own voices over their own airwaves, and the capability exists to fulfill this demand. Legislation is pending that would create thousands of new low-power FM radio licenses.  8)  Minority Ownership  Do you support providing incentives to increase diversity in media ownership and leadership?   Why to ask this : Minority ownership of media is at a 10-year low, down 14% since 1997. Today, only 4% of radio stations and 1.9% of television stations are minority-owned. And studies show that the glass ceiling for women is firmly in place at communications companies.  9)  Media Workers  Do you support laws that make it easier for media workers to form trade unions and ensure they are paid for their overtime?   Why to ask this : Media consolidation pressures media workers to abandon their professional values in order to generate maximum short-term profits. Trade unions are especially important in media industries because they serve both to protect the rights of workers and to insulate the media's role in our democracy from economic pressure.  10)  Copyright  Do you support policies that will shorten the terms of copyright and lend balance to the law by allowing fair use for nonprofit and noncommercial purposes?   Why to ask this : Large corporations are buying protection from new competition and technological innovation. No copyrighted work created after 1922 has entered the public domain — an incubator for new ideas — due to legislation extending copyright terms. If laws being considered today had been in effect a few generations ago, consumers might not have access to products such as VCRs and copiers.  for those of you that don't want to spend money or wait for your free stickers, here is a link to the pdf version of this. Print it out and hand it out to people!  http://www.freepress.net/washington/10questions.pdf
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so in my ever continuing debate with people, one of the biggest things I notice is that people assume that everyone is christian. I personally feel that abortion should be legal. There are too many "what if's" to outlaw it. so I posted my response to this complete whack-job on beliefnet, and this is how she responds (this is great)        jesusisprolife 7/26/04 1:32:52 PM AND CALL ME CRAZY, BUT I DON'T THINK VOTING FOR A POLITICIAN BASED ON MORAL VIEWS OVER MONEY IS WRONG. SINCE WHEN DID MONEY BECOME MORE IMPORTANT THAT OBEYING GOD? AND IT'S NOT JUST ONE ISSUE THAT I CARE ABOUT (ABORTION), IT'S EVERYTHING! GAY MARRIAGE, LOOK AT SODDOM AND GAMORRAH, IF WE EMBRACE HOMOSEXUALITY GOD WILL BRING JUDGEMENT ON US AS A COUNTRY. DOES ANYBODY CARE? WHAT ABOUT THE PLEDGE OF ALLEGENCE, TEN COMMANDMENTS, AND ANY OTHER REFERENCE TO GOD BEING TAKEN OUT OF OUR SOCIETY? DO YOU THINK IT'S THE REPUBLICANS DOING THAT? AS A CHRISTIAN, DO YOU HONESTLY THINK THAT GOD WOULD LIKE TO PUT A PARTY IN POWER THAT CAUSES THE LIVES OF MILLIONS OF BABIES, IN ORDER TO RAISE MINIMUM WAGE? OR WOULD ALLOW GAY MARRIAGE? COULD THAT POSSIBLE BE THE WILL OF GOD? HAVE YOU EVER READ THE BIBLE?            jesusisprolife 7/26/04 1:22:29 PM ok i just read some of the old comments about me. i don't know everything about politics, and maby you people do, but i do know that democrats are for the most part secularists. they want sex ed in our classrooms to be about all the options in birthcontrol, with no mention of what God has to say about sex outside of marriage. If you are a christian, don't you think that thats what needs to be taught to our kids? A biblical view on sex. God's plan works. Let's empower our kids with the Word of God, and with biblical morals, I don't see the democrats wanting to do that. I think all you people are really worried about is money. money money money, the democrats say they will take money from the rich and give it to the poor. thats what it's all about. Maby you think money is the answer to all lifes problems, but i say it's the Word of God.            jesusisprolife 7/26/04 12:44:58 PM i think that by having abortion on demand, we are teaching our children that we don't have to worry about consiquences to our actions. That they should be able to do whatever feels good, reguardless of how that may affect their future children. "oh who cares, we can just kill them, and anyone who has a problem with that is tring to force their morals on me" that's the attitude this generation has! i guess some people think that because you can't hear the baby cry, or see the pain on their face as their limbs are being ripped off, that it's ok. as long as we can keep having sex whenever we darn well please, it's all worth it. IT'S SICK.            jesusisprolife 7/26/04 12:36:00 PM By the way, those abortion doctors are not honest to women about how developed their child is. they will call it "a ball of cells" or a "mass of tissue" but they do not tell them that by the time a pregnancy test is able to detect the pregnancy hormone, the embreo already has a heart beat. wich means they are alive. wich means that it's murder.            jesusisprolife 7/26/04 12:35:28 PM KYMUS, 14 year olds shouldn't be having sex. If they do have sex, I'm sure they realize that that could get them pregnant. That's a risk they are willing to take. I don't think a innocent baby should pay for their parents mistakes. If they don't want their baby, I guarentee somebody else does. And even an abortion preformed in a nice clean clinic are still dangerous to women. Women who have had an abortion have a much higher risk for getting breast cancer for one thing. But that does not even come close to the emotional pain that can result in any woman with atleast half of a concience. Do you realize the huge amount of women who REGRET having their babies killed? it can ruin their life.            jesusisprolife 7/26/04 12:19:34 PM KYMUS: you say "By making abortion laws,we are taking away a persons right to choose for themselves." What about the baby's right to choose for themselves??? I realize that they may not be capable of doing much intellegent thinking, but they still have a little heart that pumps blood, and they are just as important to God as a fully grown human. And that is why we should make anti-murder laws to protect tiny babies as well as any other human. Think about it, the bible says God formed us in the womb. Do you think he would appriciate us coming along and killing that life? Even if it's father did rape it's mother? Do you really think that child is less important to or loved by God? I don't because the Bible says God is no respector of persons.   And well, I couldn't help but respond with this:        Kymus 7/26/04 5:18:01 PM jesusisprolife: did it ever occur to you that not everyone is christian? You want God to be taught in schools, that's great, take your kids to a christian school. How about we start enforcing new religious laws? Let's start with the Buddhists and Wiccans since they've started less wars, are less zealous, and understand that thing called FREEDOM OF RELIGION. God didn't smite Hitler, or Hussein, or the Roman Catholics when they rewrote the Bible, or the Romans when they were having lots of gay sex. "AS A CHRISTIAN" I am not christian, most of my friends are not christian. You are not Buddhist, you don't see me asking you to follow Buddhist law do you?            Kymus 7/26/04 5:17:51 PM That's cause I have respect for others beliefs enough to let them practice what they want and realise that passing religous laws is biased, bigoted, and wrong!. The christian coalation needs to do their homework cause there's a reason why we are a DEMOCRACY and not a THEOCRACY. I think it had something to do with Colonial Europe.. gee.. then our founding fathers said something like "lets have a country where people can practice their faiths as they wish and they don't have to follow the rules of another religion" . Since you're such a humanitarian, do you also think about the bugs that you kill? How about flowers that you pick? Or the animals that are abused when companies test their products on them? All of them have feelings, all of them can suffer, all of them are actually more concious than that "baby" that is being aborted.            Kymus 7/26/04 5:17:26 PM But I am sure you would never condescend to think about those, since they are not humans, they don't matter, right? In Buddhism is says "try not to kill". That applies to everything. But you don't see me sitting here telling you that you have to follow that because Buddha (who was a miracle worker, just like Jesus!) said so. No, see I understand that for me to press my faith on you, it's wrong! I am not Christian, so therefore why should I be bound by Christian laws, thoughts, ideals, morals, etc etc etc? Would it be right if the Moslems enacted a law that made it illegal for women to be un-modest and not cover their heads and/or faces? I'm sure that many would agree that that indeed would not be fair. But it seems that the religious right doesn't care! Yes, lets keep the republicans in power. Lets just deny 15 million people the right to happiness in a relationship,            Kymus 7/26/04 5:16:35 PM and the ability to visit their partner in Intesive Care. How would you feel if someone said you couldn't visit a loved one in IU because you're christian and christians aren't allowed to marry? that would be pretty bigoted, wouldn't it? Think for a minute how it is for others. Think about how you would feel if someone got on a religious high horse with you and told you that what you are doing is wrong because their religion said so - and you had to deal with it for all of your life. (BTW Soddom and Gamorah story is a farse - it was on a fault line!)Welcome to the world the rest of us live in - it's called Earth. Oh boy, and those republicans.. Yes, lets keep them around so that they can send us to war on false reasons, give tax cuts to the rich, give favors the the corporations, push religion on people who don't follow it, deny 15 million people civil rights,            Kymus 7/26/04 5:16:03 PM cut funding for AIDS, establish a facist regime, just like Hitler, Mussolini, Franco, Suharto, and Pinochet, and lets not forget the wonderful job in office and let everyone think that they have those good-guy values, and then they enjoy lieing to the people. Oh they also like to blame things on other people that they are guily of themselves - what wonderful people! Yes, I would prefer to have someone in office who doesn't try to make decisions for me, favors the people who need money more, and doesn't try to push their religion on me. I enjoy having a democrocy, not a theocracy or a dictatorship. I'd like to keep it that way :)  here's a link to the site: http://www.beliefnet.com/story/148/story_14856_1.html   As you can see, this lady is a complete and utter whack-job. She should really look into getting herself committed - it would do the rest of us a favor. 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the record, John Kerry wasn't my first decission. My first decision on who to vote for was  urlLink Reverand Al Sharpton . I had read some of his responces from when he was being interviewed on MTV and he seemed to have a good head on his shoulders. He said how banning Gay's from maraige is like saying that Blacks can't marry. It's funny that he mentioned that since in the 1960's there was a civil rights movement going on with them and the same lines were being used by the conservatives: "It's redifining marraige" "It will destroy the sanctitiy of marraige". Bunch of lies as we see today nothing about marraige has changed. So yes, as I was stating earlier, so many people on the Right are trying to discredit John Kerry. Let's get something straight here. John Kerry isn't the best canidate for a President, but right about now, we don't have much of a choice. We can have 4 more years of Bush where many of our friends and family could possibly get drafted to fight in Iraq and then maybe later in North Korea (there are theories that Bush has more targets planned). I don't want to see my friends and family have to fight for a greedy war. Let's not forget the deficit. I think it's down to  urlLink $477 Billion ?  When Clinton left office there was actually a small surplus for the first time. Bush says that the oil revenue from Iraq will pay for the war, but that's not true. The oil company donates money to Bush's campaign because they know that he is going to give them big kick-backs on money. All Bush does is lie. He lied at his State of the Union, he lied to Congress about a war, he lies about environmental protection.. It is really boiling down to a lesser of 2 evils...
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It never ceases to amaze me as to how brain washed the Bush Administration has made so many conservatives. I see them all the time talking about how Bush would benefit the country the most and how if you don't support Bush and the war then you're in league with the terrorists. Another one of my favorites is that questioning the president is being unpatriotic. Wtf?! NO! The Bush Administration has spewed out so many lies to the public that they need to be  urlLink impeached . Misleading and lying to congress about issues concerning war  is  a crime.  To touch up on that... The other day a person asked about exactly why Congress allowed us to go to war with such little proven intelligence. I think this is something that people should look into more. This really is a starting point to show just how terrible Bush's administration is for America. Bush got us into a preemptive war. Him and his administration were all talking about how we  have to act now before it's too late . So the first thing they did was use their slogan (which Bush and Condoleeza Rice both said) "we don't want a smoking gun to turn into a mushroom cloud" - meaning it's possible that we could wait too long to unearth the facts and we could be faced with a nuclear attack. Bush told congress that he had recieved information from British Intelligence that Iraq could fire off "chemical and biological weapons" withing 45 minutes of recieving the order to do so.  NEWS FLASH: Iraq has never had the ability to launch missiles at us ; they didn't have that ability in the first Gulf War, the didn't have it in 2001, and they never will. The next thing Bush says, and I believe this was during his State of the Union address - was say that Iraqi has purchased aluminum rocket tubes that are suitable to be used to build Weapons of Mass Destruction (WMD). According to military intelligence from people with experience with these weapons, the aluminum tubes are for M-81 rockets and aren't even compatable with the WMD. Then Bush goes on to talk about how Sadam gives weapons to Al-Quida and other terrorists. Let's get something straight here. Saddam is running a Dictatorship. In a dictatorship you do not give free radicals your best weapon. Another thing, is that the terrorists didn't even like Saddam. So these, along with a few others that you can find out if you google around, are the reasons we went to war. America isn't used to a preemptive war. But I think that now hopefully we won't let it happen again.
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the first blog I've ever had outside of  urlLink Live Journal , so it will take me a little while to figure out all of Blogger's settings and tools. Within a few days everything should be good! In the mean-time - check out my political blog on livejournal:  urlLink Phracktivist  - it is simply a mirror of what this will be. 
    
</post>


</Blog>