<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up many times last night..  Not because of insomnia but the pain in my throat.  I was waiting all weekend for a chance to get to sick call today at 0700.  When the Doctor finally saw me she knew right away and without hesitation on what I had after looking at the back of my throat---STREP!!!  No wonder it was soo painful.  Life sucks arggg.  She gave me two IVs of water solution cause she said i was dehydrated even though I exclaimed I have battled this ordeal out with Nyquil, Vick's Vapor Rub, Warm water and Salt, Cough Drops, Chicken Noodle Soup, and lots of liquids.  Ahwell sometimes you cannot win battles alone.  She gave me Penicillin and Ibuprofen-- the good stuff.  I did ask her to knock me out because I cannot even sleep without being in pain.  So now Im home now and I just took the pills.  Waiting for its effects to send me to dream land :))).   Come to think of it I have been doing a lot of cooking lately.  Some of it is actually pretty easy and other stuff I just took off the internet.  I bet you all would be surprised that I didn't know how to make french toast!  Well I finally figured that out haha.  I cannot wait to start on Sean's recipes and I do hope you (yes YOU Dad send me some of your goodies as well) and Sean as well cause I love all of it.   Im listening to Shivaree "Good Night Moon" from  Kill Bill Vol2,  the time is 10 20 and Ive got a class today and tomorrow I will be unable to attend.   I was placed on 48hr quarters so I get to be wrapped up in a blanket and drift to the warm abyss where dreams exist-- oh hey hey that rhymes!  Well this is my Monday post, i hope you guys get started and send me your blog links ok?  Andy signing out 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After much delay i finally figured out how to create another post on this blogger hehe. I am still sick but the fever is gone and so is the headache. The weakness in my body is also gone and I guess thats the lymphnotic part of my body that was wearing me down. I didn't dare go beyond the boundaries of my apartment for fear i would contrapt new demonic visages of pain. So I did what any other normal but sick boy would do and stayed inside. I really wanted to make a post yesterday concerning a very tragic day in my life.  My mother's one year memorial aniversary was yesterday and to start the occasion I lit a candle in her memory and also played some of her favorite musical pieces like James Horner's Titanic and Braveheart. I told my Dad to call me just before the final moments of her life because I rather have it 'share' then to be alone. Because I am alone here in Florida... I do not mean that alone, I have friends here and now even girls to contend with, but family wise I am alone.  My Dad gave me information on one of my cousins whom I just barely begun to reestablish contact with lives south of me and I shall be giving him a phone call to check on how he is doing.  Right now Im listening to Lord of the Ring's The Hornburg by Howard Shore, its this music that peaks me into new spell binding dimensions. Ive got some of my Homework done because of it. Speaking of LOTR and homework...  Yesterday my friends stopped by asking me to go out with them on a party but I told them i was too sick. Then after they left Tara and her sister came, Tiff had to research something and I let her borrow my computer to whom she was very impressed with *flex*. Tara cooked one of those Betty Crocker Chicken N Dumplings Complete Meals for us. A very big surprise for her sister and I because this girl is MISS PRISSY and PERFECT and does not like getting her hands dirty. Haha, i made her get dirty though cause i told her i would not be cooking at all even if I starved that night. She was like FINE, just do your HW. Then this girl has the nerve to play a DVD without letting me start on my homework (the sound blaring as such). So impatient.. She complained afterwards because she thought she messed up the end result of the meal but it turned out really good. She is always like that... So self concious and so rackety...  Well this is by far one of my longer posts so Ill jetison off for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heheh, well not really im just sittin on my computer and feeling achy, sore, and sick.  I caught a sore throat over the week.  I suppose its because i have been up a lot past my time due to some exotic activities!  Ahwell cannot blame me, i am a Daley and i love it!  Thanks Dad ehhe!  Well this is my first post.   Im smelling vicks vapor rub and i have Nitequil in my system, i can almost feel its effects soon, soooo sleepy :(.  We were watching Lord of the Rings the Two Towers before she had to go.  Women........  Ahwell, she kept her place ruff!  Andy 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>