<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, the weekend is almost over and it barely feels like it began.  Today we go to visit Denise's maternal grandparents, uncles, aunts, etc.  I haven't seen this part of her family for several years now.  She hasn't generally gotten along with them, something which I think goes back to before her mom and dad were divorced.  Since then, Denise has not been very happy about the way they act toward her mother, but there have been some recent changes for the better in that department.  It is her grandparents' wedding anniversary, so we are going to mingle.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Saturday.  Finally.  Got up today, checked to see if I got any mail from Jason.  Nope.  I'm really kinda nervous about the book-writing thing, but I am going to go for it.  I got mono to compile this morning, and I want to get around to doing the XML Encryption stuff soon.   Today I went out shopping with a short list of things to get.  One of them was a flag to replace the one that the neighbourhood punks stole from my porch.  I didn't get the flag, but I did go to Canadian Tire.  While I was browsing around, I spied a 52" ceiling fan that was about $100 off the regular price.  Since we've been looking for a ceiling fan for our bedroom for quite some time, and since this one was nice, we decided to get it.  Of course, I had to hum and haw for about 30 minutes over the fact that we were going to spend $70 on a ceiling fan, but that's a lot better than $170.  So, of course, I screwed up my plan to BBQ tonight by installing the fan this evening instead.  It looks nice.  I didn't realize before how low the ceiling is in our bedroom -- it's not even 7&frac12; feet!  The fan manual says that the blades need to be at least 7 feet above the floor.  I'm only 6" below that. :-)  Lesson learned today: go with your instinct.  I spent so much time thinking about that fan, only to buy it.  I decided that if I didn't want it I could return it anyway.  If I had just gone with what I thought in the first place all would have been well. However, because of my indecisiveness, I managed to upset the wife.  See, we had already been out for a couple of hours, and little William was with us.  We thought he would probably be quite hungry and wet.  We went straight home after that and he was fine, but the damage had been done.  I'm lucky enough to have a wife that understands me and loves me for who I am.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've decided to get around to setting up one of these blog-type things. I won't write my entire life story here, but I will try to keep up-to-date on what is happening.  Work has been going fairly well recently but I am swamped in information. I took a month off to by with my newborn son, and I came back to something that I know very little about. It's all about regulatory compliance, internal controls, and Sarbanes-Oxley, things that I don't understand. Even better, it is for a large bank which has tons of documentation for us to drown in.  I'm creating new Livelink object types to capture all of the metadata they require. I found out that other people that are also working on this in Ottawa aren't even as far along as I am -- and I thought I was working slowly! That makes me feel much better about things.  William is six weeks old today. It's hard to believe that it has been so long. I remember it like it was yesterday -- but I'm getting more sleep now than the day after he was born!  I bit the bullet today and responded to Apress. They want me to write a book about mono. I've always wanted to be published, but with the baby and work it will be hard to find the time. I hope that it works out well. As he said, all I need to do is get in the habit of writing on a regular schedule.  Speaking of mono, I was going back through some of my mail and remembered that Sebastian wanted me to work on XML Encryption. So, I'm updating my mono to see whether there is still work to do there.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>