<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't seem to breathe...  I feel..numb...and emotionless...  Why the fucking hell am I feeling like this?!!!  Someone...stab me right now...seriously. I need a drink...I am so close to just jumping downstairs and seeking out that wine bottle and just drink the rest of it. Maybe I should just go to bed...and like stare at my ceiling. --;  Oh god...haha yeah...I think I'm going to like totally loose it tonight. Peace  
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha last night was fun, I wanna do it again. o.0;; My dad opened up that bottle of red wine - dude, I've been waiting FOREVER for him to do that!!! I swear to god! Lmao. And yesh, I got to drink some. ^^ We didn't drink straight up though cause he said it was too bitter   Then after dinner and after several cups...half the bottle of that red wine was gone and my head started to spin. I was like whoaaaa!! What's going on? xD! [I've never drank that much wine in my life or enough to cause anything to happen] I was going upstairs and I saw my comp froze so I restarted it. Then I went back down to check on my brother.  My dad told me to not run up and down the stairs so much and I was like why? I had a smile on my face o.0 and he was like 'My head's starting to spin already so I don't want you to fall down the stairs.' xDD! I wasn't drunk but like I was completely aware of what I'm doing! Cept I was so happy and I wasn't as depressed as I was yesterday morning! Man, yesterday morning was a load of shit. -_-;  And after I got all spinny...haha we were dancing in the family room with the stereo on. It was funnn. *Nods* I totally forgot all about the sadness and stuff, I was smiling so much last night. We danced for about an hour until all of us just went back upstairs to rest. Took a shower, tried to sleep early ...lmao didn't happen. I tried calling Kai but no one answered so meh. I ended up sleeping at midnight with the TV on or something.   Anypoop, I gotta go ask him to see my schedule for high school. They mailed it in but I never saw it --; and I need to know where my damned high school classes are. Hehe. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well! I got to speak to him last night cept the problem was I fell asleep! It was 2 AM and I went on my bed to rest and stuff then I fell asleep. By the time I woke up to check my computer, it was like 3:30 AM or something cause they were showing the re-run of Inuyasha on Cartoon Network [yes, I had my TV on.] When I saw my computer screen and I saw a message box blinking from MSN - my heart was pounding/racing, whatever cause it was from him. When I read it, I started to feel sad cause he was on for a while but he got off and I wasn't here to say hi or bye or anything [ou...just got a de ja vu feeling of writing this -_-"] Basically, that was shitty.  Then I just went to bed, turned off everything, and I guess I drifted off to sleep. I woke up around noon for some reason [I don't usually wake up that late] and I had to attend to my daily chores or weekly ones knowing he won't be on for a while because he had work today. My brother totally pissed me off today [he won't shut up about something] and I just ignored him.  I guess the good thing is I got to talk to him, really, it was nice. But when he messaged me, my heart started to race again [I swear I haven't gotten this feeling in a long time -_-; and I must say, I'm not happy it's back cause it means something...something I can't quite put my finger on.] Anypoop, while I was talking to him - I asked him stuff and it turns out he's just sick [not emotionally but physically] and I guess I was worried and uhh...I'm still worried. [Kay..that proved absolutely nothing -_-...] And to prove my luck absolutely sucks - my net goes off on me because my connection failed or some other shit like that. ;( But I guess that was good cause if I talked to him anymore, I had a feeling I was going to cry. [Why? Gee...I got absolutely NO clue. I just had a strong urge to cry...] And my dad wasn't home yet and when he did come home, he was on the phone talking bout business. x_x!! But thank god it fixed itself!! But he's not here...would that be a good thing? I'm still worried about him. =/ Ack! I should stop worrying! He's fine...and still living [that's not very reassuring, is it?] *Sigh.* I need another vacation lmao. Guess that's it for the day...for now. I miss him. ;( Shoo much... 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...I don't know what to say or do anymore. Everything seemed to have gone downhill last night...kinda not really...I don't really know. x_x! I didn't even talk to him today cause he didn't come on till like a few hours ago but he's not there, he's away. ;( I think he's ignoring everyone or something. I don't know whether I should just forget about it cause it shouldn't bother me and it has nothing to do with me [hopefully] but then I'm just worried. I'm such a worry hog -_x;;  I changed the link colors and the header colors o.o;; I'm still trying to get use to this cause I have a xanga and xanga is easier to read for me considering they have input areas and not a big blotch where I could do whatever I want. ;P I actually prefer a big blotch so I can customize it however I want. ^-^ But...not right now. Hehe.  I'm watching the Olympics to pass the time...I hope I get to talk to him tonight ... ;( I wanna know what's bothering him. ;-; I feel so useless. Anypoop, I'm just going to go and stare at my screen and wait for him. --; Yeahh... 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eh? ^_^ Hiii...and I guess...that's all!  
    
</post>


</Blog>