<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       feeling slightly betta. gonna yet survive thru w/o using a phone. can't use mom's.. dad's calls are diverted ta her no. ... its a 3-in-1 thingy cos mom's phone line got cut fer a while tdy. Singtel had some new plans but she wasn't informed of it. ma house line got cut yst... plus ma phone got its crack.. that sums it up for 3-in-1. the phones get 'disconnected' together at one go. jees. mom keeps commenting on what a weird coincidence that is. hahaas. she didn't scold, kill or anything of that sort... (: anyways, i've thought of a new name fer meeee*, myself and Qi.. they call me inchy.....thought Inch was pretty unique. yeahhh. gonna go do up the physics worksheet now...   insy winsy spider climbing up the wall...             
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wasn't able ta blog yst. ma house line got cut.. externally. jees. all is fine now. yeah! something pretty interesting Guang said yst during chem lesson. PhD = permanent head damage. hahaas. geog test didn't really go well.. didn't have enough time ta complete the qns. ohhh wells. F.r.i.e.n.d.s was as usual.. hilarious. caught extreme makover as well.. it transforms.. or disfigures you? hmm.  ma d&t project sucked. the lacquering was too thick.. hahaa.. it was done by meee. i broke the triangular pieces while buffing. it flew.. hit and ground...and cracked. eeeeky. managed ta fix em' back together thou. adding to the moodiness.. ma precious phone's outer LCD screen cover cracked! arghhhh. thank God the LCD screen wasn't affected. *sighs. i suppose when the triangular piece flew.. it hit ma skirt.. when.. ma phone was in there. it was a strong.. great.. impact. sent it fer repair at centrepoint just now, its gonna take 1-3 days. darn sad. its barely a month old. so gonna miss it.. ..my precious. ): so screwed with everything tdy. gonna take a nap.. sleep helps! i'll just hafta sit and pray fer a betta day tmr.... can't wait ta get my phone back!!  -surviving w/o the precious thang..   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *weeeee. i've just received a volcom bag! its stripey with orange wordings. a big thank you ta weng, it really was a surprise. thank you ta dez too, who was with him.. plus calling me an asshole. (:    just finished studying geog, having a test tmr. sighhhhss.. *fingers crossed, hope i'd be able ta ans e qns. went down ta j8 fer a while in the eve. got this elseve relaxing hair wax. its suppose ta anti-frizz. hahaa.. i suppose i really do need one. hope it works. jees.   alrytes, time to chill. sch tmr......eeeky.   this is a poem that i've received as well. thought it was rather inspirational.       The twilight shone across the field,     the breeze abundant, yet stars a few.     Alone you ponder,     Alone you wonder,      looking to God.     Fears you forgot,     holding His hand,      Tears of repent,     Never alone cause I'm with you.     In God, In me, you can abide.     I promise, through times, I'll never leave your side.          -inspired by love                     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       arghh.. the weekend is passing toooo fast.    its gonna be yet another week of sch,sch and more sch. it stinks! hahaa.. it just seems to be an everyday routine. sch.. home.. eat.. sleep.. sch again.   sighs. i betta did start sticking ma ass down and start studying real hard. prelims are ard d corner, plus..the O's are coming really soon. its*haunting.....   depending on ma heavenly father for the motivation.    mom just left for a massage.. all alone at home now, dad's over at china.    still struggling with ma folio.. jees.    laters......       Ashlee Simpson - Pieces of Me    On a monday, i am waiting     Tuesday, i am fading     On a Wednesday, i can't sleep     Then the phone rings     I hear you      And the darkness is a clear view     Cuz you've come to rescue me          Fall... With you, I fall so fast     I can hardly catch my breath, I hope it lasts          Ohhhhh     It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real     I like the way that feels     Ohhhhh     It's as if you've known me better than I ever knew myself     I love how you can tell     All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me     All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me          I am moody, messy     I get restless, and it's senseless     How you never seem to care          Fall...with you i fall so fast     Well, i hit that bottom     Crash, you're all i have          Ohhhhh     It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real     I like the way that feels     Ohhhhh     It's as if you've known me better than I ever knew myself     I love how you can tell     All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me          How do u know everything i am about to say     Am i that obvious?     And if it's written on my face...     I hope it never goes away... yeah          On a monday, I am waiting     And by Tuedsay, I'm fading into your arms...     So i can breathe          Ohhhhh     It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real     I like the way that feels     Ohhhhh     It's as if you've known me better than I ever knew myself     I love how you can tell     All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me     All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me                        
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       am at buttercup coffee now...*weeet   came ta town with Jac after doing our folio.. Jesz came along with us.    met Jac's mom...hanged ard and we got beard papa's!! yeahh..     *strawberry fizz....      
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               youuuhooo!             This is ma first time bloggin'.. *weee!    its the weekends! yeahh... time ta let ma hair down and chill a lil'.   went ta school in the mornin for chinese and did a lil' of ma d&amp;t project after that. awaiting ta wake Jac up at 2.. hahaa. she's gonna come over ta do the folio. gotta hand it up by the 31st.. eeeeek. guess i'll hafta rush and finish it up fasssst... (:                  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>