<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Check out  urlLink the Dresden Dolls . They're ... um ... I'm not really sure how to describe them. They're a "rock" sort of band, but they're primarily piano/drums based. Amanda is really interesting to watch (so is Brian, come to think of it); watch their  urlLink video  for  Girl Anachronism . ((Listen to their songs  urlLink here  if you can't get the video to come up.)) Their lyrics are really amazing, and when you combine them with their odd music (I think it's called "Brechtian punk cabaret," whatever the hell that means) it leaves a really interesting combination.       So that's my contribution to the music world for today! :)    (( Edit:  Ah, I knew "Brechtian" sounded familiar. Bertolt Brecht believed that theatre should not appeal to the audience's senses but to their reason:      In the  Realistic Theater of Illusion , [Brecht] argued that the spectator tended to identify with the characters on stage and become emotionally involved with them rather than being stirred to think about his/her own life. To encourage the audience to adopt a more critical attitude to what was happening on stage, Brecht developed the "alienation effect" --the use of anti-illusive techniques to remind the spectators that they are in a theatre watching an enactment of reality instead of reality itself.      Wow. MTV actually  urlLink helped . Watch  Girl Anachronism  and this all might make sense. I guess listening would work, too, but if you watch the video, it'll  really  make sense.  ))  
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Okay, let's see if I can cover everything in the course of ... well, my attention span:      School started Monday. We had Friday off, which confuses the shit out of me -- why go to school for  four  days and then get a break? We shouldn't be tired yet! Anyhow, I guess I'm pretty content with my schedule. Even PE doesn't bother me as much anymore, although I'm still vehemently opposed to it, and not completely sure if I'll  ever  be able to bench-press seventy-five pound thirty five times (I'm sure I can run a seven-minute mile, though; I do it all the time). A break-down of my schedule, because I like lists:       MSTC AP Calculus  -- Yay! Question: how do you know if you're a complete and total dork? Answer: if you're completely and totally enthralled by the very act of being  in  Calculus (read: I'm rather excited about Calculus).     MSTC AP Biology  -- Something about the teacher bothers the shit out of me. I can't figure out what it is. That and I've never been terribly interested in biology.    PE/Health  -- O_O ((As a side note, if I  weren't  taking this class, I'd probably be taking another Adv./AP class, which means I could have potentially gotten a 5.0 GPA.))    MSTC AP Computer Sciences  -- ^_^ I like computer programming. Remember, I'm a dork and damn fucking proud of it. Java looks like fun.    Adv. US History  -- Meh. I have to take it, so I'm taking it. Should be easy enough. ((Warning: Rant. ... She's requiring us to do community service. Okay, normally, I have no problem with community service, but when it's  FORCED   and  suggested as a sign of moral character, I get rather pissed. But, I'll save my charity speech for a better time.))    MSTC AP Physics  -- Actually looks like a lot of fun. Very math-y, which is brilliantly up my alley. How is anyone friends with me?    Adv. English-10  -- A poetry unit  AND  a dystopia unit? ::faints and dies:: Ignoring all of the shitty stuff we'll end up doing, these two units will more than please me for a while.    Adv. French-3  -- Meh. It's French.    Adv. Orchestra  -- Do you know how weird it is to play with an orchestra that can  actually  hold a tune? It's rediculous. But I miss the people in other class (as in ... Victoria and Sri). The Adv. Orchestra people are rather frightening, in a, "They all ready know each other and have this weird bond-ish thing going on" way.      And that's it. My nine glorious classes.      For English, we have to do a "book presentation." One of the options is to burn a CD with songs that somehow relate to the book, and then write the "liner notes" explaining that relation. Because we're not going to play any of the songs in class, I decided to do that option ... for Ayn Rand's  We The Living . It's shocking, really, how easy it is to  force  some songs to relate to a book.       All right. My attention span is gone. We'll see if I can write more later.         
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is me trying to figure out how this works.    All right, so I figured out most of it. Good for me.  
    
</post>


</Blog>