<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I started off my Monday just like everyone else....staff meetings checking emails andnegotiating the price and schedule of my ow personal cook and cleaner for the month!  Rock on.  For the low price of $60 a month (which is all I will be here for) I get a lady to clean and cook for me.  Plus the price of groceries, which for this week is only $15!  I knew this no-profit lifestyle would finally reward me.  My laundry lady only charges me $5 a day to clean my clothes - no matter how much or how little there is to clean.  Any one want to send there laundry my way??   Ok - I must get back to work. At least writing this blog makes me APPEAR busy:)  email me folks - I am getting a bit homesick :-( 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok folks....at the suggestion of my favorite everyday (Spencer, for those that don't know) I decided to startone of these new fangled bloggy things.  Well - maybe it isn't new to others, it is to me.  So here goes.  As you all know, I am in East Timor right now - Dili to be exact.  What is it like you have asked?  Here is how my Saturday has been so far.   5am - Wake up.  Damn jet lag.  Can't get over it.  I am sure that I will be asleep tonight before 9am.  Ugh!  And what is worse - I actually have curtains in my room that block out the sun - which wakes me up bright and early everyday back home (since I can't afford curtains there!)  7am - Shower.  Not a normal shower, mind you.  No way, Jose.  And that is pronounced "J"-ose, not a silent J.  We are in East Timor remember - land of the Portuguese colonialists.  Ok - back to the shower.  I have a 2x3  section of the bathroom that is supposed to be a shower.  It has a drain.  It has a faucet and even a hand held shower hose.  Biggest problem - the shower curtain stops three inches fom the edge of the shower.  Thus making the whole bathroom - my shower.   8am - Go into the office to do a bit of work.   This is what I am here to do folks.  11:30am - Go out for a nice long walk to the hotel I stayed at the last time I was here - Hotel Esplanada.  They have a fabulous menu :-)  For the record, I had grilled lemon chicken over a couscous salad.  Yum!  Before I got there - I remembered my biggest pet peeve of this place.  No, it isn't the fact that I do not have all the creature comforts of home (read - a propoer shower), or even that I am rather isolated.  Nope - it's taxis folks.  Some NYC cabbie must have come here at some time and taught all of these guys how to be rude.  Ugh!  First - when they want to let s pedestrian know that they are available for hire - they honk.  Not a , "ah-hem, excuse me" short beeping honk.  No - I mean a "HEY YOU" kinda a honk.  Scared the beegesus out of me on several occasions today.   And they don't like to honk just once to let you know they are available.  They honk several times - starting when they are about 20 yards away all the way until when they get to you.  Some have even been (smart?) enough to install different more distinctive horns - they really do run the gamut - my favorite is the one that sounds like a siren.  How they get away with this with the police is beyond me.  Oh yeah - lack of infrastructure here.   Ok - so I am walking to Hotel Esplanada - enjoying the beach road (20 feet from the water) soaking up the sun when one of these yahoos tries to get my attention.  He honks  - I shake my head no (which usually works).  Then he pulls all the way up on to the shoulder of the road.  For a minute I think he may run over me.  But no - apparently that is a tactic to get customers.  If you run them off the road then they must want to get in your taxi because there is simply no way to get by!  How silly of me to think otherwise.  Stubborn Kourtney decides to just wait him out until he decides to leave (much like the police in Cambodia - another story for another day).  So I have a nice LONG leisurely lunch at the hotel and then proceed home.  Again, I am accosted the entire 2.5 miles back to the office by random tax drivers.  When I shook my head no to one of them, he proceeded to give me the finger.  Nice!  I would also like to mention that the cabs here are by no means regulated or uniform (remember the horns?).  Most of them look like they were just driven out of the barrio in LA - low riding hondas or hyundais with tinted windoes, various acoutrements in the front and back windows  - oh and lots of stuff hanging from the rear view mirror.  I thinkthey have seen too many bootlegged DVDs about the US.  Well - I promise you all that there is more to East Timor than bizarre cabbie behaviour.  Bu I will save that for another day.  Miss you all! K  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>