<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A middle aged man, somewhat portly and florid of face, strolled with considerable urgency past rows of trim granite tombstones towards the Church for Sunday mass. He had been delayed by a heated argument with his wife; she had refused to accompany him to worship that morning. He looked pointedly at the headstone bearing his son’s name, erected only a fortnight before, still adorned with bouquets of garish flowers. “That woman,” he thought. “That woman won’t stick t’nothin’. Firs’ little thing an’ she’s “questionin’ her faith”, I ask ye.”  Now, in a pertinacious effort to make up time and arrive at church without deviance from his livelong record of unwavering punctuality, he had exhausted himself trekking over field, through copse, and at last traversing the low wall bordering the graveyard. He felt perhaps that such a route might be sacrilegious, or that this terrific exertion on a Sunday impious, but without a definite Biblical verdict, he had decided that it would be safe to risk it.  He began to doubt this judgement, however, when he found that the ground was trembling beneath his feet with increasing intensity. He stopped dead in his tracks, and looked frantically about him for some possible cause of the disturbance. It appeared to be a localised tremor; the quiescent serenity of the hills and meadows around wholly intact. Yet close by, gravestones began to wobble and teeter precariously around him, and he had to dart as swiftly as fifty years of ale, roast beef, and pork chops would permit to evade the crushing weight of one particularly extravagant headstone.  He decided it would be best to seek the aid of the vicar, if he hadn’t yet began his sermon, and so set off towards the Church while mopping his brow and attempting to reclaim his habitual air of dignified composure, or so he considered it. Malign voices muttered behind his back of his ludicrous, haughty pomp, between exchanges of gossip about his latest marital tribulations.  With a mounting sense of relief, he approached the gate leading to the Church courtyard, when all of a sudden he found himself lifted from his feet by a particularly violent convulsion. His weight born now by his face, he failed to witness the explosion of earth behind him, the rupturing of the ground into a great chasm, the cascade of soil, fragmented granite, and putrescent segments of corpse and accompanying splinters of rotten wood. He did, however, manage to upturn himself in time to see a radiant wingèd figure disappear into the low clouds, but of course that was dismissed as concussion talk. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "The mark of the immature man is that he wants to die nobly for a cause, while the mark of the mature man is that he wants to live humbly for one."  Wilhelm Stekel (featured in  The Catcher in the Rye ).  Disregarding the majority of humanity - the hoi polloi - as they are entirely irrelevant and superfluous to any anthropological discussion of merit that does not directly involve them, I wish to ascertain the veracity and pertinence of this aphorism.  I must confess that the idea of pledging my allegiance to a cause I deem truly worthy does appeal, in, perhaps, a similar way that an ephemeral freedom from conscious thought, as in the Bacchanalia of  The Secret History,  appeals to some. While the latter frees a person from any concept of or desire for a purpose, the other provides one. Thus, rather than wandering aimlessly on whim and influence, malign or benign, through these years of experience, one would have a guiding ideal.   "A man who won't die for something is not fit to live."  So Martin Luther King would have us believe. Was this an immature statement? I certainly disagree with it. Am I mature? Am I not fit to live? I wouldn't choose to die for a cause; or at least, I do not wish to entangle myself in anything that might imbue me with sufficient irrationality to be able even to contemplate such an act. However, the prospect of committing myself to a life of humble subservience to a cause is very nearly as unappealing. I would, instead, wish to have some integral role in the cause, to be a dynamic, contributory, and enduring asset, but also a questioning, redirecting entity, only compliant as long as the ends of the cause complimented my own.  It seems to me that where Stekel says "mature" we should read "jaded", a confusion so pervasive I have almost to believe that they have become genuinely synonymous. In that case, maturity is not something to be aspired to, if the state of fulfilment to which it pertains entails this vapid quiescence, this mollifying of human vigour and valiance.  Martin Luther King's assertion probably derives in part from his religious views. Religion, being primarily (in the modern world), a mechanism employed to insulate the individual from the horrors of stark reality, an illusory solace, the opiate of the masses, etcetera, is an immaturity, because it requires a verdant ignorance that no intellectually developed person could maintain, and because that craven contentment in delusion is infantile. This devoted, deferential, injudicious belief in something just for devotion's sake that leads a person to give their life to a cause, is immature in the same way.  To conclude, I hold Stekel's aphoristic pronouncement to be true, although in a way he had not intended, holding as contemptible both of the options he presents, and suggesting instead a constructive and questioning alliance with a greater body of mutual principle to be the objective of the ideal individual. However, even this outcome is immaterial. I excerpt a passage from a conversation conducted between myself and a friend:  "Myself: Do you think that if someone formed some revolutionary movement that actually had the potential to achieve those things (I realise how quixotic a hypothetical situation that is) you could be motivated to contribute your full efforts to it?  Him: Well yes, but that's like saying: "If Sweden and Hungary went to war, causing chaos in the terpentine industry, and all other turpentine manufacturers went out of business, would you be prepared to go into selling emergency turpentine to sweden and hungary to make millions of pounds?" Obviously the answer is yes, but the situation will never arise. I don't even know what the fuck turpentine is."  This, in a somewhat obfuscated fashion, relates an important truth. In this world there is an absence of any cause of any kind that warrants either living or dying for, and any attempt to create one is doomed to almost inevitable failure by the apathy and mediocrity of contemporary humanity. So, fuck it all.   
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Common Assumption 1: Love is, in one guise or another, the modal subject of non utilitarian thought and communication amongst humans.  Common Assumption 2: Love is regarded by the majority of humanity to be one of the most important factors in their general level of happiness and contentment.  Common Assumption 3: Love, when aroused, has the most potent influence on human action of any emotion.  Omnia vincit amor . Love conquers all.  Common Assumption 4: The capacity to love and the desire to love and be loved are intrinsic to human nature.  The first thing I'd argue is that nobody even knows what love is, because it isn't anything, except an artificial abstract construct employed to romanticise a chemical technique the genome employs to aid the fulfilment of the fundamental and essential carnal instinct towards self propagation, but that viewpoint (although, I believe, veracious) is effectively irrelevant in the everyday practical world, as it is an inescapably pervasive notion.  This concept of love we have created, that evinces itself with such ubiquity in our lives, and is exalted so highly, is simultaneously the cause of damage depredation destruction degredation dilapidation denunciation delapsion disgust dismay despair dissolution death decay... Etcetera, woe is us with our stricken hearts, boohoo.  But seriously.  Heaven has no rage like love to hatred turned.  So what I ask, is whether, or whether not, it is best that this notion of love be preserved?  To be continued. 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being as it is that I have a paucity of things to recount due to the mon otony  of my present ex ist ence (it is for such phrases that I chose the username  ironictragedian ), I shall instead muse idly, contemplate languidly, ponder quiescently, etcetera, while attempting to avoid zealous pontification. Sounds like a plan, no?  So, prepare, as the floodgates of my mind are cast wide and all they contain pours fourth...         Um.           So, girls!!?!?!?!   
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Test, testing, testudinate, testy, testes. 
    
</post>


</Blog>