<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I mean, really? This boggles my mind.  How do the democrats get away with claiming Bush connections to the swiftvets without everyone just laughing in their face for their own 527  urlLink connections .   “The Democratic Party is partnering with MoveOn.org, People for the American Way, Campaign for America's Future, and dozens of other groups representing millions of Americans to organize a massive public mobilization."  Read the link for more hilarity taken from the DNC's own websites.  And  urlLink here  is some perspective on some of the 527 group's money. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink Onion  points out yet another republican conspiracy.  This one being far worse than the swift boat veterans fiasco. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a new  urlLink study  from the  urlLink Employment Policies Institute  that makes the case against minimum wage.   In this study, Drs. Peter Arcidiacono and Thomas Ahn investigate claims of positive employment effects resulting from a minimum wage. The study first highlights the multitude of reasons why, under the classical economic model—the widely accepted model of economic behavior—an increase in the minimum wage cannot lead to an increase in employment. Then, by relaxing certain assumptions critical to the classical model, a search model is constructed. This model—which runs contrary to commonly accepted economic theory—is created to study a hypothetical situation of positive employment effects from a minimum wage increase? Even in this case, the authors show that those individuals who most value minimum wage jobs—current employees—end up with a higher probability of being unemployed after a minimum wage increase. In fact, all increases in the minimum wage under this model result in decreased employment prospects for individuals.  What a strange concept, that government telling businesses what to do is detrimental to the economy. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crap!  If you've never heard  urlLink Mastodon , go and buy all their albums immediately!  I just saw them tonight opening for Fear Factory along with two hardcore bands not worth mentioning.  They were the definite highlight of the show.  I'm not a huge Fear Factory fan but even so, they were very boring.  With Mastodon's performance though I'm now a hooked fan.  I'm not even really sure how to describe what Mastodon does musically.  Somewhere edging on grindcore but more melodic with incredible drumming.  Go listen to them!  I've been told that the upcoming album  Leviathan  is based on the classic book  Moby Dick . 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is Janet really stupid?  Or is  urlLink this  just a joke? 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read  urlLink this  now.
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First they announce that want  urlLink drilling  in Alaska, which even the democrats  urlLink support , and now they want to completely legalize  urlLink pot .  All this will probably have people all over the nation, except Alaska of course, screaming.  God forbid a state excercise their 10th amendment right. 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bloodbath -  Nightmares Made Flesh  = good  With Peter Tagtgren overtaking the role as the voice of satan from Mikael Akerfeldt, Bloodbath once again releases a must buy death metal album. Evil! 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Washington Post has a decent  urlLink article  that sums up much of the swift boat debate thus far. It introduces some things I haven't read or heard about yet. It points out the KFW initials on that after action report the SBVFT claim Kerry wrote up as well as introducing another veteran, Wayne D. Langhofer, who was there that claims there  was  hostile fire on that March 13 incident.   Finally, the debate is getting somewhere.  Which reminds me, I'm sick of the democrats quoting all these star citations about the event. The SBVFT have allready acknowledged they exist and argue that they were written up based on the supposed Kerry written report and therefore are inaccurate. At least the Washington Post challenges this argument which the democrats, if they had any intelligence, should already have done.  One thing about the article that bothers me greatly is that when they are stating the witness accounts diverge stuff, they fail to mention that Kerry's "No Man Left Behind" story where all the other boats fled and only Kerry stayed was complete bullshit. Why does the article not state that these SBVFT have proved Kerry wrong once already. This along with that searing -searing- made up "Christmas In Cambodia" memory makes me wonder what else has Kerry lied or exagerrated about.  Oh, and vote  urlLink libertarian .  edit: ick, I can't link to the washington post.  It simply goes to their subscribe page.  So I changed the link to the  urlLink drudge report .  You can find the link to the story there.  It's the "Both sides have withheld info..." link. 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I guess Ben and JP sent out our demo to some folks to listen to...   One liked it and one did not.   urlLink aversiononline    urlLink darksoul7   I would have hoped that aversion would have liked us better, I really respect his opinion, but alas, I suppose we just aren't up to par yet.   I should remind everyone that our entire demo  can be downloaded at our  urlLink website .  Even more impressive though, Ben's wife gave birth to twin girls,  urlLink Tori and Presley .  Congrats to him. 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been on a  urlLink sealab 2021  kick lately, which is where the url and the "rescue toaster" title come from...   Marco:   Could my pants at least have a boot cut?  I'll pay for it!. 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it looks as though I've just gone and created a blog. 
    
</post>


</Blog>