<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink NYPSU: August 2004 
     

    
</post>


<date>25,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey babes & Hunks!  Tmr's briefing for Camp Focus will be at 3.30pm, E308 for both facilitators and participants...Those who cannot make it due to classes and all, please come to this blog to get updates... Attendance will be taken hor!  
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Camp FOCUS experience    Yea~ I was a FOCUS camper too. LoL! This camp is so fun and exciting! I got to know so mani frenz from different clubs. Like wad Hui Ping said, the 5 of us were juz freshies at that time. Whereas, those participants' post were Excos or some high positions in their clubs. We felt small and insignificance to them. But, things doesn turn out that way. All of them are so friendly and approachable. During that 2 days 1 night camp, we spent lotsa interesting experience. So happy to know them as my frenz. Personally, I feel that by participating in this Camp FOCUS, not only widen your social circle, you will learn a lot of leadership skills from them too. I can never forget my secret pal - John Lai! I made him to kneel in front of me, so that I will tell him who his secret pal is. Well, acty that person is me. Hehe! That's bad! Luckily, he didn hold against me. keke! Another incident was I slapped Dennis. Erm... Who asked him to sae sth to Hui Ping. hehE! I didn mean it~ Well, thatz how I got to know those ppl. As a union member, it is critical to know other clubs members, and create a strong bonding. Coz in future u will need their help in organizing ani events.  Camp FOCUS is coming! Hope u guys will enjoy this camp! Spend it fruitfully with ur fellow grp mates! =D  Stupid Weiming didn participate Camp FOCUS last yr bec of his chalet... Left dbi 0304 gang to 3 ppl only (me, huiping and chiho). Last year camp, only the 3 of us, kelly and xiaoyun joined. pathetic sia~ But i'm glad that this year quite a lot of ppl join this camp. :P have fun! ^_~  
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Camp Focus - My Experience  I went Camp Focus last year as a camper too! It was so fun, I want to attend again! Initially, I was feeling damn bad, because it was supposed to be a camp for leaders, all the presidents, vice-presidents, captains, vice-captains, chairpersons, vice-chairpersons, executive committee members from all the various different CCAs. And why on earth did SU sent 5 freshies? So paiseh, I just kept quiet as much as I can. Presidents: They have formed a status in my mind that they are arrogant, proud, listens only to themselves (or at least, other people of the same status) and they will have a whole mind of great ideas to shine, not going to bother people like me. Oh boy I was wrong, these people were kind, nice, interesting, fun-loving and most of all, they took care of me as a freshie~! *smugs* Even till now, we still keep in contact!!! No doubt they were people of great ideas, decisions were made fast and perfect, I was so impressed by all the initiative taken by everybody regardless of doing labour work or thinking of the finale item! Guess how we came up with the secret pal game in Camp Ohana? CAMP FOCUS!!! So fun, our DBI OGL senior was Leehui's secret pal, and we went to ka jiao him. "We know your secret paL!!!!!" In the end, we even made him kneel down and beg us for the secret!! And when Leehui sae "Your secret pal is....... ME!!!!!" He turned all red and chased Leehui all around Blk E forum!!! Haha There was this prize-giving session at the end of camp, and the Care-Bear prize goes to....... .******** Mr. Wong Chi Ho!!!! for taking care and showing concern to people around him!!! WoOOooooOOoo!!!!!! Hahahhahahhaha (though I don't know what happened to the bear, and I have nv seen him showing care n concern for me n leehui b4... yea..... anyway..) woOoOOoOoOoOo!!! Carebear!!!! Mr. Carebear!!! He got teased by us for at least a month before we let him off last year. Hahaz~
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another pair of twins!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Twins!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sentosa~&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DND 04&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Urban Escape&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Seniors After Camp Ohana!~&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Freshies@Ohana~&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Camp Ohana 2004&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Freshies~&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Manz! So stupid that my leg still not recovered. bleahx! Camy!!! U die die muz find me an assistant, ok??? haha! An assistant who can run hor! erm... itz ok that if u cant find ani~ I'll go there n kpo kpo a dae will do. LoL!  Participants in camp focus! have fun!!! keke! =D
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Changes Yoyo, juz 2 days of launching and the response is tremendous!!! Yea!!! I got no choice but to increase the shoutbox to 50 lines and scrollbar, else the next time I come in, i won't know what's happening again~ Lolz.. Btw, Chiho's birthday is this Wednesday!!! *Excited* Anybody wants to help organize something? We are packed till Sat, maybe Sun is a good choice *holidays!!!*
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha...I am like using this blog as notice board! anyways, people who are involved in Camp Focus! listen up! There's a briefing this coming wednesday, 2pm at E308 for participants and 3.30pm for facilitators.  People invloved are...*drum rolls*...  Participants: -Ee Hui Min -Gladys -Damien -Shar -Xiu Xian -Kai Way -Felicia Goh -Ken -Lim Lian Jie -Eddie Poon -Weiming & Gerlynn (bwhahaa~!~!) -Mingwei & Estee (bwahhaa~!~!)  Facilitators: -Kelly -Hui Ping -Chi Ho -Christine -Lee Hui(stupid bai ka...i'm still trying to find something for you... but just come for briefing)  okie...above are the winners and u have won for yourselves one million dollars!! *lame* *burp*   Anything not sure, call me plz..and plus plus...plz help pass ard msg on this cos busy busy me these days! *muaxhs* 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There'll be an upcomin interview for the following position:  -Social Head -Assistant Social Head -Welfare Head -Assistant Welfare Head -Sports Head -Assistant Sports Head -Publication Head -Assisitant Publication Head  Interview will be conducted on the 2nd September 2004, starting 10am. Interested members, please e-mail Camy at camy_tsw@yahoo.com.sg the preferred time and position/s interested. Thanks! 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Instructions  Hey!! I might have missed out some names in the invitation list, if you have not received any invitation mail, let me noe!!!  1. If you do not have a blog, please sign up for an account now! 2. After you have signed up for an account, click on the link in the emaiL!!!!  Yea!!!! SU rocks!
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wOoHooO!!!  yea yea!!! so cool that nypsu blog has launched! hope that from this blog, all union members can voice out their opinions and thoughts. But plz!!! no insultations and scarstism is allowed. yuppie! have fun ppl~! =) 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yoyoyo~  Thought that a lot of SU members like to do blogging, we can combine and make a SU blog to strength our bonds!!! Anybody interested to help in designing this blog or maintaining, let me know ok!!! =) Cheers~
    
</post>


</Blog>