<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good day, all you bloggers out there! It is a fabulous Tuesday morning!! I really don't have much to say right now. It's almost break time and I'm venturing out of the corporate world for some Starbucks with Sarah. There is a tall cafe mocha with extra whip cream with my name written all over it! I hope everyone has a really great day!! I know I will...it's Tuesday..that means volleyball and dodgeball tonight!!!!  
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First I would like to thank my geeky boyfriend for pointing out my excellent spelling and grammer. I had a very good night sleep last night thanks to a great conversation I had with Matt. I just got to work and I'm already having a SUPER day just thinking about him! Tonight, I must visit Sue at the Rag Shop who will help me conduct my madness...I mean....help me start my costume! I must also go back to Michaels Craft store to pick up one more wooden block since I thought there were four in the bag when I bought it.....and came home to find there were only three. I can count as well as I can spell. Well I think someone just came in with some cookies and C is for cookie...it's good enough for me..cookie cookie cookie starts with C!!!! Have a great day everyone! and Matt I will keep you entertained via text message today, love your hot girlfriend!! xoxo
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First, I would like to thank my girl Brie for introducing me to blogging. Well this morning I started working on my Halloween costume. This year I will be Talim from Soul Calibur II. I also went car shopping with my parents....How exciting!!! My mother ordered a 2005 Toyota Solara convertible in red with black leather!!! I also went to my friend Beth's bridal shower. I have never been to one before so I didn't know what to expect....but I had sooo much fun!!! I can't wait to have a bridal shower of my own minus the hidious gifts. Tonight i'm going to see "Without a Paddle" with my friend Natanya. We are now in our new office at work and it's really nice to have my own cube to decorate. My coworkers decorated with flowers, animal pictures, and dumb quotes. My cube is full of anime, cartoons, and bamboo plants....I'm starting to see a Japanese theme. Which reminds me that the Japanese Bon festival at the Morikami museum is this weekend. Woo hoo!!!!!! This weekend better fly by really fast because I can't wait to see my boyfriend Matt Friday night......counting down the days......
    
</post>


</Blog>