<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tonight was a momentous night. Apologies to Kelly Holmes, but while she was achieving her dream of olympic gold my mind was elsewhere. At just about the same time my daughter Ellie took three teetering first steps and our house errupted in a state ot total euphoria. In the seconds following the great event Ellie lost her focus and tumbled towards the ground, only to be swept up in a bear hug and given another chance. We weren't disappointed that Ellie only managed three steps, or even that she fell. Her triumphant grin and clapping hands were enough to melt the coldest of hearts. I can't help but wonder if God ever feels the same way about me. Maybe sometimes I focus too much on the end result and not enough on the joy of having a God who is there when I throw myself on Him in an attempt to do something I could never do without Him. I think next time something doesn't go my way I might try to take a leaf out of Ellie's book. Perhaps I'll clap my hands, grin triumphantly and try again, realising that a little progress can be a pretty big deal. And to Kelly Holmes mother..... I think I know how you feel!!!  
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Adventures always start in the most unlikely ways. A random email from someone with the courage to think outside the box ( thanks Si!) has tempted me to dip my toes in the world of the weblog. I don't know where this will lead, if anywhere, but a chance to unjumble some of the thoughts racing round my head can only be a good thing! I think everyone reaches a point where they have to stop and say, is this really the life that God has mapped out for me or am I just imposing his hand on my own faltering steps down the expected path. It's not that I think I'm in the wrong place physically, I just think maybe I'm on the wrong level. I think the catalyst has been the birth of my daughter. Two big blue eyes watch every move I make with unnerving concentration, taking in the things other people may have glossed over in the past. Suddenly I realise that what I say may count for very little as, seeing everything, she's going to see the truth. Don't get me wrong, there are lots of positives, I'm just ready for more. I suppose I'm just looking for a way to let my mind spill on to the screen and see if what lands there starts to make some sense! 
    
</post>


</Blog>