<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From the novel's cover to its final page, the river is the metaphor that drives and unifies Gita Mehta's  A River Sutra . Given the meaning of Mehta's title (literally translated as 'a river thread'), this prominence of the river metahpor should come as no surprise. Yet Mehta's layered use of the river, on both the level of narrative construction and story, did surprise me. At several points in my reading I found myself frustrated with the novel's resistance to narrative closure. With the "close" of each "sub"- story, I found myself feeling unsatisfied since I still had questions and wanted to glimpse further into each narrator's story than the novel allowed. Further, I read the series of stories eagerly in hopes that their culmination would sketch a fuller picture of the central narrator, but again I was disappointed to find that I was no closer to knowing his life in total at the end than I was in the beginning. Mehta uses the methor of the river in at least two important ways. First, the Narmada River, in one way or another, is the inspiration, the source, or the culminating point of each story within the novel. Second, modeling the behavior of the river, each story flows into the next without allowing the reader a definitive beginning or end.  Like the central narrator in  A River Sutra , the reader is set "adrift in the strangeness of other people's lives" (Mehta 228). Arguably, each new story-teller who encounters the narrator offers a tale that has a beginning, middle, and end. However, the beginning, middle, and end that we are offered is only a snapshot within the larger frame of their lives. The monk's tale begins in "the suffocating heat of a sports stadium" on the day of his renunciation ceremony, and it ends with the formal close of that ceremony. Several flashbacks are used throughout the tale to add details about the monk's life, but there remains a sense in which we do not know, or have not been given access, to the whole story. After the monk has moved on, our narrator confesses: "I was so fascinated by his lavish renunciation ceremonies that I never asked him to explain his first words..." (Mehta 47). This seems to be a pattern that develops throughout the novel. After each story had ended, I found myself left with questions that the story had not answered in its immediate descriptions.  The tale which most unsettled my traditional narrative expectations of closure was the courtezan's tale. I found myself engrossed in the dramatic events of kidnapping, gunfire, and the narrator's discovery of a weapons stockpile. And while the tale technically offered a conclusion with the death of the daughter, I was left wondering how the narrator resolved the situation with the police. Could the daughter's recent suicide really be explained as a murder during pursuit? What were the police to make of the weapons the narrator found? Was he forced to lie to the police in order to keep the daughter's unsanctioned marriage a secret? Despite the conventions of beginning, middle, and end, the novel frustrated me as it refused to offer me a sense of closure--a sense of every detail resolved and every character at peace with the situation. In the teacher's story, I was stunned that the narrative concluded at the moment of climax. Like a film, the narrative seemed to fade to black with the screams of the blind child as his throat is being cut. What happened to his sister? How did the music teacher relay the news to her? Could she survive the news? And what of the music teacher? Tariq Mia tells us that he threw himself under a train in Calcutta, but that too seems to be a story in itself that needs to be told. Again and again, the novel delivers conclusions without closure.  The central narrator is equally mysterious in  A River Sutra . Mr. Chagla and the other employees at the rest house refer to the central narrator as "sahib." Though the term is not listed in the novel's glossary, I assume it is a title rather than a surname since it is not capitalized and since other characters in the other narrative are also referred to as "sahib." We know that "Little Brother" (as Tariq Mia refers to him) or sahib has retired from the bureaucratic world to live in the jungle and manage this rest home, and it is through sahib that we come in contact with each of the other various story-tellers; yet we never discover sahib's name, nor do we get his tale in its entirety. From his interactions and his few related memories, we get a vague sense of his frustration with the busy world of Bombay, but we do not get the concrete incidents that drove him from his previous life. Finally, the discovery that Naga Baba left his ascetic lifestyle to become Professor Shankar seems to have a deep impact upon the sahib, but we never know precisely why or to what end. In the first place, we are left wondering exactly what drove the ascetic to leave the wilderness and pursue archeology. In the second place, Naga Baba's transformation leaves sahib "wondering for the first time what [he] would do if [he] ever left the bungalow," but we do not know where this speculation takes him (Mehta 282). Does he in fact leave the bungalow and rejoin the busy world he missed? The reunion between Naga Baba and Uma is the most striking example of conclusion without closure. There seems to be an ending of some sort implied by their reunion, and they drive off into the darkness together, but what does this conclusion signify for the reader?  Appropriately, it is the river that offers the reader a sense of closure. While each story, like the river, is boundless and refuses to be finally ended, the river metaphor makes meaning of the endless narrative threads. Tariq Mia tells sahib that "such people are like water flowing through our lives, little brother. We learn something from the encounter, then they are gone. We never find them again" (Mehta 259). Putting a similar sentiment in more spiritual terms, Professor Shankar/ Naga Baba tells sahib, "If anything is sacred about this river, it is the individual experiences of the human beings who have lived here" (Mehta 267). Throughout the novel, "experiences" and "encounters" are all that we are given before the narrators "are gone" and "we never find them again." Like the force of the river, like life itself, closure (in a traditional narrative sense) is impossible. It seems to me that when we are offered an attempt at narrative closure, we can sigh with relief, feel at peace with the reading experience we have just had, and usually put the book back on the shelf. We are not troubled by loose ends to worry over. By continually denying any real sense of closure, I think that Mehta's novel more sincerely encourages personal reader reflection after the novel's conclusion. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>