<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You ever wonder if your dreams mean anything? I do. Well, actually I believe that do mean something, maybe not all of them, but definitely some. The other night I had a dream that I was pregnant. It was strange, I could feel this hard bump in my lower abdomen. In the dream I was excited, and then scared. In the dream, I went around telling everyone that I was finally going to have a child of my own. So what does that mean? I'm only 25, and I don't think I'm ready for kids yet, although I hope in the few years to start a family of my own. I think it means my biological clock is definitely ticking. My husband agrees with this - we are trying to plan as carefully as we can. Although I don't think anyone is truly ready for parenthood. A good friend of mine just found out she was pregnant. After about a week of battling whether or not to keep the baby, she has made the decision to keep it. She is not married, but does have a boyfriend (the father). She's older than I am, by a couple years. She asked me what I thought and I told her that I know of one couple that did not keep theirs, and that was the right decision. Then I said I know of another couple that did keep their baby girl, and their lives have been changed is such a great way, and they still are getting everything out of life that they ever wanted if not more. But as I once heard on the show "Sex in the City" Miranda is talking about a friend of theirs who got pregnant and her comment was "she's been lost to the MOTHERHOOD" - I thought it was a great comment actually. When you have friends that have kids and you don't - it just isn't the same anymore. You don't call them as much because then they have to find a babysitter. It's not just that, but my experience with new mothers is that they suddenly know everything because they have children. What's up with that? I can't stand that. I also went to a baby shower this weekend, and I hate baby showers. All anyone wants to do is talk about their kids, which is fine. But I don't have any! So I talk about my dog - she is my child. I guess it's a time in my life where some of us are crossing over into parenthood. I'm just not ready. My parents screwed me up enough, that I don't want to screw up another life - not until I can get my head on straight. My mother really wanted kids and so did my Dad, but when they divorced, it was like I was on my own and took care of my younger brother. I feel like his Mom sometimes more than just a sister, 'cause I helped raise him. No one was there for me when my parents divorced. My Dad left, and my Mom left emotionally. I'm just now straightening that mess out. And it was 14 years ago! I don't want my kids to ever experience that in any fashion or form. I don't want them to know what step-parents are. I want to be the best Mother I can be and for my husband to be the best Father he can be. But I do want kids, I think I was put on this earth for that reason, I truly believe in that. I have faith that my friend who is newly pregnant will be a great Mom, although I get the feeling she might be a single Mother. Dreams mean so much to me, and the other night I think it showed me that clock is ticking, but don't rush it. Then I was happy to wake up this morning to find my "little friend" had come for her monthly visit.  Pheww!  Another one to hang on "The Dreaming Tree"...  

						
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today I will not write a journal entry, but instead share one of my poems that I feel is appropriate at this time -   Us Once a perfect union Love has left it's residue It's not enough to survive Words crash into my heart Bleeding and weeping You are no longer sewed to my side The stitches have torn Out pours my love from a hole in my heart It has been leaking for some time now It burst through to the floor And I stand in my puddle of you This cold and empty feeling But yet a breath of freedom Like breathing for the first time I was drowning inside of you You were swallowing me and who I was Limb by limb, piece by piece I was becoming you Merged together but no longer We weren't us, we were you  

						
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Even though I already blogged once today, I thought I might try it again. The night gets later, and lonelier. That is one thing that sucks about military life are TDY's - or for you folks that don't know what that means - Temporary Duty. My husband is currently TDY to Korea, and having a blast, which I'm glad he is.  I was stationed there my first year in the military, and it was scary and lonely, yet once I got started to settle in I had a great time.  But it's weird sitting here all alone, I like some alone time.  I like to gather my thoughts, and think about everything and anything.   I think that maybe I think too much sometimes.  But it seems to happen more so at night.   When the rest of the world is settling down for the night, no more phone calls, no more emails, no one to talk too.  Here I am, all alone.  I think about my past, I think about decisions I've made.  I think about the future and how the unknown can be so scary, I also think about the present.  Gosh, I think way too much.  I've never been good at being alone, and I've never had to be alone.  I've only been TDY once in my career, and it was for 3 months, but it was close by so I came home on the weekends.  So it didn't count.  I'm scared of going away myself, I was active duty for the past 5 years.  I thought that I had enough and separated.  Then I went on my first civilian job interview, the man interviewing me completely made fun of my military background, he mocked me yet he still hired me.   I didn't take the job, I didn't want to work for this jerk.  So then I joined the reserves, about a week ago.  I feel more comfortable in my uniform, I have respect that I've worked hard for.  Yet the looming idea of being deployed is wavering in my mind.  Would I survive?  Not like survive and live, I mean could I actually enjoy it or at least make the best of it?  It scares me and worries me.  Yet I love what I do, and I love being a part of the U.S. Armed Forces.  I am more patriotic, I have more respect that served before me and with me.   It's weird how all of this changes, how I started out and didn't want to stay in the military, there was no way I was going to re-up for another 4 years.  Yet, when I walked away, I realized I had lost so much.  The people that I had worked with and worked for, I missed them (well at least most of them).  So here I am, a new member of the USAF Reserves, and excited that I made this decision, yet scared.  But isn't that what life is about, taking chances?  Reaching out?  Doing things you would never normally do?  I take chances in life, it's like I jump in with my eyes closed and figure the rest out later.   Sometimes it's great, other times it's not great.  I'm a dreamer, I do things on a whim, just like getting out, and then going back in.    So many questions that I ask myself over and over again, esepcially in this time of solitude..."Where are you going?"....  

						
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So here I am, I found this website actually a friend found this website, and I love to write and keep journals of my thoughts. So why not share them right? Where could I possibly begin? As someone who sees this might recognize the "Big Eyed Fish" title, it's because I'm a huge fan of Dave Matthews Band, and I am a Pisces, so I thought "lets combine those two and see what I could come up with"  I went out last night to a local bar - which is something I do probably once a weekend, have a few beers and hang out with friends. Not that I have a lot of friends, 'cause I don't. Well not girlfriends - us women can be so moody and judgemental that it's hard to actually have a friendship with another female. I've never been the type to have a whole gaggle of friends.  What women talk about at the bar or club, we talk a lot about guys.  We talk about our womanly issues.  We gossip, we love to gossip.  We talk about love, and lost love, and confused love.  One of my friends is involved with a man that treats her like dirt, yet she still stays with him.  But as women we all need to have our bad boys.  I've had mine, married him the first time.  Then divorced him.  Now I've married that good guy, the one that brings steady, unfaltering love, and security.  But how that bad boy sticks out in every girls mind, the one that treated you like dirt, yet was exciting and fun.  I have another friend that is married, yet still thinks about the unsteady jerk that she used to be involved with.  It's strange, love is strange.  How you can love not just one person, but it might 2 or 3 or even 4 or 5.  Yet you're not in love with them anymore.  This is the drama that us girls talk about when we go out to the bar.  To a guy this may seem boring, but to any girls that I know - it's a way to figure things in the world.  A little girl talk is always the remedy toward any lovesickness.  I try not to preach to my friends that have horrid boyfriends, but sometimes you just can't help it and end up saying "An' Another Thing...  

						
</post>


</Blog>