<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, I hit the streets today in search of a job.  I would like some cash flow, seeing that I spend alot I should provide my own means of income.  Had all my classes today, my english teacher looked over my transcript and said I might be able to Graduate by January.  Hmm...I guess I have to burden myself with work and school.  I don't mind, I need to do something someday for whatever reason right?  Of course.  Met some..."interesting" people today during lunch, feels better to not be a social outcast now.  Well, less so at least.  I'm currently getting a set ready for my new clay movie, but I need R.T. *Lindsey* to help me with a script.  Quite frankly I don't beleive I will be able to commit much time to the upcoming ones with school and possibly a job, but don't be concerned, it'll be great, but it'll take longer.                                                                       -Hush 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello all,                    Hush has dug himself into a mighty big hole.  Oh well, today I left around 6:50 to catch the bus to my new school, woo indeed.  I waited there and I almost thought I was in the wrong spot, but around 7:10 people started to show up, I got on the bus and blah blah blah, then at like the third stop some teens with their kids got on the bus, I really didn't know what to make of this, seeing as they didn't have those at Aragon.  The commute from San Mateo to San Bruno is about an hour long, makes for some good cd listenin to time.  I got off the bus and went to the registration tables.  The sign behind it said  new students, please report the to the library,  you always gotta do what a sign tells you to do right?  slowly the room started to fill up with people, i prefered sitting alone in my little corner, but was joined by some thuggish mexicans,  good thing i knew some of them or I would have been rather uncomfortable.  Well we did the normal "ok we're gonna go around the room and you're gonna say your name and what school you came from and then a goal"  Well I said my info, *name withheld*, from Aragon and I wanna be a mechanic.  Not that anyone was listening of course, I could have very well said screw you all, I come from downtown and I wanna be a porn star.  You know that feeling where if you look at someone for a second it seems the turn their head the other way? Like if they were just looking at you?  I got that for the longest time today, more on that later.  We went on break and I talked to Kim and Patrick for awhile, so far they seem to be the only people I can hang out with at the moment.  Kim is a cutie, and Patrick is...well...a big big idiot, but thats fine.  Both can be a little anoyying and immature at times, but I can't make a big deal out of that cause hey, I do that alot as well.  So we got back in and we do this thing where, if we agree with the statement we have to move to either side of the library, I feel like I'm being watched again and I look out the corner of my eye and this beautiful girl says hi and waves at me,  for some reason I thought to ignore it, i bet she was waving at the guy next to me, oh how wrong I was.  The lunch bell sounds and Kim wants to get something to eat so I lend her a couple bucks and she gives me a chain that I wear around my right arm now, standin in line still at this moment and that girl comes up to me and says Hey Nick *oh yeah, my name's Nick* Gee, I guess someone was listening to who I was and what I wanted to be.  So by the time I turned around I was dumb struck in awe.  I beleive I said "uhh...Hello there..." and she asked if I remembered her.  I dont remember my own name at this point and she asks if I know her? Outlandish.  She says she went to school with me at McKinley and her name is Amber, now I start regaining sense of my limbs and I say "Amber...Puh?" and she bursts out Press.  Shit damn, I know her.  I had a major crush on her back in 4th grade, and now she is in super model status, I cannot beleive she spoke to me.  Absolutely stunning....more over, she re-introduced me to Tanisha, I haven't seen them since 4th grade.  Its amazing what time can do to people, it hit everyone but me of course, everything skips me.  Everything after that point is dull, school gets out at 1:20, busses show up around 1:25, and I get off the bus at 2:11.  I talked to everyone about how Aragon was, some people were shocked that I don't go there anymore, and some just forgot (IE: David).  More or less, I might become something one day now that I can get some credits and a job.  At the current time I like someone, no one YOU would know, but sadly, the feeling is never returned, or even a hint of it.  This isn't good cause I am semi-dating someone now.  I really wish I knew what to do...grrr.  Well I'm off to go create more lovely creations...you know...the clay toon type.  See ya.                                                                                        -Hush 
    
</post>


</Blog>