<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so for those of you who know me you will all know that I have bad luck.  You will also know that I love to vent a lot, which is why I started this thing in the first place.  As I said in my previous post, my mom thinks I'm 'bitter.' In a sense she's right. Reason why? Well I'll tell you.  In grade 10 right near the end of the year I started getting picked on. Why? To this day, I still can't answer that one. I will probably never know. All I can say is I was at the wrong place at the wrong time.  My friend had some girls after her and they saw me hanging out with her one day at school, so they started picking on me whenever they saw me. Pushing me into lockers, tripping me in the hall, threatening to kill me and jumping me anytime they wanted. As far as they were concerned, I was on their property and they owned everything. Oh and they also thought I had an attitude problem. Right.  Actually, at first it was all intimidation. They thought they could scare me and they did. I had never been so paranoid in my life. Constantly looking over my shoulders while walking to class, not wanting to go to a certain part of the school in fear that they would be there. It was driving my 'friends' nuts.  But one day they went further then calling me on. One of them actually hit me. The beginning of grade 11 during lunch, 3 of them kept following me and my friends around everywhere we went. One of them even tried spitting on me. So when the bell rang to go to class, I was at my locker with 2 friends when Veronica (probably one of the strongest of the bunch) came up to me and just punched me right in the face. I stood there absolutely shocked and terrified. I ran to my best friend who was in class, pulled her out and I just lost it. She took me to the office and soon my parents came and we went down to the Police Station. Fuckin' police, such a waste of time cuz they are USELESS! But the good thing was they got it on tape so she was suspended for 10 days. Big mistake. They came after me even more. Thats when they told me if I told anyone what they were doing to me, they would kill me- and I believed it. Skip to one year and many beatings later, I was in grade 12 and they were no longer in the school. I confided in a teacher and because of him he had them thrown out for good. But even then it didn't stop. Anytime they saw me out of school they would do anything they could think of to me. So it got to the point where I couldn't even go out of my own house. My mom was a emotional wreck. My dad...well he was very murderous, and me....well I became a hermit. High School was suppose to be the greatest years of your teenage life, well mine was absolute hell. My grades slipped, I lost friends, I had no confidence at all and I became depressed. To this day whenever they see me they still have to say something. They always will. And I guess I will be bitter for a loooong long time. I would love nothing more then to get revenge on them, but the way I see it is in 5-10 years from now they will be rotting in hell with their abusive boyfriends on welfare with their 5 kids. Nice life? I thought so too.  Anyways, this is getting pretty long so I'm gonna jet.  Bubye!  -Mel 
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since everyone I know has their own blog, I thought I would start one of my own.  Soo where do I begin? Probably the beginning. OKAY!  Well I'm a 17 year old girl from Saskatchewan, Canada and I am anything but ordinary. That's right,  I am what they call "unique."  Anyways moving on...I live with my parents and my two younger sisters. I have a Shih Tzu named China, and a Ragdoll cat named Jinx who are my babies! Well...my dog is, the cat doesn't really like me. Hmm and I still don't know why.  So that pretty much sums up my life.  Exciting isn't it? .....Didn't think so.  I've lived in this town all my life and trust me it's nothing special. Lets see...you got your preps, over populated blonde cheerleaders, gangs, goths and pretty much anything you'd find in a small town. Moreso gangs then anything but we won't go there.  So what did I do today? Well I got up around 3pm and did my daily routine. Checked my email, ate some breakfast...er lunch, exercised, then watched WWE RAW. Yes that's right, I'm a WWE fan. And damn proud. In fact, I want to be a wrestler. Which is why I'm moving to Alberta sometime next year and hopefully train. My parents are against it, but hey what can ya do? They want me to be a Nurse or a Social Worker. My mom actually told me she thinks I want to wrestle because I'm 'bitter.'  That's another story for another time. So in closing, thanks for reading and I'll catchya later.  -Mel 
    
</post>


</Blog>