<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    here's adriane and i at freshman homecoming...ill try to put a newer pic of us when i get one lol  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    thats me sleeping at the top of mt si. in the background is the town of north bend  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    theres me climbing down from the top of mt. si. if u dont kno mt si its this really big hill with some rock at the top.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    dude check out this tree!!!! its flippy 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is malakwa lake. i hiked here with my bro, my dad, and karma 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok well i've figured something out.  i got a pic into my profile, which is alot harder than it looks, at least for me.  so like it!  anyways, i decided i wanna use my newfound skill to picturify my blog!  ill post a few kool pix.  or maybe not so kool. anyway yea  doby 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm...im still a bit confused about this thing, but im bored and i saw my sister emily's.  her's is really cool, you can check it out at  urlLink http://emilyscraziness.blogspot.com .  if u kno her there you go and if u dont, then well maybe u will now.  shes just a really good artist and theres lots of drawings and photography by her on that blog.  heh, maybe i can put star man on one of these.  cuz yea that'd be kool...(jk)  is this sposed to be one of those public journal things like all u guys's xangas?  cuz if so i must say this was SO much easier to do.  sorry, but thats just the way it is.  um...lets see this week i have a dentist appointment, and wolverine walk registration thing.  i really forgot what time im sposed to be there, but o well.  its amazing that this summer has gone by so fast.  camp, camp, mexico, spokane, school. wow. tomorrow i have soccer so that is good.  our new uniforms are ok, but the shorts are now too small around and although longer still not long enough.  the jerseys are also very small around and its my *shoulders* that dont fit easily not my stomach so dont say it lol.  i am out of shape tho, VERY out of shape, so i'm glad to get to practice and work on it.  everyone will be runnin circles around me (more than usual) for a while but o well. i guess its my fault anyway. ok, well i've gotten to the point where i'm just rambling.  i'll try to actually stick w/ this thing.  later guys. doby 
    
</post>


</Blog>