<Blog>


<date>25,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        He never saw it coming And look where he is now A broken mess of tears and guilt He knows it’s not his fault, but somehow He blames himself For every little thing He cries for her But he doesn’t know what he’s done to me The pain will come and go But some things will never mend He’ll move on to someone new Though it will never be the same again {Chorus} He’s crying inside He’s dying inside He’s such a disaster— Such a beautiful disaster I was never quite sure If I felt as bad as I’d let on I told him I would be there But I might have let him fall Wasn’t I obvious? Didn’t he even have a clue? The pain that he’s feeling now Was the same pain he’d put me through {Chorus} And he’s crying inside He’s dying inside He’s such a disaster— Such a beautiful disaster {Bridge} He’s so broken within Misery has taken him And he’s so beautiful… {Chorus} He’s crying inside He’s dying inside He’s such a disaster Such a beautiful disaster He’s crying inside He’s dying inside He’s such a disaster Such a beautiful disaster      
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This may be a bit of a rush; after all, this is my first blog, but feelings are feelings, no? So I'm going to post them here. The subject: Boys. Now, if you knew me, you would know that the phrase "I'm confused!" is practically my trademark. You would hear it in my math class, when trying to open my locker, chemistry, during dance practice, or following any sort of explicit instruction at least three times. But this is a different kind of confusion. This confusion runs deep. I don't think there is a girl out there who understands what goes on in boys' minds (excluding males-gone-female...sex change, yes; psychological change, no). And sure, the guys are all, " We  are not difficult to understand! Yada, yada, blah, blah." You honestly think that you have that simple mind, do you? Well, you do in a sense. You rarely having more than three things on your minds at all times, and are slightly retarded (natural male birth defect), but that does not make you any easier to understand. Oh, how can a person like me even explain all of the confusing, messed up things that go on in that puny mind? I’m sure it makes sense to the one thinking it, just like this paragraph of horrible grammar and proper-English-deficiency makes sense to me. Ok, ok, ok. What is this all winding down to. If you were any of my past English teachers you would be red-pen-ing my paper in a mad fashion, scribbling "Where is the structure? The flow? WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME!" in the margins. So, let met just give it to you plain and simple: girls take things literally, guys. We don't liked to be played around with. If your intentions with a girl go only as far as friendship, don't make her feel special. Treat her like everyone else. Otherwise, she gets the wrong message and ends up writing down strange things in her blog that don't even make sense. It's just not fair. So watch where you're leading her, or she might end up speaking her mind about you on the internet for all eyes to see if they wish. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>