<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            It has been said the most important date on our headstone is the dash in between our birth and our death. We seldom take time to reflect on where we have been. We get so caught up in accomplishing goals and regretting those not met. We lose focus on the smaller things. We forget how to stroll through the park or gaze at the stars. We leave the simple pleasures of life to those who get paid to do it. We say our family is our biggest concern. Yet how often do we sit down to dinner together? How many phone calls do we make home to say we have to work late? Do we still get on our knees for bedtime prayer? Or do we rush through the memorized lines because the news is on or we need to prepare for tomorrow? We all have to provide for our families but do we give any more than financial support? How many of us can look back into our childhood and say our family always spent at least one night with no distractions?    For those of us still single and those of us single parents, we dream of love. We sit and watch all the happy couples wishing one day that might be us. But so many times we are seeking the idea of love. We want that Brady Bunch happy family. Or we want that Dharma and Greg opposite attraction. We read the how to books and wish upon falling stars. But if we took some time to reflect we could see that the work is not yet finished. We have to evaluate our past to see if we have done the same things. We have to be the person we are meant to be instead of trying to be what everyone else wants. When we are happy with us then and only then can someone else be happy with us too.    So many of us are caught up in our regrets. How we should have done things differently. Why did it go wrong? We focus so much on "if only". But regret is only a poor excuse for "I learned nothing." If we can look at our life and see the bad experiences as a lesson or a tool to go farther next time then we should have no regrets. The all time question is "If you could change anything in your past, what would it be?" My question is "Why change anything at all?" Everything in our past right down to the day we fell off the swing into the mud made us the person we are today. If you change that minor thing every other event would be altered. We must learn to accept our past, learn from it, and move on. Could have, would have, should have only leaves an empty "what if".     Final thoughts....    How do we each live our lives? Have we taken time to reflect today? Take 10 minutes to say "thank you" and look and at your life. CAN TOMORROW BE BETTER???     
</post>


</Blog>