<Blog>


<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Seems like I've managed to develop asthma at the grand old age of 32. I failed a lung function test quite spectacularly yesterday and now have an inhaler and an appointment to see the doctor in three weeks. In other news...my mobile is buggering around (or is it Yahoo's wap site?) and my phone locks up and switches off when I thy and access my emails. So it's probably not worth anyone emailing of over the next couple of weeks. And we are setting of for hols in Cromer very soon! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It worked! Wow. Here's the link... urlLink Wapblogger    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Guess what? I'm doing this entry from my mobile! Just going to test it works and them will post the link. This is cool! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       U read my blog and has corrected me on the information I posted about Nigel Powell's former band .... I'll try and get my facts right in future!    So, just to clear up any confusion ...   "The Unbelievable Truth (an early nineties band that U was very keen  on, he ran the official website and followed them all over the place."   WRONG!!!  They dropped the definitive article after their debut single (Building,  Shifty Disco Feb '97). So Unbelievable Truth were a  late  90s band. U had his own  un official website - Nigel did the official one! And U  only  saw them 22 times between 1st April 1998 (Chelmsford) and  Sept 16th September 2000 (Oxford)...!!!  Happy now?! :0)   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       People make me so mad sometimes. What should have been a good night out in Winchester turned into a bit of a disappointment because people have no damn respect.  There were four acts on at the pub we went to. The first, a young kid (well, about 17ish) called Dan, was pretty good, just a singer-songwriter with a guitar and he had a sweet voice. The pub was fairly empty when we arrived, but it fuilled up quickly - we grabbed the last two chairs and soon after the floor was littered with bodies. The second band, Geko, weren't bad - girl singer (slightly flat at times but otherwise okay), two guitars and drums - main problem was that the drums were far too loud and drowned everyone else out. Then the third band - Kung Fu Phinga Pik and the Lovestik - took to the stage and it became obvious that they were local and just about everyone there was there to support them - which was fine, because there was a very lively atmosphere. Shame their music didn't really do it justice. Some of the songs were okay, but they had a go at doing some strange Streets-esque acoustic rap that just didn't really come off, not least because the rapper rapped far too quickly. I think the lyrics were meant to be amusing but I could only catch the odd word here and there. U and I weren't too fussed about the music, and spent the evening messing around with the candles on the table, dipping our fingers in the hot wax and creating molten wax structures! So the music wasn't to our taste, but we respected the musicians, kept quiet while they performed and clapped politely.  Then came U's friend, Nigel, of the  urlLink Sad Song Co . As soon as the previous band left the stage and he stood up there was a mass exodus from the pub - not because of him, but because they had obviously come to support the others and weren't going to stay. Unfortunately, not everyone left - because those that did stay talked and shrieked and laughed and generally drowned out poor Nigel and his bass player (Jason). We were sitting right near the front and it was a struggle to hear what he was singing - he kept asking for the mics to be turned up but the louder he was, the louder the idiots in the pub got. You could see he was getting really pissed off by now, and he said something along the lines of "Ah well, I'll just plough through the set list, I don't care." From what I could hear he was really good, far better than the previous three acts, but the kids in the pub (all fairly pissed and probably celebrating/commiserating A level results, but that's no excuse) just carried on making a dreadful noise. There were a groups of maybe a dozen people actually listening, and at the end Nigel said "Thank you (pointing at individuals) you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, erm, you, you and you ....  and [two fingers] to the rest of you." Not a happy chappy, and justifiably so.  Anyway, we came away feeling fairly cheesed off with it all. We'd only gone to Winchester because we can't make his gig in Oxford tonight, we'd tolerated the second rate support acts and then hadn't been allowed to enjoy the headline band. Very annoying. Well done Nigel for doing your best under very difficult circumstances, and thank you very bloody much you idiots who ruined the evening.  Anyway, U bought the Sad Song Co cd so at least we'll be able to hear what he's like in peace and quiet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I have to say I am totally cheesed off with what's going on at Chelsea. And this entry will probably turn into a complete rant.  NEWS JUST IN ....  " Real Madrid have announced they are starting disciplinary proceedings against Claude Makelele following the French midfielder's refusal to train with the team on Wednesday.  The 30-year-old's decision came amidst reports of a transfer swoop by big-spending Premiership side Chelsea.  Makelele's agent Marc Roger reportedly presented Madrid with a £7million offer for the midfielder from the Blues on Wednesday morning. "  FOOTBALL365    So now we're after ANOTHER player ... and yet another midfielder? What the hell is going on at Chelsea? Last season we came fourth, we were far more consistent than we have been for years, we pulled off some great results against the top teams and (with the exception of West Ham) managed to see off the minnows as well. And we didn't spend anything during the previous summer, it was all due to the development of the team, to letting the players stick together and get used to each other and actually work AS A TEAM rather than as a group of over-paid superstars.  It was a good season, a season all Chelsea supporters could be proud of, and one that showed we could be optimistic about times to come.  And then Roman bloody Abromovitch whatever the hell his name is came along and it's all gone crazy.   Now every season you have to buy a couple of players. And with Zola gone back to Italy (sad but predictable) and Ferrer retired, we did need to make a couple of purchases to fill the gaps. But Abromovitch is just flashing the cash, as far as I am concerned. It seems like he's got the money and he wants everyone to know it, so he's buying every available player just to make the point. Yet there doesn't seem to be a great deal of thought going in to who he actually signs.  We've ended up with about four new midfielders, plus the four or so that we already had . So who on earth is going to play? Do we stick Cole (a good signing, I grant you) and Lampard in the middle because they know each other so well already? But then what do we do with Veron (over rated, IMHO), and Duff (another valid acquisition) and Petit and Gronkjaer and Stanic and Zenden? They are all top quality international players - none of them are going to be happy sitting on the bench or playing for the reserves at Aldershot.  Then of course there are the defenders ... we now have players of the calibre of Bridge and Geremi, plus West Ham's Johnson. But what was wrong with the pairing of Terry and Desailly, with Melchiot/Gallas/Babayaro on the wings? Sure, we need a couple of spares in case of injuries, but it's going to be a nightmare for Ravioli to choose the best team AND keep everyone happy.  And at the same time we're relying solely on the fantastic Cudicini (best keeper in the league) to hold the fort in goal ... two new keepers bought, but one is out injured for the whole season and the other is, by all accounts, even worse than Bosnich. Hmm. And up front, the "pick two from three" combination of Hasselbaink/Gudjohnnsen/Forsell looks strong till one of them is injured, but what then? The signing of Mutu will take the pressure off there, if it goes through, but it seems that money has been spent in areas that don't really need it.  We'll see ... my main concern is that with so many new faces it's going to take a long time for any team to gel ... and to keep all the players happy there's going to have to be some regular rotation which is going to make it even harder. Abromovitch has made no promises, at least he knows the problems, but at the same time the fans are going to be baying for instant success as usual.  As far as I'm concerned, any victories we do achieve are going to have been bought rather than earned, and that bothers me. I'd be far happier if we'd bought a player here and there and then built on the sound foundations we developed last season ... success this year is going to have a hollow ring to it for me. I won't go so far as to say I'd like to see Chelsea fail (well, actually, I have said that to a couple of people), but the display of money in the club now is, frankly, morally offensive, and I'm not having fun being a Chelsea Girl at the moment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Last night we went to Northampton Soundhaus to see  urlLink Snow Patrol , who really rocked. A friend of U's had got the tickets and is a big fan, but up till then I'd never heard of them. Bel thought she had, and said she thought they were an ambient dancy type group; U said they were like Gomez; U's friend described them as " '...a triumph of powerful ballads, pop, and the skewered [skewered?!] lo-fi' [according to  urlLink  this  Drowned in Sound article]. I predict that a) Chelsea Girl will like them, and b) I will be disappointed because my expectations are too high."   And I did, and he wasn't.  For the first two or three tracks I wasn't impressed - they didn't seem anything special, and there are so many guitar indie rock groups around at the mo. But I quickly warmed to them and was bouncy along by the end. Their new (third) album  The Final Straw  is out now and there are some samples on their website … definitely one to watch. They were supported by  urlLink  Terra Diablo  and Teer - both not bad but nothing to get excited about.  Tonight we are off to Winchester to see  urlLink  The Sad Song Company . This is a solo project by Nigel Powell, who was in The Unbelievable Truth (an early nineties band that U was very keen on, he ran the official website and followed them all over the place. The singer was Andy Yorke, younger brother of a certain Thom "Radiohead" Yorke, both of whom U went to school with) and is the drummer with  urlLink Dive Dive , who I've seen a couple of times and they are really great. I've no idea what his solo stuff is like, but apparently the songs reflect the name of the project and are rather sad. Will let you know!  We're staying at my place tonight so I can top up the cat's food and water, and hopefully find her alive and well. I've had all sorts of problems getting her to use the catflaps because she is just terrified of them, especially of the noise they make when they open. I left them propped up, one on a wellie boot and one on a wine bottle, and she did actually go through both of them into the garden before I came over here. I'm just hoping that she hasn't knocked over the supports and got stuck in the bit between the two doors - our "conservatory" - because it gets so hot out there. I really don't want to go home to find a mummified moggy!  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Starting to panic a bit .. I spent a couple of hours on Saturday fitting catflaps so that the cat can gome and go as she pleases when we are on holiday, but she is terrified of the things and won't go near them. So being the geek that I am, I started searching the Internet for advice and came across this urlLink catflap story , which didn't help me out of my predicament at all but did make me laugh. But then I realised which site this story was on ...  urlLink John Mark Ministries - Assisting churches, pastors, leaders and their spouses  ...WHY???:? Is this kind of thing recommended to vicars to use in their sermons? Now, I haven't been to church for a long long time, but if the sermons now are about things like this:   "After a few hours, a group of students approached me but, instead of helping, they removed my trousers and pants, painted my buttocks bright blue, and stuck a daffodil between my cheeks... No one tried to free me. In fact, I only got free after two days because a dog started licking my private parts and an old woman complained to the police."  ... then I might just go along! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just updated the website ... reading through it I've realised that it's a load of rubbish anyway, but have decided to leave it up there, I've just changed a few odds and sods that were inaccurate. Ought to completely redo it really but I just can't be bothered! 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Still working on the site ... you'll be able to leave comments soon, hopefully :0) 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Craze of the week in our house is  urlLink BookCrossing . Basically it's a way of sharing your books with others and tracking where they go. You read a book, register and review it on the site and get a special ID number and URL for it. Then you either pass it on to a friend or leave it somewhere ... on a bus, in a cafe, on a park bench, anywhere really ... for someone to find, in the hope that they will follow the link and register that they've found it. Apparently only about 30% of the books resurface on the site, which seems a shame, but surely the more people that know about Bookcrossing, the better!  My only problem with the site is that I love all my books, even the ones I hate or have never read, and I'm reluctant to part with them. So the answer is to buy cheap duplicates in the charity shops and use them! Then you're helping others in two ways.  I left my first book in Stoke Park, Guildford this week and have a couple more to release next week ... it gave me a bit of a buzz, sad but true! Anyway, fingers crossed I'll get lucky and someone will give my books a good home! 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Owing to various technical hitches I've managed to screw up my old blog  urlLink Blue is the Colour . Bugger, So I've decided to start from scratch, and include the remnants of my old website (all fiendishly out of date and will be changed when I get round to it!) and some new things (well, what I'm reading and listening to and a couple of links) and I promise I'll try and update this ... but then, I always do say that. *sigh* We'll see! 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Here we go again ... 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My new favourite superhero!!! I can't wait till I get clamped in the station car park now ;0)   urlLink Angle-Grinder Man  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dan has decided he'd quite like his favourite clown Crazy M to do the entertainment at his birthday party next month, so I did some investigation on the internet. Turns out she and her "silly" boyfriend (her words, not mine!) got married recently ... he's a clown too ... ever been to a clown wedding? The photos are well worth seeing!   urlLink Crazy M's wedding pics   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Thanks to  Ulen  for alerting me to a rare BBC website typo.   urlLink BBC NEWS | Entertainment | TV and Radio | Police watch on Blaine-baiters :   "Some local residents have complained about traffic coming to a standstill on Tower Bridge as motorists slow down to look at the stunt." 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       U and I are planning a very adult weekend away soon ...  this place  on Hayling Island is looking the favourite at the mo, because we can shag to our hearts content and have a jacuzzi!!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Stansfield Times : "THE place for all the Stansfield family news. If you've got something to say, an announcement to make, a link to post or just want a moan, do it here! Any family member can post on this blog ...  My latest project. At a family gathering at the weekend I mentioned that it would be good to have a website where we could all post family news and gossip - because even though we don't often get together I'd consider us to be quite a close family.  "Ooh, what a good idea, are you offering to set it up?" someone said. And so I did ... well, it got me out of doing any house work on Sunday! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       How come kids have all the fun? The kids are having a great time at  urlLink Playzone  and I'm sitting here bored out of my skull, not even able to read because the kids are so noisy. Roll on Monday when they are back at school. Mind you, I have found out that they have adult-only sessions here...now I wonder if I'd be brave enough to in down that big slide... ? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Sitting in Starbucks in the retail outlet in Swindon, having had a row in Clarks about which shoes my son will permit himself to year for school. He hates all of them, apparently, so on doubt there'll be more rows next week when I try and make him wear the ones I've chosen. I have shopping, how on earth people become shopaholics I'll never know, my head hurts. Can you tell how happy I am? Bag humbug grumble groan  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Typical. I spend hours (well, minutes) putting together some sort of nonsense for this meaningless blog in the hope that millions across the world will rush over to read my nonsense, to no avail ... and then we check out an ancient website that Katie created last year, that we haven't even thought about for months, to discover that she has had over SIX THOUSAND hits and has 564 messages waiting in her guest book!   We're presuming that she must have been selected as Page of the month or something, going by what some of the messages say, but isn't listed in the site's winners list ... and her page was registered at an old email address of mine that doesn't function any more, so we'll never know. Boo!   urlLink Katie's World!    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       "alison is an enthusiastic alison is seriously pissed off and needs cheering up alison is in demand as a jazz vocalist and performs extensively at music venues throughout the chicagoland area alison is a natural choice for this honor alison is smug alison is a partner in an airline freight business alison is fresh alison is literally one of utah's finest treasures alison is responsible for building and maintaining alliances with a wide variety of community organisations and groups alison is passionate about teaching people to live more fulfilled alison is tall and slim alison is one of the greatest voices in bluegrass"   urlLink Googlism  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like Nigel Powell felt pretty much the same about his gig in Winchester as U and I did .. but in more explcit terms!  urlLink The Sad Song Co.  It really bugs me when people have no respect for others ... just have to hope I never attend a gig like this again. Some varied gigs coming up in the next couple of months ... well, a few, anyway. Elbow in Bristol at the end of September, Mogwai in October and iron maiden (yes, you did read that correctly!) in December! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       There seem to be a fair few of us around ...  urlLink Google Search: chelsea girl  ... but I'm at the top! Woohoo!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Dave Gahan .. Legend! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not sure why it is that I'm not surprised that the majority of competitors to the  urlLink World Beard and Moustache Championships Carson City 2003  are German .... the photograph evidence is amusing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Most of the last few weeks have been taken up with recording and editing material for a college assignment - a 15 minute documentary on  urlLink BookCrossing.Com . Well, it's almost finished, and a member of the  urlLink  UK Yahoo BookCrossing Group  has very kindly put it online for me. It's quite a big download - 7.5MB or 14MB depending on which quality you choose - but I'd love to hear what you think of it!   urlLink BookCrossing Documentary   Oh, BTW, if you decide to join as a result of listening, can you stick chelseagirl or hey-miki down as your referrers! Thank you! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Guess what everyone will be getting for Xmas this year .... ah, come on, I'm a poverty stricken student!   urlLink Glass Marble Magnets  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm hoping you will join me by going to  urlLink Our World, Our Say  now to sign a petition calling for a FULL independent, judicial, public inquiry into whether parliament and the British people were misled about the threat from Iraq.  The Hutton Inquiry is limited to just a small area of the conflict. It is absolutely scandalous that an illegal war, which has caused loss of life and immense misery along with making Britain one of the most hated nations on Earth, has been justified on the basis of half-truths and deception.  On September 24, 2002 Tony Blair stated: 'His (Saddam's) WMD programme is active, detailed and growing. The policy of containment is not working. The WMD programme is not shut down. It is up and running'.  Tony Blair described the intelligence upon which his assertion was based as: 'extensive, detailed and authoritative'.   The dossier which he was quoting from went on to say: 'Some of these weapons are deployable within 45 minutes of an order to use them'.  The whole war was fought on the basis that Iraq posed an immediate threat. We were told when war started that Iraq had deployed chemical and biological weapons to use against British and US forces. No such deployment took place. A whole series of allegations were made in the build up to war and throughout the war that have been shown to be at best inaccurate and at worst blatant lies. To date, no weapons of mass destruction have been found.  Sign the petition to Tony Blair now at  urlLink Our World, Our Say  and get all your friends and colleagues to do the same.                           This is part of a major new Our World Our Say campaign to ensure that politicians are made accountable to us for their actions.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Take a look at urlLink Welcome to Ugly Christmas Lights.com! if you want to be put off your Xmas dinner ... mind you, they don't even compare to some of the appalling attempts at "festivity" around here. i did vaguely consider setting up a sight featuing manky lights, but obviously someone beat me to it :0(  Anyway, have a wonderufl Xmas and a fab new year! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Make sure you try this ... type "miserable failure" (without the quotes) into Google and hit the "I'm feeling lucky" button .... 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you're ever tempted to go and see a band called I, Ludicrous, don't bother!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Best band in the world at the moment, IMHO. Up till August last year I'd never even heard of Snow Patrol, but then I went along to a gig in Northampton with Ulen and his friend. Started off thinking they were okay, nothing special, just another guitar band but as the evening wore on they just captivated me. Since then we've seen them three more times (Reading fez Club, Oxford Zodiac and Reading Uni), I've bought the albums and the Run single (no.5!!!), got two tshirts, won a signed album and am going to see them again next month. I suppose you could say I'm just slightly Snow patrol-obsessed!  Anyway, check out the band at the  urlLink Snow Patrol Official Website , buy the album and discovoer what's so good about them for yourselves. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Apologies for the absence, I've been far too busy being obsessed with weddings! I've finally managed to get the blogger tool to work in Opera (my usual browser) so expect much more regular updates from now on!   urlLink This site  is well worth a visit. It's by a Russian woman who is a biker. One of her favourite rides takes her through Chernobyl, and the site is a series of photos of the abandoned city, and it is extremely poignant, especially the last couple of pages. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ulen and I went to Paris at the weekend. We had a wonderful time, and on Sunday evening, at the top of the Eiffel Tower, in howling winds, I proposed to him and he said yes!  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hah, no bog-standard wedding band for us, oh no!!! My gorgeous husband-to-be has only gone and provisionally booked urlLink  this lot    for our reception! And they only happen to be one of my most favouritist bands in the world!!  :0) 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It may be 67 weeks away but we are already making plans for our wedding, and will be putting all the info in a website that Ulen is putting together ... there's nothing on there yet but keep checking  urlLink www.alisonandulen.com  for all our plans! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Never again will I moan about being skint ... the urlLink Global Rich List  is sobering stuff. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wish I'd thought of doing this ... could have made a fortune the amount of mud on me!   urlLink eBay item 3824508716 (Ends 01-Jul-04 15:25:35 BST) - Genuine Glastonbury 2004 Mud ! Fresh this morning !!  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know why, but  urlLink "The Infinite Cat Project - Cats watching cats watching cats"  makes me think of Alice in Wonderland. Sometimes I'm a bit weird, I know. Now all I have to do is find a way to get Peaches to pose for the camera  ...     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As you can see, I've been making a few changes around here, in the vain hope that I'll actually remember to post in this thing a bit more regularly (Fat chance of that, methinks!)  Only problem is that in changing the format I've managed to lose the comment facility that I used. Which is okay, because Blogger now has its own comments and it would have got very confusing having two comment links, but it does mean I'm rather lacking in froggy references. Could anyone oblige and provide a few new ones, please? 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
                     And so we return home from another fantastic time  at the Glastonbury Festival. This year felt very different from last year, very  much more chilled rather than a manic rush from stage to stage, and of course  the weather played an important part &#8230; but it was still the most amazing,  fantastic, incredible weekend I&#8217;m likely to have this year!   So much to write about but it&#8217;s all a bit jumbled, so here&#8217;s  some random thoughts on the last five days. By no means a definitive review of  Glastonbury and probably won&#8217;t make much sense to anyone, but I know what I&#8217;m on  about!   Last year we had a list an arm&#8217;s length of the bands we  wanted to see, but this year I was happy to see anyone so long as I got to see  Snow Patrol and Muse. So we were much more selective and went for quality rather  than quantity, but we still managed to see getting on for thirty bands! For the  truly anal (and as a record to myself) the next entry will detail everyone we  saw but highlights were Snow Patrol (of course!), Keane, Franz Ferdinand, Elbow,  Muse, The Divine Comedy and Longview. And The Others, who sound like a  Buzzcocks/Cure hybrid. And Simple Kid, who was the first performer to make me  smile on a wet day.   Lazing around (and dozing) in the Greenfields on a sunny  Sunday afternoon, shortly before the heavens opened, guitars strumming in front  of us and drums beating behind.   In fact, I love the Greenfields so much more than the areas  round the main music stages; they seem to be the spiritual home of Glastonbury,  people are friendlier there, the grass is (literally) greener.   The moment during Keane&#8217;s set when the sun finally showed  itself after hours of rain, and the whole crowd cheered.   Sitting in the stone circle watching the world go by.   The staggered, amazed, joyful looks on the faces of the  singers of Keane, Snow Patrol and Hope of the States as they realised just how  many people were there to see them.   On the Sunday U and I were already suffering from sore feet  (not easy standing for hours when I&#8217;m too fat for me feet!) so decided to set up  camp at the back of the Pyramid field and watch Supergrass and Morrissey before  Muse. During the Supergrass set we watched a rainstorm move in from the rear of  the Pyramid, it swept across Glastonbury Tor and everyone braced themselves and  huddled under raincoats, carrier bags, bin bags, brollies &#8230; we sat really still  while the rain moved in and pounded on us for a good twenty minutes, but in the  distance we could see the clearer weather and blue sky and when the clouds  parted and the sun shone through everyone cheered and it was a really magical  moment!   Bursting into tears when XXXthousand people sang along to  &#8220;Run&#8221; &#8230; Hard to believe that less than a year ago we saw Snow Patrol in a tiny  venue in Northampton, along with probably about 60-70 other people &#8230; how on  earth did they get so big? And when is Gary Lightbody going to stop looking so  surprised that everyone knows the words?!   Mud, mud, glorious mud &#8230;. Mud like you&#8217;ve never seen it,  three or four inches deep in places, liquid mud like a fast flowing river in  places, sometimes sticky and sucking up your boots, sometimes so slippery that  even an Olympic-standard ice skater would have problems staying on their feet.  Watching people skate down the muddy slope near the New Tent. Slipping up the  slope on the way to our campsite, and then slipping back down the very same hill  on the return journey. God, the mud!   Muse were singing about &#8220;this is the end of the world&#8221; and I  looked around at the apocalyptic scene about me. Gaggles of people wrapped in  blankets, sitting on muddy stools or plastic sheets or standing round in huddles  around candle flares, everyone muddy and wet, the ground churned up and muddy  and littered with rubbish &#8230; it certainly looked like a post-holocaust scene.   The toilets were much cleaner this year &#8230; apart from the long  drop I visited where someone had done an enormous dump ON THE TOILET SEAT!!!  Ewwwwwwwww. The flushing loos were bearable, even the portaloos were a lot less  full and less smelly than last year. And we tried a couple of novelty loos too &#8230;  the African pit latrines run by Water Aid, where you squat over a hole in the  ground and then rinse away any spillage with a pot of water, and the  much-debated ShePee, a pretty pink female urinal. Nice idea, shame about the  mechanics &#8230; it involves standing against a basin with a cardboard funnel between  your legs, and although some people loved it I just couldn&#8217;t quite coordinate  holding down my trousers and holding up the cardboard funnel without squashing  it and trying not to fall over, and I was so terrified that I&#8217;d pee down my leg  that I got stage fright and just couldn&#8217;t perform! Think I&#8217;ll stick with the  long drops&#8230;   Best cover version ever &#8230; The Divine Comedy did Queens of the  Stone Age&#8217;s &#8220;No One Knows&#8221; complete with piano accordion!    Make sure you buy Elbow&#8217;s single &#8220;Grace Under Pressure&#8221;,  which is out next Monday. It includes U and me (and several thousand other  people) singing &#8220;We still believe in love so fuck you&#8221;!   Engaging in some culture .. We packed up the tent to the  strains of the English National Opera doing Wagner&#8217;s Ring Cycle (Think  &#8220;Apocalypse Now&#8221;)   Being cold and wet and miserable and tearful and tired and  wanting to go home on Saturday morning &#8230; I&#8217;m so glad I didn&#8217;t :0)   Things on sticks &#8230; no Stuart Pearce this year but Tigger,  Spiderman and a penguin.   Frisbees at the Other Stage (I found one in the mud and  brought it home for Dan!)   Naked men with balloons in the Cabaret Tent &#8230; very  bizarre.   The Dance of the Dying Swan, performed by a tattooed  hula-hooping Australian girl wearing frilly underwear that made her look like a  sexy sheep    Barbecued toast and marmalade   Longview &#8230; I just closed my eyes and soared while they  sang.   Boogieing to the bhangra band in the Gaiaspace Dome   Sneaking away to get changed and have a quick shag in the  tent ;0)   The Frank Sinatra singer in the Church of Love and Loathing  in Lost Vagueness   Glastonbury smells wonderful (apart from the loos) &#8211; around  the markets your senses are bombarded with a hundred different sensations, and  you&#8217;re never far from the sweet scent of cannabis. Just wish I&#8217;d had some to  smoke!   The flags at the Jazz World stage   Seeing Goldrush, our hoped-for wedding band, performing in  the New Tent. Ostensibly they were there as a backing band for Mark Gardener  (ex-Ride) but to me they were Goldrush.   Feeling part of something amazing.   Watching the England game on the field at the Pyramid stage &#8211;  actually, we saw most of the game from our tent and didn&#8217;t realise for ages that  England&#8217;s second goal had been disallowed (why? I still haven&#8217;t seen it  properly!), but we did wander down for part of extra time and the horror of the  penalties, and shared the moment with 60,000 other people.   Laughing at the crapness of Oasis (why did they bother  turning up?) and Paul McCartney &#8211; his Beatles songs were okay but the rest was  dreary. So glad we watched from the tent and not the field.   But the best thing about Glastonbury was just wandering  around with no agenda, never knowing what to expect. And although at times we  were cold and wet and miserable, I had the most amazing time, and I&#8217;ve probably  only really realised how good it was since we came home, and I can&#8217;t wait to go  back again! Roll on June 2005 &#8211; and thank you, Mr Eavis, for a fantastic time on  your farm.    &nbsp;    ---      
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I never fail to be fascinated by the flags at the Jazz World Stage at Glastonbury. There are more of my photos from the festival  urlLink here .    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Then there was an unexpected pause. The chickens from the factory's own slaughterhouse had stopped winding through ... We were given an early break. When we got back, a couple of dozen Belgian and blue Dutch crates filled with vacuum-packed [chicken] breast fillets had been pulled in. We were set to packing those instead.  The crates were labelled GMB Meats [a company that imports meat from mainland Europe], 'use by 25 November'; the vacuum packs said the same ... The vacuum packs were cut open and tipped onto the conveyor belts. Several chicken fillets fell down through the gaps and stayed at our feet while we packed into Sainsbury's trays for the next couple of hours ... Further down the line workers were sticking a Buy One, Get One free label on each pack as it emerged from the wrapper, before it trundled on to get its British red tractor logo and a new Sainsbury's label with a ... 'use by 27 November' date stamp."     The extract above is taken from  Not on the Label: What Really Goes into the Food on your Plate , a staggeringly terrifying book by Felicity Lawrence. I've read most of it with my mouth hanging open at the total arrogance that supermarkets show. They are in total control of our lives and we don't even realise.  I'm quite seriously considering giving self sufficiency a go, a la  The Good Life . All I need is an allotment, a cow and a couple of chickens. And some co-operative neighbours :0)  Seriously, this book describes a frightening future and a more terrifying present, because it is happening now. If you only buy one book this year, make it this one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sure everyone's already seen this site, but in case you haven't, visit urlLink preparingforemergencies.co.uk .  It's one of the best spoof sites I've seen for a while, and in fact it makes so much more sense than the official one! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>