<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a set of experimental photos that I took last night. They're all at home, and each one has something special. Oh and I think I figured  out how I messed up the order of one of the pictures in the last few sets. When I uploaded my last picture with Hello I didn't refresh blogger and then post the summary so the last picture ended up before the summary. I did it again only this time it was fixable since the last one required deleting and re-posting 7 pictures to fix, and this one didn't. Not that you care about this anyways...
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I also upped the brightness on this one, and took a picture of the faucet at an odd angle.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I played around with the brightness for this picture. It makes the boring nearly white walls a little more interesting.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took this picture in my room at night. The blinds look a bit creepy.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whenever I look at this picture, I think of an egg. It's the cool lamp-egg everybody!  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This picture's cool. It's the series of lights in my bathroom.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's just a light switch, I know. I'm experimenting with lighting. It's hard to make boring objects cool. Other people photograph switches really well.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another out of my window picture of a bus going by. That's the streaky red/yellow stuff/ As for the green stuff right under it, I have no clue. It turned out cool.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is the series of b&w pictures I said I'd make of the rejects from Canada Day. Some look pretty cool. There's still one of one of the buildings that I loathe though. Otherwise, still pretty good. Oh by the way, the lamp at the bottom of this set is part of the previous set but somehow I'm dumb enough to mess that up... hehe...
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mountains and the ocean. Ahhh, I love Vancouver.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This building was curved. It looked so cool.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      View of some buildings next to Canada Place.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sun was shining brightly.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I liked this building but the picture turned out terrible.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tourist boat passing by.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lots of birds flying over the water. There were more. I couldn't open my camera fast enough.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A lamp. Wow. A lamp.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This set of pictures was taken on Canada Day in Downtown Vancouver. I took many pictures but these were my favorites. I like most of these because of the beautiful colors. The others were just dull... I might make b&w versions then... It's a thought. Anyways, enjoy!
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Canadian Flags.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More of Canada Place.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Closer view of Canada Place.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Building in shadow.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Far away view of Canada Place.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A series of unfinished townhouses.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This building looks cool.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Architecture... Oooh...  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Flying birds! Wow! Actually, I liked this picture because of the vibrant blue sky.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, 10 pictures uploaded today. They're not that good. I used a low resolution for them so the quality sucks. For future pictures I'll do high resolution. Nothing really special yet. But I like the picture of the playground and the grey sky. That's about it. Comments?
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Viola at my house.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uncle dude at the fishing trip.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Violala. We were playing cards in the park. We're dorks.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      View from my window. Bluryness is intended. Kind of...  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Playground on a rainy day (again).  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cars and buses zooming by. Taken from my window.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the view from the campsite. You can actually go down to the lake.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Playground on a rainy day.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The campfire. Nearly scorched myself trying to fix one of the sticks...  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I finised testing out stuff. I'm keeping the plain template because I like it. Besides, there will be lots of pictures on this site anyways. So, this is Take Flight, my photoblog. Enjoy!
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The collection posted today is one of mixed subjects. I was too lazy to upload the pictures at the time so they collected on my computer and I had to upload them some day. They include pictures of my fencing club at Discover Days at the Shadbolt Center for the Arts, as well as&nbsp; pictures at Lake Cheakamus,&nbsp; a few in the city on the way home, and one random one taken for no special reason. Well there is a reason. But it wasn't planned. It was amusing. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sam and Bob fencing. Damn their greatness!  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More fellow fencers&nbsp;after the Discovery Days at the Shadbolt Center for the Arts. We were having dinner.  urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is Jimmy instructing a kid who was trying out fencing for the first time.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just the way I like the communists. On the ground and bird shitted on :) My family had so suffer through them in Romania, I was too young but the stories are terrible. I was with my friend Kriselda when I took this picture. A man walked by and looked at me like I was crazy.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lake Cheakamus and the mountains.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A side view of the bear trap.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another bear. This little (big) guy got himself caught in a bear trap right when we were getting in our car in the parking lot. They're relocating bears from the Whistler area because they're getting numerous (I saw 3 that day) and dangerous. I wish I could have gotten a better shot. You can't see the bear in this picture. I was afraid that it would go mad if I turned on the flash. Oh well... The memories...  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Black bear! Well actually this one is brown. I nearly walked into it because I was getting ahead of the group hiking back to the car. It was so freaking close to me! I back tracked and then ran for it. When I came back with the rest of the group I took this picture. The bear was far away then.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Very beautiful water. The lake once again.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The tiny beach at Cheakamus Lake.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A very clear Cheakamus Lake.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Took this in moving traffic. It looks cool as an abstract picture, but it's not what I intended at all.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another of the bridge.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lions gate bridge at night. I'm a bit miffed that I couldn't take one decent picture since the car was moving and my camera is very slow and blurs everything. But it's kinda abstract and it turned out interesting.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Excessive boredom. Nothing much really. This is what happens when I get cooped up in the house. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Self portrait. Me and my sucky/wonderous camera.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trees outside my window. Very hot and sunny day.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My precious volleyball.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Empty chocolate ice cream container. Brought to you by boredom and hunger.  urlLink   
    
</post>


</Blog>