<Blog>


<date>22,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to take a moment to wish everyone a happy Thanksgiving. I need to post this now because I'm leaving to see my grandparents in Columbus, Kansas early tomorrow morning. Have a happy Thanksgiving and drive safely.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got back from seeing that new movie, Unbreakable. I can't say much about it without giving away any of the movie, but I highly suggest you see it for yourself. And don't let anyone tell you the ending. It's more fun that way.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      Graphics coming soon... I hope...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just added the resume section, and I uploaded my resume in three different flavors: HTML, PDF, and Corel WordPerfect.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just added my class schedule for the fall 2000 semester to the school section. If for some reason you care what classes I have and when I have them, then you might want to check it out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got NewsPro installed and working on the site. Now I can post a buttload of pointless news on this site anytime I want!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mario Lemieux is making his return to the NHL tonight against the Maple Leafs. The game coverage begins at 6 PM CST on ESPN2, and the game begins at 6:30 PM CST on ESPN. I can't wait!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know that Christmas is almost over now, but I just wanted to make sure that I wished everyone a merry Christmas. I hope everyone had a great day.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      yeah... finals at 7:30 in the morning suck.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got the greatest, most unbelievable news today. After four years of retirement, Mario Lemieux is coming back to the NHL! He is by far my favorite hockey player of all time, and I so excited that he's back. He's expected to start playing for the Penguins again in January. What's cool about this is that he will not only own the Penguins, but he will also be playing for them. Not only that, but he is also already in the hockey hall of fame. How cool is that? I can't wait until January!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know It's been quite a while since I last posted news, so here is everything interesting that has happened to me in the last month.  I spent the end of December and New Years in Kansas City hanging out with some of my friends from school. I then got on a bus and headed to Denver to spend a week at the Denver Christmas Conference (DCC) for Campus Crusade. Once again, DCC was awesome! This was my third DCC trip, and every year is a blast! I learn so much, and I get to hang out with my friends as well as make totally new friends. Everyone should go to DCC at least once.  I got back to Kansas City on Sunday, spent one more night at my friend Justin's place, got back to Wichita on Monday morning, and was back at school in Manhattan Tuesday night. I had to do some last minute enrollment so that I could be a full-time student by Thursday when classes started back up. This looks to be about the hardest semester of classes I've ever had. I just hope I can keep up.  Perhaps the most interesting story from the past month happened last night. Over Christmas break, some of my friends and I thought it would be a good idea to start skateboarding. So once we got back to school, some of us started purchasing skateboards so that we could start learning. For about the last week, we have been practicing our ollies, and last night, on the way to dinner, some of my friends were out skating. Knowing that I had a few minutes to kill, I decided to try a couple ollies. On about the third attempt, something went wrong, and I ended up kissing the board! Initially, I thought I just bit my lip a bit, but once I washed all of the blood off my face, I noticed that I had one large cut on my bottom lip and an even deeper one right below my lip. After a quick trip to the emergency room, I ended up with ten stitches and a sore chin. I guess my ollie could use a little more work.  Anyway, that's pretty much all of the interesting stuff that has happened in the last month. This semester is already looking to be one of the best ever. In the future, I hope to keep up on my news postings so that I don't have to do any more extremely long postings like this one.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, here's the deal... the FATLAN Party was scheduled for March 9th, and Clint, who has been doing most of the planning for the party, is not going to be able to attend on the 9th. Since Clint can't be there on the 9th, we have decided to move the party to March 30th. That will be the first Friday night after we get back from spring break. Hopefully this date will work out for all of the people who have already registered, as well as the people who were still planning on registering. We will be sending out an e-mail to all of the K-State dorms sometime in the next couple days, and we will also have some posters up in the near future. If you have any problems concerning the FATLAN Party, please feel free to  urlLink e-mail  me, and don't forget to check the  urlLink website  for updates. I'm sorry about all the confusion with the dates. Hopefully this new date will stick.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, we've been telling everyone that the FATLAN Party was going to be on Friday March 10 or just saying March 10. We just discovered that March 10 is Saturday. What we really meant to say was that the party is on Friday March 9... yes, March 9. It will not be held on Saturday, so don't come to Putnam Hall Saturday night expecting to play video games with a basement full of people. We may still play some video games with you, but there's no way we can fit more than 5 or 6 computers in our room. I'm sorry about the confusion, and I hope this date will work out for everyone.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so excited because I just found out that MxPx will be playing on Tuesday March 13 at the Beaumont Club in Kansas City! Alright, I know it's on a school night, but I willing to give up going to a few classes in order to see one of my favorite bands in concert. It's a sacrifice i'm willing to make. I'm also excited because Slick Shoes will be one of the opening bands. I've almost seen Slick Shoes like three times, but something always happens. I'm told that the show starts at 8pm and tickets cost $15. This will be the third MxPx show that I've attended, and they're great every time. It's been over a year since I last saw them live, so I can hardly wait! Go to the MxPx website for more info.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      We've been planning a LAN party here in Putnam for a while now, and last weekend,  urlLink Darian  found a name for it... the  urlLink FATLAN . The first FATLAN is in the planning stage now. It looks like we will have the first ever FATLAN party on Friday March 9 in the Putnam Hall basement located on the  urlLink Kansas State University  campus. That date may change in the future, but I'll try to keep you posted. The party should be free, and it looks like we will be ordering pizza... twice! There will be lots of Quake Trilogy action, maybe some Unreal Tournament, Half-Life, Counterstrike, Age of Empires 2, and any other game that people might want to play. To attend the party, all you have to do is get registered on the  urlLink website  before the cut-off date which has yet to be set. So hurry up and register if you plan on going! Just  urlLink e-mail  me if you have any problems. Hopefully, there will be many more FATLAN parties to follow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Caleb got his motherboard in yesterday, which was the last needed component for his computer, so we put his computer together last night. It's a 900Mhz AMD Athlon Thunderbird with 128MB of PC133 memory, a Sound Blaster Live! Value sound card, and a Guillemot Hercules 3D Prophet II MX (GeForce 2 MX) video card. He also got an ASUS A7V motherboard, which is sweet! It comes with five USB ports which are upgradable to seven as well as several other cool features. I can't wait to see his computer run Quake 3!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to take a second and wish everyone a happy Valentine's Day. I hope everyone has a wonderful day!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just talked to Travis, and he says that the LAN Party is going to continue as planned. He was on his way to Topeka, and says that the roads are pretty clear. The party will officially begin at 7pm. Darian still doesn't feel well enough to go. I'm still not sure if I will make it to the party.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, last night, a nice layer of ice formed on just about everything here in Manhattan, and then this morning I woke up to what looks like about six inches of snow. We actually found some places where there was about three feet of snow! The good news is that all classes were cancelled. I'm told that this is only the second time in the school's history that all classes have been cancelled! The bad news is that tonight's LAN Party has been cancelled. And on top of that, Darian isn't feeling well. We might still play some video games over the Internet or something tonight. I'm told that the LAN Party will be rescheduled for the near future. I'll probably post the info when I find out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Travis and company have planned another LAN party for this Friday, February 9 starting at 7pm and going until the next morning. The last one I went to was for his bachelor party, and it was a blast! For more information about the party, go to Travis' website ( urlLink http://thebigkahoona.yi.org ).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just made a few minor updates including the addition of new links to the links and contacts sections. Updates are coming slower than I would like since I never have the time to make the updates or I just never feel like working on the site when I do have the time. I'll try to get more stuff added as the semester continues.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      The first ever FATLAN Party has ended, and it was a blast. The party started around 6pm last night. There were so many network problems, that we had trouble keeping up at first. It was around 11 or 12 before i even got to play any video games. Despite the numerous problems, the party was great. After a countless amount of pop and 15 pizzas, the party was over. Most of the gamers had left by about 7am, but a few of us stuck around until about 9:30am. I finally made it to bed around noon today. That should pretty much screw up my sleeping habits for the rest of the week! There's talk of another FATLAN Party for the end of April, so keep an eye out for that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, we started setting up for the FATLAN Party around 5, and we've been having problems ever since. Here it is over 4 hours later and i still haven't played any games yet. I'm installing some games now, so maybe I will get to play sometime soon. I'll try to post some more news a little later.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just found out that it was Pi Day (3.14) today, so I just thought I would take a moment to wish everyone a happy Pi Day!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      The show last night was a blast! MxPx was great! They impress me every time I see them. Good Charlotte and Slick Shoes were also good, although I only got to see Slick Shoes play like three songs because the concert started a little earlier than I thought. I had so much fun in the mosh pit and I was soaking wet when I got out. The only problems I had at the show were the dumb crowd surfers. They would kick you in the head, jump on your back, or just fall on top of you when you are just trying to have a good time. We all got a little beat up last night, but it was still fun. I was in the pit for the first half of the show, and for the second half, I was really close to the stage. In fact, there was only one person beteen me and the stage. I got to see Mike play "The Theme Fiasco" like three feet away from me! That was really cool. We didn't get to have dinner with Travis last night. He was in a small car accident yesterday morning and he was trying to fix the front of his car. Hopefully I will get to visit him over spring break though. The only other thing that I can say about the night was that we had a nice sweaty ride home, and we got back around 2am. And now I have to go write some essays.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      We just got back from the MxPx show in Kansas City about half an hour ago and I really stink right now. I really need to take a shower. I'll have to post more about the show tomorrow because I'm really sleepy right now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm getting ready to leave for the MxPx concert tonight. I'm so excited! I haven't seen them live for over a year and a half. We'll probably be leaving within the next half hour and I'm hoping that we will be back around 3am, so don't wait up for me! We also get to have dinner in Kansas City with Travis before the show. That should be really cool too since I haven't seen him for a while now. Anyway, I should finish getting ready to go so we can take off. I'll probably post some news or something when I get back.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ann and Jermaine are cool. They burp and stuff. --: p
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, we sent the e-mail about the LAN party out to all the dorms last week, and we still only have like fifteen people registered. We have had almost no response from the e-mail and that's not good. So if you are lazy and are putting off registering, please hurry and get registered. We really need to start figuring out stuff like how much pizza to order and how many dedicated servers we can run. I might also remind everyone that this party is absolutly free! That means a night of free pizza, drinks, and gaming! Why would you not want to come? Please register as soon as possible, and don't forget to remind your friends.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Next week is Spring Break, so all the teachers here feel like they need to give us a bunch crap to do before we leave. I actually only have one test this week, but it is going to be an extremely hard history test. I also have four papers to write and three English journals due, so this week will pretty much just suck for me. The one great thing about this week is that I'm going to see MxPx in Kansas City tomorrow. I'll get to hang out with Israel at the show, and will hopefully get to see Travis and Holly before the show. I'm really looking forward to the concert, but it may mean that I will miss some classes on Wednesday. Oh well. I just hope I'll have enough time to get all my stuff done this week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, Brice's new Dell computer was delivered on Friday, so he had Darian and I come over to help him set it up. We were there for like half and hour before we screwed it up. It appears that his computer gets upset when you try to upgrade his video card drivers to the new NVIDIA Detonators. Somehow, the video drivers that Dell provided also make the DVD drive work, so when we removed them, the video was screwed up and we couldn't get the old drivers back off of the CD. On top of all that, Windows explorer wouldn't start up, so we were also left with a blank screen and no way to fix it. So we reinstalled Windows, and everything pretty much returned to the way it was when the computer first arrived. Of course we had to install Quake 3 on it before we left, but that was a given. Another problem we found was that we could only connect to the Internet using the dumb Dellnet thing. Whenever we clicked on Internet Explorer, a window would pop up and tell us to click on the Dellnet icon. This is stupid because Brice connects to the Internet using DSL, not dial-up. Darian figured this one out when he ran the Internet Connection Wizard in the Internet Explorer folder and changing his connection to LAN. The biggest problem that I found with his computer was that it starts up entirely too fast. Of course, that's a problem I hope to have in the near future. --: p
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      My friend Brice just ordered a Dell computer last night. It looks like it's going to be pretty sweet. It's a P3 1Ghz with lots of other cool stuff like a GeForce 2 MX, SoundBlaster Live!, and 128MB of PC133 memeory. I normally would buy AMD CPUs and would prefer to build my own computer, but this entire computer was only $1029 without the monitor. That's a pretty good price for all the stuff he's getting. We went to Best Buy in Topeka on Saturday, and he bought a 19" monitor there. The computer should be here by the end of the week. I hope it runs well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just heard on tv last night that Joey Ramone just died in a hospital yesterday while being treated for cancer! This sux for anyone who loves the Ramones. Joey was the lead singer for the Ramones for over 20 years, and he was one of the greatest punk influences ever.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I started my job painting the Jardine appartments this week and it's not too bad. It does suck to wake up so early in the morning though. I have to be there at 7:30am and I get off at 4pm. I've only worked two days so far. Tomorrow, we are working in Van Zile! We have to sand, which will probably suck, but at least we will be inside.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a great weekend in Wichita for Brice and Katy's wedding. I was a groomsman in the wedding, so they had to take lots of pictures of me in a tux. I hope I can get some of them to put on my website later.  I got to see several friends that I had not seen for a while. C. Jay drove all the way up from southern Texas for the wedding. I think he said that it was something like an eleven hour drive. He got to Wichita on Friday and hung out with us until about 3pm on Sunday, so he probably got home pretty late Sunday night. Jermaine and Ann also came to the wedding. They drove from Kansas City, so it wasn't quite as far as C. Jay drove. We all met up for lunch at the mall on Sunday.  Right now, Brice and Katy are probably on their way to Mexico for their honeymoon. They will spend a week in Mexico before returning to Wichita. I think they said that they will be back in Manhattan on July 6. They will then spend a week at Brice's appartment to pack up his stuff and then leave for West Virginia.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I will be leaving in the morning to go to Wichita for Brice and Katy's wedding. My mom, sister, and youngest brother were supposed to come stay overnight at my house in Manhattan tonight, but they were running into some problems and decided to stay in Wichita and drive to Manhattan early tomorrow morning. My sister has orientation at K-State tomorrow and wanted to be here so she didn't have to get up early in the morning and drive... oh well...  I'm meeting up with Brice and Katy at Katy's house around 2 so that we can go pick up the tuxes. C. Jay will get to Katy's house around 3 or 4 and will be hanging out with us until the wedding! Tomorrow night will be the rehearsal at 5:30 and then we will be playing mini-golf after. Saturday, we will be totally free to do whatever we want until we have to be at the church at 4. I hope we can think of some fun stuff to do! Pictures begin at 5 and guests will probably start arriving around 6:30. The wedding starts at 7. Maybe something cool will be going on after the wedding too.  Oh, one more thing I forgot to do was wish Brice a happy birthday. His birthday was Wednesday (June 20) and he turned 22 i think. I just forgot to post news about it. Happy Birthday Brice!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I should be leaving for Wichita for Brice and Katy's wedding in less than two days and I'm still not positive how I will get there. I guess Darian said that he could leave early on Friday if Eric and I have no other way to get there, but I didn't really want to make him do that. I'm still really excited about the wedding. C. Jay e-mailed me the other day and told me that he will be in Wichita on Friday and will be leaving on Sunday! This makes me even more excited! I haven't seen or really even talked to C. Jay since the beginning of the Fall 2000 semester when he visited K-State and then left for Texas. He will get to hang out with Brice the entire time until the wedding on Saturday. Brice is very happy about that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Because of the rain that we received last night, we will not be having Bring Your Own Meat Night tonight at Mike, Wes, and Terence's house. Instead, we will be having Sloppy Joe Night at 6:30. Maybe we will have Bring Your Own Meat Night next wednesday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I just got a job and it's going to suck. I will be painting the K-State appartments for forty hours a week. I'm sure it won't be that bad, I'll just be really tired for the rest of the summer. I only get paid something like $5.65 and hour, so it might be good for me to work more. I have to be there at 7:30 in the morning, but I get off at 4. I will start next Tuesday when I get back from the wedding in Wichita. Terence starts working tomorrow and Mike still needs to go in and talk to the lady in charge before he can get hired. It will be a tough job, but it's not like I was going to be doing anything else next week anyway!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes I wonder why I even bother posting all this news here. I don't think anyone actually reads it... oh well!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had a pretty big storm come through Manhattan tonight. When it first started, it was just a little bit of rain and some pea-sized hail, then it stopped for a while. A little later it got really dark outside really fast. It began raining again, a little more than before, and then golf ball sized hail started falling! This was probably the biggest hail I have ever seen before. The rain and hail continued for several minutes, then it cleared up again. An hour or two later, it became very cloudy again, then it bagan raining and hailing very hard, although the hail was back to pea-sized. Once it stopped hailing and it was just raining, Eric, Brandan and I went down to the bridge by Putnam to look at the water level. It was higher than I had ever seen it before. Then I noticed that it was still rising, and it was rising fast! We waited to see how high it would rise. It got so high that it almost covered the bridge. The sidewalk by the bridge was totally covered in water too. It was really cool to see. I hope it does it again some time. Next time I think I could go without the hail. Although the hail was very cool to watch, it tends to do alot of damage and it hurts when you get hit in the head!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Crap, I just now realized it was Friday! I had been thinking it was Saturday all day because I didn't have class today! Anyway, Brice and Katy visited Manhattan today to pick up some stuff from Katy's appartment. It was really cool to see them again. They were really hungry when they got to my house, so we went to eat at Carlos O'Kelly's for dinner with Paul and two of Brice and Katy's friends. After dinner we just went over to Kerri's to hang out and talk a bit. There's only one week until the wedding and I'm really excited! That will be a really fun weekend because we will have alot of time to just hang out with Brice on Friday night and Saturday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Brice and Katy are coming to Manhattan today to move some of Katy's stuff back to Wichita. Brice said that they should be here around 3 or 4 this afternoon. I haven't seen Brice since he gave me a ride to Wichita the day after the Project 86 concert in Kansas City a few weeks ago in which Project had to cancel. Brice and Katy's wedding is only eight days away now, and I'm still not sure how I am going to get back to Wichita next Friday... maybe that would be something to talk about tonight...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonight we are having Spaghetti Night at Wes, Terence, and Mike's house. It should be alot of fun. Last week was taco night and several people from Strong Complex showed up. It was a nice little summer reunion. So if last week was tacos and this week is spaghetti, I wonder what next week will be...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I added a few pictures to the Pictures section today. I will probably add some more tonight or tomorrow or sometime this week. Check them out if you get bored sometime.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished making my new website for my summer class, MC450: Intermediate Web Communications. I presented it to my class last week. I really wasn't happy with the way it turned out, so I spent the last couple days fixing it up again. I'm much happier with the results this time. Hopefully I can put more stuff on it this time around and keep it up to date this summer. If you are interested in looking at the site that I turned in for my MC450 project, you may still be able to see it at the following link:  urlLink http://students.jmc.ksu.edu/nonjmc/ndillon/www/ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      For those of you who don't know and actually care, I have been living here in Manhattan for the last four weeks while taking summer classes at K-State. Darian and I moved into a house with Matt Shepherd about four blocks south of campus. So far, I have to say that living off campus kinda sux when you are taking classes because you have to walk longer distances to get to your classes and you actually have to wait for cars to stop before you cross the streets to get to campus. Everything else is cool though.  I've found that K-State is somewhat lonely during the summer. I miss living in the dorms where you have friends just right across the hall. I don't have a car either, so if I want to go somewhere, I either have to walk or bum a ride. I find myself home alone quite a bit, so I usually just work on my computer or watch tv or something.  I just finished one of my classes last week. I was taking Intermediate Web Communications (MC450) and I presented my website on Friday. I was excited because I ended up with an A in that class. It seemed really easy for me, but I was afraid that I would get a B for some reason. Now all I have left is my class on the Criminal Justice System (SOCIO361) and I've already taken the only test for the class and I have also already given my presentation. All I have to do now is show up for class and take a few notes.  I'll be going home for Brice and Katy's wedding on the 23rd. I have to be in Wichita on the afternoon of the 22nd so that we can pick up our tuxes and go to the wedding rehearsal. It should be a really good time. It will be one of my last chances to hang out with Brice before he moves to West Virginia to go to grad school. I'll also get to see alot of my friends at the wedding.  Justin leaves tomorrow for his summer project with Campus Crusade in Alaska! Caleb left for his project in Tennessee last week. You might want to pray for these guys this summer. I know thay are both probably a little worried about what will happen this summer, but I'm sure that they will both have a great time!  Alright, I guess that's all the news I had for right now. I'll try to keep this section updated as much as possible this summer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am currently working on remaking this website for my summer class, MC450: Intermediate Web Communications. I am hoping to get most of it done soon because I have to present it in class on Thursday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tomorrow Poopsy is going to be in charge of our paint crew at Ford and she is bringing my old Jardine crew with her. Jess will be gone tomorrow but he will be back on Monday. Poopsy and the Jardine crew will also be working in Ford on Monday. It will be alot of fun having the two crews together. Today we finished up the B wing on 6th floor. Tomorrow we will start on the A wing. Fun Fun!  Travis, I finally added the dumpster pictures so you can stop bugging me about them.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      My website was down last night so I didn't get to post my news like I wanted to!  Nothing really exciting has happened the past few days. On Monday I learned to use the rollers to paint dorm rooms. It's way harder than it looks. It wouldn't be so bad except for the ceilings. When painting the ceilings, my arms get really tired and paint drips everywhere. I was totally covered in paint after doing a the first few rooms! Monday night Brandan and I went to Dillon's and Wal-Mart. We then decided to go get shaved ice like five minutes before they closed. Last night I went to dinner at Ben and Stephanie's with Kristi. Tonight I went to Terence's house to eat. I just love free food!  Shaved Ice Update: The other night I had the root beer float flavor. It was alright at first but I got sick of it pretty fast. This is the first flavor I have found that I don't think I would want to get again. By the way, C. Jay would hate this flavor!  One thing I keep forgetting to write about is the virus that Brandan got on his computer last weekend. The virus is called TROJ_SIRCAM.A and it is a trojan virus. He got the virus from an e-mail he received from a friend. The virus then e-mailed itself to all of the people in his address book as well as some people not in his address book. When Brandan first discovered SIRCAM on his computer, it was ranked number two on the top virus list. By the end of the weekend it was number one. A security alert has also been issued for SIRCAM. The virus was removed by changing a few settings in the Windows Registry. If you get a werid e-mail with an attachment from Brandan or anyone else, do not run the attachment or you might get the virus too. If you already have the virus, go to  urlLink antivirus.com's  page about  urlLink SIRCAM  for instructions on how to remove it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mom just told me that she and my brother will probably be coming to see me on my birthday too! It will be nice to see them.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      There's only one more week until my birthday. I didn't really have any way to get back to Wichita so I was just planning on staying here in Manhattan. I wasn't planning on doing anything to celebrate because Darian was going to be gone and there aren't many other people here, but Ann and Jermaine decided to come see me for my birthday! My sister Lindsey also decided to drive up on Sunday to see me! It should be alot of fun.  "Trust in the Lord with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding; in all your ways aknowledge him, and he will make your paths strait." -Proverbs 3:5-6
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Caleb has really inspired me to get my journal going again as well as the news on my website. Caleb has been on project this summer with  urlLink Campus Crusade for Christ  and he writes in his journal every day and then posts a slighty edited version on the Internet ( urlLink http://bigme68.diaryland.com/ ). I would like to start doing something similar to what Caleb has been doing. I am just always afraid of posting anything too personal on the Internet because I know that anyone can read it. I need to find a balance between posting something that is too personal and posting nothing at all.  I finally got to talk to Brice on  urlLink AIM  yesterday. He got his cable modem hooked up this week. Brice has been online this entire time but he is always away from his computer. This is the first time that I have talked to Brice since he and Katy moved to West Virginia last Saturday.  This week, Justin told Ann that he loved me, which is funny because I was just telling a guy at work that I love Justin... I just thought that was cool.  Last night I went back to look at one of my favorite passages from the Bible: Matthew 6:25-34. It talks about worrying. The passage states that worrying is pointless. Worrying doesn't help the situation at all. The passage also says to look to God first, don't worry, and God will take care of you. This is just what I needed to read because I have been worried about several things lately. Everyone seems to think that I am really laid back, but I think that I just might hide my problems and don't let people know that I am worried. I am slowly getting better about not doing this but it will be a long process. I highly recommend reading Matthew 6:25-34.  "...seek first the kingdom of God and His righteousness, and all these things will be given to you as well..." -Matthew 6:33
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Brice and Katy stopped in Manhattan today to pick up the rest of their stuff from Brice's appartment. After packing, they began their trip to West Virginia. Brice called me before they took off to say goodbye. I am really going to miss them, but I'm sure they will have a great time in West Virginia.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Terence and I are feeling kinda like porfessional athletes at the moment. Yesterday, our paint team was told that we are no longer going to be painting the exterior of the Jardine appartments. They moved us to painting the interior of the appartments. About half the team was also relocated to different teams in Jardine. The last two days have been much easier and enjoyable. Today, Terence and I received the news that we would be moved to the team painting the dorm rooms in Ford Hall. We were traded for two sixteen-year-olds. I guess they are running out of time and they need older (more mature) painters in Ford. It's sad for us to be leaving our team like this, but it should be nice to be working in the dorms. We were also told that Danny will be going to Ford with us. That guy is really funny! I hope it's as cool working in Ford as it has been to work in Jardine. Oh yeah, one more thing... We got id cards today that will let us get into any dorm during working hours. It's pretty cool except that we were told that our cards are monitored every time we use them... oh well!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, it's been a while since I last posted news! I've just been working the past two weeks. It gets really hot outside when I'm at work too. I went to Terence's house for a bbq on the 4th. Then, instead of watching fireworks, I went back to my house and watched the Unbreakable DVD with Brandan and his brother. Darian also just bought the Snatch DVD last Tuesday. I've seen it five times now in the last week. It's a very good movie and a cool DVD. Brice and Katy came into town on Sunday. They will go back to Wichita on Sunday to finish packing up. Then they will leave for West Virginia later this week. The Vans Warped Tour is in Kansas City tomorrow. Jermaine said that she got free tickets and she had an extra one that she could have given me, but I'm broke and had no way to get to Kansas City. Oh well, maybe next year... Of course, that's what I've been saying about Cornerstone for the last four years...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oi... I forgot one thing... Friday, Danny and I got stuck in an elevator in Ford Hall! We were on our way to the basement and the elevator didn't quite make it for some reason. We had to just sit there for about ten minutes while waiting for someone to get us out. It was pretty funny. This was the second time that I have been stuck in an elevator. The first time was in 1999 during the Denver Christmas Conference. Ask me about it so
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      Poopsy and the Jardine crew have been working over in Ford Hall with us all week. I guess they are going to just finish the summer in Ford. Some people have already left the paint crew for the summer. We lost all of the food sevice people after Wednesday. Terence's last day was on Thursday. Next week will be my last week, then I have to work on getting packed and moved over to Putnam Hall as soon as possible. Danny and Terence are trying to get me to stay on the paint crew with them during the school year. I'm just not sure if I will have the time or if I will even want to work this next semester. I also need to find like six more hours of class. I need to do that soon. Maybe today.  Shaved Ice Update: The other night I had the Peach Pie flavor. This is one of the best flavors that I have tried! It contained peach, apple and cinnamon.  Friday night Brandan and Eric came over for a little while. We watched Frequency on DVD and I fell asleep again. That's beginning to become a habit for me. I've just been getting really sleepy while watching DVDs lately. We also ate some frozen pizzas and drank beer last night. We bought a six pack of Killian's Irish Red this week because I heard that it was good. I thought it was alright. I was just sick of it by the time I finished the bottle. I think I like Bud Light better, although it didn't seem to have much of a taste. I really like Mike's Hard Lemonade. You can't even taste the alcohol in that. It just tastes like carbonated lemonade. I want to try more stuff before school starts because beer is about the only thing that they will let you have in the dorms.  Yesterday I went to see Rush Hour 2 with Brandan and another guy that works at Christian Books and Gifts (CBAG). That was a great movie! I highly recommend it, especially if you like Jackie Chan movies. I also went to a party last night where Chris' bands were going to be playing their first show. For those of you that don't know, Chris is a guy that was on the Jardine paint crew with me earlier this summer. One of Chris' bands is a punk band named Dead Lemon so I was really interested in hearing them play. They were pretty good for their first show.  Matt got back from Colorado yesterday, so I am no longer alone... at least not for a day or two. He was at camp with his Youth for Christ kids. He said that two girls accepted Christ this week! Darian got back to Wichita yesterday. He spent ten days hiking in New Mexico. He said that it was alot of fun but he hurt his ankle on the tripand had to be taken off the mountain early. He has to get an MRI this week in order to figure out what is wrong with his ankle. He won't be back in Manhattan until Tuesday or Wednesday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      i think i just broke the news...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been meaning to post the stuff about my birthday since Monday. I guess I just never got around to it. I'm sure you all are just dying to know what I did last weekend so here it is...  Last Sunday was my 21st birthday and I had a great weekend! On Friday, Brandan and I went shopping to get some stuff to make dinner Saturday night. After going back to Dillon's, we went back to Putnam to watch Office Space. I fell asleep in the middle of the movie and didn't wake up until 4am. I made Brandan give me a ride home.  On Saturday, I went back over to Putnam around 4pm to bake some cookies. We made M&M cookies, Jermaine's favorite. We didn't do too bad on the cookies. I probably should have let some of them bake a little longer but they all tasted alright. Jermaine and Ann arrived at Putnam around 7pm. We then attempted to light the grill to cook some steaks. We failed. I later found out that the charcoal that we used was bad and is very hard to light. That made me feel a little better. We finally resorted to frying the steaks. They were still pretty good... at least that's what the girls told us... After washing the dishes, we all went to get some shaved ice. We then went back to my house to hang out for a while. Paul stopped by for about half an hour to say hi. After spending a couple hours at my house, we went back to Putnam where we ate our cookies and talked until about 2am. We decided that we should go to bed so that we could get up for church.  On Sunday, we all went to Westview for the 11am service. Then we went back to Putnam to look around and waste time while waiting on my mom and my sister to show up. After they got to Manhattan around 1:30pm, we all went out to eat at Carlos O'Kelly's. We went to see Planet of the Apes after lunch. It was a pretty good movie, just a little cheesy during some parts. There was a big cookie waiting for us when we got back to my house. My mom and my sister got it for me for my birthday. Jermaine and Ann left Manhattan around 8pm. My mom and sister left around 8:30pm. Brandan and I went to get some food and returned to Putnam to watch Donkey and Rush Hour.  I had a really fun weekend. It was great to see Jermaine and Ann! I can't wait until school starts and we can all be together again. Only about a week before people start getting back to school!  Shaved Ice Update: Last Saturday night I had the Fantasia flavor. I thought that it was really good. It had coconut, strawberry and blue something in it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, Canada defeated the United States hockey team to win the gold medal in the 2002 Olympics. It was a pretty good game, but I do not feel that the United States played as well as they could have. Even though I wanted the United States to win, I am still very happy for the Canadians. This is the first time that they have won the gold in the last 50 years! I was also happy to see Mario Lemieux get a gold medal.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I started a new site layout this month. I am taking Advanced Web Communications this semester and one of the requirements for the class is to fix my personal site. My site was in desperate need of some changes. Also, I have changed the name on the site from "NatoriousFAT" to "Nate Dillon." It seems less confusing this way.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm sitting here waiting for my laundry to dry so that I can finish packing for my trip to Manhattan.  I am leaving tomorrow morning with Brice.  We are both attending weddings this weekend.  My friend Pete is getting married on Sunday.  This will also be a good trip for me because I will get to hang out with Jermaine some more before I leave for Orlando.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Grades came out today at K-State.  I ended up with a 3.0 for the semester, but I got a D in one of my classes and a B in another class that I thought would be an A.  That brings my overall GPA to about 2.6, which is pretty good considering how low it used to be.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Darian and I are probably going to buy a domain and some web space next week.  We are shopping around for the best deal right now.  We also need to think of a cool domain name.  The best one I can think of so far is FATLand.org.  All the other good FATLand names are taken.  The name doesn't need to be FATLand, but that is all I can think of right now.  It would be better if the name was short and simple because we will probably have lots of subdomains, such as Nate.FATLand.org.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to update everyone on my support for the Orlando Summer Project.  I have already raised 58% of the money I need to have before I leave on June 10.  I have sent out 107 letters, 3 of those have been returned due to a wrong address, and 18 people have sent money.  Tomorrow I will be sending out another 17 letters.  I also have not yet contacted any churches for support.  I am trusting that God will provide the rest of the money before I leave.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, I think I have this thing somewhat figured out.  The template on this Blogger thing is a pain in the butt!  Well, at least it works.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      This template sux!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, now I can test out posts on two different days!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a test.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am trying out this Blogger thing, and, so far, it seems pretty cool.  I think I still need to mess with it a little, but I might use this to post news over the summer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to test this thing out to see how it works!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I forgot to post this Friday:  Well, it has been a pretty interesting week. This was my first "normal" week of the project. Work seems to just fly by. It doesn't really feel like I am even at work. I have been working on the Orlando Summer Project web site. That is my first major project. I need to get it done in the next two weeks so that they can give me my next project. For the next one, I am told that I will actually be working with the rest of the team.  Our car wash outreach was last Saturday. We didn't get many cars because it started to rain. This week has been very wet. It has been raining more every day than it did the first week we were here. Our next outreach is tomorrow afternoon. We will be splitting up into smaller groups and will go to various tourist locations, such as Downtown Disney, the Universal CitiWalk, and a couple other places. Please be praying that the outreaches go well. Also, be praying me and anyone else that doesn't have much experience with this sort of thing. It can be a little scary at times.  Last Saturday after the car wash, we had core group fun night. My core group went to see the movie Windtalkers. It was pretty good. I guess it didn't seem like the typical war movie. After the movie, we decided to go get ice cream in a town within Orlando called Celebration. The town is actually owned by Disney, but anyone can buy a house and live there... if they can afford it anyway. The town was really nice! Everything looked really new and perfect. It reminded me of that town in the Truman Show. We ended up sitting by the lake in the center of town and talking for a while.  We formed our planning teams this week. These will be the teams responsible for planning everything that happens on project. The Crusade staff are currently in charge of the teams, but they leave project in three weeks and the students will take over. I am on the Brady Bunch team, which is in charge of planning all the fun activities. We are also in charge of creating things to help us remember the project, such as a t-shirt, video, or a cd with all the project pictures on it.  I guess that's about all that I have for now. Sorry if this e-mail seems a bit long. We are busy every night here, so there is alot that happens. Anyway, I guess I should get back to work now. See ya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I made it to Orlando Monday afternoon around 1pm. It was my first time flying anywhere, so it was interesting. I didn't get sick or anything. Some Campus Crusade staff picked Darian and I up at the airport, and we went to a local church to get registered for the project. After registration, we were taken to our condos. They are really nice! I can't believe they are actually letting us stay there. Our condo has three bedrooms and three bathrooms. There will be six people staying there, so two people to a room.  We have been doing so many activities since we have been here. There are about 50 or 60 students doing the project, so I am having trouble remembering everyone's name. We were split into groups of three called Core Groups, which are led by a Campus Crusade staff member. Two of these Core Groups will meet every week to have a Bible study. We had our first one the other night. Most of the other activities so far have been some kind of orientation or something to help us get to know everyone here. Saturday we will be doing a car wash outreach.  I started work on Wednesday. They gave us a tour of the Crusade Headquarters, and this place is sweet! It's so big, alot bigger than it looks in the pictures! I would definately suggest visiting if you are ever in the Orlando area. I will be working in the computer services department for the web consulting team. I think I am going to love working here. Everyone is so friendly.  Well, I guess that's about all I have to say for now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Only three more weeks left in the project!  I can hardly believe it!  I had another great week in Orlando.  Our last outreach was Friday night instead of Saturday.  We went to a place called Waterford Lakes, which is sorta like an outdoor mall in Orlando.  It is a huge gang-out area for middle school kids on Friday nights.  We were just approaching people and asking if they wanted to do our spiritual interest surveys.  I think my group freaked out a couple kids.  We went up to them and Noe (my roommate from Mexico) started talking.  He said that his English isn't very good, so Nate is going to ask you a question.  I then asked them if they wanted to do the survey, and they said no.  I had noticed that one of them was wearing a t-shirt from a punk band, so I asked them if they were going to the Warped Tour.  They said they were, so I told them that I was going to be there too and I asked them what bands they like.  They named one or two, but didn't say anything else. That's when I realized that we had officially freaked them out, so I thanked them for their time and walked away.  It's a good thing that we had outreach training the next day.  Maybe next time will be a little better.  Saturday night was 70s/80s night.  Everyone dressed in some 70s, 80s, or just tacky clothing and we all went bowling.  It was pretty fun making complete fools of ourselves.  After bowling, we went to Lake Hart to have ice cream and watch the video of the pictures from our scavenger hunt a few weeks ago.  We also watched the Goonies to stick with the whole 80s theme.  A large group of the students went back to Cocoa Beach Sunday afternoon.  This was my third trip to the beach: the first time it rained before I got a chance to swim in the ocean and the second time was an outreach, so I didn't have time to swim.  This time, I was actually able to swim for about an hour before it started to rain.  This was my first time to ever swim in the ocean, so I was pretty excited.  I had a great time, but the salt water burned my eyes quite a bit.  There have been a couple really good speakers this week.  Tuesday night we heard from a guy that works in financial services.  He talked about using our money wisely and staying out of debt so that we could be more effective in our ministry.  He used M&Ms as an illustration for his talk, and he even gave everyone a bunch of M&Ms at the beginning!  Wednesday, I heard one of the pastors from Orlando speak about persevering in prayer.  Well, I've scanned over 150 more pictures for the web site this week, and I still don't have much online yet.  I hope to have it all up soon.  I have been working on m internship paper that will be due on Tuesday.  Hopefully I will be able to get it all done on time.  Well, I guess that's all for now.  See ya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      From Friday, July 19, 2002...  Hey everyone!  This past week in Orlando has been one of the best yet.  We had a beach outreach on Saturday.  This one was a little different though.  We did the outreach with a ministry called JoePix ( urlLink http://www.joepix.com ).  JoePix is a ministry that try to expose people to the gospel by blessing them with free photos.  They go out to take pictures of people with a digital camera.  They then give them a card with a number that they use to view the picture on the web site.  From the site, they can save the picture or e-mail to anyone they want.  They also have the opportunity to sign up for a free 5x7 photo.  When they sign up, they give their phone number and someone from JoePix calls them for an interview.  This was my favorite outreach so far this summer, and I think that we will be doing it again before the summer is over.  Below are links to a (bad) picture of me standing on Daytona Beach and to the bios of all the people on project that helped with the JoePix outreach (I should be on page 7).   urlLink http://www.joepix.com/cc02a/index.cfm?ptd=gp.cfm&u=3739661249    urlLink http://www.joepix.com/cc02a/index.cfm?ptd=meettheteam.cfm   I spent all day sunday at Magic Kingdom.  This time, there were about 15 people that went.  I had a really good time, and I feel that I am even starting to overcome my fear of thrill rides.  However, I have been told that the rides at Disney are pretty calm, so I am interested to see how I would do on bigger roller coasters now.  Last night we went to H2O Church, a new church here in Orlando.  They will be having 7 meetings before the church actually starts.  Last night was meeting number 5.  These meetings are just to get people interested and to work out any problems before they start full time.  These first few meetings have taken place in a country western bar in downtown Orlando.  The goal of the church is to attract a youger crowd that may not enjoy an average church service.  They do this by beginning the meeting by having their band perform a few popular  cover songs.  They then have a speaker, and ebd the meeting with praise songs. The praise and worship was very good and was also much more energetic than most people are used to.  After the meeting, people hang out and talk or play pool.  The church also provides coffee and punch.  It's too bad the church isn't going full time yet.  I would like to go there every week.  Here is the link to the church's web site:   urlLink http://www.h2ochurch.org/   This has just been an interesting week since this is the first time the students have run everything with the staff gone.  Well, I think that's about all I have for now.  See ya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      From Friday, July 12, 2002...  Once again, I forgot to do this e-mail earlier in the day, so now I have to hurry to get it done before I leave for the week.  Saturday, we had the Brady Bunch (my planning team) scavenger hunt. The students and staff were broken up into groups and had to go around with a camera, taking pictures of their group with a random list of things. The list included, a bathtub, toilet, animal, etc. Everyone had a really great time making fools of themselves. That night we had a "Date Night With Jesus." We went off alone around our residential community and had a couple hours to just sit and pray. This was a great time to just reflect on what we have learned here in Orlando.  On Sunday our condo participated in our first creative date of the summer. This is where one condo asks another condo to do something for an evening, usually without telling that condo what will be going on. It's just a fun way to get to know everyone better. A girl's condo asked us out, so we went over to their house at 6pm Sunday night. When we arrived, they blindfolded us and loaded us into their cars. They then drove us around for a while to make sure we couldn't tell where they were taking us. When they took off the blindfolds, we were back at the Lake Hart headquarters. They had reserved one of the conference rooms for us to eat pizza and watch a movie. It was a pretty big surprise to us, and we had a pretty good time.  Wednesday night was our last core group meeting with the staff. We went over to Mike's house and he made us dinner again. Mike is my discipler, and he is just an awesome guy... and a really good cook. He has cooked a large meal for our core group every week so far. I don't know how we can pay him back for all the meals he has provided. He will be around the headquarters for the rest of the summer, so we will think of something to do.  This was the staff's last week to be involved in the project. Last night we had a farewell party, and I was on the team planning the event. We ate dinner here at the headquarters and then had a random facts competition as we transitioned to the next part of the evening. We then watched the videos that each condo was responsible to make during the last few weeks. Most of them were really funny. After the videos, everyone had a chance to say something to all the staff and thank them for their hard work on this project. After sharing, everyone broke up into their core groups to pray for their discipler. I felt like the night went really well, and I hope that we were able to express how much we love the staff. Now we are completely in charge of the project. The student leaders have been named, and we are on our own. Next week should be very interesting.  Well, that's all I have for this week. This weekend should be a blast! I am going to the beach for an outreach and to Disney world on Sunday, but I can talk about that more next week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I forgot that it was Friday and I almost forgot to send out my weekly e-mail.  The web team was given the day off today, but I decided to come to work anyway.  I needed to get some stuff done, and if I didn't go to work, I would just be sitting around all day watching t.v.  I got to work around 10am instead of the normal 8am, so I did get to sleep in a bit.  Last Friday was men's night.  All the guys on project met outside the headquarters right after work.  We divided up by condos and had a couple challenging activities that forced us to work as a team.  After the activities we had a steak dinner, and then went to the conference room.  A couple of the staff guys gave a lesson on authentic manhood.  I have heard about this series before, but I had never gone through it at all.  We received a basic overview of the lesson Friday night.  After the lesson, the staff made us milk shakes using power drills.  It was very interesting.  We had another outreach Saturday morning.  Since the car wash was canceled, we split up into teams and went to various places.  About half of the project went to a church that was playing the Jesus film to a bunch of children.  Some groups went to malls, and my group decided to go to the Airport.  The outreach went very well, and I was actually able to share with someone for the first time.  I was also able to have my very first Cinnabon.  After the outreach Saturday, we decided to spend Sunday at MGM Studios, one of the 4 Diseney World theme parks.  Darian, Joey (a staff guy), and I were the only ones that actually went.  We went to church at 8:30am and then headed to the park right after church.  This was the first time I had ever been to Disney World, and I had a great time!  I actually went on all the rides, including the Rock 'n' Roller Coaster and the Tower of Terror.  I told myself that I would never go on the Tower of Terror before I even arrived in Orlando, but I ended up riding it twice!  Wednesday night was our International Dinner.  It was nothing like I expected.  It was a very good lesson about evangelism and the state of Christianity throughout the world.  We had another outreach last night for the 4th of July.  We went to see the fireworks at a lake in downtown Orlando.  There were tons of people to talk to.  Most of the people that we talked to were already Christian, and two of them used to be on staff at the Crusade headquarters!  That was really weird.  Well, I guess that's all for now.  Let me know if you have any questions about what I've been up to.  Bye!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once again, I forgot to post this last Friday:  Wow, I can hardly believe that it is week three already! Time seems to be moving so fast here. Work is still alot of fun. I took a break from designing the OSP web site to take pictures for a few days. I took pictures around the office of every student on the project. I am going to use them on the web site eventually. Yesterday, the whole web team went out to have a paper airplane competition to see who could get their plane to go the furthest. My plane actually went the furthest, but then two of my supervisors rolled a rock up into a piece of paper and threw them. It sounds like cheating, but they did it to prove the point that sometimes we need to be creative and think "outside the box."  Our outreach didn't start until 12pm on Saturday, so I was actually able to get 10 hours of sleep! It was so nice to sleep in. Saturday we went to Downtown Disney to do surveys and to share our faith. It actually stopped raining for a while too. It wasn't long before security noticed that we were taping some people and they asked us to leave and not to do any more surveys. Soon after that, it started raining really hard. I still haven't had an opportunity to share with anyone here. I have never done that before, so I am really nervous.  Saturday night, the girls decided to have their own little dance party, but it was for girls only. The guys responded by having a movie night for guys only. We bonded that night... literally... that's all I am going to say about that.  Sunday I went to another church called Discovery. I liked it alot. The pastor was really good, and they had good praise and worship too. I am going to stick with that chruch for the summer. Sunday night, a bunch of us went bowling. I normally don't like bowling, but I really had a good time. I scored a 140, which is my highest score ever!  This week was the first main event that was planned by the students. I thought it was the best one so far. It was also the first time that the student praise band played. It was a really good time. We also had a couple meetings this week, like core groups and planning teams. I also went to see the Borne Identity last night. It was pretty good. We were all thinking that like spies after watching it though.  Tonight is men's night. I'm not sure what is going on, but we received a note in our condo this morning, and I had the same one on my desk when I got to work. It just says that our condo has been chosen for a special mission, and we are to meet in the parking lot at 5:30pm. It says to be dressed in shorts and a t-shirt. I am kinda worried about that. Our car wash outreach for tomorrow was canceled because they think it is going to rain again. We are going to do something else, but I am not sure what that will be.  I guess that's all for now. Once again, I am sorry if this was too long. I tried not to put too much in here, so if you have any questions or want to know more, just e-mail me sometime. Bye!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alright, I completely forgot to send out my weekly e-mail Friday.  I have been extremely busy at work as I am trying to get the OSP 2002 web site finished before everyone leaves project.  I need to get 73 copies of the web site on CDs to give one to all the people on project.  There are going to be over 1000 photos on the site.  Last Saturday, we had another car wash outreach.  We only had about 5 cars for the first one because it rained most of the day.  This time it didn't rain and we had so many cars that we couldn't keep up!  I'm told that it was probably about 30 or more cars.  On top of that, there were 3 people that made decisions to accept Christ!  There might have even been more that I didn't hear about as well.  Saturday night we had S.A.L.T. groups (Sharing and Learning Together).  This was just a time to meet with about 5 other people to share in dinner and conversation.  There were several very good conversations during our time.  On Sunday Darian and I were able to borrow a truck from one of the guys on project to go to Epcot.  That place is really cool, and they have great food there as well!  It didn't take us the entire day to cover pretty much everything in the park, so we were able to jump over to MGM for the remainder of the day.  We found a place there that makes peanut putter and jelly milk shakes.  Whoever thought of that is a genius!  My brother called to tell me that he has been having a few computer problems lately.  He was playing a game in my computer at home, and he heard several noises coming from the computer.  He then heard a loud pop.  When he opened the CD-ROM drive, he found the CD in thousands of little pieces.  I guess the CD-ROM drive blew up the CD.  That is one of the weirdest things that has ever happened to my computer.  I guess I will be ordering a new CD-ROM drive this week.  Well, that's pretty much all I have for week 9.  I'm sure I will have much more for week 10 since it is the last week of project.  Bye! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      This last week has been very interesting. This is why I am sending out my weekly e-mail today instead of last Friday. Sorry if this e-mail is a little long, but I have quite a bit to talk about this week.  Last Fiday (July 26), we had men's and women's time. The guys went to the West Building conference room and had a panel of women come in to answer questions. It was a very interesting time to find out more about the differences between men and women. I think everyone would agree that even though we had over an hour, we wish that there could have been more time for questions.  Saturday I went on an outreach to Cocoa Beach. I only talked to 2 people, but they were both very good conversations. The first guy was a Christian that attends a Southern Babtist church in Massachusetts. The second guy was an agnostic that grew up in a Jewesh reformed church. I wasn't able to talk to him much about Christianity because he was not interested in it at all.  I went with a large group of people to Universal Studios Islands of Adventure on Sunday. I was not planning on going because tickets were so expensive, but since there were 28 of us going, we were able to get a huge discount. This was also one place that I was very afraid to go since I have always been afraid of roller coasters. I decided to go anyway, and I had a great time. In fact, I think I am just about cured of my fear of roller coasters. Darian and I went on the Incredible Hulk Coaster 6 times! I loved that thing! I also went on the Dueling Dragons three times (the world's first near miss roller coaster), and I went on Spider Man twice. You can find more info about these rides and watch short videos by visiting the link below.   urlLink Islands of Adventure   Monday was my twenty-second birthday, but since I was so tired from Islands of Adventure, I didn't really do anything that night. I just made some phone calls and went to bed. I had a really good day though. It's funny because the week started out great, but got sorta crazy at the end.  I had been planning to go to the Warped Tour for a few weeks. The tour was in Orlando on Friday (Aug. 2), starting at 11am. I had asked to have Friday off from work a couple weeks in advance. My supervisor (Tim) said that if it was up to him, I could have the day off, but he wanted to check with the staff project directors first. Since the staff were officially off the project, I went to talk to the student directors. Since it would be a free night, they were fine with me taking the day off of work since I wouldn't be missing any project activities. At this point I was almost positive that I would be able to get the day off, so I continued planning and I even went to buy my ticket. I probably should have talked to the staff first.  Over the next two weeks, I had not heard a definite answer from Tim. I asked him a couple times, but he still needed to talk to the staff. Finally, on Thursday, the day before the Warped Tour, he had talked to the staff and had an answer for me. He was out of the office for the day, so he called me in the afternoon. The staff told him that there was no policy against him giving me the day off, but they strongly recommended that he didn't give me the day off. Therefore, Tim decided to say no.  I was very upset, and I spent the rest of the day trying to figure out what to do. I decided to go into work at 5:30am so that I could ask to leave work early. Tim decided to let me leave at 1pm, and another girl on project was kind enough to give me a ride to the Warped Tour. I was three hours late, but I was actually able to see all the bands that I wanted to see.  I learned a valuable lesson from this experience. No matter how hard I tried, I could not control the situation, but God was in control. I know this whole thing might sound kinda stupid, but I really wanted to go to the Warped Tour. I had been looking forward to it all summer. Everything seemed to fall apart at the last minute. Last Wednesday, we had lunch with Steve Douglass (President of Campus Crusade). He talked about being in constant communication with God. He said that little things happen every day that can give you a bad attitude. If you are in constant communication with God, it becomes very difficult to be in a bad attitude, no matter what happens. I also went to H2O Church again on Thursday. We sang two songs that had words that really spoke to me: "Be glorified in me" and "I'm trding my sorrows for the joy of the Lord." I don't feel that I was glorifying God on Thursday through my actions, and I know that I wasn't trading my sorrows for the joy of the Lord.  I know that this was really long, but it's something that I have been thinking about this weekend. I guess that's all I have for now. See ya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I talked to Dr. MacFarland today for an hour about the movie.  He was able to answer the questions that we had about production.  He suggested that we avoid using copyrighted music as much as possible.  He did not feel that music would even be very necessary for the movie.  For microphones, he suggested using a shotgun (hyper-cardioid) microphone for close up shots.  We would need to get it as close as possible, under the camera, and pointed directly at the person speaking.  We may also want to hide microphones in the room, or place microphones on the actors.  All the microphones will need to be connected to a small mixer and recorded separate from the video.  He suggested not to use any additional lighting for the outdoor shots.  There are a few lights available for checkout, but Im not sure if we will need them.  We will probably just use one camera for shooting.  This will make things a bit slower, but I think it will also make things much easier.  I was told that the radio studios are open on the weekdays from 8:00am to 5:00pm.  We will need to get in there to record the voice-overs.  Dr. Mac gave me some pointers for recording the internal monologue.  He said to keep the microphone as close as possible.  Dont put it directly in front of the persons mouth, keep it to the side.  This way, the microphone wont pick up popping from the speech.  The person talking should also talk softly, as though they are speaking into someones ear.  For the shots where we need to move the camera, he suggested getting a kids wagon and laying down a long stretch of carpet to roll it on.  The bigger the wheels, the better.  For the script itself, he suggested that we break up the monologue into smaller parts, so that there is not any long sequence of talking without any action.  Also, he suggested that we give as much action to the dialogue scenes as possible.  Dont let these scenes be too passive.  Instead of the spinning box shot that we had in mind, we may have to show a shot of the box spinning, then fade to a shot of the spinning room.  From this, the audience should be able to understand that the characters are looking at the box.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went over to Clint and Davids room in Marlatt to scout the locations that we will be shooting the movie.  The majority of the movie will actually take place in their room.  This is where the dialogue between the four main characters will take place.  My two primary concerns for the movie are lighting and sound.  Since most of the movie is dialogue, good sound will be crucial to the movies success.  We came up with some more questions that need to be answered.   Is there any time that we would be able to use the radio studios in McCain to record the voice-overs for the movie? How could we get smooth shots while walking? Is it possible to edit out the singing in a song?   Another problem we are trying to figure out is a dream sequence in the script.  Clint and David would like the scene to take place on the beach, but we have no beaches.  Shots involving sand are not a problem.  We can shoot those looking down onto a sand volleyball court.  But we have no way to simulate the ocean.  So far, the best idea we have is to shoot the scene in front of a green screen, then chroma key ocean footage into the shots in post-production.  We may also be able to get away with not showing the water at all, and we could add sounds of the ocean in the background.  We also need to find some harp music to play during the dream.  There is also a complicated shot of the box spinning in the middle of the room.  From the spinning box, we want to pan up to a spinning shot of the room with the four main characters looking at the box.  We have no idea how to do this.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I met with Clint and David tonight to discuss the movie.  They asked me a bunch of questions about what they could do for various scenes in the movie.  The discussion brought up several questions that needed to be answered before production began.   What do we need to do in order to use copyrighted music in the movie? What kind of microphone(s) should we use for the movie? What kind of lighting techniques should be used for the night scene? What lights are available from the Mass Comm. Department? Can we check out two cameras at once? Are there lights that would not require power outlets? What is the best way to combine background noises in the scenes with dialogue?   They also had established a schedule for the production.   March 30: scout shooting locations at 1:00pm April 6: shooting in afternoon and evening April 7: shooting from 10:00pm - 12:00am April 8: shooting from 10:00pm - 12:00am April 9: shooting from 10:00pm - 12:00am April 10: shooting after Crusade meeting April 13: shooting (if needed) April 14-21: post-production   This schedule gives us one more week for pre-production, one week for production, and a little over a week for post-production.  Version 2 of the script was e-mailed to me today.  It is currently being edited and finalized.  I told David to begin drawing some story boards for the movie.  I feel that this will enable shooting to go a little more smoothly because it will make him think about his shots ahead of time.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Clint e-mailed me the script for the movie today.  The movie will be about a guy that is given a box that holds the secret to understanding women.  The estimated time for the movie will be about 20 to 25 minutes.  At this length we will be able to submit it to the UPC Student Film Contest in the short film category, and to the Damah Film Festival in the 30 minute category.  Entries for the UPC Film Contest are due in the UPC office by 5:00pm on April 21.  The Damah entries must be postmarked by May 15.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally got the entire movie to print to tape without any problems.  I reinstalled my firewire card and shut down everything, including background programs.  I think the problem might have been a couple Norton Anti-virus programs that were running in the background, but Im not sure.  All I know is that it worked!  Now I can delete the 10GB of video off my hard drive and do it all over again for version 2 of the movie.  I fixed up the intro a bit today.  I changed around the credits and changed the title to what David was wanting.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      David came over today to talk about the changes he wanted for the final version of the movie.  We watched the movie as I wrote down all of the changes.  I am still having problems getting the movie to print to tape correctly.  The video keeps cutting out at random times.  I dont know why it keeps doing it.  I know its not the camera now, and its not the video editing software.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didnt work on much today.  I did get the Bible verse added to the end of the movie.  I forgot to add it before, but no one seemed to notice.  I have also been getting things together for my MC490 project.  I need to have everything turned in either tomorrow or Tuesday.  My class presentation will be next Thursday.  I need to get everything finished up so that I can turn in my copy of the script and my tape logs.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      After getting a few hours of sleep, I dragged myself out of bed to print the movie to a MiniDV tape so that I could dub it to VHS for the contest.  The first version that I rendered had some problems, but I had a few hours to fix it and make some additions.  I added more music to the second version.  Originally, I decided not to use the music because of time, but the final rendering was much quicker than I thought it would be, so I had time to add the music.  However, the last few songs that I added had to be done within a matter of minutes, so I will want to go back and redo it later.  The only other changes that I made were with audio levels and transitions.  Everything seemed to be working just fine except for printing to the MiniDV camera.  The file rendered without any problems, but for some reason, both versions that I put on MiniDV had a few spots where the video cut out.  Im not sure if the problem is coming from the camera or from my computer.  The second version wasnt too bad, and since I was out of time, I just had to put that version on VHS for the contest.  I went to the UPC office around 5:00pm to submit what will be the final version of the movie... for now at least.  I still have about a week to make any changes that are needed before the movie must be submitted to the Kan Film Festival.  I can already think of many things that need to be fixed.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonight I had to finish rendering all of my final test scenes to show David and Clint what the final movie would look like all put together.  To do this, I simply put all of my latest rendered test scenes into my Winamp playlist.  We werent able to see all of the scene transitions or hear the music through this, but we were able to get a sense of the overall flow of the movie.  I spent the rest of the night quickly finishing any scenes that werent quite complete and adjusting audio.  I then did a final rendering of each scene and put them together with the music before rendering the complete movie.  After all of this I was finally able to go to bed around 6:30am.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Franks dream (Scene 12) was completed today.  I just need to add the music to it.  I brightened it up quite a bit to make it seem more like a dream.  I just hope I didnt overdo it.  David seemed to like it.  David and Clint came over this afternoon to look at what I had done and also to go over what they wanted to change for some of the scenes.  I finished putting together scene 13 while they were here and began working on the new version of Thomas dream.  I showed them scenes 14 and 15 since I forgot to render it and send it to them.  I finished putting together Thomas dream tonight.  It required some audio editing as I had to cut up the music that David wanted for the dream.  I think it will work out nicely.  The one other thing that I completed today was the intro., which includes scene 1 and the opening credits.  Im not sure if it is what David was wanting, but I think it looks pretty good.  As far as I can tell, there are just a few minor changes that need to be made.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was able to get a camera from Kedzie today.  Its just a cheap Canon ZR40 camera, but it should work for capturing and printing to tape.  One problem that I had with it was that I cannot make it start recording in play mode without the remote, and I do not have the remote.  I just needed to do this so that I could stripe some of my tapes.  I do think it will work when I print to tape because I will do it from my computer and I will give it a time code to start on.  I continued working on scene 13 today.  Its just about completed.  I also finished up Franks dream.  I think it looks pretty good, and David seemed to like it.  David will be coming over tomorrow afternoon to tell me what changes he is wanting for some of the scenes.  I really want to have a completed rough cut of the entire movie finished by tomorrow night.  I will then have all day Sunday and most of Monday to make any sound and color changes that will be needed.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didnt get much done today.  I began working on scene 13 a bit.  I also noticed that there is some footage on my tapes that I neglected to capture, and I have to have this footage.  I was planning on getting a camera for the weekend anyway, so I can just capture that stuff tomorrow.  I also started getting sick today.  I hope that I get better soon because I really need to get this movie done by Monday!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished putting together several scenes today, including scenes 2, 4 through 9, 11, 14, and 15.  I have not adjusted any of the audio levels in these scenes yet, and many of the shots still need to have a few color fixes.  So far, the people that have viewed these scenes have been pleased.  There were only a few minor changes that needed to be made.  By the way, here is a listing of the scenes in which I have broken the script into and a brief description of each:   Scene 1 - opening credits; Daren praying with voice-over Scene 2 - old man giving Daren the box Scene 3 - Darens room; Daren calls friends Scene 4 - Luke gets phone call in his bathroom Scene 5 - Thomas gets phone call in his room Scene 6 - Frank gets phone call in his room Scene 7 - dialogue about the box 1 Scene 8 - Luke gets slapped Scene 9 - dialogue about the box 2 Scene 10 - Thomas dream Scene 11 - everyone wakes up Scene 12 - Franks dream Scene 13 - dialogue about the box 3 Scene 14 - Franks bathroom Scene 15 - girl walks out of the bathroom Scene 16 - end credits 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Editing continued today as I put together the three phone call scenes, most of the old man scene, Thomas dream, and some more of the first section of dialogue.  I think I have discovered a couple missing shots that may cause some problems.  Hopefully I can find a way to fix it so that we dont have to re-shoot anything.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I began editing the movie today.  I started with the first set of dialogue.  I think we may be missing a few shots that David requested, but so far nothing too crucial.  I have never had to edit anything this big, so it may take me a little while to figure out the best way to put it all together.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I didnt get much of the footage logged and captured before today, so I had to work all day to get it finished.  I needed to get it done before the camera was due back so I didnt have to check it out again.  I spent about 12 hours logging and capturing today.  I didnt get done until about 4:30am.  I didnt split up the scenes on the last tape as much as I wanted to, and I ended up just capturing the entire last tape.  At least I have it done and I can start editing now.  One problem that I noticed when watching the footage was that the night shots from the old man scene are really dark.  I knew that they would be dark, but they are a lot darker than I expected.  But I played around with it, and I think that I can fix it up.  I would just like to note that after capturing the footage for this movie there are 186 video clips for a total of 24.3GB of space.  Im glad that I was actually able to clear enough space off my hard drive so it would all fit!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I talked to Michael Pule about logging my dialogue footage.  He suggested that I write an in-point and out-point for each clip.  He also suggested the numbering method that I was considering.  I think it will be best if I just do both.  Clint sent me Davids final version of the script today.  It includes all the shots that he wanted for each scene.  I am going to meet up with Clint in McCain on Thursday to record his monologue.  In the final version of the script, the monologue for the phone call scenes has been removed.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I returned all the equipment to Dole Hall today, but Bambi let me check out another camera for the weekend so that I can capture the footage.  This time I just got one of the Sony TRV900 cameras.  I asked Bambi if she knew the best way to log tapes for dialogue.  Since I have so much dialogue footage, I was not sure what would be the best way to do this.  She checked some books for me, but she was not sure what would be best.  I might just write the first part of the characters line.  I also might number the lines on the script and use the numbers to reference the video clips.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      We are done shooting!  Tonight we finished up our shooting schedule.  Now we just have to hope that everything we shot will work out in post-production.  If not, we may have to meet sometime next week to re-shoot some scenes.  Now I have about a week and a half to edit the movie before we have to submit it to the UPC contest.  There are now three and a half tapes full of footage.  Chris home-made camera dolly seemed to work pretty well.  It makes quite a bit of noise, so we will have to put some sound into the shots separately.  There was one shot that we wanted to get with the dolly that didnt quite work out.  We wanted to have the camera move backwards, away from Daren, while zooming in at the same time.  This would give a cool effect of the background stretching.  This is used in many movies such as Lord of the Rings.  They probably do it differently though.  Anyway, it didnt really work out because I could not keep the camera very steady.  I hope that we got all the shots we needed for the old man scene.  We started shooting later than we would have liked, so we had to shoot in a hurry.  We still didnt get done until 1:00 or 1:30am.  We may have to go back and get a few more shots.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I e-mailed Bambi my question about the different settings on the Sony shotgun microphone yesterday.  She didnt have an answer for me, but she forwarded my e-mail to Gary Pettet, the engineer for the school.  Gary sent me a response today.   The switch you are referring to is a low cutoff switch.  If you were to look at the Directionality chart you would see a tapering off of the pickup pattern from M, M1, to V.  You would use the switch according to the ambient  acoustic conditions of the room. Say for example you wanted a concert hall effect or pickup of the whole room use the M (music) position which is the full range around the mic.  Use the M1 position to say make it more directional to stop a boomy sound due to bounce from the floor or  reduce wind noise.  This is the proximity effect.  Use the V or Voice position to make it more directional and obtain clearer speech for someone talking from a distance.  If you are too close to some one talking and you have a boomy voice set the position to M for more cut off and broaden the pickup pattern.  So the best way is to have on a good pair of headphones and listen for the best listening results.   Well, I screwed up today.  I forgot to return the equipment to Kedzie and re-check it out.  It looks like I will be paying a fine for that.  I cant believe I forgot.  This is the first time I have done that since I have been using equipment from Kedzie.  I guess I was just a little tired.  We finished up shooting the all of the dialogue scenes tonight.  We ran late again, but at least we are finished with it.  The only major problem we had was that the actors spent too much time laughing.  I guess thats why we went late again.  We also finished off our third tape tonight.  That is way more footage than I was expecting to get.  It should make things interesting in post-production.  All that we have left to shoot tomorrow night is a few more slaps for Lukes flashback and the old man scene.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      We began shooting the main dialogue tonight.  The dialogue is very important because it will make up the majority of the movie.  I am told that the overall time on the dialogue should be about 12 to 15 minutes.  Before starting the dialogue, we got a few shots of Daren.  The most difficult of the night was him on his knees praying.  David wanted shots rotating around him.  In order to do this, we tried using Chris home-made steadycam.  It seemed to work alright, but we had trouble getting shots around Daren because of the small room.  It became difficult to get the shots without seeing one of the lights or a reflection off of the TV or something.  Well see how it works in post.  The biggest problem we encountered tonight was when we began shooting Thomas dialogue.  After setting up the lights and the camera, we noticed that there was a terrible reflection on Thomas glasses.  We tried to move the lights to every possible location, but we had no luck eliminating the reflections.  He had to wear the glasses for two reasons: it fit his character, and we had already shot some scenes with him wearing glasses.  Finally, we decided to just remove the lenses, hoping that no one would be able to notice that they were gone.  I think that this will actually work out very well.  The other main concern of the night was with lighting.  I tried to eliminate as many shadows from the shot as possible without making things worse.  I dont think I did a very good job.  This is my first experience with lighting and I feel clueless.  Shadows are my biggest concern with lighting.  Im pretty sure that I can fix any color or brightness problems in post-production.  Once again we went over schedule for the night.  I dont think we finished until after 1:00am.  Hopefully the guys will learn their lines a little better by tomorrow night so that we can get through the script a little faster and get the shots for each character.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was the second day of shooting, this time entirely indoors.  We shot the three phone call scenes.  We were supposed to begin shooting the dialogue scene, but we ran out of time even though we ended up staying 30 minutes longer than scheduled.  This means that we are officially behind schedule.  There was only one scene that we completed in one take.  The others had to be re-shot multiple times for various reasons.  In Franks phone call scene, there were focus problems when using auto focus.  I would have used manual focus the entire time, but the shot required me to pan and zoom at the same time.  I would have needed a third hand in order to focus manually.  I actually gained a third hand when I had David switch to manual focus in the middle of the shot.  This solved the focus problem.  The most tricky and time-consuming scene of the night was Lukes phone call in the bathroom.  First of all, lighting was not very good.  There was only flourescent lighting in the bathroom and practically no room for our additional lighting.  The result was a shot with poor color.  However, the biggest problem came from the mirror featured in the shot.  It became difficult to get only the things we wanted to appear in the mirror.  There were a few takes with other people appearing in the mirror as well as a few takes with the boom mic making an appearance.  After 6 takes, we were finally able to get the shot.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was the first day of shooting.  We were supposed to begin at 2:00pm, but I didnt know that.  We didnt start until about 2:30pm or so, and finished up around 8:30pm as we watched the footage from the day.  We had a pizza break at 5:30pm, which was really nice.  The biggest problem of the day was the rain.  It was very nice weather last week, now its cold and rainy.  We had to get most of our outdoor shots today because we couldnt get all the actors later this week.  Everything just looked pretty wet.  I forgot to white balance a couple of the first shots, but color didnt matter too much because we are going to have to change it in post-production anyway.  The shot of Thomas writing on the window did not come out as well as I had hoped.  The characters were very dark when in front of the window.  We tried to put light on them from the back, but it did not help much.  By increasing the size of the iris, I could make the characters easier to see, but the writing on the window became almost impossible to see.  I found a place somewhere in between, but the characters were still difficult to see.  I am hoping that I can fix it a little bit in post-production, but Im not sure that it is possible.  When shooting the scene where Daren follows the girl walking out of the bathroom, I encountered a few minor problems with the tripod.  The tripod holds the camera steady only when I am not touching it.  For this shot, I needed to zoom out, then pan right, then left.  This caused the beginning of the shot to be a little bumpy.  Once I zoomed back out, the shot seemed very stable.  I will try to steady the shot in post-production.  On a couple takes I noticed that the camera was having a few problems focusing.  I used manual focus for a few shots during the day, and I think that I am going to use manual focus as much as possible from now on.  I had more problems with lighting and shadows in the twinkie scene.  I hope we can figure something out for tomorrow night.  I started a tape log for everything that was shot today.  I am listing the start and end times for each shot, as well as a description.  This log will have a complete listing of what we are shooting each day.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was able to get the equipment from Kedzie without too much trouble.  It has been a while since the last time I had to check out equipment for a weekend, so I forgot that I needed to get a weekend checkout form.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Chris and I talked to Bambi today and told her what we were going to need for the movie.  She hooked us up with a Sony PD150 camera, a nice tripod, and a light kit from Dole Hall.  I have the equipment checked out until Friday, April 11.  I just realized that I may run into problems picking up the audio equipment from Kedzie tomorrow because of my class schedule (it also has a bit to do with me having problems getting out of bed earlier in the morning).  Ill figure something out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I talked to Bambi after class today about getting a camera and other equipment.  She said that she can get me what we will need for the next week of shooting.  She wanted me to come back tomorrow at 3:00pm because she had to get to another class and she said that she would have more time tomorrow.  Bambi also introduced me to Per Malm, who has been working on a feature-length movie as well as several other video projects.  He is in one of my classes and I knew he was working on a movie, but I had never talked to him about it.  Per was able to give me a few more suggestions for shooting.  He suggested that we use two lights for the dorm room scene.  The lights will need to be pointed towards the corners of the room, and we will use reflectors to bounce the light back at the actors.  One will be used sort of like a key light and the other as a fill light.  He said that we will probably want more lights for the night scene with the old man.  As for sound, Per said that the shotgun/boom microphone would be good to use.  He also said that the lavaliere microphones worked well for his movie, even when they were placed under clothing.  During the test run, we found that the only microphone that will really work well for us is the shotgun microphone.  The other microphones we tried were lavaliere, cardioid, and omni-directional.  These microphones either picked up too much unwanted noise or picked up very little sound at all.  Of all the equipment that I checked out from Kedzie, I think we will only want to use the shotgun microphone, a mixing board, and two XLR cables.  I am hoping that this equipment is not used much by other students so that I wont have to worry about reserving equipment.  The shotgun microphone is a Sony condenser microphone, model C-76.  There are three settings for turning it on: M, M1, and V1.  I have no idea how these differ from each other.  I tried to find the manual for it on Sonys web site, but I could not find one.  Here is the current list of equipment that we will need:   camera tripod shotgun microphone XLR cables (2) mixing board camera dolly home-made steady cam light kit (from Dole) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to check out equipment in Kedzie today.  I found out that almost all the cameras had been moved over to Dole Hall.  I will try to talk to Bambi tomorrow to see if I can get a camera from there.  Most of the other equipment that I needed was at Kedzie.  I was told that if I want to check it out for about a week (which I need to do), then I need a note from my professor.  I will be picking up the sound equipment from Kedzie for our test run tomorrow night.  Here is a list of the equipment I would like to get for the test run tomorrow night:   camera (Sony TRV900 or PD150) tripod (a good one that can move easily) mixing board (small; at least 4 microphone inputs) shotgun microphone (or boom microphone) light reflectors microphone stands omnidirectional microphones (2-4) cardioid microphones (2-4) MiniDisc player/recorder lavaliere microphones (2-4)   I have an Archos Jukebox Recorder that has a 20GB hard drive and can record in mp3 format.  I would prefer to use the Archos rather than the MiniDisc player because it would transfer digitally.  The minidisc player can only do analog.  I talked to Chris about helping with the production of the movie.  He was very interested in helping out.  He even said that he has a camera dolly that we could use.  I sent him a copy of the script.  Chris made a few suggestions for changing the script.  He typed it all up and sent it to me.  We will probably discuss the changes during the test run tomorrow night.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have some rather sad news.  I found out today that  urlLink Wesley Willis  died.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Google  is sweet!  They just updated the Google Toolbar so that it now has a blogger button among other things.  I thought I would take a moment to try it out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just want to say happy birthday to my brother Ben before I forget... Happy Birthday Ben!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I visited Manhattan this weekend.  I went with my mom to help my sister move into her house for the school year.  I was really excited to go because I was able to see Jermaine and hang out with her for a little bit.  I had not seen her since Darian's wedding.  This was also the first time that I had been back to Manhattan sice I graduated.  I stayed with Adam Saturday night in Putnam Hall.  That was really weird.  I felt like I should be moving back into Putnam or something.  It still doesn't quite feel like I should be out of school now.  I am really going to miss it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I think I am going to actually start posting updates on this blog again.  I just noticed that it has been exactly one year ago yesterday that I made my last post.  That was from when I returned from Florida last summer.  It's hard to believe that it was a year ago already.  The Orlando Summer Project 2002 just had a one-year reunion this last weekend.  I was not able to attend, but I heard that it was a lot of fun.  Hopefully I will be able to make the next one.  I just received the Family Guy: Volume One DVD set today.  I had never watched that show until this summer.  It's too bad Fox had to go and cancel it.  It's a very funny show.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is another link related to that Hulk Coaster story.   urlLink local6.com - News - Woman Dies Days After Ride On 'Hulk' Coaster 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just found out that someone died from riding the Hulk Coaster at Islands of Adventure in Orlando, Florida.  Darian and I rode that thing six times in one day last summer.   urlLink The Hulk Hype! - The latest Hulk news and rumors 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, people in Alabama take football a little too seriously.   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF - Man shoots at son's head after Bama defeat 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      apparently, it's couch, not coutch...  i am so dumb...  hey darian, i found a couple other typos in that blog.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to see Matchstick Men tonight.  It was a very good movie.  You have to love Nicolas Cage.  He was great in Adaptation and he was great in Matchstick Men.  The movie has a few surprises, and I just love movies with surprises.  The other movie that came out this weekend that I would like to see is Once Upon a Time in Mexico.  Robert Rodriguez is the biggest reason for me wanting to see this movie.  I have been reading his book as well as some articles about him.  He has some really interesting things to say about filmmaking and a very interesting story.  Darian went to see Once Upon a Time in Mexico, and he said it has some cool violence.  It looks like I will be making another trip to the movie theater tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I have been rather slow about getting updates posted.  Here is one that should have been posted a week ago...  I returned to Wichita last Saturday after spending a week in Manhattan.  A whole week at school without the classes.  Living in Putnam, moving from coutch to couch (it was actually only 2).  I even took my computer so that I could get some work done... although I didn't get as much done as I would have liked.  But anyway, I was able to go to a couple football games, eat in the dining centers, hang out with some friends, and even find time to apply for a job.  It was a good time.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is kinda old, but it is wicked cool!   urlLink We should all have this PC case 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy Halloween!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This program sounds interesting...   urlLink Career Connection: Association of Independent Feature Film Producers Article, Film and Television 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Relient K released a Christmas CD.  You can listen to the songs on their web site.   urlLink relient k -- deck the halls, bruise your hand 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a pretty cool site.  It has a bunch of short stories that you can read.   urlLink short stories at east of the web 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think Ebert and Roeper need to modify their rating system a bit.  Thumbs up and thumbs down just doesn't cut it sometimes.  The new rating system could go something like this:  good movies would get a thumbs up, bad movies would get a thumbs down, and if there is a movie they absolutly hate, they could give it a big middle finger.  Just a thought.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you are into DVDs, then you might want to check out FreeDVDs.com.  So far, it has been well worth my time.  You have to sign up for offers to get points, and then you use your points to get free DVDs.  Many of the offers cost like a dollar or two, but it's totally worth it!  Let me know if you want to sign up, because I think I get a few points for every person I talk into joining.   urlLink FreeDVDs.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think that I need to start a section on my web site for movie reviews.  I am just sick of sites that give good movies bad reviews.  Some people just don't know what they are talking about when it comes to movies.  Can you believe that the  urlLink  Hulk   only has an average rating of 6.2 on  urlLink IMDB ?  That movie has totally changed the way I look at editing, and it was the best looking comic book movie I have ever seen!  Alright, I guess that's enough about the  Hulk  for now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished reading  urlLink  Rebel Without a Crew   yesterday.  The second half of the book went really fast because I didn't want to put it down.  Most of the things  urlLink Robert Rodriguez  wrote in that book seemed made up because it just sounded too good to be true.  Even he said repeatedly in the book that he didn't think his new found fame would last.  He said it would all probably wear off within a few days.  Anyone at all interested in making movies should definitely check out this book.  Now I need to find a new book to read.  I've been having trouble sleeping lately.  I don't know why.  I have been going to bed pretty late, but it still shouldn't take me over an hour to fall asleep.  I hope this doesn't keep happening.  I spent most of today driving around, running errands.  My mom had a job interview at Bed, Bath, and Beyond.  She wants to get another job to make a little extra money for Christmas.  While she was at her interview, My brother Zach and I went a few places.  We checked out a new store here in Wichita called Ultimate Electronics.  The place seems really fancy.  All of the sales guys are wearing suits.  You can tell they are working on commission.  But everyone was really friendly, and they even offered us a bottle of water or coffee.  Everything in the store seems pretty expensive, but they have a lot of things that most electronics stores don't have.  They have an excellent selection of TV's.  I bought the  urlLink  Hulk   DVD at Best Buy today.  For $16 I just couldn't resist.  I know most people think I am crazy when I say this, but I think that it is one of the most beautiful movies that I have ever seen!  The editing is freaking awesome and I love the use of color!  I hope that  urlLink Ang Lee  will be directing the sequels.  I hope they use the same editor too.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Don't blame me.  This link came from Ann.  Click at your own risk!   urlLink Ann's Favorite Web Site 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I added  The Secret of Women  project journal to my blog today.  I originally kept the project journal for my class Junior Seminar (MC490).  I thought it would be nice to have them here in my blog.  I will probably also add the project journal to my portfolio.  If you want to read the logs, check out my Blogger archive for March and April, 2003.  I just noticed that the journal fills in the one year gap I had in my blog between August 2002 and August 2003.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this in  urlLink Darian's blog .   urlLink SkyHigh Airlines 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally watched  urlLink  El Mariachi   tonight.  I had been putting it off because I wasn't sure if I wanted to watch it before or after I read  urlLink  Rebel Without a Crew  .  I am almost done with the book, so I decided to watch it.  I just couldn't wait until I finished.  It's pretty cool when you think about how  urlLink Robert Rodriguez  made  El Mariachi  and what he went through to get it done.  Robert Rodriguez makes me wish that I was Mexican.  Last night I applied for two more jobs.  I re-applied at Best Buy and Circuit City.  I went four places to get applications, and all four places are now doing all applications online or on a computer in the store.  A few months ago they were all still doing it the old fashioned way.  Thanks for the spell checking Blogger!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found one more friend with a blog:   urlLink Casey 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Caleb sent me this link to a Batman fan film.  It looks pretty impressive.   urlLink TFN FanFilms | Short Films | Batman: Dead End 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      During the past week, I have been discovering that all of my friends have blogs and I never knew it.  Not only do they all have blogs, but they also update theirs every day.  They even add interesting content.  I guess I need to start posting a little more.   urlLink Caleb   urlLink Darian   urlLink Dave   urlLink Maggie   urlLink Pete   urlLink Ryan   urlLink Yugo 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Lately, I have found myself becoming more and more interested in filmmaking.  This has forced me to question how a Christian can fit into the film industry.  Seeking answers, I posted a thread on the  urlLink Relevant Magazine  forum.  Click the link below to get to the thread:   urlLink Christian Filmmaking   Here are some links that I found related to this topic:   urlLink MOVIE MEDITATIONS: THE ROCKS CRY OUT   urlLink MOVIE MEDITATIONS: GOD (AND BRUCE) ALMIGHTY   urlLink SPIRITUALLY EXPERIENCE MOVIES   urlLink RELEVANT STORE: HOW MOVIES HELPED SAVE MY SOUL 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The K-State football team may not be playing very well this season, but I hope they can at least win against Kansas and Nebraska.  They play Kansas tomorrow.   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF - College Football Preview 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to see if I could catch myself on the fresh blogs list on  urlLink Blogger.com .  ...  hmm... I guess not... what's the deal?  ...  maybe I'm just not "special"  ...  maybe Blogger just doesn't like me  ...  why does Blogger hate me?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Darian  had this link posted on his blog.  I decided to post it here too because it is wicked cool.  I love that Hummer Commercial!   urlLink HUMMER | Big Race 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I stumbled across Caleb's online journal thingy and I thought I would just take a moment to post a link to it.  I also wanted to post some links to other friends' web sites.  UPDATE: I noticed that Pete has a new domain name!   urlLink liquidcheese's Xanga Site (Caleb)   urlLink The Darian Experience (Darian)   urlLink Mercury (Pete)   urlLink Doug Armknecht's Spot on the Web (Doug)   By the way, what happened to Travis and Jeff?  They used to have web sites.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What's up with all the Linux companies now?  I used Linux a little bit a few years ago, and I have been wanting to give it a try again.  But when I went to the Linux-Mandrake site, I noticed that they no longer have CD images on their site to download.  It was the same way with pretty much every other distribution I tried.  I guess they want people to actually pay for Linux now.  It's just frustrating I guess.  I just want to be able to download the dumb ISOs!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was just looking at this new Archos mp3 player, Gmini 120.  It looks pretty weird.  One cool feature of the Gmini is its built-in Compact Flash card reader.   urlLink ARCHOS - Cinema to go 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It looks like Sony has completely taken over the Sonic Foundry media software.  You now have to go to the sony web site for support.  Also Sony has released a new version of Sound Forge, version 7.0.  I really love the Sonic Foundry software, so I hope Sony doesn't screw it all up.   urlLink Sony Pictures Digital Media Software and Services 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found where you can download the Kill Bill "Bootleg" trailers.  These trailers are basically longer versions that show more footage than the other trailers.  They are also in a different style than the other trailers.  There are two of them and they can be found here:   urlLink KILL BILL VOLUME ONE - TRAILER AND CLIPS - TheMovieBox.Net   UPDATE:  I also found a trailer on that page that I have been trying to find for a while now.  I caught the end of it on TV once, and I was beginning to think that I had imagined it.  But the trailer is on that same page.  It is called TV Spot #2 and it's source is TheMovieBox.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not sure what the "Bootleg" Kill Bill trailer is exactly, but here is where you can see it:   urlLink Kill Bill - Bootleg Trailer venues 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sweet!  NateDillon.com has finally been added to the Google search engine!   urlLink Google Search: nate dillon 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Here are some sites that I have been enjoying for quite some time, but have never taken the time to post on here:        urlLink CWD   urlLink ROKKAN   urlLink MAKKENG2   urlLink clandestina   urlLink PIXELGRAPHY   urlLink SIMONLADEFOGED.COM   urlLink SCENE 360   urlLink elixir studio   urlLink Bionic Systems   urlLink Branislav Kropilak   urlLink Renascent   urlLink CLAN.DREI   urlLink ds9r   urlLink KEEP LEFT   urlLink Isoprop.net   urlLink SvenTobiasKils   &nbsp;   urlLink conduit   urlLink WeWorkForThem   urlLink GOINGONSIX   urlLink Sybilmedia   urlLink altpick.com   urlLink Fatoe   urlLink IDIOCASE   urlLink The Best Designs   urlLink Idea Machine   urlLink RNDM   urlLink FavoriteWebSiteAwards.com   urlLink driftlab   urlLink This is Kris   urlLink TEKNISION   urlLink joey senatore    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wish iPods weren't so expensive.  I would have purchased an iPod instead of my Archos Jukebox, but the iPod was like twice as much.  Anyway, they have a couple new accessories out for the iPod that look pretty sweet.  The memory card reader is something that I would love to have if I had an iPod!   urlLink Apple iTunes/iPod: the next generation (Mac/PC) - CNET reviews 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, I almost forgot... yesterday was Ann's birthday.  She is now 22, and Adam says that is really old.  I think he's right.  Happy Birthday Ann!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made it back to Wichita last night after spending a week on the road.  K-State had two days off from school, so Kyle and I went to see  urlLink Darian  and Kerri in Detroit over the weekend.  Kyle picked me up in Wichita last Thursday, and we left Manhattan for Detroit on Friday.  We spent Friday night at Yugo's place in Columbus, Indiana (just outside Indianapolis) and then he went with us to Detroit on Saturday.  We all had a pretty good time in Detroit even though we were only there for about 31 hours.  On Saturday we went to the art museum and then went to the MGM casino in downtown Detroit.  I think Yugo was the only one that had been to a casino before, and he was the only one that made any money while we were there.  It was pretty cool though.  After losing my $4 at the casino, we went out to eat and topped the night off by going to see  urlLink Kill Bill .  That movie is AWESOME!  We thought that the theater was showing it digitally, but they told us that digital movies are not available that the theater yet.  We spent Sunday looking around the Detroit area a bit more.  Darian took us to his office in Northville so that we could see where he worked.  Then we looked around Northville a little bit and went to the mall.  We also went to see the  urlLink Vans Skate Park  which was really cool.  They have indoor and outdoor skate courses, video games, an XBox lounge, and a Vans Store.   urlLink MxPx  played a short acoustic set there the previous weekend.  We left Detroit Sunday night and went back to Yugo's place to stay the night.  Kyle and I left for Manhattan Monday morning.  We stopped in St. Louis to check out the arch for a little while.  I took some pretty cool pictures there.  We were also going to stop in Kansas City and stay the night with Justin, but Kyle said that he needed to get back to Manhattan to get some stuff done.  We did stop in Kansas City to eat dinner and hang out with Justin for a bit.  The three of us walked around the Plaza for a little while.  We arrived back in Manhattan Monday night a little before midnight.  I had to wait until Thursday to get a ride back to Wichita with Lindsey, so I was able to hang out with Jermaine for a couple days.  I think I spent about 40 hours in cars over the past week.  In a way, it's kinda nice to just stay in one place for a while.  And now I need to get back to my job search.  I'll get my pictures from the trip up soon.  I might also put some maps of the trip on my site.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it looks like  urlLink Hell Froze Over .  Apple has released iTunes for Windows.  I've been using it a bit since last night and it's actually pretty good.  There are several things in iTunes that Winamp does not have.  I do miss a few features from Winamp, but I might just stick iTunes for a while.  This is what Nullsoft gets for not ever releasing updates to Winamp3, which is buggier than a Florida swamp!  I know that the only reason that Apple released iTunes for PC is so that they can sell more mp3s, but how cool would it be if they released other Apple software for PC (Final Cut Pro)?  Just a suggestion.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am in Detroit!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just enabled the title feature in Blogger.  I guess I had never seen it there before or I just forgot about it.  Anyway, I am just trying it out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The NHL 2003-2004 season begins tonight!   urlLink ESPN.com - NHL - Morganti: Story lines, not bottom lines 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it looks like Half-Life 2 will be delayed again due to the theft of it's source code.  It will be delayed until at least April 2004, but I wouldn't be surprised if that was pushed back again.  I am guessing that it will be released sometime during next summer.  This really sucks.   urlLink Half-Life 2 Delayed To April 2004 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, I found this piece of news pretty interesting.   urlLink Half-Life 2 Source Leaked 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can you believe all this crap about Rush Limbaugh and Donovan McNabb?  Talk about blowing things out of proportion!   urlLink ESPN.com: GEN - Limbaugh on quitting: 'path of least resistance' 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mac OS X themes, icons, and other stuff for Windows!   urlLink Iceman's Emulation Page 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Search patterns, trends, and surprises according to Google    "On a monthly, weekly, and sometimes daily basis, this Google Zeitgeist page will be updated to reflect lists, graphs, and other tidbits of information related to Google user search behavior."    urlLink Google Press Center: Zeitgeist 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy Thanksgiving!  My family and I will be leaving for Columbus, Kansas in about 6 hours (maybe).  I think I forgot to mention that I did not take the job offer at Circuit City, so now I can go with my family.  I guess the trip just seemed a little too important to me right now.  At some point I am going to have to start letting stuff like this go.  Things aren't the same anymore.  Life is going to be a lot different now that I am out of school and living in the real world.  But for now, Thanksgiving remains relatively the same for me.  I did find out that several of my cousins will not be attending the Thanksgiving dinner in Columbus this year, and some of my other cousins are going to have to leave earlier than normal.  I guess that's just part of things changing.  I am still excited about Thanksgiving.  I just returned from Manhattan Tuesday.  I was planning on going up there Friday or Saturday for the football game with either my mom or dad.  Things fell through, and we couldn't get tickets.  But at the last minute, my dad and I decided to drive up there on Sunday.  While I was in Manhattan, I went to eat at El Cazador's twice (Travis would have loved that).  I went once with my dad, my sister, and Jermaine, and I went once with Kevin, Karl, Dustin, and Jermaine.  I'm not really sure how that happened.  I guess everyone was just in the mood for Mexican food this week.  Jermaine told me this week that my blog sucks (although she didn't use the word "sucks").  She just thinks that I just post random, stupid stuff, and I don't really talk about anything.  She's probably right.  Yesterday was  urlLink Darian's  24th birthday.  Man, that sounds so old.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dude, check this out.  I am actually making this post on October 18, but I am trying out this post-dating option in Blogger.  This way, I can make sure I don't forget to say happy birthday on time.  I love Blogger!  Happy Birthday Darian!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yugo is hot!!!   urlLink HOT or NOT? - www.hotornot.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is just some weird stuff.  I would never shop at Acronobie and Fetch anyway, but this article makes me think that there is something wrong with people that do still shop there.   urlLink WorldNetDaily: Abercrombie & Fitch to your kids: Group sex now! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      you want something you take it can't hide from God can't fake it he knows your heart he knows mine you've only got a lifetime  have you no integrity? your wasted mind, your apathy same old high school mystery you're too dumb & blind to see  you've already made up your mind you don't care you don't wanna find the truth will hit you like cement too bad too sad it's too late for your enlightenment
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink JACKIE CHAN WILL PLAY MARTIN'S KATO IN THE NEW PINK PANTHER 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sweet!!!   urlLink USATODAY.com - 'Family Guy' may return 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Send Them Back!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Shrek 2   urlLink The Punisher   urlLink The Incredibles   urlLink Miracle 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I turned down the job at Circuit City today.  I didn't feel that taking the job was the best thing to do.  I knew that I would feel bad about either decision.  I guess I decided that I would feel just a little bit better if I declined the job.  I just hope that I can find something else soon.  I am going to apply at some temp agencies.  I would think that I could find something through that.  I still haven't heard back from WB Kansas.  I am planning on taking a trip to Manhattan this weekend.  My dad and I want to go to the K-State-Missouri football game, but I'm not sure that we will be able to get tickets.  Even if we don't get to go, I think it will still be fun.  It seems like I haven't seen Jermaine in forever!  (It's been about 5 weeks)  I will probably stay in Manhattan until Tuesday or Wednesday, then I will head back to Wichita before my family and I leave for Columbus, Kansas for Thanksgiving.  Every year we say that this may be the last time we get to go to Columbus for Thanksgiving, so I am really thankful that we get to go this year.  I've been wanting to make an intro video for  urlLink NateDillon.com .  I think I want to make the video in  urlLink Vegas  and import it into  urlLink Flash .  Then I can add additional Flash elements and put it on my web site.  The only problem is that I know very little about Flash.  It seems like it's a really hard program to learn.  Maybe this intro video thing would be a good way to learn a little bit more.  I tried to make a little stop-motion piece for the intro with my  urlLink LEGO , but I don't think I have enough pieces to do what I wanted... I need more LEGO!  I've made a few minor changes to my blog template tonight.  I doubt anyone will even notice the changes, but I fixed several things that had been bugging me.  Some day I am going to completely change my blog and make my own template.  I haven't had to do that recently since my web site is set up so weird.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This link is for those of you who like to blog from work.  Be careful!!   urlLink  BLOGGER - Knowledge Base - How Not to Get Fired Because of Your Blog    UPDATE:  If Microsoft was really concerned about security issues related to  urlLink the picture  posted by the guy they fired, then why is that picture still online?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jermaine just forwarded these pictures to me.  The first picture is from the K-State-Nebraska game last Saturday.  The second picture is a statue in Nebraska.  I thought it was pretty funny.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know how many of you have Cox Cable, but the  urlLink ESPN web site  claims that Cox is trying to make customers pay extra to get ESPN.  This would really suck since one of the reasons my family has cable is so that we can watch some of the college football and hockey games that are on ESPN.  Without ESPN, I probably wouldn't get to see much hockey at all!   urlLink KEEP ESPN 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am currently working on my site navigation.  If you see some weird things happening at the top of my pages, please ignore it and I will try to have it all fixed up as soon as possible.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I have some good news and bad news.  I just had an interview at Circuit City tonight, and they offered me a seasonal job.  But the only way I can take the job is if I can work the day after Thanksgiving from 5:30am to 12:00pm.  Normally this would not be a problem, but my family and I have already made plans to go to my grandparents' house in Columbus, Kansas.  We only get to see them and the rest of my family once or twice a year, so we always like to stay a day or two after Thanksgiving.  If I have to be back in Wichita to work, that means that we will only be able to spend the afternoon in Columbus, then we would have to leave for Wichita.  It just sucks that I finally have a job offer and I don't know if I can take it.  I am feeling much better now as I am starting to get over this cold.  I've just been sneezing a lot for the last couple days.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a pretty funny quote that I found on  urlLink ESPN.com  about the recent K-State - Nebraska game.  "After the game, Nebraska defensive coordinator Bo Pelini approached Snyder to challenge the Kansas State coach for running up the score. Snyder may be accused of soft scheduling but no one has ever accused him of a lack of class. As my father Bobby once joked to Lou Holtz after a West Virginia-William and Mary game, 'It's not my job to hold down the score, it yours!'"   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF - Bowden: Weekend coaching 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ah yeah!!   urlLink Sony DSRPD170 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink A List Apart 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I guess I have joined everyone else that has been getting sick lately.  My throat has been hurting for the past two days.  I just kinda feel like crap, and I don't have very much energy.  I just hope that it doesn't last too long.  I am hoping to visit Manhattan next weekend, and I might have more job interviews this week.  I've just been eating a ton of cough drops!  I didn't do anything too exciting this weekend.  I watched Kansas State beat Nebraska, and I watched the Chiefs lose to Cincinnati.  It was really cool to watch K-State win in Nebraska.  This was the first time they have done that since 1968, and I was getting sick of Nebraska fans saying that K-State would never win in Nebraska.  K-State is now ranked 18 and 19 in the polls, which is like seven spots higher than last week.  It's too bad the Chiefs lost though.  That ends the unbeaten streak this season.  It just didn't seem like the Chiefs were playing very well until there was only like six minutes left in the game.  By then it was too late.  Oh well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Cxbx, The Xbox Emulator 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, MTV has really outdone itself this time.  I thought the whole newlyweds show was bad, but then I caught a few minutes of  urlLink  Rich Girls  .  These girls are pretty dumb.  One of the conversations the girls had on the show went something like this:   Girl #1:  I just don't feel like I deserve all of this.  Girl #2:  I think that since you appreciate everything you have, that means you deserve it.  Girl #1:  Maybe we all just did something really good in our past lives.  Girl #3:  Yeah.  Benjamin Franklin has the same birthday as me.  Muhammad Ali has the same birthday as me.  Maybe I used to be one of them in my past life.  Girl #2:  Who?  Girl #3:  Benjamin Franklin.  He invented the light bulb.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       DVD of the day:   urlLink  Pulp Fiction   (Collector's Edition)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's right, Face to Face is breaking up.  I always hate it when one of my favorite bands breaks up.  I'm just glad that I was finally able to see them play at the Warped Tour this year.  They will be missed.   urlLink Face to Face's Official Website 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I posted a link to an article titled  urlLink  Mom Finds Out About Blog  .  It's about a guy who is trying to figure out what to do after his mom finds his online journal and begins reading about how he spends his time.  It's a pretty funny article.  Anyway,  urlLink Blogger  has released their official stance on what to do if this ever happens to you.  Take a look:   urlLink What to do if your Mom discovers your blog... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been reorganizing all the files on my web site tonight.  I've needed to do this for a while now, but I have been avoiding it.  Some folders in the site were getting too big, some sections of the site were sharing folders with other sections... it was just a mess.  Anyway, if something on my web site is not working, this would be the reason.  Please let me know if you find anything that is broken.  Thanks!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink ROCKSTAR GAMES UPLOAD III 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Despair, Inc. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        My life is rated PG-13.  What is your life rated? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I thought this was kinda funny.  Be sure to check out the "Top 10 People Famous for Doing Nothing" on this page.   urlLink ESPN.com - Page2 - How to watch Paris Hilton at work 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Take this quiz to find out if you are a metrosexual.  I only got one question right... I guess I am a lost cause...   urlLink ESPN.com: SPORTS NATION - SportsNation Trivia 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink The Onion | Mom Finds Out About Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a pretty big day for me.  I had what I consider my first interview for a "real" job.  I had an interview for a Television Producer job at the  urlLink WB Kansas  TV station.  This position will basically be responsible for producing local advertising spots.  They guy that interviewed me was really cool, and I thought the interview went very well.  I received my  urlLink  28 Days Later   DVD in the mail today.  I was somewhat disappointed that it is only one disc.  It has some cool special features, but I just wish it included more.  The movie was shot entirely on MiniDV camcorders ( urlLink Canon XL1S ).  Although these were pretty expensive camcorders, they are still ones available to the everyday consumer.  I was hoping that the special features would include more about using the MiniDV format and how they made it look more like film rather than a crappy home movie.  Despite the lack of special features, I highly recommend this DVD simply because this is a beautiful movie.  There are also some amazing shots of empty streets in downtown London.  Speaking of good movies, I went to see  urlLink  Mystic River   with my family last night.  Like  urlLink Yugo  said, it is a really good movie.  As good an actor as  urlLink Clint Eastwood  is, I think he is probably an even better director.  Everyone should go see this movie.  I'm sure that you will be hearing more about it at the next  urlLink Academy Awards .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink ESPN.com - Page2 - Who's hottest? Finch vs. Anna   urlLink ESPN.com - Page2 - Sincerely, Anna's lawyers 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ESPN decided to find out which team has the worst uniform in sports.  Kansas State Basketball and Wichita State Baseball both made it into competition.   urlLink ESPN.com - Page2 - Page 2's Worst Uniform Bracket 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Plug'n'Pray 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My new favorite cable channel!   urlLink TURNER CLASSIC MOVIES 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm trying to learn how to use  urlLink Final Draft  tonight so that I can attempt to write some screenplays.  I have discovered that screenplays have a very specific style of formatting.  I'm told that if a screenplay is formatted correctly, each page should be equal to about one minute when made into a movie.  It looks like using Final Draft to write screenplays will be much easier than using WordPerfect or Word.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My  urlLink  Reservoir Dogs   DVD arrived today.  I got the  urlLink 10th Anniversary Special Edition DVD  with the Mr. Pink cover.  It's pretty sweet.   Reservoir Dogs  was Quentin Tarantino's first major movie.  I love how Tarantino takes what would normally be a pretty simple story of a robbery gone wrong and makes it into a great movie by using his unusual storytelling techniques.  It was released in 1992, the same year that Robert Rodriguez's  El Mariachi  was released.  I am expecting to receive my  urlLink  28 Days Later   DVD in the mail on Monday.  That is another great movie that I highly recommend.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This movie looks sweet!   urlLink Apple - Trailers - Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind   urlLink LACUNA INC. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to see  urlLink  The Matrix Revolutions   yesterday.  I went with my brothers, their friend  urlLink Brandon , and Brandon's mom.   urlLink Zach  wanted to go to the first showing in Wichita at 8:00am...  I said "No way!"  So we ended up going at 11:00am instead.  I thought the movie was pretty sweet.  Much better than the second one in my opinion.  There were some really cool special effects and fight scenes, not to mention the whole battle in Zion.  I heard that a lot of critics were giving this movie bad reviews.  Don't listen to them.  I thought it was cool.  The job hunt is looking a little better today.  I received a call from  urlLink WB Kansas , and I have an interview with them Wednesday.  I also called  urlLink Manpower Professional  to see what I have to do to get temp jobs with them.  I need to go in and fill out some paperwork next week if I want to do that.  I am also going to call back a few places tomorrow.  For some reason, I have always wanted to work at  urlLink Best Buy .  I just love that place, and it would be wicked cool if I could get a discount!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mark Messier became number 2 on the all-time career points list in the NHL tonight.  This is a pretty big achievement.  It's too bad it wasn't on TV!   urlLink ESPN.com - NHL - Frei: Celebrating No. 2   urlLink ESPN.com - NHL - Messier passes Howe for No. 2 in all-time points   urlLink ESPN.com - NHL - NHL Recap 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished watching the movie  urlLink  Desperado  .  It is the sequel to  urlLink  El Mariachi  .  It had been a while since the last time I watched  Desperado .  I didn't remember being too impressed with it.  It was cool to watch it again after reading about and watching  El Mariachi .  I even recognized some of the actors that were in both  El Mariachi  and  Desperado .  I applied at Target today.  I know they are hiring because they have hosted a couple job fairs recently.  Target is one of the stores where you have to apply in the store.  So Zach and I had to go to the store to fill out applications on the computers.  There were two people already working on their applications, so we had to wait for a while before we could start ours.  That kinda sucked, but at least we got it done.  I still need to call a few other places back to check up on some applications.  Tomorrow my brothers and I are going to buy tickets to  urlLink  The Matrix Revolutions  .  We will be going to see it Wednesday morning.  I can't wait!  I know a lot of people were really disappointed with the second  Matrix  movie, but a lot of people are also really stupid.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Vote for your favorite NHL players!   urlLink 2004 NHL All-Stars 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I discovered a new tool that comes with the Macromedia MX 2004 software.  It's called FlashPaper, and it looks pretty cool.  I thought I might be able to use it for my resume.  I'm not sure if it will make it any easier for me to put my resume on my web site though.   urlLink Macromedia FlashPaper 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just watched a feature on Fox News about the guy that made this movie.  His name is Carlos Ferrer and he is 17 years old.  It looks pretty interesting.   urlLink Scallop Pond - The Movie   urlLink Scallop Pond (2004) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out the short film "Karaoke Man"   urlLink Department of Film > Directors > Adolfo Doring 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Grease!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        You are Beaker!!  You aren't a big talker, but you get your point across.  You are extremely accident prone.   urlLink   Which Muppet are You?    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Ascii 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy Birthday Brandon!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Alien vs. Predator 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I put all my old news postings into Blogger today.  They are from back when I used NewsPro on my old web sites.  I just thought it would be nice to have all of my blogs in one place.  Any blogs posted before May 24, 2002 are from NewsPro.  The "Change Time and Date" feature in Blogger is really cool.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      A new record has been set for visits to my web site.  I had 557 visits during the month of October.  This beat the old record of 422 set back in August.  This isn't all that exciting, but it gives me an excuse to try out the file upload feature in  urlLink Blogger .  As you can see below, I have uploaded a very exciting graph of my web site statistics.  Enjoy!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pete and Charity had a baby!  It's always weird when one of your friends has a baby...  Congratulations!   urlLink Welcome to Mercury 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I miss my camera...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Darian, I found this article about building your own TiVo.  It looks like building one would be pretty cool, but it also looks kind of complicated.  It would be fun to try though.   urlLink Wired News: Building a TiVo, a Step at a Time 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's right!  I was sick of people complaining that my blog did not have comments, and I was sick of hearing that  urlLink Xanga  does have comments.  Xanga sucks by the way.  It's not even close to being as cool as  urlLink Blogger .  From what I have heard, Blogger is working on adding the comments feature to their service.  Now that Blogger is owned by  urlLink Google  I'm sure that a bunch of cool new features will be added soon.  For those of you that have Blogger and for those of you trying to decide which blog service to go with, adding comments to Blogger was wicked easy.  I just signed up for an account at  urlLink HaloScan.com  and followed their simple instructions.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Kristi, Happy Birthday!  I hope you have a great day!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone, I just wanted to say Merry Christmas!  I hope everyone has a great day!  I was going to take a nice picture of myself wearing my annual "Christmas t-shirt", but I was an idiot and I left my camera back in Manhattan last week... I am still mad at myself for that... Instead, I thought that I would post this picture that I just found on my computer.   urlLink Darian  made this thing a few years ago.  We were going to make Christmas CDs to give to all of our friends, but it never happened.  I thought that this just needed to be used somewhere, so here it is!  Merry Christmas!!!   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Want to drive traffic? Try the Google Free way. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  I was just reading the  urlLink Awful Plastic Surgery  blog, and there was a really funny quote on there about Christina Aguilera.   "Christina Aguilera is the grossest celebrity I can think of. She has so much make up, piercings, weird clothes and such that she turns my stomach every time I see her. I wonder what she would look like without all of the stuff on. It looks like you could get herpes just standing close to her."    urlLink Awful Plastic Surgery: Christina Aguilera's Expanding Chest 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  This is a great idea for a cheap last-minute Christmas gift!  I think everyone should have their own blog... don't you?   urlLink  BLOGGER - Knowledge Base-How To Give The Last-Minute Gift of Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are some awesome photos on this site, and a lot of them were taken using a Canon Powershot S30, the same camera that I have!  I really need to learn how to take better pictures...   urlLink apparently nothing at all 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Blogger  has posted a link to an article about some British blog awards.  There are some pretty cool blogs that won.  You can get some great ideas for your blog by checking out some of the links.   urlLink The best of British blogging 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Yugo  told me that he also has submitted an idea to  urlLink RandomShirts.com .  I thought I should take a moment to share the method that Brice, Brent, and I used to come up with some random shirt ideas.  For those of you who would like to join in the fun but can't think of any good ideas, this is for you.  You need two people in order for this to work.  The first person thinks of some random picture without telling the other person what it is.  The second person thinks of some random phrase without telling the other person what it is.  Once a random picture and a random phrase is chosen, you sorta just put them together.  Now you have a t-shirt idea!  We tried this method for quite a while last week.  Although we never came up with many great ideas, it seemed to keep us entertained for quite a while.  I do have to say that the ideas were TOTALLY random, even if they weren't very funny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      uh, yeah... Happy Birthday Yugo!  I hope you have a great day!  How old are you anyway??
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just submitted a t-shirt idea to  urlLink RandomShirts.com !  Just so you know,  urlLink Effingham  is a real town in Illinois.  Kyle and I drove by it on our way to visit Darian.  Anyway, here is my idea...   FRONT:  I went to Illinois and all I got was an Effingham sandwich!   BACK:  Effingham, Illinois
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink BLOGGER - Knowledge Base-How To Get A Book Deal With Your Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got back from another trip to Manhattan last night.  I didn't think that I would make it up there this week, but Brice called me the other day and asked if I wanted to go up there with him.  Brice and I left Wichita Tuesday morning and pretty much hung out together all day.  That worked out really well because Jermaine had to study most of the day, and she had a test Tuesday night and Wednesday morning.   Tuesday   After arriving in Manhattan, I went to eat at  urlLink Chipotle  with Brice, Brent, and Caleb (Brent's friend).  Then we went to the mall for a bit so that Brice could do some Christmas shopping.  We also spent like half an hour buying cigars (there were way too many to choose from).  I ended up getting the Macanudo Maduro Hampton Court.  It came in a cool case.  Kyle went to buy a cigar later that night.  I told him to ask the people that work there about two indecisive Mexicans and a white kid that were in there earlier.  That way, he could see which cigars we got, and he could get a different one.  He asked them, and they actually knew who he was talking about!  But they couldn't remember which cigars we had picked out.  After the mall, I went over to Jermaine's house while Brice went to visit one of his old professors.  Jermaine had to study most of the time that I was there, but it gave me a chance to remove a virus from her computer... It's too bad that I broke her Internet in the process...  At 8:00pm, I went over to Paul Scheele's house to smoke cigars and drink  urlLink Guinness  with Brice, Brent, Justin, and Kyle.  I have never been a big fan of Guinness, but this stuff was really good.  We had the Guinness Draught in bottles.  Paul gave us glasses to pour it in because he just found out that beer tastes better if you let it breathe.  It was really good stuff.  We left Paul's house and went back to Putnam.  Kyle had to study for a wicked hard final, but the rest of us decided to watch  urlLink Fight Club  (Brent had never seen it).  I got back to Lindsey's around 1:30am.  I tried to order stuff online, but Columbia House sucks!   Wednesday   Wednesday was nice because Jermaine was all done with finals, so I was able to see her quite a bit.  I went with Lindsey to Wal-Mart to help her print some pictures for her project.  After lunch I went with Jermaine to run a few errands.  We had dinner at  urlLink Quiznos  (mmm... toasty).  Jermaine volunteered to work for Amy for a little while so that Amy could go to a review session.  While Jermaine was working, I went with Justin to Acacia, and we started watching  The Two Towers  extended edition DVD.  I left after like an hour though.  I can't wait to see  The Return of the King !   Thursday   I was able to spend quite a bit of time with Jermaine on Thursday too.  We went to the Beach Art Museum and looked at a sweet exhibit!  It was called  urlLink  Everything Must Go   by Randy Regier.  The exhibit "transforms a gallery space into a self-contained toy store."  But the cool thing about the toys is that this guy made all of them!  They are all supposed to be a joke though.  I love how he made them look like they were really old and came out of the 50s and 60s.  It was some very cool stuff.  Jermaine had to go back to work at 9:00pm.  I went to Putnam to say goodbye to some people, and I went down to Quik Cats to hang out with Jermaine for a little while.  Lindsey came to pick me up around 10:00pm, and we left Manhattan around 11:00pm.  I am pretty mad at myself because I left my camera at Lindsey's house!  I really want to have that for Christmas!  Despite leaving my camera there, I had a pretty good time in Manhattan this week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I guess I should probably explain the  urlLink previous posting  that I made.  Last year there was some confusion between Ben (my brother) and I.  He wanted to see  urlLink  The Two Towers   with me, but he also wanted to see it the day that it came out.  Well, I was at school in Manhattan when it came out, and I was told that he could not wait until I cam home for Christmas to see the movie.  I hadn't planned on going to see it while I was at school, but some people invited me to go see it the day it came out.  I thought Ben had decided not to wait for me, so I thought there would be no harm in going to see the movie with my friends... I was wrong...  When Ben found out that I went to see it, he was all mad at me.  He has a really bad temper too.  One time when he was mad at me, he put cat poop in my bed!  I was back in Manhattan again this week when  urlLink  The Return of the King   came out.  Once again Ben wanted to go see the movie with me when I returned.  I thought it would be funny to play a little joke on him.  That's why I posted that stuff about going to see  The Two Towers .  It was really funny when I read  urlLink his response on his blog .  By the way, the part that I wrote about a drunk guy puking was real too.  It happened when Jess went to see the movie the other night.  Anyway, that's what that posting was all about.  I'm sure most of you don't really care, but I thought it was funny!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just went to see  Return of the King  tonight in Manhattan.  That movie was awesome!  I will have to go see it again in Wichita in a good theater.  Also, some guy behind me was drunk and puked!  ...   UPDATE:  Just kidding  urlLink Ben !  I got you pretty good didn't I?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Ryan  tells me that this site went live to the world 22 minutes ago!   urlLink Spiderman 2 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished drinking the Kool-Aid that I made the weekend before Thanksgiving... Kool-Aid can't go bad can it?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wish I could do this stuff...   urlLink BeatBox.TV 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Make-a-Flake - A snowflake maker by Lookandfeel new media 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      omg...   urlLink Apple Store Japan   I'm sure Yugo would be one of those people if he were back in Japan!  Thanks for the link  urlLink Ryan !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      MTV.com News explains why P.O.D.'s new album will not be sold in 85% of Christian bookstores across the country.   urlLink P.O.D.'s Latest Album Refused By Most Christian Bookstores 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      sweet...   urlLink A nodding Virgin Mary is the ideal Kitschmas gift  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  This site is great!   urlLink The Lord of the Rings UK - Middle-earth Name Translator   Dear Nate Dillon,  If you were a Hobbit, your name would be  Merum Jackley  and if you were a (male) Man, your name would be	 Blenyc  and if you were an Elf, your name would be  Isondil  and if you were a Dwarf, your name would be  Koilir  and if you were an Orc, your name would be  Vudish  Your nearest Tavern might be called  The Golden Stool  and your sword would be called  Narduring   I didn't know the name of the nearest bar, so I just put Best Buy instead.  ...  I put in Rusty's for the bar name and tried again, and the only thing that changed was the nearest tavern name.  Wtih Rusty's my nearest tavern might be called  The Bowl's Rim .  I think both tavern names are pretty funny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blindside has a blog, so why don't you?   urlLink Blindside Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is a little interview that Relevant Magazine did with a Christian screenwriter.  Pretty interesting stuff.   urlLink RELEVANT magazine - Q&A WITH SCREENWRITER BRIAN GODAWA 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      More pictures from the Big XII Championship.     &nbsp;   urlLink     &nbsp;     urlLink      urlLink     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   urlLink     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   urlLink     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   urlLink     &nbsp;     urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
          urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Technology News: SBC Fights Back over RIAA Subpoenas 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks for the mp3  urlLink Darian !!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      my web site sucks.  i want a new one for christmas.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       K-State 35, Oklahoma 7    "K-State was supposed to be just another stop on OU's path to history except someone forgot to tell the Wildcats."   Wow... Can you believe that K-State could dominate Oklahoma like that?  I was just hoping that K-State would make the Big XII championship a close game.  I don't think anyone expected them to completely blow out Oklahoma like they did.  And now K-State completely screwed up the BCS.  K-State's bowl game seems almost meaningless compared to tonight's game.  It was pretty cool that K-State screwed Texas out of a BCS spot too.  I would also like to add that Darren Sproles is my favorite K-State football player ever!   urlLink Roberson, Sproles deliver 1-2 punch   urlLink K-State planning Fiesta with Big 12 title   urlLink Longhorns lose chance at BCS   By the way,  urlLink Darian  and I might be the only two people in the world that really uderstand the title of this posting, but trust me, it's really funny.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, this is where my family has Thanksgiving dinner every year!   urlLink First United Methodist Church in Columbus, KS 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink  Put The Star Wars Kid in Episode III Petition  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The official web site for  urlLink  The Passion Of The Christ   has been launched.  I've been hearing so much about this movie.  There are a lot of people in Hollywood that didn't want this movie to be made for some reason.  It should be very interesting.   urlLink The Passion Of The Christ - Official Movie Website 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      A here is yet another link... This one comes from Zach.  He found this web site for a Wesley Willis tribute album.  The site had full mp3s that you can download.  For those of you who don't know who Wesley Willis was, he was the greatest musician of all time... and he liked to headbutt people... enjoi!   urlLink Loved Like a Milkshake: A Wesley Willis Tribute Album 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey  urlLink Caleb , thanks for the link!  These videos are great!!   urlLink Edited GI Joe Cartoons PSA overdubbed 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      silly apple...   urlLink Prank Phone Call to iTunes    urlLink Prank Letters to Rock Stars 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know, someday someone is going to make some kind of book about blogs, and that person is probably going to make like a billion dollars for that book.  I mean, if there is an  urlLink eBay  book, why couldn't somebody make a  urlLink Blogger  book?  And why couldn't that somebody be me?  ...  Oh yeah, I guess I would have to learn to read first... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Does anyone else think it's funny that the  urlLink Blogger  spell check tries to correct the word "blog"?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Street named for Joey Ramone 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      what the...   urlLink Dodge plans Lingerie Bowl at Super Bowl halftime - Dec. 2, 2003 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      dang...   urlLink Sony Ships Blue Laser-based Professional Disc for DATA 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      After reading  urlLink Yugo's blog  about his top 10 albums of all time, I thought it would be fun to make my own list.  I thought I would list the albums that were most influential to me.  These may not necessarily be my current favorite albums, but these are the albums that helped shape my musical preferences.  Also, I don't really feel like putting them in order, so I am just going to list them.   Squad Five-O - What I Believe  I bought this CD at the Squad Five-O concert in 1997, my first punk show ever!  Darian and I couldn't find the place, so we were really late.  It was supposed to be $5 to get in, but no one was at the door to take our money.  We decided to spend that money on the band's merchandise instead.  The radio station said that they were a ska band, and I was really into ska at the time.  It was a huge shock when I discovered they weren't a ska band.  This is where I first began to fall in love with punk rawk.   MxPx - Life In General  This is probably still my favorite album ever.  Every song on this album absolutely rocks, and MxPx has been my favorite band ever since I first heard this CD.  I had never heard any band play this fast... I loved it!   Various Artists - Song's From the Penalty Box (Vol. 1)  I got this CD because I liked many of the punk bands on it, but that's not what made this CD so special to me.  There were several bands on there that were a little too rough for me (Blindside, Living Sacrifice, Zao).  At first, Darian and I listened to those bands and just laughed.  But after a while, we began to really like those songs, and next thing I know, we were buying the CDs.   Weezer - Blue Album  How could anyone not like this album? (that's what I keep asking  urlLink Zach )  Every song on it is really good, and Weezer had some great music videos to go along with it.  All of my friends in high school loved these guys.   Less Than Jake - Losing Streak  I noticed that Yugo also had a Less Than Jake album on his list.   Losing Streak  is still my favorite Less Than Jake album.  I think I picked it up at Best Buy for like $6 or something.  It was one of the best music purchases I ever made.  I love how Less Than Jake considers themselves a punk band with horns rather than a ska band.   MxPx - Slowly Going The Way Of The Buffalo  I wasn't a huge fan of this CD when it first came out (my senior year of high school I think).  I guess I was still stuck on  Life In General .  But I gave the album another chance in college, and now it's on this list.  In many ways, it's much better than  Life In General .   Ramones - Ramones Mania  This was the first Ramones album that I ever bought.  It's just a collection of their greatest hits (well, most of their greatest hits).  When I got this CD, I didn't even realize that the Ramones had broken up just a couple years earlier.  Can you believe that they were together for over 20 years?!?!  That's really impressive considering they didn't have a lot of commercial success.  They fixed everything that the Beatles screwed up.   Face to Face - Self-Titled  I joined one of those music clubs my freshman year of college.  I was supposed to make some initial CD selections to get for free, and I had one left and didn't know what else I wanted.  I had heard of Face to Face before, but I had never heard any of their music.  I took a chance on it, and I loved it.  It's too bad that they broke up this year.   Huntingtons - High School Rock  The Huntingtons are the ultimate Ramones rip-off band.  This is by far their best album.  Everything before this was recorded poorly, and I don't like much of their stuff after this album (except  File Under Ramones  of course).   Arthur - Loneliness is Bliss  Arthur is the side project of the guys in MxPx.  Mike was writing a lot of slower, more EMOtional songs that he didn't feel really fit MxPx.  So the guys from MxPx formed Arthur and put out this six-song EP.  I love Arthur as much, if not more than MxPx.  They were supposed to release a full CD a while ago, but it never came out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My blog now has a higher ranking on  urlLink Google  than my main web site.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I had a pretty good Thanksgiving.  It was kinda sad to see how many people didn't go to my grandparents' this year, but we had a good time anyway.  There weren't as many people there to play the annual football game.  We just rotated players.  That way, everyone plays on the winning team.  I fumbled the ball for one team, then went over to the team that recovered the ball, and then I made a "block" on  urlLink Ben  for the winning touchdown.  Ben has a different story though...  We went to see  urlLink  Elf   on Friday.  That movie was really funny!  Right before we left for Columbus, Ben and I started playing  urlLink  Knights of the Old Republic  .  I think it is the first Star wars RPG ever.  It takes up like 4GB of hard drive space too!  I think I have been playing it too much.  It's a really cool game, but I may be starting to get kinda sick of it, which is good, because I have other things that I need to be doing.  Plus, it makes my computer crash a lot.  I'm watching  urlLink  Scent of a Woman   on  urlLink AMC  right now.  I have never seen it before and I missed the beginning, but so far it seems really good.   urlLink Al Pacino  is awesome!  He is really good at pretending to be blind.  For some reason, we now get MTV2 at my house.  They play a lot of rap music on that channel.  I did see a really cool Sick of it All video on there earlier though.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This book looks pretty sweet!  You can make your own cover!   urlLink America 24/7 - with custom cover! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HP has released a DVD writer that has video inputs on it.  This means that you could record video from your TV or video camera onto a DVD.  I thought it looked pretty cool.  The only problem is that it is USB 2.0 and not firewire.  That kinda sucks.   urlLink HPshopping.com - hp dvd movie writer dc3000 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This looks very interesting... too bad they sold out!   urlLink Turkey & Gravy Soda at JonesSodaStore 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not sure what to think about this news.  I would think most studios would want to give Pixar whatever they want.  On the other hand, if there was one company that I think could actually do without Pixar, it would probably be Disney.  I'm sure they are planning something else for computer animation now that Pixar will be gone.  The only question is, will it be as good as what Pixar can do?  Pixar shouldn't have any problems finding another studio that will give them whatever they want.   urlLink NEWS - TheMovieBox.Net - PIXAR DUMPS DISNEY: STEVE JOBS SAYS "WE'RE MOVING ON" 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, sometimes I don't understand the  urlLink Academy Awards  at all!  I was looking at  urlLink this year's nominees , and I made it down to the Best Film Editing section.  That's when I noticed that it's pretty much all of the same movies that were nominated for almost every category.   The thing is that out of the movies that I have seen that were nominated for best editing, I don't remember any of them being that special when it comes to editing.  I do have to admit that it would be quite a task to have to edit one of the Lord of the rings movies, trying to get it down to 3 hours.  But for the most part, all of them were edited the way that almost every other movie is now edited.  I know I bring up   urlLink Hulk   quite a bit, but why wasn't it nominated for best editing?  I mean, the editing in that movie was simply amazing!  I had never seen anything like it before in my life.  Say what you want about the story.  Sure it's just another in the long line of comic book movies being released now.  But that movie was just beautiful.  The only problem is that it didn't make as much money as   urlLink Spider-Man   at the box office.  And it wasn't one of the biggest epics of all time like   urlLink The Return of the King  .  So I guess those are good enough excuses for the Academy to just ignore it.  I dunno... maybe I just don't understand what qualifies as good film editing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          urlLink create your own visited states map   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I started building my new web site today.  I think that this one may end up being more of a trial run to help me figure out how to do some things in CSS.  I am going to try this table-less CSS stuff.  It seems to be pretty tricky so far.  Just when I think I have figured it out and I know what I am doing, something weird happens.  I feel like I am trying to program again.  So far, it almost seems like every page is going to have to be typed out rather than put together in Dreamweaver.  When I am working on a page in Dreamweaver, everything looks all messed up.  I don't know if that is normal or not.  If I am going to have to do every page by hand, it may take me a little bit longer to make all of my pages.  But like I said, I am still trying to figure this whole thing out, so I could be wrong.  I am just glad to have the hard part pretty much over with... designing a layout.  I get so frustrated sometimes when I am trying to make layouts.  I am not a great graphic designer, but that doesn't keep me from wanting everything to look perfect.  I know what I want in a layout, but I just have trouble making it look good.  I think I finally have a fairly simple layout that I can live with... well, for at least a week or two.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is yet another name generator that I found.  This one generates pirate names.  My brother, Flintlock Freddy the Hook, says that I put too many of these on my blog.  So this is for everyone except him!   urlLink What is your pirate name?   I also found out that if NASA finds evidence that there was an ocean on Mars, Long John Silver's will give everyone a free giant shrimp.  I just thought I should let everyone know.  You wouldn't want to miss out on this offer.   urlLink IF NASA FINDS CONCLUSIVE EVIDENCE OF AN OCEAN ON MARS, AMERICA EATS FREE GIANT SHRIMP   By the way, my pirate name is "One-eyed Willie the Squeemish".
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  This movie looks great!   urlLink Starsky & Hutch 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm... this would be a great way to spend the summer.  But at the price of $1000 per class, it had better be worth it!   urlLink  USC School of Cinema-Television - Summer Program   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Big news for  urlLink Blogger  users today.  Blogger just added a site feed feature to their service.  They are using Atom for their site feeds.  I have no clue what that is exactly, but I've heard that it is way better than RSS for some reason.  Anyway, if you use site feeds at all, you can now add my site to your list.  Here is the link to my site feed:   urlLink http://www.natedillon.com/blog/personal/site_feed.xml   I think that is where I am going to keep it permanently, but I still might move it.  I don't really know what all I can do with a site feed right now.  I am trying to figure that part out.  Here are some links that talk about Atom and how to use it.   urlLink  BLOGGER - Knowledge Base - What is Atom?   urlLink Blogger Developers Network   urlLink AtomEnabled    UPDATE:  I changed my site feed filename from site_feed.atom to site_feed.xml because that is the way the people at Blogger did it in the tutorial.  I think it works both ways though.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Although this program may not be very useful, I still think it's wicked cool!  If you have Windows 2000 or XP, it might be fun to check it out.   urlLink Vitrite - Useless window transparency since 2002 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink RandomShirts.com  posted a picture of the third shirt that I got for Christmas.  I would have posted this earlier, but I accidently left my camera in Manhattan before Christmas.  This is the shirt they sent me because the order my mom made was running so far behind.  This shirt is not available to the general public yet, but they sent me a link to a page with a few shirts that they have as special offers right now.  The new shirts will be available to everyone soon.  They are pretty cool, and they are dirt cheap!  The e-mail told me that I could share this special offer with my friends, so let me know if you want to take a look at the new shirts.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink MikeRoweSoft Design    "I received an email from Smart & Biggar, Microsoft's Canadian lawyers, informing me that I have been committing copyright infringement against Microsoft. They told me that I must transfer my domain name over to Microsoft as soon as possible."   OMG!  Have the people at Microsoft completely lost their minds?  What makes them think that they can just go around demanding that people give up their domain names?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You can all call me "Big Wicker Ventriloquist" from now on!   urlLink Recordstore.com Wu Name Generator 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this link on  urlLink Ryan's blog .  There are some pretty funny words on this list.   urlLink American Dialect Society - 2003 Words of the Year 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink website mixmaster 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink To share Contacts between Microsoft Outlook and Outlook Express  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just read a small posting on  urlLink Slashdot  about an FBI raid concerning the Half-Life 2 source code.  I think that  urlLink The Hungry Programmers  are the group that the FBI suspects stole the code.  I highly recommend that you read  urlLink the blog posting about the raid .  It's pretty crazy to hear someone talk about something like that.  I also thought that it was really funny to see some of the  urlLink stuff that the FBI took  from this guy's house.  Some of it just doesn't make any sense.   urlLink Slashdot | FBI Conducts Raids Over Half-Life 2 Source Theft    urlLink The whole surreal story    urlLink The Hungry Programmers 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is part of a message from Chris Pirillo at  urlLink Lockergnome :   For years, I've witnessed people putting off the inevitable upgrade - stating that they're waiting for digital cameras to "get as good as" their film predecessors. I know plenty of professional photographers who've already made the leap and would never consider turning back. Photoshop, to them, is a part of Maslow's Hierarchy. When Kodak made their  urlLink earth-shattering announcement  the other day, I was far from surprised. They're no longer going to produce traditional cameras, opting to concentrate on the future of the industry. I can't think of the last time I had a roll processed; the idea (to me) seems as archaic as having only three channels on the television. What's going on here? Progress. Change. It happens - and you either accept it and adapt, or you suffer from yesterdayism.   I totally agree with Chris on this one.  I know of a few people that are really stuck on film, and say that they will never like digital as much.  I never understood that.  It doesn't make any sense to me.  Digital cameras are wicked cool.  They are the future of photography.  Get over it.   UPDATE:  I can understand why people would want to continue using film cameras, and there's nothing wrong with that.  In fact, I want to get a new film camera some time.  It's the people that are totally against ever going to digital that I don't understand.  People that are like, "I've always shot on film, and that's the way real photographers should shoot."  I watched a video in one of my classes that had a photographer saying that the reason that he doesn't use digital is because most photographers that shoot with digital cameras delete most of what they think are unimportant photos.  He said that the photos they delete may be important some day, but they would have deleted them already.  The whole time I was just wondering why he couldn't have a digital camera and just not delete his photos.  I didn't understand his problem with digital cameras at all.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's a little something that my dad found recently.  It was something I wrote a really really long time ago for school.  It must have been pretty good because I got an A on it.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink DepicT!  is the unique competition that challenges you to make a micro-movie of under 90 seconds.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   I just got a couple of really cool toys tonight.  The first is a sweet LEGO watch!  My brother brought me one to show me because he thought it was kind of funny, but I loved it so much that I had to have one!  I just couldn't make up my mind when it came to decide which one to get.  I ended up getting the Orient Expedition one.  The watch itself looks kind of cheap, but it said on the box that it is guaranteed to work for one year.  I figured that it was pretty good for only $12.  You can look at all of the other LEGO watches by clicking the link below.  I really like the creator one, but they didn't have it at the place I got this one.   urlLink LEGO Watches   My other toy is a new  urlLink Microsoft Blue Optical Mouse .  I had been thinking about getting one for a little while now.  Best Buy put them on sale this week for $15, so I went ahead and bought it.  I am about to hook it up now, and try it out on a game or something.  I just watched a commercial for the   urlLink Once Upon a Time in Mexico   DVD that comes out in a few days.  I think that should be my next new toy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks for the link Kristi!   urlLink PBGY Graphics - Bud Light's Real Men of Genius 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is a cool trick that I read about on  urlLink Lockergnome :   In response to the last Gnewbie Gnook of the year in which Gnomie Michael told us how to check the legitimacy of a URL by typing:   javascript:alert("The real URL of this site is: " + location.protocol + "//" + location.hostname + "/");   into your address bar, Ron Goers writes:  I have been plagued with spoofs [of] PayPal and eBay lately. Many messages are obvious, but some are real good fakes. A few go as far as stealing the graphics off the real Web site, and set up theirs to look just like it. I was pleased to find the tip from Michael in today's issue of Lockergnome Windows Fanatics. I went one step farther... I used the snippet of code to create a link on my IE toolbar. Now, any time I visit a site I'm unsure of, I simply click the link, and it reveals the real identity of the site. Cool! That's what I like so much about LG... great people sharing great tips! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Sony Pictures Digital Vegas 90-Day Challenge Winner 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Zach  sent me this from  urlLink IMDB :   The cast of hit show Friends have been given a record breaking $2 million each to make a reunion special that takes place one year after the program's finale. Jennifer Aniston, Courteney Cox. Lisa Kudrow, Matt LeBlanc, Matthew Perry and David Schwimmer all agreed to make the single 90- minute special, which will be filmed right after shooting finishes on the last ever episode of the Manhattan-based comedy. A spokesperson for television network NBC says, "We knew it would be tough to get the Friends stars together again once they'd gone their separate ways. So we put an offer on the table to persuade them to film the reunion right away." In the special one-off viewers will see the New York sixsome come together for Thanksgiving dinner, which will be screened in conjunction with the holiday in America during November.   The way I see it, NBC is getting a really good deal on this reunion show.  Right now, each star of  Friends  is paid $1 million per epsiode.  That's $1 million for 30 minutes.  The reunion episode is 90 minutes long, which would normally cost $3 millon per person, but NBC is only paying $2 million per person.  NBC is saving $1 million per person!  What a great deal!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Joho the Blog: Amazon Easter Egg 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I don't think that my font came out very well.  I may try again later using something other than a Sharpie.  You can download my font by clicking the image below.  Go to  urlLink Fontifier  to make your own handwriting font.   urlLink      To install the font:   Windows  Double-click the Fonts icon in the Control Panels folder. Drag the font file into the Fonts window to install your font.   MacOS X  Double-click the font file. A sample of your font will be displayed. Click the Install Font button to install your font. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Fontifier lets you use your own handwriting for the text you write on your computer. It turns a scanned sample of your handwriting into a computer font that you can use in your word processor or graphics program, just like regular fonts such as Helvetica.    urlLink Fontifier 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just found this on  urlLink Lockergnome :   Windows XP SP2 will include a long-awaited concurrency feature that will let multiple users connect simultaneously to the same PC. The feature is mysteriously absent in the current SP2 beta release, and how Microsoft will implement the feature and how many concurrent interactive users it will support is unclear, but a Microsoft representative confirmed to me this week that the concurrent sessions feature, called multisessions internally, is happening. The next XP Media Center Edition (MCE) version, due this fall, will use the feature to enable as many as five Media Center sessions to remote Windows Media Center Extender devices. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you are a Seinfeld fan, you need to check out this site.  You can download all the episodes, watch clips, read quotes, check out the episode guide, and more!   urlLink Seinfeld Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I recently discovered that I have over 400 web sites saved in my Favorites folder right now.  Because there are so many and they are so unorganized, it's pretty much impossible for me to really find anything in my Favorites.  I've realized that I either need to find a better way to organize them or I just need to delete them.  In trying to find out how other sites organize their links sections, I stumbled upon a site called  urlLink linkdup .  The entire site exists to collect and categorize web sites.  I might try to organize my Favorites in a similar way and then try to get them on my web site eventually.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For those of you that are still in college, you may want to take a look at this article.  I can't believe that people can actually get away with this stuff.   urlLink FOXNews.com - Views - Straight Talk - Nader Scams College Kids 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Fourth Annual Weblog Awards 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mom surprised me today with three shirts from  urlLink RandomShirts.com .  She had ordered two shirts to give me for a Christmas present, but since they were so late, they sent a third one for free!  Here are some pictures:      urlLink      urlLink        The third shirt is a new design that they haven't even put on their web site yet.  I'm pretty excited about them.  I really needed some new shirts.  Just ask my brothers.  I also received my  urlLink X2  DVD today.  It looks pretty sweet!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dangit... everytime I watch that Michel Gondry DVD I get one of the White Stripes songs stuck in my head!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Crap... After reading about these Lomo cameras, I have decided that I want one.  The cool thing about them is that you don't have to know what you are doing; you don't even have to look through the viewfinder or anything.  In fact, this site encourages you to just point and shoot randomly.  Anyway, the site makes these cameras sound really cool.  I thought that they would be cheap, but then I looked at the price... $180!  I couldn't believe it.  If I ever decide to get one, I will probably buy a used one.  They are only like $50 on  urlLink eBay .   urlLink The lomographic Society International 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Snyder said that Roberson and the other players that violated the team rules before the Fiesta Bowl would still be punished, but no one had any idea how he was going to punish them... now we know...   urlLink MSNBC - Open letter from Bill Snyder    urlLink ESPN.com - NCF - No charges, scholarship for Roberson   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF - Roberson sorry 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Zelda game that I played most was the one for Super Nintendo.  I played that game quite a bit, and I loved it.  I have to admit, the 3D Zelda games for N64 made me kind of lose interest in Zelda.  I never felt like I really wanted to play them very much.  That is why this Ocarina of Time 2D thing looks pretty cool to me.   urlLink The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time 2D 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink DECAPOLIS : Drinking a Sin?   This is an article written by Conrad (from Ghoti Hook) discussing Christians and alcohol.  I agree with everything he says in the article.  He even brings up some good points that I had never thought about.  He references a lot of Bible verses to support his thoughts.  It's a very good article.  THANKS  urlLink ZACH !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got this from one of the  urlLink RELEVANT  slices...   Democratic presidential front-runner Howard Dean said that his decision as governor to sign the bill legalizing civil unions for gays in Vermont was influenced by his Christian views. "From a religious point of view, if God had thought homosexuality is a sin, he would not have created gay people," he said ...   This guy is an idiot!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Blogger Forum - Blogger to have RSS soon, likely to be Atom 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Blogger Forum - Blogging help, tips and Blogger support 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This looks handy.  It uses JavaScript to encrypyt your e-mail address for your blog and web site.  By doing this, you can keep spam bots from finding your address and sending you a bunch of crap.   urlLink Dynamic Drive Email Riddler- email encryption script and tool 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Snoop Dogg - Tha Shizzolator   I was going through my Favorites when I ran accross this link.  It's the Snoop Dogg Shizzolator.  You can type in the address of a web site and it will shizzolate the text for you.  I think Darian sent it to me a while ago.  It's pretty funny.  One of the funniest things I tried in the Shizzolator was my blog.  That quote that I posted yesterday from Andy Rooney was great!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Yugo, this is for you...   urlLink shunt.org: Fargo=not photogenic 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  I was just checking out the stats for my web site this month when I ran accross the top search strings for my site.  I think that if you use these to do a search in  urlLink Google , my web site should come up somewhere.  edited gi joe cartoons psa overdubbed h2o church orlando xanga illinois hummer big race commercial driftlab funny gi joe psa overdubbed gi joe psa overdubbed k-state roberson assault sexual assault roberson sony dsr-pd-170 reviews
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Andy Rooney said on 60 minutes a few weeks back: (for those of you who don't know Andy Rooney, he is an 82-year-old American TV commentator)   I like big cars, big boats, big motorcycles, big houses and big campfires.  I believe the money I make belongs to me and my family, not some governmental stooge with a bad comb-over who wants to give it away to crack addicts for squirting out babies.  Guns do not make you a killer.  I think killing makes you a killer. You can kill someone with a baseball bat or a car, but no one is trying to ban you from driving to the ball game.  I believe they are called the Boy Scouts for a reason, that is why there are no girls allowed.  Girls belong in the Girl Scouts!  ARE YOU LISTENING MARTHA BURKE?  I think that if you feel homosexuality is wrong, it is not a phobia, it is an opinion.  I don't think being a minority makes you a victim of anything except numbers.  The only things I can think of that are truly discriminatory are The United Negro College Fund, Jet Magazine, Black Entertainment Television, and Miss Black America.  Try to have things like the United Caucasian College Fund, Cloud Magazine, White Entertainment Television, or Miss White America; and see what happens.  Jesse Jackson (and his illegitimate kids) will be knocking down your door.  I have the right "NOT" to be tolerant of others because they are different, weird, or tick me off.  When 70% of the people who get arrested are black, in cities where 70% of the population is black, that is not racial profiling, it is the Law of Probability.  I know what sex is, and there are not varying degrees of it.  If I received sex from one of my subordinates in my office, it wouldn't be a private matter or my personal business.  I would be "FIRED" immediately!  I believe that if you are selling me a milk shake, a pack of cigarettes, a newspaper or a hotel room, you must do it in English!  As a matter of fact, if you want to be an American citizen, you should be required to speak English!  My father and grandfather didn't die in vain so you can leave the countries you were born in to come over and disrespect ours.  I think the police should have every right to shoot your sorry  _ _ _  if you threaten them after they tell you to stop.  If you can't understand the word "freeze" or "stop" in English, see the above paragraph.  I feel much safer letting a machine with no political affiliation recount votes when needed and I know what the definition of lying is.  I don't think just because you were not born in this country, you are qualified for any special loan programs, government sponsored bank loans or tax breaks, etc., so you can open a hotel, coffee shop, trinket store, or any other business.  We did not go to the aid of certain foreign countries and risk our lives in wars to defend their freedoms, so that decades later they could come over here and tell us our constitution is a living document; and open to their interpretations.  I don't hate the rich.  I don't pity the poor.  I know pro wrestling is fake, but so are movies and television.  That doesn't stop you from watching them.  I believe a self-righteous liberal or conservative with a cause is more dangerous than a Hell's Angel with an attitude.  I think Bill Gates has every right to keep every penny he made and continue to make more.  If it ticks you off, go and invent the next operating system that's better, and put your name on the building.  Ask your buddy, Al Gore, who invented the Internet, to help you.  It doesn't take a whole village to raise a child right, but it does take a parent to stand up to the kid; and smack the little b---- ds when necessary, and say "NO!"  I think tattoos and piercing are fine if you want them, but please don't pretend they are a political statement.  And, please, stay home until that new lip ring heals.  I don't want to look at your ugly infected mouth as you serve me French fries!  I am sick of "Political Correctness."  I know a lot of black people, and not a single one of them was born in Africa; so how can they be "African-Americans"?  Besides, Africa is a continent. I don't go around saying I am a European-American because my great, great, great, great, great, great grandfather was from Europe.  I am proud to be from America and nowhere else.  And if you don't like my point of view, tough.  DON'T PASS IT ON!!  I did like it so I am passing it on. Do what you like.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got   urlLink The Work of Director Michel Gondry   DVD tonight.  That guy is awesome!  I have no idea how he does most of his videos or how he comes up with the ideas for the videos.  I knew that I had to get this DVD after watching   urlLink The Work of Director Spike Jonze   DVD that I got for Christmas.  They both are great at making music videos, and now they have both moved on to direct big Hollywood movies.  I highly recommend checking out these DVDs.  They are both part of the  urlLink Directors Label  series from  urlLink Palm Pictures .            
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink COME TRY OUR BAWLS 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This guy really likes his  urlLink Bawls !   urlLink 100 BAWLS    [2004.01.05 - 11:15:43 PM] NatoriousFAT:  it's good enough that if someone tried to take it from you, you would yell "get your hands off my bawls!"
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey  urlLink Zach , have lots of fun smoking cigars, looking at porn, and buying lottery tickets today!  Happy 18th Birthday!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is some more info on the Roberson situation.  No one will know anything for sure until the game tonight.   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF/BOWLS03 - Roberson cleared to play... if his coach lets him 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dang, is it still new year's day?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It looks like Roberson is in more trouble for missing curfew right now than he is for the sexual assault accusation.  He may not start for the Fiesta Bowl or he may not even play at all... It's all up to coach Snyder.  No matter what happens, I think K-State fans should be pretty angry with Roberson for thinking that he is special enough to break the rules.  If he doesn't get to play, it is his own stupid fault!   urlLink ESPN.com - NCF/BOWLS03 - Out late, Roberson may miss out on Fiesta Bowl 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it turns out that my computer  is  Y2K4 compliant.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dang...   urlLink SI.com - NCAA Football - K-State's Roberson suspected in sexual assault - Thursday January 1, 2004 7:30PM 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's now 2004!  I don't usually do anything very exciting for New Year's Eve.  I've just been hanging out with my dad and my brother tonight.  I only know like two people in Wichita, and Jermaine is in Arizona right now.  I heard that the New Year's party in Tempe is one of the top ten places to be for New Year's Eve.  I thought that was pretty cool.  Now I have to think of some new year's resolutions for 2004.  I also found out tonight that  urlLink Conan O'Brien  does a New Year's countdown for the central time zone.  He said that he feels sorry for all the places that get screwed on New Year's Eve because they are not on the east coast.  I thought that was really cool.  Hey  urlLink Darian , Happy New Year from the past!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink ROBERT RODRIGUEZ STARTS DIRECTING FRANK MILLER'S 'SIN CITY' NEXT MONTH    urlLink GIBSON'S THE PASSION CONTINUES TO MAKE A KILLING IN THE BOX OFFICE    urlLink 'FAMILY GUY' CREATOR SETH MACFARLANE IS SET TO MAKE HIS DIRECTORAL DEBUT 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Build anything in your imagination using virtual LEGO bricks, right on your computer!   urlLink LEGO.com Make and Create LEGO Digital Designer  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         You are Billy Idol. A true lover of punk rock and just good music in general.  However, the cops are always on the lookout for you, and your best friend may have killed someone. Try not to get involved and just have fun.   urlLink  Which '80s Pop Star Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink CSS Creator 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink FlashPlayer.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      uh... I think my quiz got me confused with someone else...       I am Face     The Faceman is the man to talk to to get things done. He's got a fast tongue and the connections to get the A-Team out of some of their most difficult moments. Has many disguises, this smooth talker is very persuasive, and doesn't hesitate to use this in working it with members of the opposite sex.    urlLink  Which A-Team member are you???  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow!  A woman died here in Wichita while watching   urlLink The Passion of the Christ  !  The theater that she was at is known as being a really nice theater.  I think she was in the one that has what I heard was the largest screen in the country too.  Maybe the combination of that theater and that movie were just too much for her.   urlLink Woman Dies Following 'Passion' Screening 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is Roger Ebert's review of   urlLink The Passion of the Christ  .   urlLink THE PASSION OF THE CHRIST / **** (R) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink EMediaLive.com: DivXNetworks Partners With Plextor to Release First DivX-Certified Hardware Video Encoder    urlLink EMediaLive.com: DVD-Copy Ruling a "Hollow Victory" 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this on the Internet somewhere, and I thought it was pretty funny.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a really different kind of blog.  The site lists obituaries of people who have passed away.  It's actually pretty interesting.   urlLink The Blog of Death 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        "The NAB ICE Award is a unique honor bestowed by industry leaders to the best and brightest artists in the digital media arena. It is designed to recognize those who stretch their creativity to the limit and craft outstanding works."   This looks like another pretty cool contest to enter.  They have lots of different categories to enter.  Too bad the entry fee is $125.  Maybe next year...   urlLink NAB2004 - ICE Award 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow... Yugo sent me this quiz, and I didn't score like I thought I would.  My score was  "47% (Yankee). Barely into the Yankee category."   I thought that I was more of a Yankee than that.   urlLink Yankee or Dixie quiz 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just found this page that tells you how to make a working camera out of a piece of paper.  It's funny because the paper that you make it out of has a drawing of a camera on it.   urlLink Dirkon - The Paper Camera [pinhole.cz]         urlLink Darian  said that he did this same sort of thing before with an oatmeal box.  Here is a link that he sent me that tells you how to do that.   urlLink Oatmeal Box Pinhole Photography  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I received a letter today that makes me laugh every time I think about it.  Quite a while ago I went to a web site to register for my part of a settlement involving the music industry.  By registering, I could be entitled to a payment.  I had almost completely forgotten about it until I received this letter.   Dear Kansas Music Purchaser:  As Attorney General for the state of Kansas, I am pleased to enclose payment for your claim in the settlement of the Compact Disc Minimum Advertised Price Antitrust Litigation.  The lawsuit was brought by the counsel for Private Class Plaintiffs on behalf of purchasers of music CDs.  In accordance with the terms of the court-approved settlement, payment is being made to music purchasers who filed a valid and timely claim.  Whether you filed your claim online at the settlement web site,  urlLink www.MusicCDSettlement.com , or by mail, the attached payment represents full payment of your portion of the Settlement.  Please note that the attached payment instrument must be cashed by May 20, 2004.  It is a pleasure to bring this matter to a satisfactory conclusion and to return value to consumers who purchased CDs while the challenged pricing policies were in effect.  Phill Kline Attorney General of Kansas     Enclosed in the letter was a check for $13.86.  I thought that if they ever sent me any money for this, it would only be like $2 or something.  I was pretty surprised to see a check for over $13! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Which Olsen twin is right for you?  Find out here:   urlLink Mary-Kate or Ashley.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Act One is an organization that seeks to train Christians in the entertainment industry.  They offer several programs, including four-week scriptwriting programs in Washington DC and Hollywood.  I also noticed that they have something in Wichita called "Festival of Faith and the Arts" listed in their Seminars & Conferences section.  There are also a lot of very useful filmmaking links listed on their web site.   "Act One, Inc. exists to create a community of Christian professionals for the entertainment industry who are committed to excellence, artistry, and personal holiness, so that through their lives and work they may be witnesses of Christ and the Truth to their fellow artists and to the global culture."   Thanks for the link  urlLink Ryan !   urlLink Act One: Writing for Hollywood 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm... I just read this article, and it seems like a bunch of crap to me.  The article is about Mel Gibson and  urlLink  The Passion of the Christ  .  Someone else please read it and tell me if I'm way off.  The writer is trying to say that  The Passion of the Christ  should not be considered a great movie because Mel Gibson is a bad person.  At one point, the writer is getting onto Mel Gibson for putting a quote from the Bible in the movie.   urlLink Kansas.com - Holier than Mel 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Darian  sent me this link.  It is about  urlLink Michel Gondry's  new music video for the band Steriogram.  Michel is once again using stop-motion animation for the video (Everyone remembers his Lego stop-motion animation video for the White Stripes, right?).  Anyway, Michel is a crazy director.  He comes up with the strangest ideas that are just so weird that they have to be cool.  You can download his new music video from this page:   urlLink Dancing Diablo Creates Stop-Motion for Michel Gondry and Steriogram 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Darian and I are probably the only two people in the world that would think this is cool.   urlLink Will the browser apply the rule(s)? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is a pretty interesting posting from the guy that made the new  urlLink Mozilla Firefox  logo.  It includes some information about how he came up with the idea, and it even has an original sketch (which I have stolen and placed below).   urlLink hicksdesign - branding firefox     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have found a great new method for finding employment.  This new method is highly experimental, but I think I am going to give it a shot.  To see the new method in action, check out this link:   urlLink decaffeinated.org - hr@decaffeinated.org? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoa... I almost forgot that today was my grandpa's 81st birthday.  He keeps saying that if you turn the numbers around, he would only be 18.  He also likes to talk about Michael Jordan a lot because they share the same birthday.  He is such a funny guy!  So even though he will probably never read this, Happy Birthday Grandpa!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ha!   urlLink Chris Pirillo  is so funny!  He is actually renting out his chest as a way to send messages to people.  It's only $20 per message.  To rent his chest, just click the link below:   urlLink Rent My Chest!   This reminds me of this picture that I found on his webcam a couple years ago.  I've been waiting to show this picture to everyone again, and I guess this is my chance.  This picture makes me laugh every time I look at it!  For those of you who don't know who Chris Pirillo is, he is a really funny computer geek who started a computer/tech web site and e-zine called  urlLink Lockergnome .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Last night,  urlLink Zach  mentioned that he was looking at the  urlLink Huntingtons'  web site, and he found out that all of the members of the band have  urlLink xanga  sites.  The Huntingtons are one of my favorite punk bands, so I thought that I might check out these sites.  It's kind of interesting to see what they do everyday and to read about some of the stuff they talk about.  One thing that I find interesting about the Huntingtons is that they are all about my age.  I often think about what I might be doing at this point in my life if I would have done some things differently.  Maybe I could have been in a band like this.  That's just something I think about every once in a while.  I just like to read about what these kinds of people are up to.  Here are the links to their sites:   urlLink rick   urlLink josh   urlLink mike   urlLink tom   By the way  urlLink Caleb , Mikey Huntington is really into poker.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a pretty interesting web site for people who have any kind of debt.  It has a calculator that helps you figure out how long it will take to pay off a bill.  Anyone with some student loans may be interested in taking a look at this site.   urlLink Learn about debt, credit cards, debt counseling and bankruptcy, all at Real-Life-Debt.com  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this link in a page of examples of sites that use Flash for video.  This is a pretty cool site.  I am always trying to find web sites of movie and video directors, but it seems like they are pretty hard to find.  Anyway, this is a good one.   urlLink Director Dario Piana 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This page talks about how the  urlLink Sundance Film Festival  has been using Macromedia Flash to deliver independent films to people through the web.  I think that Macromedia has been pushing to get more people to use Flash for online video.  Here is an interesting tip that I found on this page:   "If you'&#146;re using a sampling of videos on your homepage, break them into smaller files, three-to-five-second files, and make a long playlist. With each clip downloading in the background, dial-up users won'&#146;t have to deal with a long wait to experience the site."    urlLink Flash Video and Sundance 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Looking to waste some time?  Try out this  urlLink yeti sports 2  game.  It's pretty fun!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Fast Company | 35 Ways to Land a Job Online 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Razzies honor the worst achievments in movies.   urlLink Razzies.com - Home of the Golden Raspberry Award Foundation 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just found this link on  urlLink Lindsey's blog .  These are the people responsible for the new Quiznos commercials.   urlLink The Lair of the Crab of Ineffable Wisdom - a load of stuff by Joel Veitch that will probably crush your will to live 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just wanted to wish everyone a Happy Valentine's Day (especially my wonderful girlfriend, Jermaine).  Jermaine gave me some really weird looking Incredible Hulk Jelly Pops.  I got a good laugh out of that.  Each jelly pop is actually "hand decorated."  They are really funny, but at the same time, they are kind of scary looking.  But they look like they would actually taste good, so I can't wait to eat them.  I wish I had my camera so that I could take a picture of them.  Anyway, I hope everyone is enjoying their day today.  Happy Valentine's Day!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This looks like an interesting little program.  It allows you to share copied text with other computers on your network.  Here is a little bit of what the makers of the program had to say:   "We, the PhDs of Copy&Paste, have toiled for many a weeks to fully understand what is copying, what is pasting and how should they incorporate into the next generation of network computing, the simplicity of extending the copy, the paste beyond one's PC is essential component in the unification of user interfacing and multitasking made easy."    urlLink NetPaste - Network Copy & Paste 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This page is pretty cool.  It is a list of all the blogs of students, faculty, staff, and alumni from Wellesley College.  I wish K-State had a page like that.   urlLink Blogging at Wellesley    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blogger just posted another "Creative Tutorial."  This one is about how to date and blog.  Here is a bit of the article:   "If you are dating a non-blogger, be gentle. Be patient. Explain the intricacies of the blogosphere to them. And if their eyes start rolling back in their heads, give them some espresso and forge ahead. Talk about how you blog and why you blog. And then come up with some guidelines for what is and isn't acceptable to share on your blog. He or she may not want you to use their real name. They may not want you to post pictures of them at that nude beach you visited last summer. These are reasonable requests, and it's important that you listen respectfully. Otherwise, you many end up alone and blogging on a Saturday night. Not that there's anything wrong with that."    To read the rest of the article, click the link below.   urlLink BLOGGER - Knowledge Base - How To Date and Blog 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey, today is my mom's birthday, so I just wanted to wish her a happy birthday.  I don't think anyone really knows how old she is because she has been lying about her age for as long as I can remember.  I think she is thirty-something... ;-)  Anyway, Happy Birthday Mom!  I hope you have a great day!   UPDATE:  We went to eat at Golden Corral with my grandparents tonight for my mom's birthday.  The people working there did a good job of embarrassing her by singing a song.  When they asked how old she was, my mom just said, "let's just say 39."  So the guy working at Golden Corral yelled to everyone that she is "approximately 39 years old."  I thought that was pretty funny.  My mom was really embarrassed.  She continued to eat her food while they were singing to her.  I think she was trying to pretend that it wasn't happening.  There seemed to be a lot of people celebrating their birthdays at Golden Corral tonight.  So to all those birthday people there, Happy Birthday!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not a big fan of American Idol and I've never really watched it, but Kristi sent me this link and I thought it was pretty funny.  Be sure to watch this guy's audition video if you have never seen it before.   urlLink William Hung: A Real American Idol! The Online Tribute to Will Hung a.k.a. Hong Kong Ricky Martin 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink Mozilla  just changed the name of their "next-generation browser" from Firebird to Firefox.  They also released version 0.8 today.  They have made a lot of improvements from version 0.7, including the addition of an installer.  The biggest problem I was having with Firebird was with the extensions.  Some extensions did not seem to work well with others, and there was no way to remove the extensions once they were installed.  I suppose that was mostly not Firebird's fault though.  Other than the extensions, I really didn't have any problems.  Because of the new release today, all of the Firefox extension web sites have gone down today due to heavy traffic.  Firefox does a few things better than Opera, but I think that I will still stick with Opera for now.  I just love it too much.  But those of you who still use Internet Explorer should give Firefox a try.  By the way, I just love the new Firefox logo.  Here is where you can get some Firefox buttons to add to your web site:   urlLink http://www.mozilla.org/products/firefox/buttons.html 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, as some of you may have noticed, I uploaded my new site tonight.  I still haven't finished making all of the pages for the site, but everything that is up now should work.  Some of the links will take you to pages from my old site.  I will start adding the newer versions of those pages soon.  Let me know if anything is not working correctly.  I just got the new site up and I am already sick of it.  This seems like it was more of a test to learn CSS than anything.  Now that I kind of know what I'm doing, I feel like starting over.  I think I will stick with this one for a while though.  I might make a few minor changes to the layout.  Also, you may want to read my blog posts from the last few days.  The last several posts I made were added to the new page and not the old one that everyone had been going to.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All I can say is... wow...   urlLink Scott Blake - Bar Code Art 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is an article about what shy people (like me) can do to build a network of contacts in order to find a job.   urlLink Monster.com - Networking for the Shy 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DVDFILE.COM did an interview with one of my favorite directors, Robert Rodriguez.  Here is a bit of the interview:    As many converts to the digital cause as there are, there are also these people, say Roger Ebert, for example, who are very, very vociferous and angry almost. And there are filmmakers too who will say I will never abandon film. Do you think they misunderstand the techology?    urlLink   Absolutely. I mean film is a technology, too. People seem to think film is more organic, and it's like that doesn't grow on trees. You forget, it's such an old technology that that too is a technology, and we tend to forget that. It was just the best technology we could come up with at the time. And it's really just outdated at this point. But people who have a real love for nostalgia just don't want to hear that sort of thing. But I did get some great reviews from Roger Ebert on "Once Upon a Time in Mexico." He wrote actually the movie looks really great. So I was like, Yes, I finally broke him! That was cool.   When George Lucas showed me some early footage from "Star Wars," I was like, Hey, I didn't know it was that far along. I hadn't heard a thing about it. I was actually angry that people had been hiding all that great information. So I went out and shot a test, and I went, Oh my God, people obviously don't even know what they're talking about it. That's been the case mostly.   I saw that 10 years ago with editing. They didn't want anything to do with an Avid or a computer. So this was not real. You weren't touching the film. But the technology isn't the art form. Touching the film on a flat bed isn't editing. Editing is manipulating images. Whether you use a computer or not it's the same art form. So that's what I think Ebert needs to shift to, is to what is the art form truly? Story telling by moving images, but that's not tied to celluloid.    Click the link below to read the rest of the interview.   urlLink DVDFILE.COM: In the Director's Chair - Robert Rodriguez 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I watched an ad for this sports film contest when I was watching Fox Sports.  The finalists get a Sony Camcorder, an appearance on the  Best Damn Sports Show Period , and most importantly, an internship at Fox next summer.  Those internships can be pretty hard to get, so it's a pretty big deal to win one.  I would enter, but I just found out that it is for current students only.   urlLink FOXSports.com | BDSSP Film Festival presented by Sony Electronics 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This program looked kind of cool.  It adds a bunch of extra stuff to Windows.  I might give it a try sometime later.   urlLink NuonSoft :: ShellEnhancer - Product Information 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  Thanks for the link Caleb!   urlLink LawForKids.org LawToons - TP Spells Trouble 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to let everyone know that I have been uploading bits and pieces of my new web site during the last few days.  If you are having any problems with my old site, it's probably because I messed something up while working on my new site.  I am hoping to have the new site completed sometime this week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Learning Movable Type: Concerning Spam 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just  urlLink spewed .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink MooseKGJ's Xanga Site - top 25 guy movies 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           I AM 42% GEEK! 
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Pacific Digital > Products > MemoryFrame 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       [2004.03.23 - 11:49:07 PM] Kyle Whitley:  I'm 45% punk, i don't know how though
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am 18% Punk Rock   urlLink     It's not a fashion craze, or even a cool thing to do. I should just swallow it, get Lost, and take my friends with me.   urlLink  Take the Punk Rock Test at fuali.com   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just came across a good article about how to make video look more like film.  I don't understand everything in the article yet, but it is still very interesting.  You will have to sign up for an account on this web site before you can view the article.   urlLink DV.com: Features - How to Make Video Look like Film   ...  Here are some of the things in the article that I found interesting:   "To get the best results, start long before you use any plug-in or proprietary process. The key building block is to shoot video with film production values: fine lighting, careful exposure, good composition, lens filters, and controlled camera motion. You must take as much care shooting the original video as does a film crew on a $50 million feature."    "Deinterlacing is at the core of all post processes used to make video look like film... Some software deinterlaces by simply duplicating one of the fields, effectively halving the vertical resolution. Sony consumer camcorders also do this when they are operated at a shutter speed of 1/30 second. However, the Canon XL1, XL1S, and GL2 can run in a true 30p 'frame mode,' which has made the cameras attractive to filmmakers."    "The effect of a subtle gamma curve change has a huge impact in perception. Highlights become more pastel, shadows become denser, and midrange colors appear more saturated."   ...   UPDATE:  I was eager to try out some of the simple techniques that this article talked about, so I decided to mess with one of my old projects a little bit.  I opened up my  Secret of Women  video and tried to adjust the colors.  The article includes this graphic which shows the gamma curve differences between video and film:      "(right) A typical film's gamma curve has a mild S shape, (left) while video cameras are usually engineered to have a flat gamma response. A gamma curve shows the distribution of gray values, or midrange tones."   I opened up my video in  urlLink Vegas  and changed the color curves to look like the curve on the right.  Here are the results:              To me, this simple change makes the image so much better.  When I was working on  The Secret of Women , I wanted to try to fix the color after I finished editing.  I ended up running out of time and never messed with the color at all.  Now I wish that I had tried something like this a long time ago.  I don't know if this makes the video look more like film, but it sure does look a lot better!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink RODRIGUEZ DROPS HIS DGA TO CO-DIRECT WITH MILLER AND TARANTINO   I generally don't like unions.  They seem to make everything so complicated.  I also heard that Tarantino is not a member of the Director's Guild because he doesn't like them or something.  I really like this picture of Robert Rodriguez.  It's funny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Sony Digital University 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just realized why it is a bad idea to read 5 Lockergnome Newsletters at once.  There are just too many good links.  Rather than post all of these links separately, I am just going to put them all in one post here.  I am planning to change my blog format around so that I won't have this problem in the future.  I think I got one of these links from Darian's web site.    urlLink DVD Shrink: Shrink your DVDs to fit DVDR!    urlLink 10 new ways to speed up download time : evolt.org, Site Development    urlLink Internet Archive    urlLink Scribbling.net - Help the Googlebot understand your web site    urlLink Calendar Updates - Free Holiday and Sport Team Schedules for Microsoft Outlook    urlLink The Official Web Presence of Gorilla 2: The Return    urlLink XHTML Quicktime Object 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink ITnews Australia     Corel Announces WordPerfect Office 12  Corel, which is under new management, announced last week that it will issue a new WordPerfect Office release in April that will see the suite return to its former position of glory. Corel says that WordPerfect Office 12 will take on Microsoft Office 2003 head to head, offering lower prices and competitive features. And the company will no longer be content with simply selling upgrades to existing customers -- a losing strategy if there ever was one. To that end, WordPerfect Office 12 will offer document compatibility and even application compatibility with Microsoft Word; in other words, users who make the switch can configure WordPerfect to look and work exactly like Word does. "We're after the consumer and small- and mid-sized business market," Corel WordPerfect Product Manager Wendy Lowe said. "We've found that a lot of [people] are looking to an Office alternative and getting savvy that there are cheaper alternatives. That's where [WordPerfect Office] 12 plays nicely; it has a set of features comparable to the standard edition of Microsoft Office, but it's cheaper."    I've always liked Corel WordPerfect better than Microsoft Word.  It just seemed to work better for me.  I've been using WordPerfect Office 2000 for about five years now.  I should probably think about upgrading.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      From the Thursday edition of the  urlLink Lockergnome Windows Fanatics Newsletter .    urlLink http://shortscripts.com/   {Share and find short scripts} Film makers and Spielberg wanna-bes, this is the place for you. Short Scripts is a central "meeting" spot, so to speak, for finding and letting others know about your short scripts. The site doesn't store the scripts, but rather stores the summary and e-mail contact information so you know where to go. Its sole purpose is short scripts and it costs nothing to use the site. Copyright concerns? The FAQ addresses that. I wonder if any interesting stories have resulted from the contacts made on the site. [ urlLink Meryl ]
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is from Tuesday's  urlLink Lockergnome Windows Fanatics Newsletter .    Gnomie Ron Enderland writes:  I had a DSL account with Southwestern Bell. When they cut some sort of deal with Yahoo! to take over DSL, I instantly started getting spam on my swbell.net e-mail address. This is an address that I never, ever used, or posted anywhere! The only reason I even checked it for mail was because SWBell would occasionally send me DSL news and account updates. I complained to Yahoo! about it, and got some clueless automatic reply about what to do if a user abuses one of their free e-mail accounts (confirming that they don't read customers' e-mails). My tiny revenge: leave all messages on the server. Eventually, the spam they got me by selling my e-mail adrress will take up noticable server space (I hope). 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Man, I love Johnny Ramone.  I love him even more after reading this article.  Believe it or not, Johnny is a Republican.  In this article, he talks about how his political views caused a bit of conflict within the Ramones.  I still can't believe that he hasn't been playing guitar at all since the Ramones broke up.  He said that he sold all of his guitars and amps right after the break up.  That's sad because he is one of the greatest punk guitarists to ever play.   urlLink Johnny Ramone: Rebel in a rebel's world - The Washington Times: Entertainment 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here is an article about the removal of the Propagandhi song from the  Rock Against Bush  CD.  It includes a message from Fat Mike.   urlLink Absolute Punk Forums - Propagandhi Are A Little Out There    "I am trying to unite people not alienate them from each other."   Either Fat Mike is a liar or he really doesn't have a clue.  What does he think he is doing to all of the conservative punks by releasing  Rock Against Bush  and by launching the  urlLink Punkvoter  site?  I don't think that he is uniting everyone.  Oh, he must be assuming that no one that listens to punk music can possibly like Bush.  And you know what happens when you make an assumption?  (Just watch  urlLink  The Long Kiss Goodnight   to answer that one)  Fat Mike, I love your music, but I can't understand or agree with your political views at all!   UPDATE:  Ha!  I was just reading the comments at the bottom of this article.  Some of them are really funny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha!  Finally there is a political punk site that doesn't lie about it's purpose like  urlLink Punkvoter .  This site is pretty much the opposite of Punkvoter.  It's the "The 'Right' Side of Punk".   urlLink Conservative Punk Magazine   Thanks for the link  urlLink Zach .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     You are Joshua Abraham Norton, first and only Emperor of the United States of America!   Born in England sometime in the second decade of the nineteenth century, you carved a notable business career, in South Africa and later San Francisco, until an entry into the rice market wiped out your fortune in 1854. After this, you became quite different. The first sign of this came on September 17, 1859, when you expressed your dissatisfaction with the political situation in America by declaring yourself Norton I, Emperor of the USA. You remained as such, unchallenged, for twenty-one years.   Within a month you had decreed the dissolution of Congress. When this was largely ignored, you summoned all interested parties to discuss the matter in a music hall, and then summoned the army to quell the rebellious leaders in Washington. This did not work. Magnanimously, you decreed (eventually) that Congress could remain for the time being. However, you disbanded both major political parties in 1869, as well as instituting a fine of $25 for using the abominable nickname "Frisco" for your home city.   Your days consisted of parading around your domain - the San Francisco streets - in a uniform of royal blue with gold epaulettes. This was set off by a beaver hat and umbrella. You dispensed philosophy and inspected the state of sidewalks and the police with equal aplomb. You were a great ally of the maligned Chinese of the city, and once dispersed a riot by standing between the Chinese and their would-be assailants and reciting the Lord's Prayer quietly, head bowed.  Once arrested, you were swiftly pardoned by the Police Chief with all apologies, after which all policemen were ordered to salute you on the street. Your renown grew. Proprietors of respectable establishments fixed brass plaques to their walls proclaiming your patronage; musical and theatrical performances invariably reserved seats for you and your two dogs. (As an aside, you were a good friend of Mark Twain, who wrote an epitaph for one of your faithful hounds, Bummer.) The Census of 1870 listed your occupation as "Emperor".   The Board of Supervisors of San Francisco, upon noticing the slightly delapidated state of your attire, replaced it at their own expense. You responded graciously by granting a patent of nobility to each member. Your death, collapsing on the street on January 8, 1880, made front page news under the headline "Le Roi est Mort". Aside from what you had on your person, your possessions amounted to a single sovereign, a collection of walking sticks, an old sabre, your correspondence with Queen Victoria and 1,098,235 shares of stock in a worthless gold mine. Your funeral cortege was of 30,000 people and over two miles long.   The burial was marked by a total eclipse of the sun.   urlLink Which Historical Lunatic Are  You ?    urlLink From the fecund loins of Rum and Monkey.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got back from work.  Now I need to pack, take a shower, and then I'm off to Manhattan without any sleep.  I can sleep during the two and a half hour trip there, but I don't know about getting any more than that today.  I haven't been in Manhattan for about three months now.  More importantly, I haven't seen Jermaine for about three months now!  I will be in Manhattan until Tuesday or Wednesday.  This should be a good trip.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink The NES (Nintendo Entertainment System) Home Theatre PC System Modification 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Links from  urlLink Big D :   urlLink Homemade 35mm to DV Camcorder Depth of Field Adapters    urlLink Homemade 35mm Adapter 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this link on  urlLink Darian's blog .  This is a production company run by some guys in Belgium.   urlLink another state of mind   Their photos and videos look great, but what makes these guys even more impressive is that they made  urlLink their own Mini35 kit .  This is a kit that allows them to shoot MiniDV video through an old SLR film camera to give their digital video a film look.  They used this kit along with a Canon GL-2 to make their short film  urlLink  Marla  .  I have done a little bit of research in the past (mostly on  urlLink Google ) to try to find out if there was a way to make digital video look more like film.  I had no idea that something like this was possible, which is weird because, like Darian pointed out, there are Mini35 kits available to buy.  I guess I really suck at looking stuff up on Google.  Ok, now I just have a ton of questions about how this Mini35 thing works.  Why is the MiniDV camera pointing down onto the top of the film camera and not into the back of the film camera?  Did they have to take that film camera apart to get this to work?  Did they have to adjust the video much in post-production to get it to look more like film?  These are just a few of the questions that I have about this kit.  I hope they come out with some kind of tutorial for how to build a Mini35 kit because I want to make one now.  I already told my brother that I am going to have to "borrow" his 35mm camera once I get a MiniDV camera...  Marla is pretty cool by the way.  From what I gathered, it's kind of a side story from the movie  urlLink  Fight Club  .  Anyway, I suggest that you go to their web site and watch it for yourself.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Who returns a can of tuna at 3 in the morning?  Come on people!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ok, those of you who know when I started reading the first  Lord of the Rings  book will find this really funny... Last night I finished reading  The Fellowship of the Ring !  That's right, it only took me a little over two years to finish it.  I have been reading it every day at work during my "lunch" break.  I have been really bad about finishing books.  I started reading several books in college that I just never finished.  I am trying to break this habit now.  I am also trying to spend at least a little bit of time reading every day.  Having an hour-long break at work really helps.  One thing that I liked about reading  The Fellowship of the Ring  after I have seen the movie is that I know what's going on in the story no matter how long it has been since I last picked up the book.  There are a few changes that were made in the movie, but for the most part everything is the same.  The book just adds a lot of little details that the movie had to leave out.  Now that I am done with the first book, I am ready to start reading  The Two Towers .  It looks a bit smaller than the first book, so I am hoping to have it done in about a year and a half...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink 10 Tips on Writing the Living Web: A List Apart 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Cloud King : An Art Gallery 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Press Action: Winning the Love of Warbloggers in 11 Easy Steps 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         This is Perry Penguin.  He was a gift from Jermaine.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I have been working at Wal-Mart for a whole week now.  So far I really like it.  The job is pretty easy, it's just really tiring.  When I get home at 7:00am, I am ready to go to bed!  So my schedule goes something like this now...  I work from 10:00pm to 7:00am.  I get home by 7:20am each day (I have to have my dad's car back so that he can go to work and take my brother to school).  I sleep from 7:30 or 8:00am until about 3:00 or 4:00pm.  I then have a few hours of free time before I have to go back to work.   One cool thing about third-shift stocking is that we don't have to be at work for our entire shift.  We can leave whenever our work is finished.  We have already finished early a couple times since I have been there.  The only bad thing is that stockers also have to work until everything is finished.  So if 7:00am comes around and things aren't done, someone has to stay and finish it.  I don't really have a way to stay though because, like I said, I have to get my dad's car back to him.  So far this hasn't been much of a problem though.  I will be working Tuesday through Saturday, and I will have Sunday and Monday nights off.  This makes things kind of weird because I pretty much miss the entire weekend.  I have also found that this will make it interesting to try to make it to church on Sunday mornings at 11:00am.  I think I will just take a short nap, get up for church, then sleep some more after church.  The store that I work at is in the process of expanding from a normal Wal-Mart into a Super Wal-Mart.  The grocery side will be opening later this month.  They told me that this store used to be the busiest store in the region until Wichita opened a Super Wal-Mart on the west side.  They are hoping that it will once again be the busiest once this new addition is completed... fun fun...  With the new expansion, the store had to hire about 35 temporary employees.  That is in addition to the regular full-time spots they had to fill.  I was lucky enough to get a full-time spot, so I will be able to keep my job when the grocery side opens.  The store hangs every new employee's photo on a wall in the break room.  Last time I counted, there were 64 photos on that wall.  That's pretty crazy.  I know that my strange schedule and new job isn't too exciting to read about, but I thought that I should just post something about it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dang, I wish I could go to this!  Maybe I could meet Robert Rodriguez there...   urlLink SXSW 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jermaine sent me these pictures a couple weeks ago, and I thought they were pretty amazing.   "These are all drawings done on sidewalks... so keep in mind the surfaces are FLAT."                   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Wired News: Webmonkey, RIP: 1996 - 2004 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, I think this guy upset quite a few bloggers with this article.  The writer claims that blogging is over-rated and pointless.  He also makes a few dumb statements such as this one:   "I wish there were some way of licensing who can blog and who can't; then we could say there were some with quality."   If you had to get a license to blog, then all blogs would be exactly like the T.V. stations, radio stations, and popular books that we already have because it would most likely be the same kinds of people creating all of the blogs.  Oh yeah, we would all also have to be communists for that to happen.  And by the way, we already have some blogs "with quality."  We don't need licensing for that!   urlLink Geek.com Geek News - Blogging--survey says, "Not so hot"   You know, I was just thinking that if this was 10 or 15 years ago, this guy would probably be saying that the Internet is over-rated because any idiot with a computer can make a web site.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink FILMMAKER ROBERT RODRIGUEZ SIGNED TO HELM A PRINCESS OF MARS AFTER "SIN CITY"    urlLink LOTR STAR, BILLY BOYD WILL VOICE CHUCKY'S CHILD    urlLink THE LION, THE WITCH AND THE WARDROBE WILL JUMP FROM THE PAGE TO THE SCREEN 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       For those of you who don't know, I got a finally job last week.  I will be an overnight stocker at the local  urlLink Wal-Mart .  I know it doesn't really sound like any kind of dream job, but in a weird way, it sort of is for me.  I have been wanting to try being an overnight stocker at a retail store for a while.  I was almost one when I worked at Builders Square, but they ended up changing the shift to start at like 5am!  So I just took another shift.  I think the overnight stocker position sounds fun though.  There won't be as many customers around, and it just sounds like it would be cool to get paid to stay up all night.  I have never been happy about having to start working at 7 or 8 in the morning.  Plus, the overnight positions get paid $1 an hour more than the other positions.  I start my new job tonight at 10pm, and I will be working until 7am.  I just hope that I can stay awake.  Last night I stayed up until 4:30 or 5:00am so that I could sleep in later today and be as rested as possible for work tonight.  I'm still not sure how well I will adjust to this new schedule.  The way I see it, I have almost the same schedule as my dad and brother.  But instead of working or going to school from 7am until about 4pm, I am sleeping.  And instead of sleeping from 10pm to 7am, I am working.  I just hope that my body agrees with this theory.  I am pretty nervous about starting my job tonight.  One reason is that it's new, and I always get nervous when I start something new.  I am also nervous because I still don't know exactly what I will be doing.  I mean, I get the basic idea, but I still don't know all of the details about my job yet.  I am also worried that the sudden change in schedule will come as quite a shock to me.  I'm used to doing pretty much nothing all day.  Now I will only have a few hours of free time every day.  I'm sure that it won't take too long to get used to though.  It never has before.  But then again, this is the longest amount of time that I have ever spent doing nothing before.  I am just happy to have some kind of job.  I really really needed to start working and make some money.  I know that it was God that gave me this job, and I am extremely thankful.  I am going to try really hard to make the most out of this opportunity.  Who knows, this may end up being the most fun job I've ever had!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A couple moths ago I started looking at a lot of "photo blogs" on the Internet.  Looking at these photo blog sites really made me want to start taking more pictures so that I could have my own little photo blog.  One site in particular that really inspired me was a site called  urlLink  apparently nothing at all  .  The reason that I like this site so much is that most of the photos on it were taken with a  urlLink Canon Powershot S30 , the very same camera that I own.  This proved to me that my camera really has the ability to produce great photos, I just need to become a better photographer.  Now that my camera has been returned to me after I left it in Manhattan for a couple months, I am going to try to post my photos on my blog at least a couple times a week.  I'm sure that most of them are going to really suck, but at least it gives me a reason to practice taking more photos.  So here is my first photo.  This was taken today... or I guess it was technically yesterday (Sunday)...     I really hate camera flashes.  They always make my photos look way to bright, and thus crappy.  Sometimes I turn on the flash just to make something really weird happen.  This is one of those times.  I was outside taking pictures of some cool looking clouds with my brother  urlLink Ben .  I was trying to take a picture of him with the clouds in the background, but the background was too bright and he was too dark.  I just turned the flash on to see what would happen.  I have another photo of him that is very similar.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In case you haven't noticed, I've made another small addition to my sidebar.  I've started another blog on  urlLink Blogger  for all of the interesting sites that I find on the Internet.  I did this so that I wouldn't have so many posts in my personal blog that are nothing but links.  I haven't set up the archive pages yet, but once I do, I will be able to have a short description for each link.  You can find this new blog under the title  Bookmarks  in my sidebar.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      David is the #6 most common male name. 2.363% of men in the US are named david. Around 2894675 US men are named david! source  urlLink namestatistics.com   Nathan is the #108 most common male name. 0.185% of men in the US are named nathan. Around 226625 US men are named nathan! source  urlLink namestatistics.com   Dillon is the #825 most common last name. 0.015% of last names in the US are dillon. Around 37500 US last names are dillon! source  urlLink namestatistics.com     Nate is a very rare male name. Very few men in the US are named nate. Be proud of your unique name! source  urlLink namestatistics.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't been posting much lately.  It seems like I have had a lot of stuff to talk about, but I have just been too lazy to type it.  I have also been trying to get my web site re-structured.  I never really finished this design either.  My site has a lot of problems, so I decided to pretty much start over.  I hope that I can get it finished during my next days off.   Last Wednesday, the  urlLink Wal-Mart  store where I work had it's grand opening as a Wal-Mart Supercenter.  Rather than close the store down and re-build a new building, Wal-Mart decided that they would just expand the current store while keeping most of it open.  The only new thing that the grand opening added to the store was most of the grocery section.  I took my camera to work with me last week to take some pictures.  There are a lot of funny signs and things at work.  I will probably put them up once I get my new photo blog started.  My brother was also able to borrow a  urlLink Lomo LC-A  camera from his teacher, so we went out and took a bunch of pictures with it.  I got those back today, so I will post them soon as well.  I was really excited to try out that camera.  My black and white photos seemed to come out better than my color photos.  Maybe that is because I bought the cheapest color film that I could find at Wal-Mart.  The  urlLink NHL  playoffs have started, and so far I have only been late to work twice.  It wouldn't be such a problem if the games didn't keep going into overtime.  The first round of the playoffs is great because there are usually four games every night.   urlLink ESPN  used to play all four games every night.  They would have two on ESPN and two on ESPN2.  They haven't really done that this year.  They have only been showing two or three.  I don't know why.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I woke up this afternoon expecting to watch the hockey game on  urlLink ABC .  I checked  urlLink ESPN's web site  this morning before I went to bed, and found that there would be a game starting on ABC at 2pm Central Time.  I decided that I could wake up in time to watch the last period of the game.  When I woke up this afternoon, the game was not on ABC.  Instead, the local ABC affiliate,  urlLink KAKE , decided to replace the hockey game with a literacy telethon.  This did not make me happy at all.  Although the telethon is a good thing to do for the community, I think KAKE made a very poor choice when they decided to not play the hockey game.  It would have been different if they would have normally been playing re-runs or a movie or something today.  The hockey game is meant to be a live event.  You can only watch it live once.  Even if they re-played the game later (as if ABC would even do that), most people would not watch or enjoy it because they already know what happens.  KAKE probably upset most of the hockey fans in Wichita by not playing the hockey game.  Also, I don't even know how KAKE was able to replace something like a hockey game.  I would think that ABC wouldn't like that very much.  There are a lot of advertisers that have paid ABC to play their ads on national TV.  How does that work out if all of the affiliates are not playing the game or the ads that go with the game?  Instead of having a telefund, why didn't KAKE just give the literacy fund all of the money they would have made off of local ads they play during the game?  Maybe the ads from one hockey game wouldn't have raised as much money, but they had been playing that telefund all day.  I'm sure that all of the ads for the day would have come close to raising that much money.  I know that it sounds like I am making a big deal out of this whole situation, but this is just one of those things that really annoys me.  I don't think KAKE would have done this for any other major sport, like the basketball playoffs.  They probably just thought that no one would care.  I think it just makes me feel better to complain about it on my blog.  As I was telling my dad and brother today, it's probably a good thing that KAKE was having a literacy telefund, because now they can learn to read the schedule to find out when they are supposed to be playing the hockey games on their station.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Ha!  I just tried to go to check all of my friends' blogs, and I got a page with this error message for all of the  urlLink Xanga  sites.  I guess that's another good thing about using a blog service or program that publishes to a separate web site.  Even if  urlLink Blogger  goes down, all of my blog will still be up as long as my web host is still up.  But I'm sure that Xanga will fix this problem soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink EMediaLive.com: Adobe Premiere Pro To Demonstrate High Definition Video Production at NAB   I was just reading this little article about Adobe announcing that they will demonstrate Adobe Premiere Pro with high definition (HD) video solutions.  The article says, "Adobe Premiere Pro-based HD systems can be configured for as little as US$5000."  What exactly does that $5000 include?  Doesn't  urlLink Vegas  just do HD video by itself?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      uh... ok...     You are a  GRAMMAR GOD !  If your mission in life is not already to preserve the English tongue, it should be. Congratulations and thank you!   urlLink   How grammatically sound are you?    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Is my Blog HOT or NOT? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Holga tonyLim 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm... Maybe instead of a  urlLink Lomo LC-A , I should get this  urlLink Holga 120SF ...  The LC-A is normally $200 (I can find it for $85-100 on eBay).  The Holga is regularly $60, and I can easily find them for less than $20 on eBay!  I was just reading a little bit about the Holga, and it seems like it is almost as cool as the Lomo LC-A.  I think they both use the same concept when taking pictures: "Don't Think, Just Shoot".
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Lyra A/V 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have added two more friends' links to my sidebar:   urlLink Jason   urlLink Robert 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink RODRIGUEZ'S FUTURE ON "MARS" IS NOT LOOKING TOO BRIGHT 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Make Your Own PZM Microphone 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink dvspot review: Canon Optura 20 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I keep forgetting that today is April Fools Day, but I did remember long enough to play a little joke on  urlLink my sister .  Lindsey's friend had a baby last night, and Lindsey borrowed my camera to take some pictures of the baby.  Tonight she was asking me to send the pictures to her.  That is when we had this AIM conversation (which has been edited for content as well as to cover up my inabilaty to spell):   Session Start (NatoriousFAT:carebeardillon): Thu Apr 01 19:02:26 2004   carebeardillon:  hey can you PLEASE send me those pictures i took last night?!?  NatoriousFAT:  well crap  NatoriousFAT:  somehow they got erased off of my camera  carebeardillon:  WHAT?!?!  carebeardillon:  no they didn't...  NatoriousFAT:  i dont know  carebeardillon:  they can't  NatoriousFAT:  i have the pictures of zach on there  NatoriousFAT:  but nothing else  carebeardillon:  nate  carebeardillon:  stop it  carebeardillon:  please send them to me  NatoriousFAT:  stop what?  i'm being serious!  NatoriousFAT:  i can send you the pictures of zach's hair, but you dont want those do you?  carebeardillon:  well send them with the pictures of corben  NatoriousFAT:  that's all i have!  carebeardillon:  nate!  NatoriousFAT:  wait, here is the problem  NatoriousFAT:  i dont think you took any pictures  carebeardillon:  yes i did!  NatoriousFAT:  look at this  carebeardillon:  there were 7 of them  NatoriousFAT:  this is the last picture i took with my camera  *** carebeardillon has received IMG_2890.JPG.   NatoriousFAT:  and this is the first picture that was on there from last night  *** carebeardillon has received IMG_2891.JPG.   NatoriousFAT:  it is a picture of zach  carebeardillon:  nate stop it!  NatoriousFAT:  the numbers go from 2890 to 2891  NatoriousFAT:  that means that there were no pictures taken in between  carebeardillon:  that's not funny  carebeardillon:  fix it  NatoriousFAT:  how can i fix it???????  carebeardillon:  find them please  NatoriousFAT:  there is nothing to find  carebeardillon:  zach was messing with it  NatoriousFAT:  i copied all of the pictures from my card to my computer  NatoriousFAT:  and that's all i have!  carebeardillon:  ahhhhhhhhhhhhhkhsahaaaaaaaaaaakhfkaljadsjfklasjgahkldfkahklfhaaaaaaaaa!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  carebeardillon:  >:o  NatoriousFAT:  what is that supposed to mean?  carebeardillon:  i am angry!  NatoriousFAT:  at me?  carebeardillon:  at the situation  NatoriousFAT:  what am i supposed to do about it?  carebeardillon:  i don't know  NatoriousFAT:  they were just pictures  NatoriousFAT:  it's not the end of the world  NatoriousFAT:  i think you need to calm down  NatoriousFAT:  and remember what day it is...  carebeardillon:  uh they were the only pictures i have of my best friends baby that i waited and waited and lost sleep over  carebeardillon:  i won't get to see him again for at least 2 weeks or more  carebeardillon:  and he will look different then  NatoriousFAT:  ok, and what day is it today?  carebeardillon:  ahhhhhhhhhhhhhdklfhalkfhksdfhlj!  carebeardillon:  i am so mad at you!  NatoriousFAT:  heh  carebeardillon:  not funny  NatoriousFAT:  here are your dirty little pictures  carebeardillon:  thanks alot!  NatoriousFAT:  no problem  *** carebeardillon has received 20040331.rar. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink BridgeBuilder-Game.com - The ultimate bridge building games website 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Web Hosting 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
                     this is a test of posting through  e-mail   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      test
       
    
    
</post>



</Blog>