<Blog>

<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Usapang Babae   Feeling ko ako ay isang lalake na napapaligiran ng nagdadakdakang babae sa isang harem at ang kanilang pinaguusapan ay mga nagsasayawang exhibitionist, belly dancers at kung anu-ano pang kahalayan lalo na nung nagkwento ang isa tunkol sa bridal shower na kanyang naatenan habang ako ay namumula habang nakikinig sa usapang babae tunkol sa mga lalake.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Mga Forwarded Messages ni Gian kay Arianne   "Your temporary absence from my immediate vicinity seems to affect a slight depression of sorts within this realm of today's existence...In short..."I miss you..."  "If you'd ask me who I want to spend the rest of my life with, tatabihan lang kita, tititigan ka sa mata at ngingiti.  I'll hold your hand like never before & I'll whisper 'Ikaw ang gusto kong makasama habang buhay'  A prayer for the romantically disenfranchised, delusional or merely hopeful:  Lord, if he's the one, please let everything fall into place.  But if he isn't, Lord, pwede bang sya na lang?  *The last one was sent to me*    Mga Aktibidades sa Araw na Ito   - Binasa ang Win2K Modules.  Di pa nga ako tapos.  Nasa Module 2 pa lang tungkol sa user accounts. - Binisita ang mga sites na kasali sa Webby Awards.  Binot ang site ni Reige. - Nagbasa at nagsulat ng sagot sa e-mail - Kumain ng pizza and ice cream    Isang rebyu ng "Beauty Lies..." ni Reige   Ang short story na "Beauty Lies..." ay tungkol sa isang babae na  plain looking  at ang kanyang naging karanasan sa loob ng sinehan na nagpapalabas ng Die Hard 2.  Ito ay isang istorya tungkol sa  appearances .  Kung pano nakakapagiba ng ugali at impression ang dilim at liwanag.    Kung tatanungin nyo ako e ikukuwento ko na ang kabuuan ng storyang ito kaya...wag na lang.  Bisitahin nyo na lang ang  site  ni Reige.  Ang kanyang mga sulat ay nasa Hope.  Kung maenganyo kayo sa kanyang  website  e baka matatagalan bago nyo mabsa ang "Beauty Lies..."   Okay  lang yun.  Visit his site at  urlLink Nuda Veritas     Pinapatanong nya kina W--- at S--- kung pwede nya silang maging e-mail pals.  Argh.  Bakit?  Bakit gusto nya?  Bakit ayaw ko?  Bakit ako affected?  Pero sabi ko okay.  Okay!  Natural pinapalawak nya ang kanyang mga kaibigan.  Sorry na lang ako at ang lumalawak ay female friends di ba?  Isa pa ano ba ako?  E di hamak na "friend" lang din na nakilala nya sa internet.  Malamang hindi lang naman ako ang madalas nyang kausap sa telepono.  Andyan si ano at ano.  Aaaahhh.  Talaga naman.  E kasi ikaw sagot ka rin ng sagot at basa ng basa ng mga e-mail.  Lecheng e-mail yan.  Hmmm...siguro naman sa susunod na makita ko sya e mawawala na ito.  Siguro.  Gusto ko ba?  Ah magulo.  Magulo talaga.  Iniisip ko tuloy kung kakausapin ko sya mamaya.  Edi ano enjoy the talks, enjoy the mails, enjoy the time na meron?  As if naman naghahanap ako ng boyfriend eh noh?  Oh e kaya nga e!  So bakit ganyan ka?  Bakit nga ba?  Hindi naman siguro ganito ka pathetic ang buhay ko 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Today not much calls.  Just a regular, normal day.  I finished reading volume 3 of the shoujo manga "Miriam".  Waiting for the next volumes and also for the next scanslation of Chizumi & Fujiomi from Mangasync.  Great guys ^_^
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Menstruation   - The monthly discharge of blood from the uterus of nonpregnant women from puberty to menopause;    "the women were sickly and subject to excessive menstruation";   "a woman does not take the gout unless her menses be stopped"--Hippocrates;    "the semen begins to appear in males and to be emitted at the same time of life that the catamenia begin to flow in females"--Aristotle    [syn: menses, catamenia, period, flow] 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Just Say You'll Love Me   Chicago   Take me as I am  Put your hand in mine now and forever  Darling here I stand, stand before you now  Deep inside I always knew  It was you, you and me  Two hearts drawn together bound by destiny  It was you and you for me  Every road leads to your door  Every step I take forever more   CHORUS:  Just say you'll love me for the rest of your life  I gotta lot of love and I don't want to let go  Will you still love me for the rest of my life?  'Cause I can't go on  No, I can't go on  I can't go on  If I'm on my own   Take me as I am  Put your heart in mine, stay with me forever  'Cause I am just a man who never understood  I never had a thing to prove  Till there was you  You and me  Then it all came clear so suddenly  How close to you that I wanna be   CHORUS   Bridge:  Do you believe a love could run so stong?  Do you believe a love could pass you by?  There was no special one for me  I was the lovely one, you see  But then my heart lost all control  Now you're all that I know 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
           Scenes      Webshots    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       CAN'T HELP FALLING IN LOVE (Elvis Presley)    Wise men say only fools rush in  but I can't help falling in love with you  Shall I stay  would it be a sin  If I can't help falling in love with you   Like a river flows surely to the sea  Darling so it goes  some things are meant to be  take my hand, take my whole life too  for I can't help falling in love with you   Like a river flows surely to the sea  Darling so it goes  some things are meant to be  take my hand, take my whole life too  for I can't help falling in love with you  for I can't help falling in love with you 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      One Night   The Corrs   Long day and I'm ready I'm waiting for your call 'Cos I've made up my mind My heart aches with a hunger no want that you were mine No I cannot deny So for one night is it allright That I give you My heart - my love - my heart Just for one night My body - my soul Just for one night My love - my love For one night - one night - one night  When morning awakes me Well I know I'll be alone And I feel I'll be fine So don't you worry about me I'm not empty on my own For inside I'm alive That for one night - it was so right That I gave you My heart - my love - my heart Just for one night My body - my soul Just for one night My love - I loved For one night - one night - one night  For one night - it was so right That I gave you My heart - my love - my heart Just for one night My body - my soul Just for one night My love - my love For one night - we loved - one night - one night One night ... yeah
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Tuesdays At GSC   The Engagement Rings e-mail came from Jaz w/c in turn came from a friend of hers.  These so-called engagement rings include the  urlLink Missionary  position w/c Shai identified as the 6th picture in the mail.    Before this mail we, er, they were talking about engagements and weddings.  Tina is going to spend 50,000 for hers.  Half of it for liposuction because she wants to be beautiful on her wedding day.  She means not fat.  Tina is already cute. ----- Where is the faint smell of Christmas?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Mondays At GSC    carabao = water buffalo =  kalabaw   brought about by Radji's ym friend asking for a picture of a kalabaw in the fields w/c led to discussions about tamaraws, bulls, cows and kung gano kakunat ang karne ng kalabaw ----- I can see the ships on Manila Bay from here.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Books Up For Grabs   A Band of Angels - Julian F. Thompson - Young Adult Dead Giveaway (A Charles Paris Mystery) - Simon Brett - Mysery Discontinued - Julian F. Thompson - Young Adult False Colours - Georgette Heyer - Romance Jean and Johnny - Beverly Cleary - Young Adult Lady of Winter - Emma Merrit - Romance Lorna Doone - R.D. Blackmore - classic Phantoms - Dean Koontz - Suspense Regency Quartet - 4 Authors - Romance Strangers - Dean Koontz - Suspense Swan Song - Robert R. McCammon - Suspense Talk Before Sleep - Elizabeth Berg  Talking to Dragons - Patricia C. Wrede - Fantasy Tam Lin - Pamela Dean - Contemporary/Fantasy  The Lilac Bus - Maeve Binchy  Complete list of my books  urlLink here .  All others not in the list above are already spoken for.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Funny things   Approver1 can authorize 0 and Approver2 more than 0. What?! - from GSC E-mail  Shai: ComDom! Kae: ComDom? Ano ang ComDom? Shai: ComDom! *as in ano kaba? ComDom!* Kae: Ano? Dirty Old Man, Clean Old Man?  Later...after much laughter over somebody else's...  Kae: Ano ba kasi yung ComDom? Shai: ComDom! Di mo alam? Ano ka ba Kae?  Other officemates makes everything clear  Kae: Ah condom! E kasi ano ba naman yang sabi mo comdom! 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Update above
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Instituto Cervantes   I. GENERAL SPANISH LANGUAGE  	 A. Intensive  	(3 Wk Course, 12 Sessions) 	Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday & Friday 	9:00-11:30 am, 1:00-3:30 pm, 5:30-8:00 pm  	Nov. 26 - Dec. 17 	Jan. 07 - Jan. 24 	Jan. 28 - Feb. 14 	Feb. 18 - Mar. 14 	Mar. 18 - Apr. 04  	Course Fee: Php1,660 	Text Book: Php450  	 B. Regular  	(6 Wk Course, 12 Sessions) 	9:00-11:30 am, 1:00-3:30 pm, 5:30-8:00 pm  	Tuesdays & Thursdays 	Dec. 03 - Jan. 21 	Jan. 28 - Mar. 13 	Mar. 18 - Apr. 29  	Wednesday & Fridays 	Dec. 11 - Jan. 29 	Feb. 05 - Mar. 19 	Mar. 21 - May 02  	Course Fee: Php1,660 	Text Book: Php450  	 C. Extensive  	(10 Wk Course, 10 Sessions) 	Saturdays 	9:00-12:00 nn, 1:00-4:00 pm  	Nov. 16 - Feb. 01 	Feb. 08 - Apr. 12  	Course Fee: Php2,000 	Text Book: Php450  For more details, special course or a fax copy call 526-1482
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      So, anyway, my blog is up again.    Ang aking kapalaran sa Libre  Love: Umiiyak ka tuwing may naririnig na love song Money: Magbalik-loob sa pagkain ng gulay Career: Huwag mong gagawin kung pagod ka na  Duh?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       C3Con   Got there late.  As in after the program has finished!  Arrived at 6 pm, was able to get the one day ticket at  Comic Quest .  You know what happened?  I got looooost!  Where was my sense of direction?!    Saw Megatrade Hall 1. It was full of furniture so I though "If Mega 1 is herrre, then Mega 2 is waaay over therrr."  Right.  So I went. Like two times.  Like I made the 5th floor building A & B an excercise field when Mega 2 was right beside 1! *slaps forehead*  But Php150.00 is 150.   Sbarro  na yun noh! Spent two hours going round and round the place, checking and admiring the entries, looking at the coveted mangas that cost nearly Php1,000.00 for gosh sakes!  Chatted with some friends who were there, had the first ish of  urlLink  Culture Crash   signed by  Memer  and dedicated to  *urhm*   She might kill me.  Memer's secret priestess *grin* and I even conspired to take away  Tammy Tamaraw   Oh, well better luck next con.  Just the enjoyment on my friend's face convinced me that C3Con was, indeed, successful.  More power Culture Crash!  Oo na. Sayo na si  Jedd .  Pagtityagaan ko na lang si  Dante . Move over  Mina.   You understand don't you   dear?   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Christmas Gifts   I got  a) a pair of blue plastic chopsticks from my sister Kat b) a blue mini thermos from boss Marc c) a blue fan from My d) a checkered hanky from Shai e) a mini poster of a saying from Marge f) a silver paper box from January g) a figurine from Tina h) a yellow Winnie The Phoo mini pen from Alex i) a  boyfriend  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "...and when I hear you laugh, nothing else exists but that moment" -- Hard ------------------------------ "And in the end there is a larger barrier than there was before. The world is a cold place...and no matter how warm you try to be...it's always going to be a cold place" -- Hard ------------------------------ "It's so twisted to be scared of something you want so bad...like contact, like kindness, like love, like warmth, like affection, like attention."
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I shall never make a new friend in my life, though perhaps a few after I die."   - Oscar Wilde - 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "A man's very highest moment is, I have no doubt at all, when he kneels in the dust, and beats his breast, and tells all the sins of his life. "    - Oscar Wilde -  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "The only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad enough to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved... The ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn, like fabulous yellow Roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars."    - Jack Kerouac - 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Naked Truth walked down the street one day. People turned their eyes away.  Parable arrived, draped in decoration. People greeted Parable with celebration.  Naked Truth sat alone, sad and unattired, "Why are you so miserable?" Parable inquired.  Naked Truth replied, "I'm not welcome anymore. No one wants to see me. They chase me from their door."  "It is hard to look at Naked Truth," Parable explained. "Let me dress you up a bit. Your welcome will be gained."  Parable dressed Naked Truth in story's fine attire, with metaphor, poignant prose, and plots to inspire.  With laughter and tears and adventure to unveil, together they went forth to spin a tale.  People opened their doors and served them their best. Naked Truth dressed in story was a welcome guest.   - A Jewish Tale -   Taken from  urlLink Nuda Veritas 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Where now I have no one to blush with me; To cross their arms and hang their heads with mine; To mask their brows and hide their infamy; But I alone must sit and pine; Seasoning the earth with  showers of silver brine; Mingling my walks with tears; My grief with groans; Poor wasting monuments of lasting moans.   - William Shakespeare -  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I was thinking that I should delegate a separate page for my poems and for the poems that I like, but since I am lazy and my musings are in itself poetry then I'll just keep it here in this page.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This post is supposed to be about christmas parties, but I changed my mind. I don't know what this post is about.  Inday Badiday's  Dolphy interview is in the background here inside the rentals.  I called my Dad before going to mass this morning. Told him that I love him and miss him. I also asked him if he's really going home next year, but he said that he is still working on his papers and that it's hard to go out and come back in the US right now because of the  911  incident.  Kasama sya sa wish ko.  I guess hindi ko na ie-expect na matupad sya this March pero malay natin.  A woman answered the phone when I called his apartment.  I wonder who she is...  Pagdumating dito sa Daddy, date kami.  May mga itatanong at sasabihin ako sa kanya.  Ikukwento ko sa kanya ang taong unti-unting minamahal ko.   Miss na kita, Dad. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Medyo matagal na rin akong hindi nag a-update ng blog.  So eto:   My Big Fat Greek Wedding   urlLink    Ang pangarap ng family ni Tula ay makapagasawa sya ng isang fellow Greek at magkaron ng isang Greek family.  Tumatanda na daw sya at mukha nang matanda.   Shaolin Soccer   urlLink    Starring Stephen Chow, Zhao Wei (Vicky Zhao) etc. Comedy from start to finish at grabe may buhok o wala  ANG GANDA NI ZHAO WEI!!!!   Sa totoo lang tinatamad talaga akong magsulat ng movie review ngayon.  Wala ako sa mood.  Hindi ako ma-inspire na mag come up with a good, at least one paragraph review so I provided a link to the said movies.  Basahin nyo na lang yung review ng iba. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       If You Forget Me    by Pablo Neruda   I want you to know one thing.  You know how this is: if I look  at the crystal moon, at the red branch of the slow autumm at my window, if I touch near the fire the impalpable ash or the wrinkled body of the log, everything carries me to you, as if everything that exists, aromas, light, metals were little boats that sail toward those isles of yours that wait for me.  Well, now, if little by little you stop loving me  I shall stop loving you little by little.  If suddenly you forget me do not look for me, for I shall already have forgotten you.  If you think it long and mad, the wind of banners that passes through my life, and you decide  to leave me at the shore of the heart where I have roots, remember that on that day, at that hour, I shall lift my arms and my roots will set off to seek another land.  But if each day, each hour, you feel that you are destined for me with implacable sweetness, if each day a flower climbs up to your lips to seek me, ah my love, ah my own, in me nothing is extinguished or forgotten, my love feeds on your love, beloved, and as long as you live it will be in your arms without leaving mine.  *Thank you Luthien **A companion to  urlLink This Is How We End 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Only Time   Enya   Who can say where the road goes Where the day flows Only time...   And who can say if your love grows As your heart chose Only time...  Who can say why your heart sighs As your love flies Only time...  And who can say why your heart cries When your love lies Only time...  Who can say when the roads meet That they might be  In your heart...  And who can say when the day sleeps If the night keeps all your heart ...night keeps all your heart...  Who can say if your love grows As your heart chose Only time...  And who can say where the road goes Where the day flows Only time...  Who knows? Only time... Who knows? Only time... 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Across the Nightingale Floor   Bumili ako ng bagong libro na nakita ko nung Tuesday siguro mga 3 weeks ago sa National Bookstore.  Ito ay ang  "Across the Nightingale Floor."   Kung mukhang sobrang ina-advertise ko na sya e pasensya na kasi talagang maganda naman ang librong ito.  Nabili ko sya for Php539.00.  Sulit naman.  Hindi ko naiisip na pwede na pala akong makabili ng cd ni  Enya  or kumain sa  Cibo.   Ang story ay tunkol sa batang si  Takeo  na inampon ng isang lord ng Otori na si  Shigeru  pagkatapos na maligtas ng huli ang bata pagkatapos ma-massacre ng masamang si  Iida Sadamu  ng Tohan ang village nila.  Maganda syang talaga!  Descriptive yung novel in the sense na hindi sya na kaka-detract from the story.  Minsan kasi may mga novels na sasabihin mong "Pwede ba action na?"  Habang binabasa mo sya ay nai-imagine mong naga-unfold sa harap mo ang mga pangyayari.  May mga magagandang lines din na makukuha sa librong ito.   "I've been overtaken by disaster," she thought at one moment, and at the next, "How can this feeling be a disaster?"    "She was what I desired; she would save me from the feeling that I was a living ghost."   And more.  For reviews, message board on the book and other info, visit  urlLink The Otori 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       One Afternoon   It's moments like these that I am glad to be alive.  I am watching the sun set.  Not as orangey like yesterday.  It just passed by 1/8s of the building ahead.  Tapos parang cloak nya yung clouds.  Ganda talaga.  You can't help but notice lalo na at yung rays ng sun e directly tumatama sa mata mo.  Parang magandang babae na malayo ang abot ng ganda.  Naks.  Wala pa akong nakikita o nakikilalang ganun.  Sabagay kasi nga naman siguro babae ako at iba ang level of appreciation kesa sa lalaki.  Ang ganda talaga.  Have you ever felt so happy na iisipin mo pwede ka nang mamatay?    Ako hindi pa naman.  Aaah masyado na akong nagagalak sa nakikita ko.  Hmm...may naisip ako.  Sana isang araw may tao na ganito rin ang turing saken.  Para syang nanunood ng sunset sa hapon ng 4:59pm and feeling nya at that moment e kuntento na sya sa lahat.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Sentimental Quote of the Day    "It's so twisted to be scared of something you want so bad...like contact, like kindness, like love, like warmth, like affection, like attention." -- Hard     Minsan kapag may nakita akong magandang scene, be it tree, sky or sunset I'd wish na meron akong camera handy to take shots or I'd wish na magaling akong photographer para makuhanan ko ng mabuti ang gusto ko gaya kanina.  Portion ng sky na pure solid blue and grand sunset.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Site of the Day    urlLink Sexy Losers   urlLink A Heart Made Of Glass 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Secret Garden   Bruce Springsteen   This makes me think of full moons, of soft breezes, of dry leaves crunching beneath one's feet, of trees and of smiles.   "I was just about to tell him that I love him! I do! I love him! I love him! I love him!  I love him for the man he wants to be and I love me for the man he almost is!  I love him! I love him!"   She'll let you in her house If you come knockin' late at night She'll let you in her mouth If the words you say are right If you pay the price She'll let you deep inside But there's a secret garden she hides She'll let you in her car To go drivin' round She'll let you into the parts of herself That'll bring you down She'll let you in her heart If you've got a hammer and a vise But into her secret garden, don't think twice  You've gone a million miles How far'd you get? To that place where you can't remember And you can't forget  She'll lead you down a path There'll be tenderness in the air She'll let you come just far enough So you know she's really there She'll look at you and smile And her eyes will say She's got a secret garden Where everything you want Where everything you need Will always stay A million miles away 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Culture Crash   Not till after CCCom came out with their 9th ish did I become a fan.  When the first issue came out I wasn't that interested yet.  I was more into anime kasi and my money went to other things during my school days.    So what is this about?  This is a thank you.  Your work is wonderful at kuha nyo ang humor ng Pinoy.  You certainly got mine.  I love the stories.  Although I draw, I am not much into criticizing the "technical" details of other's works.  Kinakain ko yung story.  My favorite is Pasig, but I like all stories.  Nakahiram ako ng backissues from a friend of mine.  Certainly if I can find some issues to buy for myself e go na.  Advantage sa situation ko ngayon e hindi ko napagdadaanan ang frustration ng mga fans habang naga-antay ng susunod na issue.  Well, not until I read the 9th.  Then I'd scream for more.  And wait.  I hope not to wait too long.  As with an artist friend, kung kaya ko lang mag sponsor I'd sponsor CCCom.  Pasensya na ito lang muna ang mabibigay ko.  My dreams for you guys and buying the issues.  Ofcourse I'll send this through e-mail once I confirm what the addy is.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Can't Buy Me Love    urlLink     Click on the image   Isa sa dalawang tapes na ni-rent ko this weekend.  Ang  Can't Buy Me Love  ay isang 80s movie tungkol kay  Ronald(Patrick Dempsey) , isang lawn mower man at tagahanga ni  Cindy Mancini(Amanda Peterson , head cheerleader ng school.  Sa kagustuhan mapalapit ni Ronald kay Cindy, e imbis na bilhin ang kanyang matagal na pinagipunang telescope e binayaran nya yung bagong biling suede outfit ni Cindy.  Ang nasabing outfit ay kapareho ng namantsahang damit ng mommy ni Cindy.  Ginamit nya ito ng walang paalam.  Sa madaling salita binayaran ni Ronald si Cindy para maging girlfriend nya ng isang buwan.  Kaya ko nirenta ang movie na ito dahil hindi ko sya natapos nung high school ako.  Naalala ko na pinapanood ko ito isang gabi sa isang local channel nang biglang lumabas si mommy sa kwarto, nagalit at pinapatay ang tv.  Ang tv ang dahilan kaya hindi na nadagdagan pa ang taas ko.  At long last, natapos ko rin ang nakakatuwang movie na ito.  Ang gwapo ni  Patrick Dempsey  nung binata sya!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       UK Film Festival      Courtesy of CinemaLibre   British Cinema once more takes the limelight when select feature films from the UK are shown at the Shangri-La PLaza Mall from 29 January to 4 February 2003.   Bend it like Beckham  tops this year's line-up of cinematic gems. The fil is about two 18-year old girls playing football. Both girls dream of playing professionally, and are on their way with help from their coach, Joe when they fall in-love with him  Other film titles scheduled for the film festival are  Born Romantic  and  Divorcing Jack . Alongside this, in collaboration with BBC, a selection of TV materials to include  Absolutely Fabulous  (comedy),  Pride and Prejudice  (classical drama) and  Wallace and Grommit  (animation) will also be shown at the British Council Information Centre.  Wallace, the eccentric and naive, cheese-loving inventor and his faithful dog, Grommit were introduced to the world when the film A Grand Day Out was nominated for an Academy Award in 1989. The entertaining comic-book story revolves around the adventures of the somewhat inept Wallace and the real brains behind the partnership, Grommit.   UK Film festival schedule of screenings   Cinema 1, Shangri-la Plaza Mall    Jan. 29   8 pm  - Bend It Like Beckham   Jan. 30   1 pm  - Divorcing Jack  5 pm  - Born Romantic  8 pm  - Love and Death on Long Island   Jan. 31   1 pm  - Love and Death on Long Island  5 pm  - Divorcing Jack  8 pm  - Last Resort   Feb. 01   1 pm  - Divorcing Jack  5 pm  - Bend It Like Beckham  8 pm  - Born Romantic   Feb. 02   1 pm  - Bend It Like Beckham  5 pm  - Born Romantic  8 pm  - Last Resort   Feb. 03   1 pm  - Love and Death on Long Island  5 pm  - Last Resort  8 pm  - Born Romantic   Feb. 04   1 pm  - Last Resort  5 pm  - Divorcing Jack  8 pm  - Bend It Like Beckham   Information Centre, British Council    Feb. 05   2 pm - 3:30 pm  - Walking with Dinosaurs Ep. 1 & 2  4 pm - 4:30 pm  - Wallace & Grommit:  The Grand Day Out  4:30 pm - 5:00 pm  - Wallace & Grommit: The Wrong Trousers  5:00 pm - 5:45 pm  - Wallace & Grommit: Close Shave   Feb. 06   2 pm - 3 pm  - Absolutely Fabulous Ep. 1 & 2  3 pm - 4 pm  - Fawlty Towers: Basil the Rat  4:30 pm - 5:30 pm  - Pride and Prejudice Ep. 1   Feb. 07   2 pm - 3:30 pm  - Walking with Dinosaurs Ep. 1 & 2  3:30 pm - 4:30 pm  - Absolutely Fabulous Ep. 1 & 2  4:30 pm - 5:30 pm  - Pride and Prejudice Ep. 3   Feb. 08   2 pm - 3 pm  - Pride and Prejudice Ep. 5  3 pm - 4 pm  - Pride and Prejudice Ep. 6  4 pm - 4:30 pm  - Wallace & Grommit:  The Grand Day Out  4:30 pm - 5:00 pm  - Wallace & Grommit: The Wrong Trousers  5:00 pm - 5:45 pm  - Wallace & Grommit: Close Shave  For inquiries, pls. call 914-1011 to 14 or email britishcouncil@britishcouncil.org.ph. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Afternoon Walk Back To Work   Sounds, faces.  I was aware of them as I was walking on the infernal cobbled steps back to work.  Snatches of conversation, the beep-beep of vehicles along Gil Puyat, the sway of branches ahead, the multitude of colors.  I feel the muscles of my face lifting.  At that moment I was happy.  Lost.  Invisible.  Content to be part of a streaming body going god knows where.   "Quite early on I discovered the overlooked space open to those of us with a silent life. I didn't argue with the policeman who said I couldn't cycle over a certain bridge or through a specific gate in the fort - I just stood there, still, until I was invisible, and then I went through.  Like a cricket.  Like a hidden cup of water.  You understand?  That is what my brother's public battles taught me." - Kip,  The English Patient  -  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Things, Events, Announcements    Chinese New Year  - February 1, 2003 Saturday  The  Arroceros Park  is now open to the public!  Free entrance on Fridays to Sundays.  Thanks to  Winner Foundation  and the volunteers.     Hero  starts regular showing on February 2, Sunday.  A Chinese epic starring  Jet Li  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was selecting items to delete in My Documents when I found this:   Marge says:  - basta dont give too much - magtira ka for urself.... - but be honest always - and learn to be sensitive of his feelings   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - yun din ang sabi ni mami. - sabi nya >> josef wag ko daw sya masyadong tatablahin - kahit pabiro lang   Marge says:  - baka kc sobra syang sensitive   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - ayaw nya yung maglalambing sya na mahal nya ako tapos magjo-joke ako na hindi - or na hindi sya importante   Marge says:  - san sya sa novaliches? - syempre no - kailangan mo ng maging sensitive sa mga sasabihin niya - pero i-explain mo din sa kanya na nag-aadjust ka pa rin sa situation niyo - at sa kanya syempre - ano nga pala sabi ni shai?   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - ah wala naman. nagtatanong tanong. may nagbago daw ba sa mukha ko - ganun - tapos nape-pressure na tuloy daw sya   Marge says:  - bakit naman sya mapi-pressure? - dadating din kamo yung para sa kanya - ako masaya para sa'yo   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  eh kasi pag may nagtanong saken or nagbiro eventually babaling yung tanong sa kanya   Marge says:  tuwing kelang kayo nagkikita?   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - minsan lang. okay lang naman. kita kami this sa jan 11 - palabas na ba nun ang two towers?   Marge says:  yes   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  araw-araw usap...iniisip ko nga kung magkakasawaan sa araw-araw na usap sa telepono   Marge says:  - i thing jan 4 ang showing nun eh - hello??? - kami kaya ni ramil araw araw nagkikita at nag-uusap   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  mula nung october ata kami nag usap sa phone tas naging everyda nung november   Marge says:  - ok lang yun ano - at least you'll get to know each other well - dun naman nag-start ang foundation ng isang relationship eh   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - tinaong nya dati kung ok lang araw-araw. eh test nya pala yun para malaman kung eventually magsasawa kami at magfe-fade yung pagka gusto nya - kasi sabi nya inaasahan daw nyang mawawala ang "infatuation" after a month or so...eheheh hindi nangyari   Marge says:  - kaya 2loy 2loy pa rin kayo - basta,take one step at a time - kilalanin niyo muna ang isa't-isa - be happy in doing things 2gether - at saka a lot of patience and understanding!!!!    Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - oo. di naman kami nagmamadali. actually dapat di pa kami magiging kami! ano ba yan dapat this year pa. hmmm...kasi naman hehehehe oh well sabi nga nya e hindi kami mage-enjoy ngayon kung saka pa naging kami   Marge says:  nangyari yun kasi yun ang dapat mangyari   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - oo nga. di pa namin masyadong nakikita ang panget na ugali namin. di pa kami nagaaway. biro nga kami gawa kami ng "mock fight" gusto daw nya malaman kung pano namin iso-solve yung pagaawayan namin - e sabi ko wala namang motivation   Marge says:  correct   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  ah buti kausap kita. kasi nalalaman ko tuloy ang fear ko. kasi tinatanong nya ako ng mga fears ko e. fear ko pala na pano na kung may ugali akong ayaw nya...  mahal parin kaya nya ako?   Marge says:  - wag kayong gawa ng away - kusang darating yan - ilang araw pa lang kayo no - pag mahal mo mamahalin mo lahat ng pangit na ugali and eventually,nari-realize mo na dapat mong i-change yung mga bagay na makakasira sa relationship niyo - ndi madali kae - as in - sobrang struggles - madami kang dapat na kaining pride - para sa ikakabuti ng relationship niyo - at mas magiging madali kasi ginagawa mo yun para sa taong mahal mo,di ba? - basta,go with the flow ka - enjoy mo lang yung moments niyo 2gether    Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - okay. basta may usapan naman kami. kung may ayaw sya sasabihin nya tas ganun din ako - tapos ayaw nya yung magpapahula pa ako hehe   Marge says:  minsan,kailangan mo ding manahimik muna   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - e hindi naman ako nagpapahula - ah ganun ba? - sige nga explain mo saken - kung kelan minsan bakit ganun?   Marge says:  - at kailangan mo ring unawin minsan na kailangan niya munang manahimik - para makapag-isip - basta ba sasabihin mo rin sa kanya kung anuman yun - minsan kasi pag galit ka,nakakapagsabi ka ng masasakit na salita na later on,mari-realize mo na sana di mo na lang muna cnabi - baka mas masaktan mo pa sya - at magsisi ka pa   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  ah oo napagusapan nga pala namin na kapag ganun sasabihin muna namin na wag muna usap   Marge says:  - pero minsan kailangan masaktan ka rin para matuto ka  - kae - alis na ako - usap na lang ulit tau mya   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  - ok - sige - tenks   Marge says:  - at ipakilala mo sa amin yang bf mo ha? - good luck   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  obkors   Marge says:  - im happy for you!!! - bye   Kae - HAPPY NEW YEAR! says:  bye 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       BtVS Season 3    BUFFY:  I guess. But what if I can't? I've seen too much. I know what goes bump in the night. Not being able to fight it... What if I just hide under my bed, all scared and helpless? Or what if I just become pathetic? Hanging out at the old Slayer's home, talking people's ears off about my glory days, showing them Mr. Pointy, the stake I had bronzed.     ANGEL:   Buffy, you could never be helpless or boring, not even if you tried.    BUFFY:  Don't be so sure. Before I was the Slayer, I was... Well, I, I don't wanna say shallow, but... Let's say a certain person, who will remain nameless, we'll just call her Spordelia, looked like a classical philosopher next to me. Angel, if I'm not the Slayer, what do I do? What do I have to offer? Why would you like me?     ANGEL:   (quietly) I saw you before you became the Slayer.    BUFFY:  (confused) What?     ANGEL:   I watched you, and I saw you called. It was a bright afternoon out in front of your school. You walked down the steps... and... and I loved you.    BUFFY:  Why?     ANGEL:   'Cause I could see your heart. You held it before you for everyone to see. And I worried that it would be bruised or torn. And more than anything in my life I wanted to keep it safe... to warm it with my own.    BUFFY:  That's beautiful. Or taken literally, incredibly gross.     ANGEL:   (grimacing) I was just thinking that, too.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       MSN Chat of the Day   Ako si Kae says:  Anong english ng "alanganin?"  Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   hmmm   Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   use in a sentence please   Ako si Kae says:  Alanganin kung kumain ako ng lunch before 12 kasi nag breakfast ako ng 10  Ako si Kae says:  pwede ko namang gamitin yung "I am still full" kaya lang gusto ko pahirapan ang sarili ko  Ako si Kae says:  hehehehe  Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   anak ng teteng!   Ako si Kae says:  gandang palaisipan di ba?  Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   hesitant   Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   not sure   Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   third sex   Ako si Kae says:  hahahahahaha  Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   hindi ko alam   Ako si Kae says:  ok sige salamat. napatawa mo ako  Ako si Kae says:  next victim.....  Magpakabait ka or I will rate you with a 1! Hahahaha! says:   hehehe   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Heaven    urlLink   The movie starts with a helicopter flight simulation and Filippo asking, "How can I fly?"  Overwhelming emotion flowed out of the movie.  It was intense in its silent moments.  They spoke not so much in words, but in gestures, eyes, heart.  "Heaven" stars Cate Blanchet and Giovanni Ribisi.  The two was last seen together in "The Gift" with Katie Holmes and Keanu Reeves.  For more information and reviews about the movie, click the image above.   A Silly Poem   Something wild, something gay whatever happened to me today? On the road, sitting here it's been a while since I had a beer. Dark outside, blinking lights, my butt is aching, wanna say goodnight. Where are you? Come to me. Go away! Let me be. Silly me...  *Found my poem still posted in the Pacific forum.  Good thing! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Yuu Watase's "Epotoransu! Mai"   Epotoransu! Mai is one of  Yuu Watase's  (creator of Fushigi Yugi/Ayashi no Ceres) earlier works.  It is about  Mai , a high schooler, who received an electronic notebook on her 16th birthday.  When Mai accidentally typed "Epotoransu",  Takuma  appeared before her as the being inside the notebook.  He then helps Mai win the regard of her school mate,  Nimura .  I was introduced to  Fushigi Yugi  then  Ayashi no Ceres  before this and it came as a breather from the first.  Whereas FY and AC have dark and heavy themes, EM is lighthearted and funny, less clingy.  The manga was completed after two volumes.  The story could've been explored more like maybe Takuma's quest to become a real human being!  Takuma over Nimura anytime!  Mai is so dense to not notice that when Takuma said "I love you" it was meant even though he took it back because he was just "joking."    Sigh.  More!  More Epotoransu! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        A Look At a Day in GSC   Yehey, may sweldo na!  Huhu madami akong babayarin this payday.  Dalawang plans and isang cable.  Dad, brightened my day with his e-mail even though it's about the remittance that he sent.  Not that the remittance is not important.  It's just that he does not send personal mails as often as I like.  He's mostly busy with work I guess.  Nakahiligan ng mga officemates kong babae ngayon ang mga articles sa  urlLink Peyups   Ano daw ang  Italian Chandelier ?  Hmmm...dapat nagre-research ako kung pano ginagawa yung teddy bear e!  Ayun!  Imagine this.  Girl on bed facing roof.  The guy is the bed and the girl lifts herself up and down.  Kung ayaw nyo mag-imagine, click this  urlLink link .  I know, I know.  This is not teddy bear manual.  Whew.  Malamig kasi dito sa office.  Kauulan lang, see?  5:20 PM.  Serious na ulit.   GSC Quotes of the Day   "Akin okay lang kahit bastos"  - Tina to Jaz regarding e-mail   "Bakit bigla akong nawala, Jaz?!  Wala akong vacuum cleaner!"  - Shai to Jaz regarding e-mail   "Bakit 'Getting up immediately' requires 36 calories?"  - January referring to an e-mail forwarded to her about the number of calories burned under header POST ORGASM   "Mahirap tumayo afterwards kasi nga pagod ka nun e"  - My reply to "Getting up immediately"   "WHAAT?!"  - LOL.  Funny!  Kasi naman pumasok si Alex sa kwarto at sabi nya "Magre-resign na pala si Jing!"  Reaction namin "Uh...ano?"  So sabi namin labas sya ulit para masaya at saktong okay ang reaction namin isa balita nya.  Labas naman daw sya.   Hehe sabi nya corny na daw the second time around pero labas pa rin sya.  "Magre-resign na pala si Jing!"  Ang cute!  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Weekend That Was    Saturday  - LOTR with Josef.  His first visit home.  Introduced him to Audrey.  He said it was kind of weird.      Comments from my sister,  Arianne :  "Hindi sya nag po-po and opo," "May pagka maarte sya," "Mga Atenista talaga magkakamukha.  Puro kalbo!"    Sunday  - Watched  Ring 1  on vcd. Downloaded  Windows Media Player V9  so that I can install  Kazaa .  Both dls successful so I was able to download "Anywhere Is" by  Enya .   How To Transfer Files From One HDD to Another   You can have one  primary  HDD and one  slave  disk.  Flooble is acting up.  What is the model of your HDD?  The  jumper settings  will depend on your HDD. Usually there's a diagram of how the jumper settings should be set if you are going to configure it as primary or slave. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        HOW TO ADD A DEDICATED PRINTER   OS: Windows 2000 Printer is dedicated to one PC (A).  Two other PCs (B & C) will share access.  Share printer.  Allow printer management to profile Everyone in properties of printer  PC using network domain: - Add printer using "Network printer." - Input share name of printer in this format: \\ip adress\share name - Test print  PC using local domain: - Add log-in username as new user in PC (A) - Allow printer management to new profile except if Everyone is allowed - Run PC name of owner using format: \\pc name - A window for said PC will appear.  Double click on the shared printer. - Test print   GSC Quotable Quotes   San ka tumatawag?  Gusto ba namin yan?  - Tina on Marlowe's order at Yellow Cab   Isa pa non.  14 inches lang.  - Marlowe ordering at Yellow Cab   January 10, 2003 Friday.  Sir Harry Soriano's birthday.   HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SIR!  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Game of Go   For the past two days, I have been toggling between work and reading the how-tos of  Go .  No, no, not my supplier of  literotextica .  Oops.  I am talking about the Japanese game of strategy.  This is probably the game that I see sometimes being played by men and boys using  tansan , other bottle caps of the same color and plywood with intersecting lines.  Then again, maybe not.  Anyway,  urlLink Toriyama World  hosts a manga scanlation of  Hikaru no Go  which is about a boy and the game of Go.  They also have a link explaining the concept of the game and from there I was able to get to another site dedicated to the game.  It is basically about defining territory and capturing prisoners.  For more information go to  urlLink http://www.kiseido.com/    Monks who have a talent for it play go with women and become their lovers - Yamaoka Genrin, Edo-period essayist -  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We are going to see each other on the 11th.    One of the things I miss is when he tossles my hair and I complain that it's getting messed up.  I eventually told him that I really don't mind.  Actually, I love it but didn't want to get comfortable with the gesture because there was no "us" and it would not do to want and miss something like that.  What would it be like to finally see him again?  What would it be like for him?  Dad sent another batch of computer books.  It would probably take me forever to read all of them.  Most of the books are UNIX.  Will come up with a list of said books and probably put them up for sale either on  urlLink Bidshot  or the book sale happening on the 18th.  For more details visit  urlLink http://mparaz.com/booksale.html   We've got new VHS tapes like "The Wedding Planner", "Girl Interrrupted", "Shakespeare In Love."  We also have three DVDs that will probably be screened by someone else because we do not have a DVD player.  January 07, 2003 Tuesday.  January's birthday.   HAPPY BIRTHDAY WALENG!  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bagong Taon, New Year   Ngayon ay January 2, 2003.  Masanay na tayong magsulat ng  "3"  sa pagkatapos ng "200".  The usual ang celebration sa aming pamilya ng New Year.  Handa, kain, patugtog ng malakas, paingay ng torotot, hugas ng pinggan and finally tulog.  Nagluto si Mommy ng ham, lumpiang shanghai.  Gumawa rin sya ng fruit salad.  Bumili kami ng Black Forest sa Red Ribbon, umorder ng imbotido kay Sis. Elvie, bumili ng mabilog na prutas.  Nagluto ako ng pasta.  Sinindihan namin ng 11:30 pm ang colored candles na regalo ni Shai para sa New Year.  Naglagay kami ng coins sa bulsa ng aming damit para i-jinggle sa bagong taon.  Nagsabit si Mommy ng grapes sa may bintana.  Okay naman.  Ika nga ni  urlLink Van  "Same old, same old."  Resolutions?  Wala ako nun.  Sigurado naman kasing makakalimutan ko.  Gagawin ko na lang.  Gaya ng pag plantsa ng damit para sa office in advance.  Promise ko sa  kanya  ang two weeks worth of clothes kung tatapusin nya ang tatlong kwarto na kailangan nyang linisin.  Nagawa ko na ang kalahati kahapon.  Galing di ba?  Binibenta ko nga pala ang  Ericsson A2618s  ko.  Kung may interesado dyan just leave a message.  Ah, oo.  Isa ito sa mga goals ko.  Ang maibenta ang cellphone at bumili ng bago.  Ang susunod ay tawagan ang  Instituto Cervantes  sa Biyernes.  Ah, bukas na nga pala yun.  Siguro sa Monday na lang.  Tutal yun naman ang pasukan ng karamihan sa paaralan.  Itatanong ko lang kung naka-quota ba sila ng mga interesadong mag enroll sa Saturday class nitong darating ng Pebrero.  Ah Pebrero!    Valentine's Day!    Ehehe.  Marami akong gusto.  Tignan nyo na lang yung  urlLink 1,000 Wishes  link.  Ika nga ni  urlLink Jovan , ano kaya ang pangakong taglay ng 2003 para sa akin?   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Sigh. I am tired. I want to go home. I feel like the only person I talked to the whole afternoon was Alicia S from Singapore. First, her problem was a batch number that has an error. Then the next problem was she did not know how to cancel the check in the system Then we encountered an error in deleting her voucher. It all came down to the fact that the account that she used for the voucher is already closed *dammit* Pressure here because she wants to finish the closing activities tonight. And ofcourse here we have to exhaust all means of troubleshooting first blah blah blah before talking to the big guns upstairs. Natarayan pa ako. Buti na lang nag reply yung naka copy furnish ng mail and took the matter off my hands. *whew* Yun lang.  Away. Away.. Away... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Relationship Blues   A break in routine brings a sense of foreboding 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Birthdays of February   Christopher Go Jovit Val Cojuangco Shinette Pagba Mavis Mallari Jose Marcelino Vega Vergel Clavecillas John Emmanuel Nervez Jocelyn M. Nervez   HAPPY BIRTHDAY!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Movie Review: HERO   Napanood ko ang  Hero (Ying Xiong)  last week ng Sunday kasama ang aking kapatid na lalake.  Ang direktor ng pelikulang ito ay si  Zhang Yimou  na sya ring nag direct ng  Not One Less  and  The Road Home .  Kung nanonood ka ng  AXN , you can't miss the last two that I mentioned.    Anyway, panoorin nyo ang Hero.  Syempre late na itong review ko ano?  Kasi naman natabunan na sya sa takilya ng mga bagong movies.  Kung maipapalabas man ito ulit dito sa Pinas ay malamang sa  Art Film  sa Greenbelt o kaya sa Chinese film fest sa Shang, Greenbelt, UP, CCP at iba pa.  Magaling sa cinematography ang director na ito.  Ah oo nga pala.  Bago sya naupo sa director's chair ay cinematographer talaga sya.  Ang gumaganap na hero dito ay si  Nameless (Jet Li) .  Ang storya ay set sa China before the unification meaning bago pa magkaron ng iisang emperor na namumuno sa bansa.  Ang ruler ng  Qin  ang pinakamakapangyarihan sa mga naglalabanang kingdoms sa China kaya may mga gustong pumatay sa kanya.    Sinasabi ko na na ito ay  SPOILER .  Kaya kung kayo ay may balak panoorin ito at sensitive sa spoilers ay lumipat na lang sa ibang site.  Tatlong assassins ang nasa top list ng Qin.  Si  Sky (Donnie Yen) ,  Broken Sword (Tony Leung)  &  Flying Snow (Maggie Cheung) .  Para lumapit ng 20 paces ang layo from the ruler of Qin, kailangang matalo si Sky.  10 paces pag matalo si Flying Snow and 5 paces (forgive me kung medyo off and paces ko)  kapag natalo si Broken Sword.  Lahat ang ito ay na-achieve ni Nameless dahil sa pagpapanggap.  Tinatamad na akong magkwento.  Bakit ko sya nagustuhan?  Bukod sa kwento ay dahil nga sa cinematography.  Let me enumerate ang mga natatandaan kong scenes:  1.  Passing shadow ng clouds on the gray earth with thundering horses' hoofs for background.  It seemed to me that the clouds themselves are the ones charging. 2.  Synchronized spears of Qin's archers. 3.  Fight scene of Nameless and Sky while the old man plays koto in the background. 4.  Fight scene of  Moon  (Zhang Ziyi as Broken Sword's pupil) and Flying Snow.  Vivid autumn colors of yellow, orange then finally blood red.  I will not even try to compare this movie to  Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon .  They are both wonderful films.  For me there is no comparison or maybe I just love them both.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, yes, I know.  My blog is all film schedules and nothing about me or someone else.  Ah, well.  I hope something big like me going away happens this year.  It's a bit like being a coward, I know.  Anyway, my goals for until March hopefully will reap desirable results. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       PELIKULA at LIPUNAN Film Festival 2003 Screening Schedules    SM Megamall Mandaluyong City FEBRUARY 17, 2003 Monday   AM  9:00  Anak by Rory Quintos (Screening for Makati Public Schools)  11:30 Anak by Rory Quintos (Screening for Makati Public Schools)   PM  2:00 Anak by Rory Quintos (Screening for Makati Public Schools)  4:30 Retrospective Pagdating sa Dulo by Ishmael Bernal  6:30 United Kingdom Titus (Titus Andronicus) by Julie Taymor  9:30 Japan Hush by Ryosuke Hashiguchi    FEBRUARY 18, 2003 Tuesday  AM 9:00 Ganito Kami Noon, Paano Kayo Ngayon by Eddie Romero (Screening for Makati Public Schools)  11:30 Ganito Kami Noon, Paano Kayo Ngayon by Eddie Romero (Screening for Makati Public Schools)   PM  2:00 Ganito Kami Noon, Paano Kayo Ngayon by Eddie Romero (Screening for Makati Public Schools)  4:30 Retrospective Waywaya by Lamberto Avellana  6:30 USA The Hours by Stephen Daldry  9:30 USA Punch-Drunk Love  by Paul Thomas Anderson 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY TO ALL!   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember the nursery songs your parents used to sing to you or the ones that you use to play with your friends?   On Top of Spaghetti   On top of spaghetti,  All covered with cheese, I lost my poor meatball,  When somebody sneezed. It rolled off the table, And on to the floor, And then my poor meatball, Rolled out of the door. It rolled in the garden, And under a bush, And then my poor meatball, Was nothing but mush. The mush was as tasty As tasty could be, And then the next summer,  It grew into a tree. The tree was all covered, All covered with moss, And on it grew meatballs, And tomato sauce. So if you eat spaghetti, All covered with cheese, Hold on to your meatball, Whenever you sneeze. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       EIGA SAI: 2003 Kurosawa Kiyoshi Filmfest     February      SHANGRI-LA   26 7:00 pm - Charisma  27 3:00 pm - Cure 5:30 pm - License to Live 8:00 pm - Suit Yourself or Shoot Yourself  28 3:00 pm - Charisma 5:30 pm - Serpent Path 8:00 pm - Barren Illusion    March    1 3:00 pm - Suit Yourself or Shoot Yourself 5:30 pm - Cure 8:00 pm - Serpent Path  2 3:00 pm - Barren Illusion 5:30 pm - Charisma 8:00 pm - License to Live  3 3:00 pm - License to Live 5:30 pm - Barren Illusion 8:00 pm - Cure  4 3:00 pm - Serpent Path 5:30 pm - Suit Yourself or Shoot Yourself 8:00 pm - Charisma    CULTURAL CENTER OF THE PHILIPPINES    11 4:00 pm - Suit Yourself or Shoot Yourself 6:30 pm - Cure  12 4:00 pm - Serpent Path 6:30 pm - Charisma  13 4:00 pm - Barren Illusion 6:30 pm - License to Live   14 4:00 pm - Cure 6:30 pm - Serpent Path    UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES    17 3:00 pm - Serpent Path 6:00 pm - Barren Illusion  18 3:00 pm - Suit Yourself or Shoot Yourself 6:00 pm - License to Live  19 3:00 pm - Cure 6:00 pm - Charisma   20 3:00 pm - License to Live 6:00 pm - Barren Illusion  21 3:00 pm - Charisma 6:00 pm - Cure 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Aviary, CDs, Fountain   For those of you who have heard of an  aviary  in Makati, particularly in Greenbelt, and are meaning to go there I am sorry to tell you that it does not exist anymore.  The birds were donated to the Parks and Wildlife organization in Quezon City.  For those looking for Chinese or Japanese cds and tapes, go to  Mei-Ah  located along Ongpin in Binondo.  Heaven.  And speaking of  Binondo , you should check out the great  fountain  in front of the  Manila Post Office .  Hehehe.  Best if you visit at night.  The most wonderful display is there. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       eKsperim[E]nto Film & Video Festival    For more information please visit  urlLink http://www.geocities.com/eksperiment3/main.html   Sorry for not promoting and giving more information here.  It's just that I am late updating and it's 15 minutes before I drag my stuff out of the office and head for home so I'm just not up to making time.  Film enthusiasts, though, should check it out.  This is also an alternative for the  financially challenged movie addict individual  because some of the featured films are for  free  or cost  less  than 50 pesos 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       IT    Stephen King   The real terror struck him then and there was nothing at all supernatural about it.  It was only a realization of how easy it was to trash your life.  That was what was so scary.  - Richi Tozier -    I don't understand this all.  I don't understand any of this.  Why does a story have to be socio-anything?  Politics...culture...history...aren't those natural ingredients in any story, if it's told well?  I mean...can't you guys just let a story be a story?  - Bill Denbrough -    ...on those days Ben would sometimes look sideways at Beverly, stealing her face, and his heart would both hurt desperately and somehow grow brighter at the same time  If a hole leading into the underworld had opened before him at that very moment,  Ben would have dropped into it without a sound...or perhaps with the faintest murmur of gratitude. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Wedding Letter   Congratulations to one of the best days of your lives.  I am happy to have met and known two imperfect persons who came together and became the perfect couple for each other.  Syempre alam nyo na siguro na there should be compromise =).  It's interesting to note how this sounds good coming from me, but a bad idea when the person giving the advice is in that situation.  Ito ay sinulat ko sa fifth floor ng Edsa Shang habang umiinom ng mango-kiwi shake from Big Chill (order kayo) kasi bawal uminom sa mrt.  Nabanggit ko kay mommy na bukod sa ikakasal kayo ay meron pang dalawa na officemate ko rin: si Roger at Arnie.  Naisip ko tuloy na baka isipin ni mommy na gusto ko na rin lumagay sa tahimik.  Ayoko pang mamatay.  Did they not say that marriage is suicide? 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       WHY DO THINGS HAVE TO BE THE WAY THEY ARE?  'Well  YOU DON'T KNOW, DO YOU?  'Not exactly. The whole thing is meant to be a mystery, see?'  The stranger stared at the holy man for some time, causing the man to feel that his head had become transparent.  THEN I WILL ASK YOU A SIMPLER QUESTION. HOW DO HUMANS FORGET?  'Forget what?'  FORGET ANYTHING. EVERYTHING.  'It . . . er . . . it happens automatically.' The prospective acolytes had turned the bend on the mountain path. The holy man hastily picked up his begging bowl.  'Let's say this bowl is your memory,' he said, waving it vaguely. 'It can only hold so much, see? New things come in, so old things must overflow  NO. I REMEMBER EVERYTHING. EVERYTHING. DOORKNOBS. THE PLAY OF SUNLIGHT ON HAIR. THE SOUND OF LAUGHTER. FOOTSTEPS. EVERY LITTLE DETAIL. AS IF IT HAPPENED ONLY YESTERDAY. AS IF IT HAPPENED ONLY TOMMOROW. EVERYTHING. DO YOU UNDERSTAND?  The holy man scratched his gleaming bald head.  'Traditionally,' he said, 'the ways of forgetting include joining the Klatchian Foreign Legion, drinking the waters of some magical river, no one knows where it is, and imbibing vast amounts of alcohol.'  AH, YES.  'But alcohol debilitates the body and is a poison to the soul.'  SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.   - Soul Music, Terry Pratchett -  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Francophonie Film Festival at the Equitable PCI Bank, Tower II   To highlight  La Journée Internationale de la Francophonie  (International Day of the Francophonie), six countries who are members of the Francophonie are sponsoring Le festival des films Francophones (Francophonie Film Festival) from March 17 to 22, 2003 at the Antonio Molina Hall, Equitable PCI Bank, Tower II, Makati Avenue cor H.V. dela Costa St. Makati City.  Admission is free  on a first-come-first-seated basis.  In collaboration with the Manila Chamber Orchestra (MCO) Foundation, Equitable PCI Bank, and Alliance Francaise de Manille, the Embassies of Belgium, Cambodia, Canada, France, Lebanon and Switzerland will be screening award-winning films from their respective countries.   Belgium  will screen on  March 17  at 6:30PM the film  "Toto le héros"  by Jaco van Dormael. The film tells the story of Thomas and Alfred who were born around the same time. A fire in the nursery had the nurses scrambling to save the newborns. Because he felt that he deserved Alfred's good fortune at being born into a wealthy family, Thomas conceives the idea that he and Alfred were switched at birth, and he can't help seeing that his unhappiness should be Alfred's, from the loss of his sister to his inability to have a relationship with Evelyne. So, as his life is ending, he formulates a plan of revenge against his bitter enemy, his lifetime adversary, the man who stole his existence.  On  March 18  at 6:30PM,  Cambodia  will screen  "Raja Bori"  (Royal City). The film is produced and directed by President of the National Assembly of the Kingdom of Cambodia, His Royal Highness Prince Norodom Ranariddh. Prince Ranariddh produced the film to show the public the rich cultural tradition and heritage of Cambodia. These treasures are the greatest accomplishments of King Jayavarman II and King Suryavarman II, who are the most famous in the history of Angkor and the Khmer Empire.   Canada  will present  "Leolo" , a multi-award winning film by Jean Claude Lauzon, on  March 19  at 6:30PM. The film tells the story of Leo who is torn between two worlds - the squalid Montreal tenement that he inhabits with his family, and the imaginative world that he constructs for himself through his writings. His experiences of growing up affect his response to both these worlds.   France  will screen on  March 21  at 6:30PM the film  "Metisse" (Café au lait) . In this comedy directed by Mathieu Kassovitz with Julie Mauduech and Hubert Kounde, a beautiful West Indian mulatta named Lola learns that she is pregnant. The question is, who is the father? There's Felix, a goofy Jewish bicycle messenger and there's handsome Jamal, a law student and wealthy son of an African Ambassador.  On  March 22  at 4:00PM,  Lebanon  will screen the film  "West Beyrouth"  by Ziad Doueiri. It is a moving and uplifting 'rights of passage' tale of three young Lebanese teenagers set against the war torn city of Beirut in 1975.  On the same day,  Switzerland  will screen at 6:30PM  "Les Années Lumière" (Light Years Away)  by Alain Tanner. Set in Ireland, "Les Années Lumière" tells a story about a detached old man who lives in a hangar full of birds. He is now ready to share his secret. In a Dublin bar, he meets a young man who agrees to follow the hard initiatory course until the day when his old master builds himself a pair of wings, flies away and disappears. The young man now inherits the garage, and especially the wisdom of the old man.  The Francophonie will be celebrated in Manila in collaboration with the Alliance Francaise de Manille and the members of the Francophonie that have representation in the Philippines: Belgium, Bulgaria, Cambodia, Canada, Czech Republic, Djibouti, Egypt, France, Haiti, Ivory Coast, Laos, Lebanon, Lithuania, Monaco, Morocco, Poland, Romania, Senegal, Seychelles, Slovenia, Switzerland, Togo, Vanuatu, and Vietnam.  For details and more information, you may contact Christopher Daniel, Public Affairs Officer of the Canadian Embassy at telephone: 8670026.   pelikula @ titus brandsma http://www.pelikula-titus.tk  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Sila na!  Sila na!   FINALLY!   Bad trip.  Buti naman!  Matagal-tagal rin akong naghintay 'langya kayo!  Maganda daw ang  Chicago .  My gas hindi ko pa napapanood!  Pati ang  The Guru   Manga collection updates: -  Black Cat  of Chapter 2 of Volume 3 is up in  Toriyama . -  Full Moon Wo Sagashite  Chapter 3 of Volume 1 is also up in Toriyama. - Currently downloading and reading scanslations of  Hana Yori Dango  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Updates   I spend a lot of time online, but I never get around to updating my blog.  Sigh.  There's a  Kokeshi Dolls  exhibit at the Grand Atrium Shangri-La Plaza Mall from March 05 to 26.  It's open to everyone so go visit.   Maid in Manhattan  starring Jennifer Lopez and Ralph Fiennes starts regular showing today.  Today is  Ash Wednesday    Page One , the bookstore in Rockwell is now called  Fully Booked .   7th Day  will have an exhibit at  Encomium Cafe  on March 8.  The cafe is located at FBR Arcade, Katipunan.  I'm back to being just me last February 25. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I created a failure.  Please disregard the post below and go to  urlLink http://onlinenews.blogspot.com  for a version that makes sense.  It's a newsletter of sorts.  I'll be keeping this site for future rants if there are any.  Anyways, I've got nothing better to do unless you've got an idea? 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       LITERARY:  Orange is the title of the novel that Mr. Somebody has written.  There's a teaser of about four Chapters.  http://saikee.tripod.com/orange/index.html    COMICS:  Comic strip by R.K. Milholland.  Loads of sarcasm here.  A breather from all the manga I've been reading lately.  www.somethingpositive.net    THEATER:     Repertory Philippines   POWER PLAYS  By George F. Walker Straight Play/Drama   Carlos P. Romulo Auditorium, RCBC Plaza, Makati March 13, 14, 15, 16, 20, 21, 22, 23, 27, 28, 29, 30, 2003 April 3, 4, 5, 6, 2003 Saturdays and Sundays at 10:30 am  Winner of five Chalmers Awards and four Dora Awards, Power Plays showcases both the development and the culmination of Walker's engagement with the film noire style. Ridiculous, imaginative and packed with action, Power Plays is a three-in-one play that's sure to draw praise even from the most discriminating audiences.  * * * THE WOMAN IN BLACK by Stephen Mallatratt (Adapted from the novel by Susan Hill)  Straight Play / Mystery-Thriller  Carlos P. Romulo Auditorium, RCBC Plaza, Makati 2003, April 24, 25, 26, 27  2003, May 1, 2, 3, 4, 8, 9, 10, 11, 15, 16, 17, 18   Arthur Kipps is a troubled man with a story that must be told... desperately. He hires an actor to help him prepare for the audience: his family. then, the actor turns his manuscript into a chilling theatrical device. A child's terrifying scream, a vengeful mother, and a horrible accident in a misty swamp provide the atmosphere for a masterful telling of a chilling ghost story.  Taken from http://www.repertoryphilippines.com/    FILMS:     Alliance Francais de Manille   April 30 Le Placard (2001) (French version with English subtitles, 81 minutes) dir. Francis VEBER with Daniel AUTEUIL   Forty-something Francois Pignon, who has worked for years as an accountant for the same contraceptive manufacturer, becomes desperate when he learns that his company is downsizing and he is about to lose his job. Work has meant everything to this boring and unhappy little man ever since his ex-wife left him two years ago. To make matters worse, his 16-year-old son has started avoiding him. Things change when Pignon's psychologist neighbor persuades him that he can save his job by coming out to his employers as a gay man -- even though he isn't.   GREETINGS: Welcome back  Tubs ! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Star Mandarin returns to Home Cable  Saturday and Sunday was spent mostly watching Shaolin Soccer, The Irresistible Piggies (Porkchop), God of Gamblers, Fat Choi Spirit, Dry Wood Fierce Fire etc.  This is only temporary though.  Star Mandarin is on Channel 77.   Power Books Summer Sale 2  Summer Sale Part 2 ! at all Powerbooks Branches.  Promo runs from April 14-May 15,  2003 50% on selected titles
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       QUESTOR EXTREME MANGAMANIA   I was on my way home when Comic Quest beckoned to me so I sashayed over, first to look at the window displa then to go in...oops. Questor Extreme Mangamania? Hmmm...to the counter I went and asked to see a copy and confirm if it's a comic book. Now, I read somewhere that there's a disctinction between comics and manga. Some people might take offense and call me "baka." Holler and forgive my ignorance. Anyway, to make a short story shorter, I bought the first ish of QEM.   SIDESWEEPER:   Think You're Under Arrest. A few grammatical errors. Dialogue could be better.   FREE SPIRITS:  Group of friends out for a week of project making and vacation. Medyo naguluhan ako sa panels.   CANTE ISTA:  About four strangers called to a place in Wyoming. Dean Koontsy. Mahilig sya sa "strangers coming together" or "going back to a baaad place."   CAMP BIG V:  Voltes V meets Gate Keepers  I'll wait (like I'm waiting for OTHER issues...ang tagal) for the second ish before I say that I'd rather not buy anymore. Maybe I'm such a manga addict right now that I've reached a point where the reading is flat.   urlLink  www.anime-club.com/extreme   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       "I wanted so badly to tell you that I loved you. The words, each time,      graced my lips like an impostor, only to fall away like some great blizzard         that was taken out to sea to rain it's fury on the dark ocean, alone,            unbeknwowsnt to any hearing...                And whether that day is tomorrow, or next week, or next year, or next           lifetime...I will finally get to tell you to your sweet face. The face I        will miss more than I could ever tell, that...I love You. And you'll smile wryly, close your eyes, say 'catch me baby,'...and fall."    --Eric Schaeffer, from the movie "Fall"  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday Five Answers for April 04, 2003   1. How many houses/apartments have you lived in throughout your life?  - My grandparents house on my mother's side - My grandparents house on my father's side - The apartment in Manila 3   2. Which was your favorite and why?  - The current place which is the apartment in Manila because it's in the city and most of my growing up years were spent in this city.  It is near UST where there are lots of trees.  It's near a lot of retail stores, malls and the Walled City of Manila.   3. Do you find moving house more exciting or stressful? Why?  - I was too young to appreciate moving out.  I never left since I got to where I live right now.  In theory, maybe if the place I'm going to is my own house or somewhere that is really great and better than where I am then I'd be excited.   4. What's more important, location or price?  - Price   5. What features does your dream house have (pool, spa bath, big yard, etc.)?  - It would have stained-glass windows.  Well part anyway.  Or if not reall stained-glass then glass art.  I have always thought that part of my house would have a domed roof.  The roof of my room anyway =)  It would have a side or backdoor to a raised walkway placed over a mini-river or pond.  My house would be airy, a bit minimalist.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Unwell by Matchbox20   All day staring at the ceiling Making friends with shadows on my wall All night hearing voices telling me That I should get some sleep Because tomorrow might be good for something Hold on Feeling like I'm headed for a breakdown And I don't know why   [Chorus]  But I'm not crazy, I'm just a little unwell I know right now you can't tell But stay awhile and maybe then you'll see A different side of me I'm not crazy, I'm just a little impaired I know right now you don't care But soon enough you're gonna think of me And how I used to be...me I'm talking to myself in public Dodging glances on the train And I know, I know they've all been talking about me I can hear them whisper And it makes me think there must be something wrong with me Out of all the hours thinking Somehow I've lost my mind   [Chorus]  But I'm not crazy, I'm just a little unwell I know right now you can't tell But stay awhile and maybe then you'll see A different side of me I'm not crazy, I'm just a little impaired I know right now you don't care But soon enough you're gonna think of me And how I used to be I've been talking in my sleep Pretty soon they'll come to get me Yeah, they're taking me away   [Chorus]  But I'm not crazy, I'm just a little unwell I know right now you can't tell But stay awhile and maybe then you'll see A different side of me I'm not crazy, I'm just a little impaired I know right now you don't care But soon enough you're gonna think of me And how I used to be Yeah, how I used to be How I used to be Well, I'm just a little unwell How I used to be How I used to be I'm just a little unwell   *Thanks to azlyrics  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Opera   Having fun using  urlLink Opera  brower.  Faster page loads and downloads!  No pop-ups!  Although there are sites that Opera can't properly display, but really this is good! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks to Leyds for  A Walk in the Clouds  and  Doctors .  I also bought  The Redemption of Althalus  by the Eddings at Booksale.  I'll post a review for each if and when I get the time and effort to do them.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Maze of Moments will not be updated for a while.  Apart from the fact that my life is boring and I need more money, there's nothing else to say so see you in  urlLink Online News   Ja Ne! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Desiccator   The desiccator is used to store dried samples in a dry atmosphere. It should not be used to dry an object, but to maintain an already dried object indefinitely in a dry condition.  ----- I am so CSI these days.  I even want my own microscope. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Quote   "The best intentions are fraught with disappointment"   Grissom to Sarah CSI Ep. One-Hit Wonder, Season 3   "Apologies are just words"  Lady Heather to Grissom, Season 3  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       WISH LIST    Books  Grass For His Pillow - Lian Hearn Cloud of Sparrows - Takahashi Matsuoka Fingersmith - Sarah Waters Possession - A.S. Byatt   Audio CD  Voyage 2 Silk Road The Best of UB40 Utada Hikaru Golden Key - Isgaard Perhaps, Perhaps, Perhaps Narda   Video CD  The English Patient Hero Cats and Dogs Series - Green Hope (with Stephen Fung) Happy Times 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         Xingfu shiguang (Happy Times)   Happy Times is about a guy who has finally found a girl to marry after 50 years.  He pretended to own a hotel so that he would look like he can afford 50 grand  for their wedding.  After his girlfriend's urging, he took the blind stepdaughter to work in the hotel as a masseuse.    This is not a and-they-live-happily-ever-after kind of movie.  It is sweet and real.  The ending is open-ended, but one that I don't mind.  It is enough.  You tend to dwell on the happy times that they spent together. =)  Directed by Zhang Yimou and stars Zhao Benshan, Dong Jie, Dong Lihua, Fu Biao among others. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And then moonlight slides unto the ceiling it wakes her, and she lies in the hammock, her mind skating.    She finds reset as opposed to sleep the truly pleasurable state.  If she were a writer she would collect her pencils and notebooks and favorite cat and write in bed.  Strangers and lovers would never get passed the locked door.  To rest was to receive all aspects of the world without judgement.  A bath in the sea, a fuck with the soldier who never knew your name.  Tenderness towards the unknown and anonymous, which is a tenderness to the self.   - The English Patient -  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Beary 01   Dear Maman,  	Kamusta ka na?  How's the family and clinic doing?  Anong balita sa Caloocan?  Sana dyan ka pa rin para matanggap mo ito.  Kung hindi naman e siguro nakalipat ka na sa mas magandang lugar.  	Ayos naman ako and family.  Medyo mahirap ang pera unlike last year or the year before.  Feeling ko tuloy sinayang namin ang mga panahong iyon.  	Nag-take ako ng French Module 1 nung summer.  Titignan ko pa kung makakapag enroll ako for Module 2 this August.  Sana matapos ko till Module 5.  I plan to learn Japanese, Mandarin and Thai too.  Pero syempre isa-isa muna.  Pag naging multi-lingual na ako maghahanap ako ng work sa immigration or embassy or =), well who knows?  	Dito pa rin ako sa trabaho ko.  Madalas akong late pag ang pasok ko is 8 am - 6 pm.  Tagal ko na hindi nakakapag sine =(.  Daig pa ako nung officemate kong hindi mahilig manuod.  She was able to watch Charlie's Angesl and Tomb Raider 2.  	Kamusta na si Papa Albert?    	Nga pala nasabi ko na ata na break na kami ng boyfriend ko ano?  Parang.  Well, anyway...wala pa rin akong boyfriend lol!  Hindi rin naman akong sobrang naghahanap kasi pinapangarap ko pang magkatawang tao ang picure ni  Zhu Xiao Tian  or  Wu Jian Hao.   Hahaha!  Yes, F4.  Although dati medyo jealous or possessive ako sa mga biglan nahilig sa chinovelas.  Kasi naman konti lang ang nanonood, mahilig at nakaka-appreciate dati tapos ngayon yung mga dating nagtatawa e join na rin.  Oh well =)  	Do you still go to the gym?  Anong balita sa clinic?  Wala nga pala akong cellphone, so kung minsan magpadala ka ng text e thank you po!  	Have you ever been to Pacific Star sa Makati lately?  Kung mapadaan ka have tea sa  Tea Republic .  Recommended ko yun.  	Wala akong balita sa iba.  I hope they're okay.  Si Jay temporarily sa Cebu ngayon nakatira at nagtatrabaho.  Isang mahabang temporarily.  Di ko pa alam kung hanggang kelan sya dun.  Sana palarin sya at makabangga nya ang true love nya.  	Sige hanggang dito na lang muna.  Try ko rin tumawag.  Bu-bwelo muna ako, duibuqi.  Kasi gasgas na ang boses ko and social skills sa hindi pag exercise tumawag sa mga kaibigan.  Wag ka mag-alala hindi pa naman ako tuluyang nakakalimot.  Magsusulat muna ako.  Dito ko mas nae-express ang thoughts ko.  Kung hindi lang ako tamad at madaling ma-bore I might be a writer.  Haha right.  	Oh, where will the wind blow next? 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Recent downloads:  Full Moon Wo Sagashite anime Utada Hikaru mp3   Music:  Listening to radio stations broadcasted over the internet recently via Windows Media.  I've got four Japanese stations, NU107, Crossover, and Fordham University in New York.  I also listen to Yahoo's Launch.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are the mystery woman    urlLink   Which Ultimate Beautiful Woman are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so goddamn tired  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       News for the wondering souls    Family:  Grandfather on mother's side had a stroke.  Got angry at one of his kids.  Work:  English brigade.  Speak in English even if the person on the other line is speaking in Tagalog.  Health:  Still waiting.  Seems regular, but not right on schedule like it's supposed to.  I am talking about my menstruation.  Friends:  So out of touch.  Sorry.  My life, basically, is boring.  Yes, yes it's a sign that I am getting older :).  I try to put a smile to every day.  I had this idea for an essay about education last night, but did not get around to actually do an outline or organize what I wrote which is just a paragraph long. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hole in My Soul by Aerosmith   Im down a one way street With a one night stand With a one track mind Out in no mans land (the punishment sometimes dont seem to fit the crime)  Yeah theres a hole in my soul But one thing Ive learned For every love letter written Theres another one burned (so tell me how its gonna be this time)  Is it over Is it over Is it over cause Im blowinout the flame  Take a walk outside your mind Tell me how it feels to be The one who turns the knife inside of me Take a look and you will find theres nothing there girl Yeah I swear, Im telling you girl yeah cause Theres a hole in my soul thats been killing me forever Its a place where a garden never grows Theres a hole in my soul, yeah I should have known better cause your loves like a thorn without a rose  Im as dry as a seven year drought I got dust for tears Yeah Im all tapped out (sometimes I feel broken and cant get fixed)  I know theres been all kinds of shoes underneath your bed Now I sleep with my boots on but youre still in my head (and something tells me this time Im down to my last licks) cause if its over Then its over And its driving me insane  Is it over Yeah its over And Im blowin out the flame  Take a walk outside your mind Tell me how it feels to be The one who turns the knife inside of me Take a look and you will find Theres nothing there girl, yeah, I swear Im telling you girl yeah cause theres a hole in my soul Thats been killing me forever Its a place where a garden never grows theres a hole in my soul, Yeah I should have known better cause your loves like a thorn Without a rose 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 02   Dearest Dad,  I bought five issues of Time for 10 pesos each.  I have three 2003 and two 2002 back issues so that I won't get bored with just one.  A current issue of Time costs 90 to a hundred in stores.  Orient Pearl, where I purchased the magazines, houses computer shops, pirated cd and secondhand book vendors.  It's in recto next to National Bookstore.  Do you subscribe to magazines?  I hope that I'd live in my own apartment on my 26th year.  That's next year.  These days cellphone loads can be had for 30, 60, 115 apart from the usual 300 and 500 from prepaid cards.  Instead of buying cards, your nearest sari-sari store or budy can send your phone text and call credits via text.  My officemate who knows this guy introduced us to this little business.  I ended up buying John the sim card (150) and automatic load (500) for selling.    One of my favorite appliances is the television.  It broke yesterday.  Just a small part.  The main switch.  Sharp service man came over today.  I left money for mom to pay for service and when I called this evening John said that we paid double what we expected because a part really had to be replaced.  Luma na talaga kasi.  Heard of Vienna Teng, Dad?  She's good.  I was at the Music One record bar the other day and her album was featured in one of their listening stations.  I hope to buy her album this coming payday.  If not then after bossaManila.  How's Tito George and Kuya Not?  How are the lovebirds? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 01   Have you read any of  Neil Gaiman's  work?  This morning, I have it on my lap again.  Maybe for the 5th or 6th time after finishing it last.  The book is  Neverwhere  and one of my favorite characters is  Door  because she can open all kinds of doors and locks.  She lives underground in London much like R. Perlman's Vincent in  Beauty and The Beast .  When the old woman said  "I'm sorry.  It starts with doors,"  you can just imagine a grandfather clock's long hand click.  The book says that there are things you can't see because you don't want to or because it seems out of place that you credit it to dream or illusion.  I've also read  Stardust  and I find it okay, but I love Neverwhere and his graphic novel  Dream Hunters .  How are you, Dad?  Were you able to watch the Oakwood incident last weekend?  It's political isn't it? 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 06   Dearest Dad,  Hi!  Kamusta ka?  Today is an improvement over a gray day yesterday.  We had no water around noon at home too.  Something about a clogged tank.    John's been busy going out with a friend to apply for work.  I bought two shirts last Tuesday.  It was on impulse and I remembered him saying na wala na syang shirt.  Lalabhan pa kasi.  What's going on over there?  John's current favorite music is from the band Me First and the Gimmie Gimmies.  They do rock versions of old and new songs.  Thank you sa remittance.  Never mind the birthday thing.  Send me a card =).  Love you! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 05   Dearest Dad,  Last week I was reading a part in Tom Clancy's Net Force: Cybernation about John Howard practicing his shooting skills.  The guns he used were also described like tha Magnum.  I remembered that I used to watch you target practice in Bacolod and i wanted to tell you that's why I called.  I am currently reading a site about steganography.  How are you? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 04: Mike Arroyo in Senate Hearing   It's raining hard today.  It's probably raining just as hard outside the building where they are having the senate hearing.  I listened to it inside the fx on the way to the office.  He said that he does not remember doing business with LTA regarding a property in '98?  I am not sure since the radio transmission is jumpy.  Matagal na daw yun at hindi nya maalala.  They mentioned Mission St. and I remembered na dating address nyo yun.  They talked about visits by Rosebud and Victor Corpuz and the help that Mike Arroyo provided for them.  The people there were also discussing if they have the authority to subpoena the bank accounts of Arroyo and Pidal.  Someone asked about the Tuazon and Arroyo family, it's members, whether there's a will left etc.  It just seemed nice to hear the news on the radio this morning while it's raining outside.  The rain was hard enough that for about three hours, we could not go out of the house because of the flood 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to Dad 03: Books, remittance, F4   Dearest Dad,   How are you? Today is 2:25 p.m., Saturday.  Last week I bought four books.  Clive Barker's "Weaveworld", John Sandford's "Fool's Run", Robotech #2 and a romance book by a female author whose name I forgot.   Thank you for the tuition fee for Arianne and Kat.  Kat just finished her exams.  Mom complains to me that she does not see Kat study hard, that Kat does not give her reviews enough time.  I tell her that maybe Kat understands her lessons well enough that she does not need to take the time to memorize.  Arianne will take her exams this week.   Dad, since the money you sent is for tuition, you will still send us the second half of the allowance right?  Mom used almost all of it to pay for the girl's tuition.   The family is watching Magandan Tanghali Bayan.  The grand finals of the Feeling F4 contest is being held today.  On September, two of the members and Barbie Xu will have a concert.  The concert tickets are steep, but the fans will surely go ahead and buy.   How and where did you spend your birthday? Next month ako naman.     Kathreen is out practicing for the sabayang bigkas.  She said that she is also one of the hosts of the event.   Mom keeps on mentioning to me the past two days that maybe Arianne and her boyfriend broke up because we don't see Gian as often as before and we don't see them talking on the phone anymore.  Maybe it's her way of telling me to ask my sister about it.   While I'm waiting for the page to load, I scan the amazon website w/c currently lists Clive Barker's books.  An acquaintance of mine mentioned the author as his favorite maybe two years ago and it's just now that I gave Clive a chance to get a response out of me.  "After three, the multitude."   Sometimes there are books that call out to me so that everytime I get into a bookstore I always go to the section where the book is and look at it to see if it may be worth my money.  Other times I remember conversations where an author or a title of a book was mentioned and I start to check it out.   Here comes the 5th group contestant of the Feeling F4 contest.  I wonder if the real F4 are also watching.  Okay di ba? I mean, Meteor Garden, the soap which catapulted them to fame was released about 2 years ago pa sa Taiwan, HK, Singapore, Thailand and other kapitbahays pati na sa US tapos ngayon lang sumikat sa Pilipinas so hanggang ngayon kumikita pa rin sila.  Phenomenon sila ulit.   Anong balita dyan? From the news iniimbistigahan pa rin ang mga officials na kumikita ng maliit pero maraming bahay at kotse.  Nabalitaan mo ba na may 3 bold stars na kinuha ang pangalan sa failed coup? Glorietta Magadalo, Tanya Trillanes and Angelika Rebella.     Re:Books, remittance, F4   Mahal kong anak,     Thank you for asking. I'm slowly going back to my old exercise routine. It's getting better.I hope I don't reinjure it. About Arianne and her BF, it could simply be a little spat that both of them could patch up. If they can't make it they should move on, continue with their studies. It might be better that way--excel in their school work.   As for Kathreen, I hope she's not letting up on her studies. Alam mo naman, pag mediocre ang marka sa escuelahan mahirap makakuha ng trabaho. Kathreen and Arianne should keep that in mind. Nobody else will help them--not their boyfriends.  Anak, what or who is F4? Sorry, snob si Dad mo. Wala akong Filipino Channel. I'd like to but most Filipino shows aired here by ABS-CBN are lousy. The acting is terrible, dialogue is dull, and stage set lacks creativity. These kind of programming insults a person's intellect. Akala nila tanga ang kanilang viewers. That's what happens when you don't have any competition.  In the meantime, in the US, rumors of additional coups abound, reports of the first gentleman's supposed assets gloss our publication. Have you heard about absentee voting and dual citizenship? Well, presidentiables are here campaigning--Roco, Macapagal, and Lacson.  Before I forget, anak, I'll have the last third of July's remittance soon the other half of August a bit later. And, I have your CD's (Michael Buble and Norah Jones). They'll be in the BBox with some of the DVD's  I burned for you. Talk to you later, mahal kong anak. Please extend my love to John and your two sisters. Again, ingat lagi.   Dad 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       First Time In Baguio   Hi guys!  How's everybody?  Ako inaantok.  What's new with that? :)  Just got back from Baguio.  Sorry, no pasalubong.  Ako ay isang Dukha until elevated to Maharlika status come payday.  Yeneway, ako ay napagod at nasiyahan.  Napagod dahil sa hagdan na inakyatan at binabaan sa cathedral, Lourdes Grotto, Bell Church etc, at sa paghahanap ng hairpin halos isang oras mula 8:30  ng gabi dahil na-lock ang pinto ng kwarto namin.  We went here and there just to find a hairpin at the suggestion of my friend S.  Baka daw God will bless us for attempting to pick the lock and thereby ensuring our entry in the Thieve's  Guild.  Si J naman ay sobrang worry kasi sya ang last touch sa doorknob.  Ako at si N ay sunod lang and trying to insert a calmness to the situation by asking how long will the hunt for the "one" hairpin that will end our troubles going to last. Finding no hairpin, we proceeded to buy toothbrush and mineral water at 7/11 and had dinner at Jollibee.  Natulog na lang kaming 3 babae sa kwarto ng aming bading na kasama while he went to Gimbals and Alfonso(ata) to drink  blessed beer with his friend S.  We were able to open the window of our bedroom at about 8 in the morning using the DSL brochure.  Yehey!  Nasiyahan because we were able to commune with nature sa Botanical Garden, Mine's View, Wright Park, Camp John Hay.  I was seriously expecting the traditional christmas tree pine tree pero wala akong nakita.  Dahil marami kaming pictures.  I have doubts about how I look in them though.  My hair is probably sticking out in different directions.  Dear, there goes my cute picture.  Ipo-post ko pa naman dito sa Friendster.  And syempre best of all I was able  to buy chocolate mallows, peanut brittle, chocolate and milk flakes, sundot kulangot, choco crinkles, legua de gato and ube jam for me and my  family!  Ube jam with coffee.  Makes sense to me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was thinking of a non-mushy topic to post after reading fanfic updates of X&X.  I looked left and right.    I share the table with my officemate, January.  She sits next to the window with the blinds down.  I can see the outline of buildings.  It's 5:35 pm and the sky is dark.  On my left is a silver Verbatim cd copy of the album Bling Bling.  I burned a copy earlier at the request of Ms. J.  Under this are two more cds from CDR King containing recently burned copies of Smallville season 3 episode 4 & 5.  Under that is an envelope containing pictures of our October visit to Baguio.  My first time.  Before these are my Publishing Digital Video book, steno pad, Reader's Digest, Chinese in Three Months by Hugo, cellphone, tissue paper, scratch papers, three identification cards and a red pen.  Under these is a slip of paper with the meaning of ambiguous taped on the table.  Then there's my Alcatel phone logged on to 5508 and my big black bag which is, as usual, open.  On my right is a red thermos mug.  A gift from the boss last Christmas.  There are two plastic Nemo fishes in front of said mug.  One is Dory, the blue forgetful fish which they sometimes call me here and the yellow fish whose name I do not know.  I have two dead fishies on my desk.  They are here because I can't stand the sight and knowledge of them adding to the clutter at home.  Then there's my bear figurine where to my delight sometimes contains candy or chocolate courtesy of whoever is  galante  that day.  Mouse and StarFile where I keep some cds, other documents, Pentel pens and kikay kit.  Re-reading this I proceed to arrange my things into a semblance of order.  My eyes went to the fishies.  And away.  Can't decide what to do about them. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
                 Karen Nervez was   a Strange Poker Player   in a past life.   Discover your past lives @ Quiz Me             
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      All families are embarassing and if they're not embarassing, they're dead. - Kitty to Donna,  That 70's Show  -  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Novembers, and surely Decembers, bring mornings in the afternoon.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       IMPORTANT BRASH YOUNG CINEMA ANNOUNCEMENT   On November 14, 2003, 8 PM, Brash Young Cinema and Steadybear present BULONG SA KAWALAN, a short film by Bobi Bonifacio.  It will be starring Dave Corpin, Abby Yao, Racquel Villlavicencio and Ronnie Lazaro.  We are really excited about this movie, coz it is the first time we have produced anything ourselves together.  And it is our first step in conquering Philippine and world cinema (BWAHAHAHA!) manic laughter!  But seriously, we have finally come to realize, that the only way to produce better cinema is to create it ourselves.  So this is our first swing at it, and hope you all come to watch us bat.  BULONG SA KAWALAN, what is it about?  Well cant really tell you coz we dont want to spoil it, but basically it is a psycho-thriller, and I got scared.  But of course, Im easily scared.  But even me being so scared of horror movies had the guts to produce this one coz Bobi is da man.  Anyway, hope you all come!  BULONG SA KAWALAN will be shown on November 14, 21, 22 and 28.  All screenings will be at 8 pm at the Brash Young Cinema, located at the basement of the S&L Building, Esteban corner Dela Rosa Street, Legaspi Village, Makati.  Well have more screenings if we make money. ;)  Tickets will be at 60 pesos.  Charged at the gate.  Thanks! -------------------------------------------------  I watched yesterday, November 14 and I tell you come and watch the movie.  Really good!   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       MOM & JERRY YAN   I was reading  almost married ; Kat was reading  Fool's Run  and mom was playing solitaire when she said "Kar,  nakauwi na kaya si Jerry Yan "? (Kar, do you think  Jerry Yan  is already home/back in Taiwan?)  "Ummm,  ambot  (Bisaya word for "I don't know")  "Three days  daw sya dito e. Siguro nakarating na yun sa Taiwan. " (They say that he will stay here for three days. Maybe he has arrived in Taiwan already.) And she proceeds to hum the theme song of  Amazing Twins . 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      QUOTE OF THE DAY  "Just hit him once, hard, and then move on.  I suggest you go for the crotch  para mabaog.   It's called closure."  -  almost married , Tara FT Sering - 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know what to write about first.  I'm not even sure that I want to write about anything.  Apart from the regular every two weeks change in shift, daily problems of users at work, answering calls, e-mails, checking up on tickets that are not yet solved while listening to mp3s, reading Ximen & Xiao You & the rest of the gang fanfics and wathing a movie or series on my pc, there is nothing going on with my life.  So, what I'm doing now is trying to see whether I can still write. If I can still express myself well enough in writing in the English language.  If I can still make a passable composition about someone else's life.  Mine.  How interesting is that?  And now here I am, rice corned beef and ampalaya with egg and shrimp for dinner in front of me and thinking how I sometimes mentally berate myself for cursing in my mind when I should be like San Cai except that I won't be shouting "Dao Ming Si!"  I'd be yelling "What the FUCK!" at the top of my lungs from the rooftop of Petron Mega Plaza.  After a few minutes of dinner concentration, I wondered how a boyfriend of one year will take it if his girlfriend farted while in the same room with him.  Nice dinner topic huh?  Is it even possible that there's no chance at all of the girl, or boy for that matter, farting while together with his/her loved one within a year?   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So how's everybody's Christmas?  Our family's was peaceful.  After the mass we ate and opened gifts.  My sister gave me a pair of red earrings shaped like Chinese lanterns.  Before mass I prepared my traditional pasta, Pasta Paradiso.  Love the smell of cooking wine.  Thanks to jeffer for updating  urlLink Homecomings  and coming up with another  urlLink fic .  For X&X fans, I recommend you read her  urlLink My Beloved .  No, I did not watch the F4 concert last Dec. 26.  My officemate who did bought me a calendar though. ^_~  I was and still am short on money, but it did not deter my hunger for a book.  I found myself browsing Powerbooks Greenbelt after finding out that the branch in Pasay road is closed.  Not finding anything that could whet my appetite, I proceeded to Book Sale (?) beside Tokyo Tokyo.  A Different Bookstore near Rustan's finally had what I wanted.  Dai Sijie's  urlLink Balzac and the Little Chinese Seamstress .  The fact that the movie version which I failed to see was shown in Greenbelt ArtFilm for some weeks helped.    The ending stunned me.  After some education from books stolen by Lou the storyteller and violinist and narrator she took off for the city!  She said "There is one thing I learned from Balzac.  Beauty is a price beyond measure."  Now, where is she going?  Be an actress?  Model?  Find a sponsor?  Why was I stunned?  I was comfortable with the story.  The young men's visits to the Little Seamstress, the mountains, the straightforwardness of it all and then they were burning the books!  My latest music food today is Italian composer Ennio Morricone.  Check him out.  He composed scores for movies and tv like Malena and Twin Peaks.  His official website is  urlLink Ennio Morricone  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Could not help, but post the lyrics to  "I Believe"    I BELIEVE THAT ALTHOUGH U R GONE i believe guden gyothe ojiman  THIS CANNOT B D END, CAN IT? Idero ibyorun anigejyo I BELIEVE THAT UR JOURNEY BACK TO ME I believe naege onun girun  IS JUST DELAYED, ISNT IT? jogum molli doraor punigejyo I REMEMBER SO WELL, THAT I HURT MYSELF modu jinagan gu giogsogeso nega narur aphuge hamyo  AS I CRY nunmurur mandurjyo I HOPE U DONT CRY AS I DO na mankhum urji anhgirur gudemanun I HOPE U WONT CRY AS U LEAVE nunmur obshi nar phyonhage bonejugirur  I KNOW U WILL RETURN SOMEDAY onjenga dashi doraor guderanun gor argie BECAUSE I BELIEVE nan midgo igie I WILL WAIT FOR YOU, JUST YOU gidarirkeyo nan gudeyo yaman hajyo  I BELIEVE YOU SHOULD NOT CRY I believe nega aphaharkabwa WHEN U THINK ABOUT MY PAIN gudenun urjido mothegejyo  I BELIEVE MY TEARS WILL BRING U BACK TO ME I believe hurunun ne nunmuri  MY EYES CANNOT FORGET gudr dashi nege dollyojugejyo THAT IT IS YOU WHO MAKE THEM CRY jaku momchunun ne nungir sogeso I HOPE U DONT CRY AS I DO gude mosubduri tolla nunmurur mandurjyo I HOPE U WONT CRY AS U LEAVE na mankhum urji anhgirur gudemanun I KNOW U WILL RETURN SOMEDAY nunmur obshi nar phyonhage bonejugirur  BECAUSE I BELIEVE onjenga dashi doraor  I WILL WAIT FOR YOU, JUST YOU guderanun gor argie nan midgo igie MY TEARS WILL BRING U BACK TO ME gidarirkeyo  MY EYES CANNOT FORGET nan gudeyo yaman hajyo  THAT IT IS YOU WHO MAKE THEM CRY BEFORE I MET YOU na gude argi jon isesangdo THE WORLD WAS NOT SO BEAUTIFUL irohge nunbushyonunji  BENEATH THE SAME SKY gu hanur areso ijen ALL ALONE I CRY nunmullo namgyojyojiman  BUT I WILL WAIT HERE ijarir nan jikhirgeyo  JUST FOR YOU guderan iyumanuro EVEN IF WAITING IS HOPELESS naegenun gidarimjocha  IT'S ALREADY ENOUGH chungbunhi hengboghagejyo  TO THINK OF LOVE saranghan iyumanuro TIME MEANS NOTHING TO ME to haruga jinaga go onun gir ijodo I WILL WAIT FOR YOU, JUST YOU gidarirkeyo nan gudeyo yaman hajyo  JUST YOU nan gudeyo yaman hajyo  Track from the Korean movie  "My Sassy Girl"  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Me:  i left the house @ 1030 nanood muna ako ng Lady Lady sa channel 2 yung driver ng fx na sinakyan ko e nangunsumi sa dalawang pasahero nya. kasi gusto bumaba sa di naman babaan.... yung pangalawang pasahero mapilit. parating daw dun sya binababa...ayan meron daw nagbababa dun   Him:  then what happend? i mean binaba ba ng driver?   Me  binaba ng driver. bilisan lang daw ang pagbaba...sabi pa ni manong driver..."kaya di umaanseso Pilipino e" tapos alam naman daw mali bakit daw gagayahin kung may ibang gumagawa pagdating ko ng makati nagpunta akong banco de oro para bayaran yung memorial plan ko...tapos nagpunta akong equitable para i-report yung lost atm card at magpa-replace na rin. buti na lang naiisipan ko na baka may nag surrender ng atm ko dun. meron nga so nakuha ko naman agad naiwanan ko kasi sa taas ng atm machine yung atm card ko kagabi stupid   Him:  di naman minsan, aksidente lang. buti na lang walang nanakaw sa account mo.......at least newt time alam mo na.   Me:  buti na lang may fastnet ang equitable sa internet. nung di ko makita yung atm card ko nag text ako sa friend ko para kunin ang account number nya then tumawag ako sa office. pinatransfer ko lahat ng pera ko sa account ng officemate ko through internet   Him:  i see.....di nag below average daily balance ka niyan.   Me:  ok lang naman kasi payroll account naman yun   Him:  as for me, ang atm ko konti lang ang pera palaga, the most is ten thousand. pero pag big account. walang atm... only checking. then what happend next?   Me:  na-retrieve ko nga yung atm ko tapos pumasok na ako sa office  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow is Saturday. Tomorrow is December 13, 2003 Tomorrow is CSPI's christmas party. Tomorrow is titus brandsma's monthly film showing Tomorrow is the start of C3Con Tomorrow I might go ice skating Tomorrow I might head for Tutuban Mall and forego titus. Tomorrow is another day that spawns another as it leaves. When tomorrow comes, will I still remember yesterday?   Vorbis laughed. Brutha wondered why. The puzzle wasn't why he remembered, it was why everyone else seemed to forget 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This cold morning, I noticed the tree near the bus stop beside the university.  A nice leafless tree less grand than  urlLink this , but still gives a reason for one to smile.  I imagine myself walking in the park, snug in a thick comfortable coat, the birds flying overhead, sun shining and leafless trees around.  An impromptu  urlLink Qtek  training happened today.  I am glad to be away from my seat and learn to operate a new gadget.  I hope they issue us a unit or two to familiarize ourselves with the features.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If I find myself in a vegetable state, my life sustained by tubes, will I prefer unplugging and thereby end the painful waiting or go on and sustain the hope  that I will one day get better? Will I order an  urlLink Advance Directive Kit  in preparation for when the decision to plug or unplug comes up online?      A Celebration of Life @ Pelikula@Titus Brandsma   Nights of Cabiria,  Federico Fellini, 1957  Patibong,  Wowie Hao, Philippines, 2003 (Short)  A Place in the World/Un lugar en el mundo,  Adolfo Aristarain, Argentina, 1992  Tampopo,  Juzo Itami, Japan, 1988  Showing on December 13, 2003 Saturday.  Show starts at 1 pm.  For more info visit  urlLink Pelikula@Titusbrandsma  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of my brain tissues feel like they're lose and whenever I walk they jiggle.  Walk, walk.  Step, step. Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle, jiggle.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How's the plumbing? Salty liquid trailed down my left eye.  Lying in bed, cellphone in hand I think of what other thing to say other than what has just been typed.  How's the plumbing?  I am happy.  God is good!  I am glad you're my friend.  I care.  All these encapsulated in a question about pipes.  I decided to send the message as it is.  Coward.  Police chief to Spiderman before latter goes to burning building: I'll be here when you get back! - Shounen-ai! Hehehe...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A sentence in bold red sent through mail is like a red flag or cloth (ano nga ba ang tawag dun) that you wave and display in front of a bull.  Now if you insert some chinese lantern images or hearts or a christmas tree, well, it's a sign of good-will don't you think?    A toss coin solves the problem of who gets the last choco twist of Mister Donut.  New Memo. Enter. Alt+Tab. F9. wHat mAKES 100%? And I wonder 'Does this sum up my day?'   Ambigram . Legible both ways.  Illuminati . You guessed right.  I am reading  Angels and Demons  by Dan Brown
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wrapping books, Kidd, LuEllen and Bobby   VioletJersey: yeah... but i'm not in the mood to read children's books at the moment...	 (S) Karen: :)	 VioletJersey: i even have Neil Gaiman's Coraline, Lemony Snickett series & Artemis Fowl...	 VioletJersey: kae, how do you wrap nga ulit yung hardbound books mo?	 (S) Karen: tissue	 (S) Karen: yung parang japanese paper	 (S) Karen: parang opaque na paper that one can buy sa supermarket	 (S) Karen: wax paper	 VioletJersey: as in... yung ang ibabalot ko instead of the plastic National Bookstore one?	 (S) Karen: yes	 (S) Karen: ay wait	 (S) Karen: no. yun saken the whole book is wrapped	 (S) Karen: parang gown that you keep in tissue paper and put in a box	 (S) Karen: :D	 VioletJersey: but... masisira sya pag binasa ko... right?	 VioletJersey: e di hindi masyado makikita yung cover...	 (S) Karen: no. y sya masisira? you just unwrap the book from the paper and fold the paper. set it aside	 (S) Karen: yung mga naka wrap are kept in a box	 (S) Karen: they're really not for shelves if you keep them in wax paper	 VioletJersey: kasi what i do is wrap it w/ plastic cover... like what we do w/ our schoolbooks before...	 (S) Karen: ah...	 (S) Karen: kasi ako pag may hardbound book and syempre may paper flap sya...	 VioletJersey: okay...	 (S) Karen: i tend to get curious and look at the actual	cover..	 (S) Karen: i mean minus the flap	 (S) Karen: so i don't use plastic	 (S) Karen: kasi sabi ko sa sarili ko...	 (S) Karen: what if yung ibang taong magbabasa is as curious as i am?	 (S) Karen: di ba yung actual cover minsan iba dun sa flap?	 (S) Karen: you'd want to see that too kahit na blank lang pala hehehehe	 VioletJersey: awww...	 VioletJersey: i do that before i wrap the book...	 VioletJersey: ang ganda ng hardcover nung latest ni John Sandford...	 (S) Karen: a prey novel pa rin?	 VioletJersey: wait... so yung flap ang binabalutan mo ng wax paper?	 VioletJersey: yeah... i have all his books!	 (S) Karen: no. the whole book talaga	 VioletJersey: ang ganda nung latest Kidd novel nya! Super astig talaga...	 (S) Karen: tapos i just secure it with a ribbon	 (S) Karen: or one of those thin rope things	 VioletJersey: hehehe... actually, i only read it because of LuEllen...	 (S) Karen: astig si luellen noh?	 (S) Karen: you know what? we can learn from her hahahahaha	 (S) Karen: how to be a professional burglar	 VioletJersey: tapos after 10 years of "friendship"... saka lang sinabi ni LuEllen what's her real name kay Kidd...	 VioletJersey: hehehe... sinabi mo!??!	 VioletJersey: i love the whole phonebooth thing... pwede pala yun...	 VioletJersey: and the best tip of them all... wear tennis clothes went stealing at broad daylight! (S) Karen: yung hooking up your laptop to a phonebooth?	 VioletJersey: best advice in the world! LOL!	 (S) Karen: hahaha yes...para you can act like you're jogging	 VioletJersey: no... yung puputulin nila yung cord tapos ring lang sya ng ring...	 (S) Karen: ah that one	 (S) Karen: para malaman kung may tao	 VioletJersey: yeah! I tell you... if i plan to steal from someone... i'll read all her stunts!	 VioletJersey: yeah! i didn't know you can do that!	 (S) Karen: cool. ano ba official site ni sandford?	 VioletJersey: www.johnsandford.org	 VioletJersey: i wanna send nga ang email thanking him for writing a Kidd novel...	 VioletJersey: and begging that i hope it's not his LAST!	 VioletJersey: siguro pag na-meet ko sya... baka maiyak ako!	 VioletJersey: he's one of my dearest idols... kahit na yung kidd novels palang nya halos ang nababasa ko!	 (S) Karen: hahaha	 VioletJersey: damn... may message board pala sya...	 VioletJersey: i'm gonna acquaint myself to them! hehehe...	 (S) Karen: teka teka	 VioletJersey: i'm probably the only one here in the Phils who have all his novels...	 (S) Karen: i am reading the synopsis of the hanged man's song	 (S) Karen: shit	 (S) Karen: double shit	 (S) Karen: bobby's fucking gonna die in this book????!!!!!	 (S) Karen: WHY????????????????????????????	 (S) Karen: he's the freaking shadow of the book	 (S) Karen: angel and devil	 VioletJersey: not that i'm bragging or anything... pero	 damn... it took me a good 6-7 years bago ko nakuha lahat yan...	 (S) Karen: pero shadow na lang oks na saken	 (S) Karen: constant sya	 (S) Karen: nyeta naman o	 VioletJersey: and murderous stares from the sales clerks of all the Book Sale branches I've been to! Hehehe...	 (S) Karen: i don't believe this....hahaha - to murderous stares from book sale people	 VioletJersey: hehehe....	 (S) Karen: anyway, why kill bobby?	 VioletJersey: i know! it was like... "TANGNA!?! PATAY NA SI BOBBY!?!"	 (S) Karen: bobby is the man! next to kidd ofcourse...y o y	 (S) Karen: he's supposed to be untouchable	 (S) Karen: i am not going to get over this....	 VioletJersey: sabi ko nga sa parents ko nung nasa US "kahit yun na lang ang ipadala nyong book... okay na po sa kin!	Papasko nyo na sa akin!"	 VioletJersey: hehehe... believe me... i couldn't put the	book down...	 VioletJersey: kahit sa work dala ko sya... kahit pagne-NET kinalimutan ko...	 VioletJersey: basta matapos ko lang sya...	 VioletJersey: and when it was over... i was like... "WOW"	 (S) Karen: ok. don't spoil anymore ha	 VioletJersey: I pray to the Heavens that this is not the last we will see of the dynamic duo! (S) Karen: hope not...pero bobby!!!!	 VioletJersey: no... i won't...	 (S) Karen: :'(	 VioletJersey: it's the best ever!	 VioletJersey: i know... it's a painful thought!	 VioletJersey: but the story will never end... i hope!	 (S) Karen: tanungin mo kay master john kung bakit nya ginawa yun	 VioletJersey: damn... sikat kasi masyado si Davenport eh!	 VioletJersey: hehehe... i swear, the next time i go to the US, iti-time ko sa paglabas ng mga novels nya...	 VioletJersey: tapos stalker brigade ang lola mo!?!	 (S) Karen: teka lang...log off lang ako	 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Excerpt from The Flanders Panel by Arturo Perez-Reverte   "The sentence I am now writing is the one that you are now reading."  He looked at Belmonte in surprise.  "So?"  "That's all there is.  That sentense was written by me a minute and a half ago and you read it only forty seconds ago.  That's to say, my writing and your reading correspond to different moments in time, but on that piece of paper 'now' and 'now' are undoubtedly the same 'now'.  Therefore, on the one hand the sentence is true, but on the other hand it lacks all validity.  Or is it the concept of time that we're failing to take into account?  Don't you think that's a good example of a paradox?  I can see you have no answer to it.  Well, you'll find the same problem with the enigmas posed by my Van Huys or by anything else.  Who's to say that your solution to the problem is the correct one?  Your intuition and your system?  Fine, but what superior system can you count on to demonstrate that your intuition and your system are valid?  And what other system can you call on to corroborate those two systems?  As a chess player, I imagine you'll find these lines interesting."       The player too is a prisoner      of another board      Of black nights and of white days.       God moves the player and the player the piece.      But which god behind God begins the weft      Of dust and time and sleep and dying?  "The world is just one vast paradox," the old man concluded.  "And I defy you to prove the contrary."
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kat and I had a double movie last Saturday.  We watched   Crying Ladies   and   Mano Po 2  .  Funny because they both have Chinese funerals.  Notice too that in Crying the name of the deceased is Washington while in Mano it is Antonio, but both are called Tony.  I was irritated at the couple beside me during Mano Po 2 because they were discussing the relationship of the characters to each other, the traditional Chinese funeral and what-not till the end of the movie!  Talk about rudeness.    Tama ba ang sinasabi nila? Are they speaking correctly?   Referring to the times when the characters speak in Chinese (subtitled).    Why did he do that?  What does the paper being thrown out of the funeral car mean?    Bad trip!  Hello!  Just watch the movie!  The parents of my sister's best friend gave my sister a puppy yesterday. We wanted to keep it, but we would not be able to take care of it properly since we live in an apartment so mom told my sister to return him.  Downloaded two Love Storm mp3s.  On Vanessa's question regarding Balzac, I bought it for about Php700 @ A Different Bookstore in Glorietta.  If you want, I can lend it to you. :)  It is interesting.   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't got the time to change the outline of my blog.  Will do so once I get the time and mood to do it.  My latest favorite Taiwanese series is Love Storm starring Vivian Hsu, Ken Zhu and Vic Zhou.  I borrowed my friend's cd last week and finished the last episode (Ep 21) today.  Episode summaries available in this  urlLink site   Today is one of those "morning in the afternoon"
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "For the last time..."   For the last time?  When did the first time happen?  Second?  Third?  Secret  ba 'to  until the last time came which is the first time the requirement came to our attention?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please post part-time job openings in the comments box. Need extra income. Am poor in sales.  Am available during weekends. Maybe the CCP guys can take me in...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was it last year that Vince was here?  I appreciate what he said about the Philippines. It's home and that for all its imperfections and political confusion, it's still a great place. Disappointment creeps in when a friend expresses desire to leave the country because the Philippines is this and that.  Not that I wouldn't like to go abroad. Am I living in a bubble? Inside looking out? Seeing, not experiencing? All I know is that If I die out there, I'd want to be taken home.  A lot of Valentine contributions to 2BU has been published and out in today's paper.  I haven't read all of them yet.   Pam Pastor's  article contains traces of "My Sassy Girl". I requested for a softcopy.  Kapal ko noh?  I was not able to bag that section of the paper for further reading e.  Speaking of  My Sassy Girl , I met my nth lover yesterday.  Kwong Sang-woo!  PAPA! *me like Motosuwa-kun with a nose bleed*  A sticker of Bugs Bunny and Lola is stuck on the window of the right passenger door. Bugs is naked while Lola wears a sleeveless top and shorts. A lot of thoughts here like maybe Bugs is genderless and why can't Lola be naked. She could've been drawn without breasts. Just stick a ribbon. Whatever.  Oh, yeah.  Why do most conversations tend to lean toward matters of the heart when V day is approaching?  What started out as a request to configure an AS400 connection ended up in  "Ok ka ba?", "Masasabi mo bang OK ka?", "I'm loveless" .  I just listen and say "Yes, I'm generally okay." 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My black Pilot ballpen is unremarkable.  It's just like any other ballpen around.  I was a baby today about it when I did not find it and the post-it on my desk nor on the three places I was at this morning.  I rummage my bag while saying  Asan ka na?   I seriously felt like crying.   Kabibili ko lang kaya ng ballpen this morning!   20 pesos  pa ang ginastos ko and out of my small baon.   Aargh!  Finally, after looking around our room I found it lying there all tidy in front of another pc.   Sino ang salarin?   Definitely not me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My brother and youngest sister likes to watch WWF on Solar.  I look at the crowd around the arena and sometimes wonder at the entertainment that these people get from watching.  It's like the soap opera for muscled idiots what with sons, daughters, fathers fighting each other and coming back from the dead.    Sarah lent me  "The House of Sand and Fog" .  I'm not sure if this was made into a movie.  Good storytelling.  A former Persian colonel living in San Francisco.  Bought a house from an auction to start a business of buying houses and selling them again.     "I pass a Filipino maid pushing her cart and I take notice that she smiles.  And even bows her head."   Small ouch.  Filipinos portrayed as a maid again.  Stings, but true.  On the way to Glorietta, I look at the back of the book.   "Becomes obsessed..."   I am not someone that one can get obsessed with.  Comforting thought.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Film schedules   Pelikula @ TitusBrandsma will have their monthly film showing this coming Saturday, March 13.  The theme is "Faces of Eve".  Please visit  urlLink this website  for details.  On the right frame of the website you will also see schedules for Eiga Sai at the CCP Dream Theater.  For the eKsperim[E]nto International Film Festival, click  urlLink here  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The roof of my mouth, specifically the sides are a bit tender because I immediately ate the cheese pizza that I ordered last night from Yellow Cab after watching "When The Rain Lifts" at the CCP.  I ordered the 10" one and left four slices for the people at home.  An ambulance trailed behind the jeep I was in on the way home.  It went weeoo, weeoo, weeoo.  I'm sure that when we hear an ambulance's cry, we wonder what happened to the person inside.  We wonder at the drama unfolding inside.  We wonder if maybe the driver is simply just in a hurry.  Just like in the movies?  The middle window on the right side of the ambulance was open about 4 inches wide.  The vehicle wasn't trailing behind now, but coming along side our jeep.  I observe my fellow passengers' actions when the opening comes within eye level.  Amusing to see heads turn, eyes peer.  It's like seeing a sexy woman and watching how the male species react to her.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The House of Sand and Fog   The Behrani family died except for the daughter who's already married. The son got shot, the wife was killed by the husband and the husband killed himself. They're off to a better place where they're not harassed to leave the house that they bought at an auction and where they don't have to pretend that they've got money and can still live a life of luxury like when they were in Iran.  The former owner and the married boyfriend went to jail. It's depressing.  I thank my parents for I did not turn out much worse than other people and that  here  is not a bad place to be.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The glass pane is dotted with silver rain drops from the afternoon downpour making up for the starless sky while the landscape is dotted with orange-yellow city lights and my face reflected before them.  Uncapture moment.  Feeling model in music video with Utada Hikaru singing "Final Distance"
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep eyeing J's rice crispies. Looking at it made me think of Lolo Bitong, my Dad's Dad. He used to bring home these big bars of rice crispies from the market when I was a kid in Bacolod.   Alias Season 3 Episode 21  Syet, syet, Mars! Matatapos na sya at sobrang exciting! Aaaay konti na lang...   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Suffice it to say that add to the warmth here in the office on a Sunday, I was hot.   Last Samurai Comments:   "Shit! They shot Silent Bob!" (Silent Bob is the silent samurai cum babysitter of Tom Cruise's character Capt. Nathan)  "Aw..." (With matching tear when the last few samurais left where gunned down with that big armalite thingie. I don't think I spelled it right)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      N asked if it's okay with me that we switch schedules.  It's supposed to be my day off this Sunday then back to work Monday and him the opposite.  He has overnight outing with his friends starting Saturday that is why he wants a trade.  I said yes, okay.  I get the feeling again.  Nothing against N.  I am feeling left behind, that I've got nothing to do so I might as well work.  Why can't I ask for a leave just like that?  Because there is nothing to take a leave for.  I don't even have much time to binge on movies.  Maybe I should make a list like Justine in "Tough Love".  Ten things that I've never done before and dare myself to do?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, sometimes I talk to God.  In my head.  Like today.  I was inside the fx on the way to work, flanked by 3 others.  One on my right and two on my left.  My bag is on my lap, left hand holding a biggie size Coke and my right holding a paper bag that contains fries from McDonald's.  Squeezed like that and maybe looking harassed while drinking and eating fries, I sighed in relief when one on my left stopped at City Hall.  More space for me and my bag and my elbows.  I hoped that no more passenger will hail this fx and squeeze in to make us four again, but then I thought that maybe it's the driver's first drive this morning so it's a pity if he doesn't earn and I said okay fine God's will.  Right God?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank you God I was able to watch the third season ender of Alias.  Not as kick-ass as Season 1 or 2, but still Lauren got shot a lot of times by the Fafa Vaughn.  Whoowee!  Last night was Buffy's super final episode.  Sniff, sniff.  Anya died.  Spike died.  Angel showed up and gave me more hope that eventually Buffy and him will still end up together.  Thank you for entertainment like this that makes me forget my money problem.  If you want a blow-by-blow recap of some of your favorite shows including Alias, go and visit  Television Without Pity . It's right up there on my links section.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Wednesdays thru Fridays, my work starts at 12 noon so I can either take an early lunch at home or a late lunch at work.  For sure, my breaktime during these days will almost always include a trip to the Japan Foundation library at the Pacific Star Building.  When I'm there, I practice my Katakana and read Banana Yoshimoto's Kitchen.    It has been a while since I jotted down something I read from a book.  Here's one now from Kitchen:  	 Sotaru had said that even though she'd been seeing him for a year, Yuichi's girlfriend didn't understand the slightest thing about him, and it made her angry.  She said Yuichi was inacapable of caring more for a girl than he did for a fountain pen.  	Because I wasn't in love with Yuichi, I understood that very well.  The quality and importance of a fountain pen meant to him something completely different from what it meant to her.  Perhaps there are people in this world who love their fountain pens with every fiber of their being - and that's sad.  If your not in love with him, you can understand him  	-------------------------------- 	 	The conversation we just had was like a glimpse of stars through a chink in a cloudy sky. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's the difference between  marmalade  and  jam ? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>