<Blog>

<date>27,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mercury News | 11/27/2002 | First human clone soon to be born, doctor says 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This here  is a wonderfully funny article in the Wall Street Journal ostensibly about one item in particular -- TiVo -- and its pattern recognition habits. If you care to look at this article a little more closely, you'll find that it's actually about artificial intelligence and consumer profiling.  Simply put, I don't want people to know what I purchase: it's no one's business but my own. I don't care who you are or where you work, the fact that I'm taking home 15 boxes of Oreo cookies affects no one but me. Right now there's a lot of data mining going on. Air Miles was one of the first and probably the most well known, but Safeway and, more recently, Shoppers Drug Mart have also stuck their noses in. And it's this leveraging of information under the guise of consumer benefit that has me concerned.  Sure, these organizations do throw you a bone for allowing them to rape your private life: one reward mile for every $20 spent, twenty cents off fishsticks, etc. And don't forget what a big favour they're doing for you by being able to personalize your advertising! No more need for us carnivores to see those annoying veggie-burger ads.  The facts are that Air Miles et al are making ridiculous amount of money tracking spending habits and releasing this data to third parties. Advertisers want to get more bang for their buck by targeting ads and really couldn't care less about consumer benefit, although they do use it as a smoke screen. And I really hate to do this, but it's only a matter of time until someone, somewhere, starts looking for correlations in spending and purchases to see if you've been planning something naughty... how many false alarms is this going to bring down each year? You mean I'm being questioned over the styrofoam cups I bought in December and the fertilizer I bought in April? Ridiculous!  Look advertisers. If you want my personal information, ask me for it. I'm more than happy to cooperate. In fact, I enjoy filling out surveys and giving companies feedback. Furthermore, I hold companies that do this in higher regard than those that go sneaking around behind my back, gathering data the way dogs dig through garbage. Spend less money on advertising and more on making good products! I promise you, if the product is good it will sell itself.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink   urlLink   urlLink   urlLink  Everyone knows I play backgammon. Everyone knows I like computers.  There was an  urlLink article in Discover  a few years ago about computers playing board games. The subject is always near the front of my mind as it often comes up in backgammon -- how well does the best computer play? In backgammon, the top computers play  almost  as well as the top humans. Almost, but not quite. Now, this Discover article is about six years old, but not much has changed despite the fact the computers have gotten more robust.  This all grew from a post in Wired News about IBM's new computer that's as  urlLink fast as a human brain . From there I took a leap to a discussion on  urlLink Deep Fritz vs. Vladimir Kramnik , which, for what it's worth, finished in a 4-4 tie. Then, the last line in  urlLink another article  brought me full-circle, and thinking about  urlLink Marion Tinsley and Chinook . I also looked at  urlLink this article on Tinsley  from the American Checker Federation.  Look, I like genius, okay? I'm attracted to it, and it doesn't show up often enough. When I read about someone with an incredible gift, I am enthralled by it. Every day we're faced with issues of so-so people in a so-so world making hideous mistakes and acting completely foolishly. People like Tinsley remind me that there is a remarkable depth to humanity; a hidden depth, sure, but one we do catch glimpses of occasionally. It's a reminder that although we may not be on the right path as a race, there is always hope for the individual. And maybe, one day,  urlLink these people  will change the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wired 10.12: God Is the Machine 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wired 10.12: The Pope's Astrophysicist 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Raving lunatic walking down the street talking to himself: unacceptable.  Raving lunatic walking down the street talking to himself while holding a cell phone: acceptable.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      You know, last night I read an  urlLink interesting article  in Wired news, about the effects, if any, of prayer on the physically ill. It's well written and a good read, but most fetching was this paragraph:   The time for miracles had run out on Elisabeth Targ. It was a scary moment for the uninitiated, her lungs suddenly gasping for air, trying to hang on, hyperventilating, nearly barking, spasming for more than half an hour. But this literal last gasp is how most die, and Comings knew this, so as he held her in his arms he felt relieved that she would soon be free of the illusion that is this world.   This is how my grandma died: a shell, empty inside, gasping for breath not through some desire for life, but because of an uncaring biological imperative. It was disgusting to see this woman who once spoke and laughed and loved reduced to this hollow automation. Thankfully, as in the article, it didn't last. How hard this must have been on Elisabeth's husband as he held her in extremis, torn between having it all mercifully over, and never, ever letting her go. And the worst part of all is that the article says, "But this literal last gasp is how most die." I'm sure it's true, but I don't want to believe that life is really so cruel.  There's a right to die rant in there somewhere, but I'm going to let it lie. This time.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, here it is: the first post in my blog. I suppose every blog starts out this way -- but believe me, I'm not going to be trite.  With Colleen attending Westerns as SEDA's adult delegate, I was forced to take her place on the radio today. I was on CJTR 91.3, Regina Community Radio, talking about SEDA on CultureJam. Colleen said, "You've been here a long time, you know what the deal is. You'll be fine." And, you know, yeah, I have been here a long time, and yeah, I do know what the deal is, and yeah, I was fine.  However, fine is always the bare minimum in my life. To be worthy, everything I do has to be exceptional. And although I was able to reasonably hold my own on CultureJam and fill in the general public on what SEDA is all about, there was an aspect of this that left me feeling uneasy. I wasn't able to put my finger on it until I was driving back to the office.  There is a subtle art to the deflection of questions: that is, giving an answer without answering at all. Some debaters are inherently good at it, and it's one of the skills that debate develops. Colleen, as a former debater, is good at it. Deron, as a non-debater, needs practice.  As a for instance: I was asked if SEDA also involves groups other than students in our programs. I responded that we don't currently have anything set up for adults who wish to debate, or other similar groups, but that being involved with students through the school system is the most effective way to reach the largest number of people with our organization's resources. That was good! Later on, I was asked how one of SEDA's debaters placed at Worlds. As I didn't have that information with me, and I had no idea, I said that I didn't know. That was bad. Better would have been that I didn't know, but that attending Worlds alone showed the amount of effort and dedication he had put into his activities.  Answer without answering. I'll work on it. The important thing is that next time I will be all the better.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm still around, not to worry; the holiday malaise has not claimed me yet. But this will be my last post before heading home for the holidays. The reason for my absence is that I was slowly working on a story -- I have this theory about all blogs heading toward a state of prose. But as it's currently in a state of limbo I thought I'd make what might be my last post of 2002.   urlLink Dr. Laura's mom died . Dr. Laura was estranged from her mother for a number of years -- he mother's choice, she says -- and her lack of a family life was one of the reasons she pushed so hard for family values.  There are other ways to look at this, of course: Dr. Laura's lack of a traditional family unit didn't prevent her from reaching success, such as it is. Perhaps appropriate role models and the proper spin of life's ups and downs are more important in the long run? An older, wiser confidant shapes a younger person into a responsible adult?  A topic for another post, probably. But the topic of this post is that some of us get the choice to spend the holidays with our families and some of us don't. Some of us like spending the holidays with our families, and some of us don't. But it's great to be able to have that kind of choice, and it's awful when we yearn so strongly for what we once had.  Yeah, I don't really savour the idea of spending the holidays with my family. But really, things are not that bad. I, like everyone, should try and keep this in perspective.  Signing off of her show, Dr. Laura said: "I just want to remind you as I do all the time, hold your family very tight, very close and very dear and don't sweat the petty stuff -- the bad stuff is bad enough."  Finally some good advice from the woman.  Happy Holidays.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Before I forget again, I wanted to post something on God-given talents.  I have an acquaintance who raps. He also happens to be a Christian fundamentalist and, oddly enough, he raps about God. This is fine -- whatever makes his bed rock and all that -- but I have to wonder what's going through his head while he raps. Does he feel God's spirit moving through him? Does feel that he's going to convert someone to Christianity through his rap? I joked with a friend one day, "You know, I've been an athiest all my life, but your rap really changed my mind." I seriously think he's waiting for this scenario to play out. I expect him to say that his rapping talent is God-given.  So this got me thinking about what exactly is a God-given talent. Does rapping even qualify? If so, what about a talent like walking and chewing gum? What if I was the best there ever was at walking and chewing gum? I've logged thousands of miles walking and chewing gum, and I've never slipped, fallen, gotten out of step, spit out or swallowed my gum, or forgotten to chew. I'm just hoping that my God-given walking and gum-chewing talent will show people the light.  What if I could point out physical or mental flaws with people? Is that a God-given talent? What about the ability to steal anything and not get caught? What about if I was able to kill people better than anyone who's ever lived? Would God grant someone such a dark blessing? What exactly qualifies?  The answer came to me as I was stuffing envelopes, of all things. It all ends up being a matter of perspective. Walking and chewing gum may not be a God-given talent, but perhaps dexterity is. Rapping may not qualify, but maybe eloquence does. As for the darker gifts I alluded to, there may be aspects like insight, foresight, or intelligence inherent in any of those "skills" -- these are the qualities may be God-given, but it's how you use your talents that's important.  And anyway, it all remains a matter of perspective: you see what you want to see. "Wow! His rap is amazing! Only God could create such an awesome ability!"      or "Oh crap, here comes that rap guy again. I'm sure the devil put him here to annoy me."
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I've got to start being less self-conscious about what I'm writing. Maybe this blogging thing, like all things, just comes with time.  I'd like to take a moment to share a joke that I love, but no one appreciates:  A man goes up to a cabbie in New York City. "How do you get to Carnegie Hall?" he asks. "Practice," says the cabbie.  Today I was leafing through what I believe was the October 2002 issue of Rolling Stone. Inside they had a brief review of Kurt Cobain's diary. The review is positive overall, and they share a few tidbits about the content -- one of them being that he consistently misspells heroin as "heroine".  A few things ran through my head as I read that. Firstly, I largely regard gross misspellings as a sign of intellectual weakness. But this is Cobain we're talking about -- maybe not the sharpest knife in the drawer, but certainly no idiot! My second thought was that maybe I was being too hard on the guy.  But, you know, I'm not. Language is a tool for effective communication, not a method whereby you should cater to the lowest common denominator. Sure, even with the worst misspellings and punctuation, you can certainly get the gist of whatever it is someone is trying to get across. But I don't believe we should continue to settle for the least possible effort. I don't believe that we should continue to let the bar be set at adequate. I believe that we should strive to do our best, and I believe that we should attempt to use language to communicate to the best of our abilities -- if this means looking up a word or two in the dictionary that we feel we may be misspelling, so be it.  I tend to be a stickler about such things. I want to write well and I want to speak well, mostly because, like everyone, I wish to be understood. I recently met someone who is as much a stickler as I am, and whenever she points out one of my mistakes I am mortified. I don't want to be branded as an idiot -- but then again, by blogging isn't there a danger of branding myself?  There is a reason that Shakespeare has lasted so long, why his works resonate so well with people of different ages and backgrounds: he was able to take mere language and elevate it to an art. He was able to string words together to describe thoughts and feelings that were previously only vague terms and wild gestures. He showed us that, although it's nothing more than a system of mutually agreed on sounds, language can be beautiful. Forgive me if I respect the man and his medium. Forgive me for wanting everyone to be beautiful.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      It occurs to me today -- just now -- that this blog is me.  I looked into the history of Weblogs and found that a lot of them were originally social commentary or discussions and opinions on certain Websites or the state of the Web. Since they've gained popularity they've become more on-line journals than alternative news sources.  I didn't want to stray too much from the original formula. I mean, I'm fairly old-school, I don't really need to keep a journal of my thoughts, and really, there's more than enough Web content out there to satisfy even the most die-hard pundit. But the problem was that this blog, like most things in my life, lacked focus and direction. I wanted to talk about issues important to me, but I wanted to look at them from a third-party perspective. And that just wasn't working.  This blog is me. This blog is my life, my opinions, my commentary. It's time I took the reins. As Cameron said in  urlLink Ferris Bueller's Day Off : "I am not going to sit on my ass as the events that affect me unfold to determine the course of my life." Word, homey.  So I'm reading in Wired News about  urlLink World AIDS Day and the Link and Think campaign . I think it's a marvellous idea. Although everyone is familiar with AIDS few stop to actually measure the social impact that the disease has. As has been said in more eloquent prose, these people are your brothers, your sisters, your parents, your friends. 42 million people is just a faceless number, but to put it in context is to clarify the awful power of this virus. Although I currently don't know anyone now who has AIDS, odds are strong that one day I will. If we want to stop the spread, education and awareness are our greatest resources.   urlLink A story referenced in the article  is a must read. It's well-written, heartbreaking, tragic, uplifting. A story of hope and salvation in the midst of despair. It's these kinds of stories we need to share. We need to put a human face on this monster.  42 million  people . Remember.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Funny, I thought my last post was also my  last  post; good thing I always have things to talk about.  I was at the library book sale today and I picked up a book called  urlLink God Doesn't Believe in Atheists  by Ray Comfort. I only got to read the first 16 pages during lunch, but it's already completely insulting to anyone who is actually searching for truth.  It occurs to me that the churchies have far more to gain than the atheists and agnostics. They move under this pretense of salvation, but really they don't want to be alone, like a child in the dark. The more people they can gather to their side of the argument, the less alone they feel and the more justified their position. Why do you think they always talk to you in greater numbers? I don't remember the last time I saw a parade of atheists and agnostics handing out tracks and warning people away from their freedom of religious choice -- and yet this is the same kind of hypocrisy we deal with all the time from religious groups. Where's the non-religious or anti-religious programming on Sunday morning television?  I was at home one day when the doorbell rang. Outside were two pretty young mormon women -- perhaps both looking for a husband, I couldn't say. Anyway, they asked me what religion I was, and I told them I was an agnostic. "So you don't believe in God?" the one said. "No," I replied, "I believe that the fundamental question about God's existance is unknowable. I'm sure they knew what an agnostic is, they apparently just didn't want to get into it with me -- which was a good choice on their part. The next day we found a little yellow religious tract in our mailbox telling us, essentially, that non-believers were going to hell. Again, this is an interesting tactic: if you can't strong-arm them, and you can't reason with them, scare them.  I'm not trying to say that my beliefs are right for everyone, or anyone, or even myself. I've had a progression of beliefs that have lead me down the road I'm on, and I'm sure they will evolve further. But I resent people telling me that what I believe is wrong when they themselves don't know any more than I do. I resent that my freedom of belief is infringed by these religious groups. I resent that I am asked to support my beliefs when I accept theirs unquestioningly. Spend your energy converting through works and example. Spend your energy caring for the starving and homeless. Show me how the world could be, and let the people come to you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's days like this that I feel I'm no longer living, only prolonging my agony.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      No matter how much you love someone, watching them slowly erode will destroy you.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You know it's love when there's only one wiener left, and you cut it up into  her  Kraft Dinner.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I want to write in my blog, but I really have nothing to say. Well, there's some relationship stuff that I was thinking of last night and this morning, but really, shouldn't I change tunes for a while? I mean, don't I have anything else to talk about?  Perhaps after my pita.  And you know, while I'm here, there's one great thing about these little updates -- seeing my blog on the Top Ten Recently Updated Blog list at Blogger really gives me a self-esteem boost. I wonder if anyone reads it?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes love is acceptance. Sometimes love is sacrifice.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      You reap what you sow. And you have to be so careful, because you never really know when harvest time is.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      If one goes on a strike at work, one stops working. But if one goes on a hunger strike, one stops eating. Where's the logic? If you're on a hunger strike, shouldn't you stop hungering? Instead of starving, you should stuff yourself with food at constant intervals throughout the day to avoid even the slightest hunger pangs! And why stop there? People hunger for all kinds of things -- sex, alcohol, money, etc. The you should be constantly satisfying these cravings immediately and fully, gorging yourself to gross excess on the object of your desires. Furthermore, as most old-style hunger strikes take place in public, yours too should be on full display! Let the people see what you are willing to tolerate for your beliefs!  I see only two problems. Firstly, it makes less of a political statement: eating chicken to stop human rights abuses certainly isn't going to make the front page. Secondly, people in North America act this way already.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Just FYI: based on an informal poll done this evening, male genitalia is, in fact, unattractive.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had today off, but The Boss phoned me at 9:00 this morning to talk about work. Which is cool, as I half-expected her to call. But we ended up talking about full-frontal nudity.  Last night, you see, I watched about three-quarters of the excellent movie  urlLink Quills  last night, which stars  urlLink Geoffrey Rush  as the Marquis de Sade. I like Geoffrey Rush; I've liked him since I saw him in  urlLink Shakespeare in Love . What I mentioned to The Boss was that he, Geoffrey Rush, seemed to be naked throughout a good part of this film.  "Ewwwwww!" she replied. And thus started the talk on full-frontal nudity.  Now let it be known that I am fully in favour of full-frontal nudity, of  both  sexes -- a little tat for tit, shall we say. The problem is that there aren't a lot of films where you get to see a naked man. An abundance of movies with naked women, but naked men are fewer and farther between.  This could be traced back to the movie industry -- men being the ones in power and all that. it could be traced to the movie going public -- it's not what the people want to see, etc. But really, I think it's traced to the male anatomy itself -- they're just not attractive.  It's not to say that men aren't attractive, because some men are. You look at these photos of guys like  urlLink Vin Deisel  in the shower and you can totally see how women find him attractive. "If I only looked more like that," you think, " then  I'd get the babes." But even then, with him naked in the shower, with rivulets of soapy water running over his glistening muscles, you don't get to see his... ummmm... part.  I think we should all face up to the fact that men just don't show that thing because it's not a good looking thing. Flacid it looks ridiculous, and erect it's something a guy can be proud of... but to everyone else it just looks silly. You can't continue to be Vin Deisel unless you've got a great looking package. You can't continue to be Tom Cruise unless you're hung like a mule. If you can't get a full erection, are uncircumsized, have some sort of warty disfigurement, or whatever, you're sunk.  But what about all the boobs? Well lookit -- guys are constantly searching out boobs anyway. Guys like boobs. Guys will go miles out of their way just to see a set of boobs. I mean, ladies, we're looking at your boobs all the time. They're already so prominent and on display, showing them sans clothing really makes little difference. And regardless, ugly boobs are still all right... but an ugly wang is horrible.  I'm not really sure if this was a lecture or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I never know how to end these blog posts, and I think I do so ineffectively; in the future perhaps I'll try punctuation and leave it at that.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      When you're eating in a Chinese restaurant, it's easy to tell when people are ready to order: they start playing with the chopsticks.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'd just like to point out that I said, more than four years ago, that Internet users don't like banner ads, but if we don't continue clicking on them we'll be inundated with more obtrusive forms of advertising.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Men are babies. Women are strong, because they have to be. Women do things that men could never bring themselves to do. When a woman lashes out it's usually not out of spite or malice, but because the load she is forced to carry has become too heavy to bear.  By the way, I think I may have to actually inject some humour into this blog, or I fear I will become  gasp  uninteresting! The horror!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wired News is running a three-part series right now on the newsgroup alt.suicide holiday, or ASH, as it's known. Apparently their "pro-suicide" stance has been linked to the deaths of at least 10 people.  urlLink Today's article  talked specifically about a guy named Michael Benjamins, now deceased, who was a frequent poster to ASH. The series deals with the theme of suicide being a valid lifestyle choice.  I read  urlLink part 1  yesterday and thought about it all night. I've lived with suicidal thoughts almost half my life. When I read about Michael and what he posted to ASH, in one sense I could really relate to him. People will always tell you things will get better  eventually , that life can be better with drugs and counselling. But when you haven't eaten in four days and the passing minutes are torturous in their length, and there's nothing that gives you even the smallest bit of solace or respite from the pain and lonliness, it's hard to listen to people who tell you that in a year you'll look back on this time and laugh. A year from now? I barely pulled my ass through  today , and only by sleeping for twenty hours. I no longer eat out of enjoyment or hunger or even habit, but because I force myself. The only things I think about are how cruel and unjust the world really is, and why the fuck aren't I dead already. People who regularly advise drugs and counselling haven't ever really reached that place where there's only emptiness, where you are truly and completely disconnected from everything there is. You have so little desire you can't even cry about it. You can't even speak. In fact, there's nothing you  can  do, because there is nothing you  want  to do.  I'm a firm believer that there are times when murder is justified. I also believe there are times when suicide is justified -- terminal illness, for example. And I've sometimes thought that there are some people who should not have been born. Some people are capable of coping better than others; some people are put off by even the smallest of life's disruptions. Maybe there are no easy answers when it comes to this subject. I think that, dispite my "illness", I have it relatively easy: I don't want to die. I've never attempted suicide, I've just often thought about how sweet a release it would be. But for me, hope does spring eternal. I have my troubles -- we all do -- but I also have my joys. And while I'd be willing to let go of some of them for a short while, in death you give up everything you've ever enjoyed. Forever. For me, it's too dear a price.  But is it for everyone? Is suicide a valid lifestyle choice? Are some of the people posting to ASH on a lark, not knowing there are people taking them seriously? Do drowning men really grasp at straws? I don't know. I don't know any of these things. I don't know if I should force someone to continue living if he or she truly wants to die. All I know is that when I read Benjamins' final post on ASH, I wanted to embrace this man. For his comfort or my own, I could not say.   "I want to thank all of you Ashers for being my friends in this last month. Here I was able to talk about my feelings and plans without having to fear the repercussions. I do not think I could do that in real life. I have been in a mental ward before, and I do not want to go back.  "None of you really knew me as a person, other than through my posts. That's good. I kind of wanted it that way. But at the same time, I want you all to know that I am ... I WAS ... a living, breathing human being. Someone with an identity and dignity, who wanted only to be free of depression, to be loved and to feel safe.  "I am Michael Benjamins. Born March 19, 1976. An artist, cat-lover, computer programmer, and thinker, who had a tendency to wear all black clothes. I tried my best to be a decent person....   "I hope you all find peace and happiness."    (abridged from  urlLink his post  on alt.suicide.holiday)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hiya. Been awhile.  My mind is swimming with recent events. My trials are far from over, but I'm pulling through as best I can. As always, I have done a lot of soul searching and may once again be moving in new directions. I find that it's always after these life-shaking events that you take stock of yourself. I still don't know if I measure up, but I do have some excellent friends that deserve my best. Thank you for everything, everyone.  Now, in spite of my foul mood, I need to put down some funny ideas I've had in the last few weeks.      Militia Ready:  much like Labour Ready, but for unemployed militia members. Any time you needed armed forces at a moment's notice you could just swing by in your pick-up truck or troop carrier, or maybe just phone and ask for ten men with guns to repel some foreign invaders.    Spamming With Spam:  I want to send cans of Spam through regular mail to random people in the city. Imagine their faces when they reach into their mailbox and pull out some Spam! "Great, now my mailbox is full of Spam too!"    Schizophrenia Society of Saskatchewan:  if you were to walk into the office, do you think you'd see staff talking to people who weren't there or answering phones that weren't ringing?     Also, go see  urlLink Cockeyed.com . It's funny.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have torn out my soul and put it on display, only to have it grow again within me so the cycle can repeat.  I put my soul into everything I do. But the world doesn't want souls, it wants flesh. Souls are intangibles; flesh is solid. Flesh has value. Flesh is something you can measure. Do the work of a hundred men and the world praises your abilities. Do the work of one man -- a singular work of genius and passion -- and you become a pariah, using far too much soul and not nearly enough flesh.  Back into your box, you! Back you go! We want consistency and productivity in this new world! We don't want design. We don't want differences. We don't want passion or life or any of those things that set us apart as humans. Run back to your sweatshops! Return to your factories! Pollute this world, destroy whatever doesn't fit, whatever takes you down, whatever is above you, whatever you don't understand. Club it down, beat it senseless; do not remove thine eye, but what offends it.  We're dying. And yet I wonder if death truly is the end, or if some will die more than others.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A three-year-old girl was sitting in the first seat of the bus this morning. The driver stopped to pick up two older women, and the girl watched with rapt attention as they walked by and found seats further down the aisle.  That's your future, kid, should you be lucky enough to live that long. The girl was unaware of this, however, and was probably more concerned with the ladies' coats or handbags, or just that they were different, and therefore interesting.  I wonder when it is that you get a grasp of your own mortality, and of the finite time you're allotted.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The reason you have laugh lines is because, as a child, humour is everywhere; but as an adult, you need to remember every one of your smiles.  I don't think I like this layout.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Too many people have no concept of their worth in this world.  urlLink She's one of them . Others would have me believe I am as well, but I feel they all severely overestimate me. A lot of the time I feel like costume jewelry, cheap iron rings covered with the thinest gold veneer.  Today, however, isn't one of those days.  Yet.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's not what you know, it's who you know. Never forget that. As long as you portray yourself as someone capable of learning the required skill set and have a wide range of social contacts, you can have any job you wish regardless of your educational background.  I think the upshot of this statement is that you should spend less time in school and more time socializing, perhaps at the bar or pool hall. Also, smoking seems to be a very social activity, maybe you should take that up as well. And since pot seems to be more and more acceptable, indulging in that once in a while seems like a good choice too.  Somehow, though, I don't see this looking good on a resume, or being endorsed by your Guidance Counsellor as a valid career path.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am not about to turn my blog into an  urlLink evangelizing  platform, but the more I use Windows 95, the more I realize it was created by a bunch of programmers expecting it to be used by a bunch of programmers. And don't forget, this was in 1995, when the Internet was gaining popularity and home computers had been a fad for at least 10 years.  Everyone who knows me knows I have a penchant for Apple Computers, and it's mostly because I was fortunate enough to be able to use one way, way back in 1985 at Microage in Moose Jaw. Look at that name: it's even before the age of intercaps. Anyway, the computer was completely unlike everything I knew about computers: stylish, innovative -- it had graphics! It had this little clicky-dooey called a mouse! And whatever you typed or drew on the screen  came out looking exactly the same on the printer!  Let's face it, it was a product that revolutionized an industry and literally changed the world.  Enter Windows 95. Objectively, Windows 95 is little more than a cosmetic upgrade to Windows 3.1, which is barely tolerable. But putting aside all the philosophical problems I have with Windows 95, what set me off today was the alert boxes. I was working in Excel and re-opened the same spreadsheet I was working on. A box popped up telling me that if I chose to re-open the spreadsheet it would erase all my changes. That's all good and well -- I mean, I knew that already. But when I thought about the box the message came in, I was struck with exactly how unwieldy these messages are: they're crammed into this long, skinny box in the center of the screen, in a single colour, with nothing to differentiate the options you're expected to choose from. The box should be  LARGE!  Expansive, even. The text should be big, spaced out for comfortable reading; perhaps even positioned so the choices are more obvious. This is the type of alert dialog you get in the Mac OS. The Windows alert is what you get from a bunch of programmers creating for public consumption: the bare minimum. And at that, it feels like an afterthought -- you get the impression that they'd rather just have the screen flash, or have the computer beep with a "Y/N" option appearing. I mean, real programmers don't need that kind of instruction, therefore no one does.  And looking a little deeper, this is typical of the kind of stuff you get from Microsoft in general: shoddy design, minimal effort, bells and whistles hyped to downplay the shortcomings. Windows 95 is hard to use and forces the user to adapt to its eccentricities. But I guess you can use anything as a hammer, if you need to.  Now, detractors will tell me that Windows has come a long way since Windows 95: look at Windows 98, for instance, or Windows Me, Windows 2000, or Microsoft's latest and most dubious achievement, Windows XP. Yeah, all right, I concede. Windows  has  come a long way. But by the same token, typing monkies can eventually turn out Shakespeare, and I imagine it would be much easier if they had a good template to follow. Further, the idea of the GUI was invented in the 70's and has been stretched almost to its limit: there's not a lot of innovation left in that area.  The question I wish to pose, though, is not about the similarities between Windows and the Mac OS, but why the public would adopt a ridiculous, unintuitive, backward product when a clearly better alternative already existed?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Blogger's urlLink   Blogs of Note is always a good read. The blogs they list there are always of a high quality (higher quality than mine, anyway), even though sometimes the content is... well...  urlLink more suited to a vertical market .  Anyway. Today I was reading  urlLink Anne... Straight From the Hip . She's a deliciously good writer, each word like a summer apple freshly fallen from the tree. But what prompted this post was not her writing style, but her comments on depression. Is it just me, or is it that all of the good blogs -- all of the good writing -- comes from the ones who have been tempered by life's fires? I also picked up  urlLink Who Has Seen the Wind  today; I don't know if that fits into this post or not. It probably does, I just don't know it yet.  I should write more. Maybe we all should. Blogging ourselves toward a collected consciousness.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So lemme get this straight: Adam and Eve were created without the knowledge of good and evil, but gained that knowledge from eating of the Tree of Knowledge of Good and Evil.  I wonder if they ate from the Tree of Knowledge of Effective Gardening Techniques too, or the Tree of Knowledge of Small Engine Repair. It's a cinch they didn't eat from the Tree of Knowledge of The Ancient Art of Self Defense, or God would have had a harder time evicting them instead of just pointing a finger and shouting "Begone!" He probably hid that tree way in the back, behind the Tree of Knowledge of Victory Through Passive Resistance, or the Tree of Knowledge of How to Piss Your Creator Off in One Easy Step.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
        "Current estimates place the world's population at six billion people. The pile of pennies above would then be nearly enough for two pennies for every person on Earth. The U.S.Mint currently manufactures about this many [10 billion] pennies every year."  --  urlLink The MegaPenny Project     Perspective. Something I'm lacking, something I think maybe a lot of us are lacking. While I don't want to believe that these quotes at the top of my entries have any bearing to the content of the posts, this one might be a notable exception.  I released two books on BookCrossing.com today: two copies of  urlLink Homebody  by  urlLink Orson Scott Card  that I picked up at the RPL booksale. Why two copies? I purchased one copy, then, apparently, purchased another a few days later. This is something that I rarely do. I normally have excellent recall as far as books I own, but Card and I have something of an odd relationship. I tend to think that his books come into my life at the most appropriate times, and I'm unsure whether the mistakenly purchased second copy of Homebody can be chalked up to mere coincedence. When I bought  urlLink Ender's Game  in 1999, the phrase  when the student is ready, the master will appear  was embedded in my mind since the moment I rose from bed that morning. It ended up being one of the best novels I've read, and for weeks after that everything in my life fell wonderfully into place.  Enter  urlLink Treasure Box . It was awful. I wish I could say it has some profound impact on my life, but... no. Rather, the only thing I retained after reading it is a note in my book log and my disappointment that Card would ever reduce himself to such tripe. Of course, I was reading this book at a dark time in my life, and I've always wondered if that lack of light made it harder for me to find the meaning behind the words.  I finished Homebody on Saturday. Again, not at the level of Ender's Game, but it certainly did have some good parts to it.   "When she moved into that room it would no longer be his. He would knock at the door if he wanted to speak to her. If she invited him in then he would go, but as a visitor. That was the way of it, for a builder like Don. You made beautiful spaces, you built with your whole heart, and then you invited someone else into the space you had made and gave them the keys and locked yourself out of it forever. But you were still there, that was the secret. Don was still there in the houses, watching out for the people, enclosing them, sheltering them. He was still there, soothing their eyes, stilling the sounds of the outside world, framing their lives so that all their dreams could be contained in a place where they had only to reach out and touch them and they would come to life again."    I related a lot to the Don character in this novel, and not only because he was brooding and distant, and not because he was either afraid or unwilling to open himself to other people. I connected with this character because of things like the line above, because he created things, and he did it with energy, and vigour, and soul. It's the person I   want   to be. We have a national-level event coming up in less than two weeks, and part of the work I do will be preparing the materials that go to the delegates. It's not quite the same as building a house, but it's still the basic kind of framework. One person will keep their materials in a shoebox on their bookshelf and revisit them from time to time, someone else will ditch the solid stuff and only keep the memories of the event: the places they visited, the people they met. Either way, this event will stay with these people for a long time, and I want it to be comfortable, and solid, and   right   to them, just as Don's houses were built to be homes.  Now, a lot of this goes unfelt and unnoticed. The building contractors and engineers know if you've done a good job, and you yourself know where you've cut corners. But the average person doesn't see the creation process, doesn't see the late nights, the anxiety, the sweat, or the tears, they see only the finished product. It's hard, sometimes, knowing the amount of effort you've put into something, and knowing how it will never be fully appreciated.  But we should   try   to appreciate it. We should slow down sometimes, pull ourselves back and try to see things in a different way. Ever notice how fluid our movements are sometimes? How your arms or legs or fingers just natually seem to be in the right spots at the right times? Tying your shoes is a delicious feat of dexterity, yet most adults perform it without a second thought. Remember how frustrating it was when you were three? How you would practice but you were all thumbs, and you would wear the uncomfortable shoes with the velcro straps so you wouldn't have laces to tie. Now, grown up, you do it unconsciously. Most people don't even think about the shoes they're tying until after they have them on. But at one point you chose your shoes carefully, focusing yourself tightly on the task, hoping that this would be the time you got it right.  Reflect on the little things and the big things in your life. Remember the way things felt and contrast it with how things are now. Think about things in odd ways, ways that make you appreciate your thoughts, your actions, all the underlying effort that makes the world what it is. Think about 16 pennies to an inch. Think about ten billion pennies filling a football field every year. Think about the one who chose a particular font out of 2000 others and why, and think about the builder who fastened a nail three inches off-center so you could have a place to store your memories and live your life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "It's about a hard-drinking yet loving family of soccer hooligans. If they're not having a go with the birds, they're having a row with the wankers." --  urlLink Homer Simpson, describing the sitcom 'Do Shut Up'   So my friend Sam had a birthday this weekend. It's hard for me to believe that he's already one year old. Unfortunately I was busy this weekend and missed his birthday, but I don't think he'll be all that stressed out about it. Jerry Seinfeld said once that your first few birthdays and your last few birthdays are much the same: you have to be told it's your birthday, some people have gathered that you're told are your friends, and you need help blowing out the candles.  It's hard shopping for someone who's one. Everything I looked at had the Telletubbies on it, or Barney, or something equally as insulting to his intelligence. I eventually bought him a card with the least amount of writing on it (Outside: "Hi!" Inside: "Happy Birthday!"). I feel, however, that he deserves a little note from me on this milestone, so that completely negates the lack of text on the card. I'll make sure to point out the irony to him, though I don't think he'll get it. He's more into physical comedy right now.  Tomorrow I'm going to try and find a stuffed animal for him. probably something non-traditional, like a bird, or an elephant, or a buffalo. One of the reasons I liked Beanie Babies so much was the abundance of non-traditional animals -- then they found out they could be making a lot of money off bears, and... well, we all know what happened. Anyway, I had a giant stuffed frog when I was growing up, and I loved it to pieces -- anyone with no imagination can love a teddy bear.  My uncle Monte (I always take the time to point out that his full name is Monte Cristo -- no shit!) turns 50 today. He had a stuffed dog with a rubber head when he was growing up, and my grandpa -- his dad -- still has it. Nearly fifty years old, well loved by more than one member of our family, and still going strong. I doubt that today's toys are made of such stern stuff, but I like to believe that Mont looks at that dog every so often and thinks about how important it was to him when he was younger. That's the kind of gift I'd like to give Sammy on his first birthday. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Listen, anybody that can talk clean can talk dirty. Dirty talk is just like normal talk, except dirty. Your wife wants dirty talk, so give her dirty talk. Something like, 'Those breasts are first-rate,' or 'I am going to give you a darned good orgasm,' or, if she likes the rough stuff, 'I'll tell you this, I am about to give you the business and I don't want to hear any guff about it.'"  --  urlLink Sex Tips from Donald Rumsfeld   When I said I might add this feature to my blog, I meant the funny quote, not the music on the crotch. Besides, the only song I can play is Ol' Susanna, and while it's catchy, I don't think it's enough to get anyone off.  You may find that a lot of people are concerned about their personal space. If you end up standing too close to them at the bus stop, say, or in an elevator, you'll either get people shying away in an effort to preserve their personal space, or they may become belligerent, forcing you out of it.  I, however, am more concerned with my mental space. Whereas personal space is an area roughly a metre in radius from a person's body, mental space expands and contracts during the day depending on your location and the medium of information you're exposed to. Generally, your mental space is equal to the room you're occupying. Things like television and radio expand your mental space, as you're forced to interact with more people. If you're alone in your house, you are the only person in your mental space. If you're at a concert, sporting event, or something similar, your mental space is filled with hundred of other people.  This is the crux of the mental space concept: while you can choose whether or not to allow people in your physical space, you can rarely choose to not have someone in your mental space. And just as some people don't like to be touched by strangers, there are people who don't like their mental space "invaded". But I believe that we are forced to develop a certain level of tolerance as we grow up, because our mental space will be filled daily with people we feel have no right to be there. It's just that some people will have more tolerance than others.  As with many things, I find the battery metaphor very useful here. Imagine your tolerance level being the charge in a battery. As undesirable people come into your mental space, the charge decreases; if the charge gets to zero, or appreciably close, something bad happens -- you blow up, swear, become violent, burst into tears, or whatever. Essentially, you revert to some mode of protective behaviour that allows you to stop the drain of your battery in the quickest, most effective way. Then you begin recharging your battery, until the next draining episode. It's always about give and take, isn't it? 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      " urlLink It plays music on your crotch. " One of the more interesting quotes I've ever read. I may add this feature to my blog.  Last night I went to a body building competition my friend Colin was entered in. It was an interesting event -- at four hours, it did drag on a bit, especially since you can only see so many guys flexing their abs before they all start to look the same -- but all the same, it was a  very  good time!  One thing I found out is that body building is like any other sporting event. Spectators are encouraged to cheer on their favorites, and many of the competitors -- if not all of them -- feed off the crowd's enthusiasm. I felt bad for some of the people near the end of the show because it was obvious that the crowd was getting restless, and the level of excitement was waning. One guy walked off stage shaking his head as though he had not done as well as he expected. But it was just the crowd, guy! Just the crowd! If there's a lesson here, it's definitely not to judge yourself on other's opinions -- it's the adjudicators that matter, not the audience.  I was people watching before the start of the show, and I commented on the level of narcissism present. I suppose that birds of a feather do flock together and all that, just like you'd expect few whites to show up at a black power rally, or few illiterates to be a poetry reading. Just the same, nearly all the men in the audience were huge and muscular, and a good part of the women were tall, skinny, bleach-blondes with big, fake boobs. Not that I have much of a problem with this, but my knee-jerk reaction is to equate this kind of behaviour with a level of insecurity -- are you really so displeased with your looks that you have to enact such radical changes? And must you date someone searching for the same kind of outward security? Isn't it truly the inside that matters, or are looks really all that's sufficient for some relationships? Are these people really happy, or are these relationships time-sensitive, being relegated to the garbage as the years pass? It's hard for me to say, but I'm a firm believer that personality trumps everything, and I have my doubts that the beauty of those people was anything more than skin deep.  Once the competition started I found myself riding the energy level of the crowd. I was shocked at the level of support these people had for the competitors. It occurred to me that body building is the same kind of event as any other, but it's slightly more personal as you're not just putting your skill on display, but your body as well. By allowing yourself to be objectified in this manner you're opening your entire self up to inspection -- your level of training, your posing routine, and, inevitably, your body. A pianist, for instance, is not judged by how big his head is, or how much weight he carries; but body builders are judged on many fronts, leaving themselves open to a fuller defeat. It takes a special kind of person to get onto that stage, and I'm curious to know what it is that would drive a person to those lengths, and what it takes to psych themselves up.  Several things did show clearly from this competition. One was the camaraderie of the competitors: it was friendship borne through war or intense competition, where they've all been through the same training, the same preparation, the same intensity. They had all shared the same experiences, and although there was no quarter given in the competition, there was a level of respect for each other that was never breached, even during the two unfortunate incidents when the crowd openly disagreed with the judging. This attitude came through especially strong during the pose-offs, where the competitors got a chance to expose their personalities and play off the crowd and each other.  There was also a strong feeling of accomplishment present, even among the people who didn't win awards. All the competitors were proud of their work and their trials. This, for me, was the most satisfying part: knowing that, win or lose, the people present had achieved the goals they had set. When I talked with my friend Colin after the performance, he was glowing with happiness, and I was so very proud of what he accomplished. At 52, he was competing with many people less than half his age. In the Masters category (age 40+), he placed third of three; in the Middleweight category he had much stiffer competition, but much to my surprise and delight, managed a second place finish out of seven people. That was definitely the highlight of my evening.  I think I learned a lot about body building by attending this event: it's not just a bunch of brainless, self-obsessed people showing off their bodies for their own satisfaction and the delight of people who enjoy watching these kinds of things. Rather, it's just as intense a level of training and competition as any other sport, and the people are as friendly and appreciative as anyone else. I don't think it's something I will find myself doing anytime soon, but Colin waited until his fifties -- I have plenty of time to change my mind.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink It's funny 'cuz it's true .  Why does the world suck like a $200 hooker?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I should wait to post until I read all of my daily news, but it's important that you read  urlLink this story  abut the death of a cameraman.  Look, war happens. Sometimes there's no way to avoid it. But by God, we should  try  to avoid it. At all costs.  War is rarely a case of "us versus them", and with the advent of the Internet we are putting more of a friendly face on even the most unfriendly people. In WWI there was a similar problem with the military brass needing to take the humanity out of the conflict: we're only human; it's hard to kill someone we know, but much easier to kill a faceless bad guy. Try as they might, the US wants us to believe that they're doing the right thing -- and maybe they are, in the long run, who the hell knows? But every person who dies in this conflict has a story similar to the one of this BBC cameraman: they all touch lives, they all have friends, they all lived and laughed and loved. Each individual had a store of knowledge and wisdom and experience that was suddenly removed and erased, like it never existed -- or wasn't meant to. It's unfair. It's unjust. It flies in the face of what we call civilization. It's a blight on humanity.  But maybe that's part of what humans are, really: vile, base creatures too content to remain in the filth, rather than try to lift their heads out. We gorge our appetites, we lust, we fuck, we belittle, tease, torture, and fight. We are all too quick to acknowledge our faults, but hide our virtues for fear of... what? Corruption? Or mockery?  It sickens me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I don't want to start jumping on every bandwagon I come across on  urlLink daypop , but  urlLink this is such an interesting story  I just have to share it. It's a shame, 'cuz he sounds like such a great guy, too.  While I'm at it, let me list my other new pastimes:   urlLink Utopia  A "rule the kingdom" game which is quite good, when the severs are running. I'm levendis of the province Nividian Steppes in the Kingdom of Ski (10:6).   urlLink Hattrick  Not a fantasy soccer league, but a virtual soccer league. It's very interesting, but the waiting between matches is interminable! I'm the manager of the team Militia Ready.   urlLink Paranormal Deathmatch  A rock-paper-scissors game where all you do is fight and collect money. My character is jbananapop. It's much more addictive than it sounds. Seriously.  It occurs to me just now that I need to get out more.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think that John Cusack is the new Kevin Spacey.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you out there in the blogosphere who don't know, we've had a bizarre snowfall in the last few days, resulting in drifts in some places up to my knees.  No big deal, you think. We live with snow in Saskatchewan at least half the year; we know how to handle it. But not so. The first thing that happens is that people start driving like they've never seen a winter before. No, it doesn't matter that winter just ended; people act as though any experience they had driving on anything but dry pavement has melted along with the snow. As a result, people get into accidents and get their cars stuck all over the place.  The second thing that happens is people can't remember what it's like to go outside. No, it doesn't matter that winter just ended; even though we suffered through weeks of -40 degree weather, asking people to go out in this relatively warm but snowy weather is tantamount to asking them to amputate a limb.  Look, I'm the first to admit that winter stinks, but cold weather or a foot of snow doesn't grind anything to a halt. Maybe I'm just looking at this from the wrong direction, but a few flakes -- or a few billion -- aren't going to stop me from going the places I want to go! If I want a burger then I'm hitting the drive-thru. If I want entertainment then I'm going to a movie. If I want sex then I might consider getting a hooker who delivers. But for God's sake, if I want out of the house then I'm leaving, and few things are going to stop me.  So I just can't understand these people who refuse to go out because it's too cold, or too snowy, or too rainy, or whatever. Do we really have it so easy that we'd all prefer to remain inviolate in our houses than brave the elements for some basic human interaction? The prairie settlers a hundred years ago froze to death in the darkness of their sod huts, and even then they went outside to milk to cows, feed the chickens, and slop the hogs. Somehow the people of today can't find the energy to use their command start, leave the house for the comfort of their pre-heated car, and then leave the car for the comfort of a movie theatre or coffee house.   I don't get it. Ya buncha freaks.  In other news, I'm going to revolutionize the fried chicken business: Deron's Drumstick Depot. I'm going to sell drumsticks in a tasty chicken coating similar to KFC. The difference is that instead of a bone, the meat's going to cling to a crunchier version of my batter. This way there's no waste -- you can eat the whole thing! Much like that soup in a bread bowl idea from Tim Horton's: "Today I had a drumstick for lunch -- and then I ate the bone!"  Actually, those cement-based candy sticks from Lik-M-Ade are practically indestructible, they'd be a good second choice if this batter thing doesn't work out.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
        I showed this card to a friend who said, "What the hell's in that bowl-- bong water?!" Is that why the ceramic animals are so drawn to it? Is it their magical pond?  --  urlLink Weight Watchers recipe cards from 1974     Well, I guess my writing on  Reloaded  gets to wait again. This is a treat -- excerpts from old e-mails, found while cleaning out my inbox. These are my  Lectures on Everything , aren't they? What the hell, I can put anything in here I want. And besides, I find that my writing always looks better in retrospect.    ...I want sex that's going to leave me bruised like ten rounds with a prizefighter. I want to vacuum scraps of my flesh out of the living room carpet days later. I want to find teeth marks on body parts I don't know I have. In essence, since sex and sexual desire are such base emotions anyway, I want to remove the higher mind from the equation altogether and just let the lower animal out to play. Raw, primal, bestial lust in its purest form.    ...we went out for a smoke between debate rounds, and I was talking to him about societal conventions and how I'm just not fitting in anymore. He told me he's becoming less eccentric in his old age. I told him that I'm becoming more and more eccentric, and furthermore, not only do I not care, but I'm giving free reign to my impulses. Now, none of this can come to any good -- but, you know, there are weddings at the legislature: people come in with their groomsmen and bridesmaids and professional photographers, and regardless of the fact that three other wedding parties had had their pictures taken in that same rotunda that same day, off they go to "immortalize" their "special day". I said that I thought it was all ridiculous, that I couldn't understand how these people could believe that they weren't having a real wedding unless it held all these trappings. He tried to pass it off as ritual, but I told him it runs deeper than that. People fall in line as they grow up, garden seeds planted row on row. Children are the ones who don't respect these boundaries, and that's where the truth lies. No one is better than children for broaching social mores -- they eat nothing but candy, pee their pants, yell and scream in public, have imaginary friends, play make-believe, and they even eat things that aren't food (or shouldn't be). As adults we have it all so ingrained into us that this kind of behaviour is wrong, we never stop to question whether it actually   is  . I don't know about you, but I am too big for society's "box". I'm like the bread dough you pull from the oven, much too big for the bowl and still rising.    ...arts and science gets a bad rap, you see, and I'm tired of it. Arts can be an academic career in and of itself, without being some crappy jumping point or, worse still, just a bunch of hoops you have to crawl through in order to get to "the good stuff". Look, man, pre-journalism means arts. Pre-med means arts. Pre-dentistry means... yep, arts. Just say you're in arts already. Who are you trying to impress? The people who don't know any better aren't really worth impressing, and the people who know better won't be impressed at all. So just suck it up, brother. "I'm in my second year of arts, and I'll be going into journalism."    ...let me help: I have money in my pocket, prozac in my backpack, wine in my fridge, and a hot tub in my yard.  I will use the money to fill your belly with food; the prozac to fill your brain with serotonin; the wine to fill your head with naughty thoughts; and the hot tub to fill the air with the scent of bromine.  Romance is dead.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
        "Johnny calls me 'da man!' That puts me at ease. It makes me feel comfortable, because I am Black and that's how Black folks talk to one another."  --  urlLink Black People Love Us     So here I am, a little later than I had hoped. I have now comfortably passed into the 34th year of my life. Today, like all days, was something of a struggle. Emotional ups and downs took me from laughing and lightheadedness to a withdrawn distance, closer to tears than to reality. And again, as always, truths emerged: I have good friends who care deeply for me; life never sucks nearly as much as we want to believe it does; and change comes from within -- but effort is the groom that mates with desire, and change is their offspring.  But I didn't want to write about my birthday. I wanted to write about movies and  The Matrix Reloaded , and how sequels rarely live up to the expectations placed upon them, and how commercials are tarnishing The Silver Screen, and how The Globe and Mail ruined the ending to  Reloaded  before I ever had a chance to see it.  But these thought will have to wait. It's late. I'm tired. And tomorrow is a big day; the first day of the rest of my life, you might say. So instead of insight, I provide you with what Yahoo! gave to me: a list of interesting events that share my most important day.  To my many, many friends: bless you all. I could never have made it this far on my own, and I certainly would not be here today without you. Thank you so very much -- not just for what you do, but for how you do it.   May 20, 2003    Thought For Today   "The more corrupt the state, the more numerous the laws."  -- Tacitus, Roman senator and historian     Birthdays  Rhythm and blues singer Naturi Naughton is 19. Actress Angela Goethals is 26.  Rapper Busta Rhymes is 31.  Rock musician Tom Gorman is 37.  Actress Mindy Cohn is 37.  Singer Nick Heyward is 42. Singer Susan Cowsill (The Cowsills) is 43.  Actor Tony Goldwyn is 43.  Actor John Billingsley is 43.  Actor Bronson Pinchot is 44.  Rock musician Jane Wiedlin (The Go-Go's) is 45.  Ron Reagan is 45.  Actor Dean Butler is 47.  Musician Warren Cann is 51.  Actor-comedian Dave Thomas is 54.  Singer-actress Cher is 57.  Singer Joe Cocker is 59.  Actor David Proval is 61.  Actor Anthony Zerbe is 67.  Actor James McEachin is 73.    This Day in History  On May 20, 1861, the capital of the Confederacy was moved from Montgomery, Ala., to Richmond, Va.   In 1506, Christopher Columbus died in poverty in Spain.   In 1861, North Carolina voted to secede from the Union.   In 1902, the United States ended its three-year military presence in Cuba as the Republic of Cuba was established under its first elected president, Tomas Estrada Palma.   In 1927, Charles Lindbergh took off from Roosevelt Field in Long Island, N.Y., aboard the Spirit of St. Louis on his historic solo flight to France.   In 1932, Amelia Earhart took off from Newfoundland for Ireland to become the first woman to fly solo across the Atlantic.   In 1939, regular transatlantic air service began as a Pan American Airways plane, the Yankee Clipper, took off from Port Washington, N.Y., bound for Europe.   In 1942, Glenn Miller and His Orchestra recorded "(I've Got a Gal in) Kalamazoo" at Victor Studios in Hollywood.   In 1961, a white mob attacked a busload of Freedom Riders in Montgomery, Alabama, prompting the federal government to send in U.S. marshals to restore order.   In 1969, U.S. and South Vietnamese forces captured Apbia Mountain, referred to as Hamburger Hill by the Americans, following one of the bloodiest battles of the Vietnam War.   In 1989, comedian Gilda Radner (news) died in Los Angeles at age 42.   Ten years ago: An estimated 93 million people tuned in for the final first-run episode of "Cheers" on NBC TV.   Five years ago: The House voted overwhelmingly to block future satellite exports to China. The government unveiled the design for the new $20-dollar bill, featuring a larger and slightly off-center portrait of Andrew Jackson. In Beverly Hills, Calif., Hollywood royalty bid farewell to Frank Sinatra, who had died almost a week earlier at age 82, in a private, invitation-only funeral.   One year ago: President Bush said he wouldn't budge toward easing restrictions on trade and travel with Cuba until Fidel Castro's government took steps to hold free and fair elections and began to adopt meaningful economic reform. FBI Director Robert Mueller said it was inevitable that suicide bombers like those in Israel would strike the United States. East Timor became the world's newest nation. Paleontologist and author Stephen Jay Gould died in New York at age 60. Veteran Los Angeles TV newscaster Jerry Dunphy died at age 80. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I find it hard to believe that it's been nearly a month since I last posted. It's not like I've run out of things to say, just ways to say them.  Anyway.  My birthday is rolling around in the next few days, but this year it's not looming nearly as large nor looking as menacing -- in fact, this year it's like an overly affectionate puppy that you can't shoo away. Or maybe like a comfortable sweater with a hole in the sleeve. Either way it's becoming almost tolerable.  Anyway.  When you're young, it's important to have  The Day Off  for your birthday: you're a special  person, this is your special day, and you shouldn't be required to do chores, let's say, or homework, or go to school. Invariably you have to, but if you got to choose a day to have off, your birthday would be it.  As you age, though, having your birthday off means less and less to you, even though the importance of your birthday may remain the same. The true sign of maturity is no longer asking for the day of your birthday off, but the day   after   your birthday.  It must be because you need less recovery time when you're little.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today I found out that  urlLink Lectures on Everything  is the first hit on  urlLink Google  for  urlLink Athiest Lectures .  I don't know whether to be honoured or correct my typos.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm buying a leaf blower next winter, so I can just blow a path to the bus stop.  Tamara's right, it makes no sense.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  certainly took me by surprise! Not   the   Christopher Taylor, but a good second, possibly.  I mean, the   real   Christopher Taylor is interesting, funny, and brilliant.  urlLink This guy  is like a clone who was left in the vat 30 seconds too long -- he's interesting and all, but he seems to take himself a little too seriously.  I bet he doesn't watch  urlLink Homestar Runner .
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "'Cuz every hand's a winner, and every hand's a loser, and the best that you can hope for is to die in your sleep."  -- The Gambler, by  urlLink Kenny Rogers 
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I said goodbye to my friend Rodney tonight, as he's decided to move with his job to Saskatoon. He's a great guy and I'm going to miss him terribly, even if it is only 250km away.  Rod provides me with hope that, regardless of my direction, I can still be successful. Even if I never find a career or a purpose, I can still be successful. I see a lot of myself in Rod, and I think that's why I enjoy his company. Him seeing himself in me, now that would just be flattery.  I'm meeting His Royal Highness, Prince Edward in the morning. Wish me luck.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "I got tired of not being able to make eye contact with these people. I thought, 'What skills could they have?' Holding a sign was an obvious one."  --  urlLink Andre Jehan, the owner and founder of Pizza Schmizza 
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This site  is worth literally hours of fun. I'm going to regret it in the morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I asked Tamara the other day if there were  urlLink Duke of Ed  award holders that haven't gone on to success. Like, are their award recipients who work full-time at McDonalds, let's say, or living on the streets.  "Not a chance," she said unequivically. "The amount of work the award holders go through, the efforts they've put in and the challenges they've overcome -- there might be some working at McDonalds if that's what they   want   to do, but there's no way these people have not moved on to success. There's no way."  It's exciting for me to look at the tools that today's youth have available to them, and how future success is quite literally within their grasp -- especially looking back from the perspective of a failed adult. But I suppose it's not too late for me, either.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Unfortunately, there were two farmers that heard, but they didn't realize he was in need of help. They thought he was fixing something. He realized that nobody was going to come for him, and he thought he'd been captured by a cult and he was in Mexico and they were preparing a feast and they were barbecuing meat -- but the meat was his hand."  --  urlLink Beverley Kanciruk, speaking about Abernethy area farmer Bruce Osiowy's ordeal 
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "I knew that nobody could say I didn't have a family. Canada has finally figured out it's unfair to deny this to anybody."  --  urlLink Robbie Kemper, age 11 
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "It depends on how much food you want Erin Weir to eat: if you don't want him to eat any, you order a sandwich and soup; if you want him to eat a little, you order a sandwich and fries; and if you want him to eat a lot, you order nachos."  -- Tamara Harder speaking on Erin Weir
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am hamstrung in my life by three things: my feelings of inadequacy, fear of the unknown, and dogged loyalty.  I also find it funny how quickly my mood can swing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I found a delightful way to make a bad first impression with a hideously low chance of redemption.     When introduced to someone for the first time, make note of their name.  For the rest of the day, refer to this person by a name similar to their real name. e.g. Jamie/Jessie, Darren/Darrel, etc. Be creative!  When they finally correct you, respond with, "Are you sure?" e.g. "Hey, ummmm... My name's Jeffrey, not Jerry." "Oh. Are you sure?" "Yes, I'm sure. Asshole."    Now go forth and reap the rewards of a bad first impression!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "The kid at the Trader Joe's looked strangely at the receipt, then back up at me, as if to say, "Are you really him?" I trucked out of there before he could ask, and in my haste to escape, nearly ran over an eight year-old standing in the doorway. I apologized, which was a dead giveaway, since the real Zeus would have just fried the kid with lightning. I'm such a fake Zeus."  --  urlLink The Credit Card Prank 
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Out of the way... FREAK!" "ARGGGH!"  --  urlLink The UNH! Project 
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It occurs to me that I like my women slightly overweight when they're younger and thinner when they're older. So I'd like to meet a nice girl at 20 and have her lose about a pound a year until she's 50.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Now the associations of homosexuals have a potent arm to obtain further concessions on the road toward full equality with married couples, including the right to adoption."  --  urlLink Karl Cardinal Lehman, on homosexual rights 
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So, I don't know what, exactly, that I've done right in my life, but I must have done something:  urlLink Ellen  just wrote me   the longest   e-mail ever about her summer holidays, and it was fascinating! The upshot of this is that I rate enough for an e-mail, which makes   me   feel pretty darn special, because   she's   pretty darn special. So thanks Ellen, you made my day.  Tonight, however, was less than cool. I spent the night with some friends at a hideous, no-frills nightspot called  The Warehouse , which, of course, I refered to constantly as  The Whorehouse .  I spent most of the evening wondering why I continue to go to these places when I obviously don't fit in. The abundance of shitty music did not at all make up for the overwhelming number of shitty people. The guys there -- without exception -- have only recently left the trees in favour of walking upright ("And cell phones," my friend Jacqueline mused. "They left the trees for cell phones."), and the women -- also, without exception -- were painfully vapid with a decided lack of original body parts.   You know, and there I am, being... well, me. I just don't thrive in that kind of environment. it's like being stuffed into an uncomfortably small container and being slowly roasted over the period of several hours. As it was, I sat with my back against the wall, had a couple of drinks, and suffered through the evening as best I could.    "Hey, man! Check me out -- I'm wearing a ball cap!"  "Cool, man! I too am wearing a ball cap! Therefore, chicks will dig us both!"  "Hey, guys! Not only am I wearing a ball cap, but I am annoying all the ladies with my ridiculous dancing, not to mention my boob and ass-touching antics!"  "I, as a woman, am completely attracted to these microcephalic buffoons, as their ball caps proclaim them to be the most virile of their species." 
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Remember: for every inside there is an outside.  And sharks have the ability to turn their stomachs inside-out! How cool is that!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is the crux of friends and relationships, right here:  "Carrie, we like you. Fred, we like you too. Say, wouldn't it be great if Carrie and Fred got together?"  So you see, your friends are not trying to be a pain in the ass when they try to set you up with someone; they're only trying to put people they like togther. After all, Carrie deserves a good guy, and Fred deserves a good girl, right?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I wonder if I was put on this world for the people who "can't" or "won't".  Sure, they're viewed as more polite and all, but a lot of the time they just can't say the things that need to be said. Or won't.  That's where I come in. Most days I really don't give a fuck. I mean, I want to be an angel, I really do -- but sometimes someone's got to call a spade a spade, and it's usually me that's doing it.  I hope it's not bad karma.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "Seriously, I haven't had a boy in a really long time, and I'm really craving ... just a kiss, man. Just a kiss would be nice."  --  urlLink Britney Spears coming out about her virginity 
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      We bought some mini-donuts at the Dragon Boat races today. Everyone loves the mini-donuts -- there was a line of at least 50 people at  urlLink Lanterns on the Lake .  What is it about these mini-donuts that people like so much? What about a  maxi-donut  the size of a life preserver: would it sell as well?  I wonder if I could make any money selling Cheerios as mini-mini-donuts. There's a secret message in every bag:  oooooooooooooooo .
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tamara and I picked up our lanterns today from  urlLink Globe Theatre , for  urlLink Lanterns on the Lake  tomorrow. Now, I think I did a good job on my lantern, in spite of myself and my non-creative ways; it started out looking a lot like an  urlLink eggplant , but ended up looking like  urlLink something by Matisse . Tamara and I also won prizes, and we got our pictures  urlLink posted  on the Globe Theatre Website!  Tamara had quite a few people comment on her two lanterns; mine seemed to have been the red-headed step-child of the family, and mostly ignored. But here's where this is going: Tamara's lanterns are good, original pieces of work, while mine is a hodgepodge of ideas I shamelessly lifted from other lanterns at the lantern-making workshop. Not that mine's not original -- I made it, so it's original by definition -- but Tamara's are both somewhat better than mine, and I think her originality and creativity shows through.  I think people are mostly like me in that they're not very creative independently. They don't come up with good ideas on their own, but have to borrow and modify them from others. This is where fads are born: someone creative starts something which other non-creative people find interesting. Fads die when  someone else  creative starts  something else  interesting, and then we all follow along like sheep. If  everyone  had creative ideas in a consistent manner there would be fewer fads, as people would be too busy pursuing their own ideas. There would still be  some  fads, however, as some ideas would shine like brilliant lights from a distant mountaintop.  Y'know, like blogging, for instance. Everyone's got to get in on this.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "When I pull the string to make it talk, the results are muffled and unintelligible or make no sense at all. Is this supposed to be some kind of rotten joke on your customers?" &nbsp;--  urlLink Matt Little complains about the G.W. Bush action figure 
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'd better keep this thing updated; it seems that I'm becoming more popular. Not that I mind. I think I need to flex my writing muscles more often. I've been running again these last few weeks, it's a good idea to work my brain as well as my body. Though I don't think that blogging will hurt my head the way running hurts my legs.  The other day I wrote letters to  urlLink Kraft foods  and  urlLink Diana Sauces  thanking them both for making such marvellous products. In Kraft's case I was referring specifically to  urlLink Bull's Eye Hot Southern Cajun Barbecue Sauce . That barbecue sauce has spoiled me for all other barbecue sauces -- it's tasty   and   they've got the spiciness just right.  I know I can't speak for everyone -- though I try, I do try -- but it seems no one can get the level of spiciness to the place where I want it. Oh, they reach for it, but they all, without exception, chicken out right near the end. "We don't want to offend our customer base," they bemoan. "No one really wants something that spicy," they say. Those shaggy grey-beards, dragging their limp members, clucking their tongues, they've forgotten what spicy food was supposed to be.  Well   I   want something that spicy. I want a sauce so hot that it was shat from the Devil's own bowels. I want my head to burst open on the first bite and have molten lava run streaming down my face. While the Hot Southern Cajun sauce isn't  quite  that hot, it's still got enough of a kick to it that I  know  they had it higher and backed it off a little. They're not afraid to push the envelope, and that's enough to earn my respect.  Now, the  urlLink Station Place  in Saskatoon makes   incredibly   hot chicken wings. And  urlLink this story  is pretty funny too.  I've also tried two of Diana Sauces marinades -- Steak Spice and Lemon Pepper -- and both were delicious. Probably good enough to drink straight from the bottle. In this case, the  meats  compliment the  sauce . The day after we barbecued steaks using this marinade, I wanted more so badly I wanted to just open the fridge up and tip the bottle back. Maybe they make it with crack instead of cracked pepper.  I'd like to tell you all that I'm writing to these companies simply to be congratulatory, but that would be a half-truth. I'm also writing because I shaved off a week's worth of facial hair (which really isn't much more than a day's worth) with my Mach III Turbo razor, and found the experience to be so delightful I was prompted to write Gillette, telling them of my experience. They, in turn, sent me a coupon good for $5 off   any   Gillette product. They suggested I try their shaving cream, but as I use  one can of shaving cream a year , and even at that,  not an entire can , I chose instead to give it to a friend who wanted a new razor.  Anyway, the moral of this story is, if you write letters to the companies of your favourite products, they'll send you stuff in return. The other, more subtler moral is that Deron shaves his patchy, slightly post-pubescent facial hair on an irregular basis, and it's impolite to bug him about it. He knows you will anyway, but it's still impolite.  Oh, and I didn't win on those Scratch Tickets either, Mysterious Stranger. But it's the thought that counts.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday I received a wonderful postcard from Tamara, who sent it during a short layover in Edmonton. It features a huge, red dragon hanging menacingly from some sort of scaffolding, with the words "West Edmonton Mall" written below. I don't know how this frightening, supernatural monster represents  urlLink the largest mall in the world  better than, say, the  urlLink Fantasy Land Hotel , or  urlLink the water park , or the  urlLink dolphin lagoon  -- I know I'd much rather be terrorized by a gargantuan, flying, fire-breathing lizard than enjoy myself  urlLink playing mini golf . Maybe this postcard is a newly hatched marketing plan --  West Edmonton Mall: when you're in the mood to be devoured whole by some of the scariest monsters on the face of the earth .  For those of you who don't know already, I collect tacky postcards. I have this theory that, for some reason, photos that would not be acceptable for display anywhere else will eventually appear on a postcard. These are typically from the last one or two shots on a roll of film -- the ones you get rid of haphazardly when you're in a hurry to get it developed. I have postcards of a man talking to a moose, two Cubans and a pig on a bicycle, sumo wrestlers wrestling (including a gratuitous sumo ass shot), and three Maritimers holding a fish. I have many more in storage, including a Sonny and Cher light switch cover (which is also a postcard), and the star of my collection, a 3-D postcard of the Pope that was sent to me from the Vatican! It's always good to receive a postcard, and it really brightened my day.  Today, however, I received an unsigned greeting card that was sent to the office. It was a  urlLink WWF  card featuring three happy brown bears on the front. Inside was written:   Thanks for being you &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;-- an unending source of enlightening wit...   Also enclosed were two $1  urlLink Scratch-and-Win tickets .  Everyone knows I'm in kind of a dark place these days, so this card was perfectly timed. I have a hard time with me; too often I expect more from myself than I can give. Anything short of the yardstick I measure myself with is woefully unacceptable, and as a result I constantly deride myself. My life is sometimes little more than blow after blow to my self esteem -- sometimes from others, mostly from myself.  But this card thanked me for being   me  . The person who sent it believes that, as Deron Staffen, I have some value. Too often we remember only the negatives and forget the positives; moments like this come like a warm fire and a friendly dog on a blisteringly cold winter's day. It reminds me to cherish and be thankful for what I have: friends, anonymous or otherwise, who appreciate me and my efforts, and want me to feel good about myself. The world is not as bad as I sometimes believe, and neither am I.  Thank you, Mysterious Stranger. Your card has made more of an impact on me than you may have expected. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There's a game show on the  urlLink Game Show Network  called  urlLink Friend or Foe , which I believe to be the most insipid game show in television history -- and this includes all those game show parodies you see on  urlLink SNL  and  urlLink MadTV , and those weird ones from other countries, too.  The show pairs two strangers who attempt to answer trivia questions, gaining money for each correct answer. At one point in the game the players go to what they call the "Trust Box", and are asked to choose either Friend or Foe. If they both choose Friend, the players split the money; if one chooses Friend and the other chooses Foe, the player who chose Foe gets all the money; if both players choose Foe, neither gets any money.  Looking at things probabilistically, there are four possible combinations of answers, each with an equal probability of .5: Friend/Friend, Friend/Foe, Foe/Friend, and Foe/Foe.  Let's suppose you choose Friend. Let's also assume that the total value of the money is 1, and that a portion of the money can be represented by a decimal (50% = .5, etc.). There is a 50% chance that your opponent chose Friend and a 50% chance that they chose Foe. If your opponent also chose Friend, you get half the money; if your opponent chose Foe, you get nothing. This makes your expected value for Friend:  50% x Half the money + 50% x None of the money, or (.5)(.5)+(.5)(0), or .25.  Now let's suppose you choose Foe. Again, there is a 50% chance that your opponent chose Friend and a 50% chance that they chose Foe. If your opponent chose Friend, you get all the money; if your opponent chose Foe, you both get nothing. This makes your expected value for Foe:  50% x All of the money + 50% x None of the money, or (.5)(1) + (.5)(0), or .5.  What all this means is that   in the long term   you are expected to receive about 25% of the money if you choose Friend each time, and 50% of the money if you choose Foe. It doesn't take a rocket surgeon to see that there is a distinct advantage to taking Foe.  What sets this game apart, though, is the point where you try and convince your opponent to choose Friend. A typical exchange goes something like this:   "Opponent, we played really well together during the rounds, and we deserve to both leave winners. So let's both choose Friend and split the money."  "Opponent, I agree with you, and as you know from my ridiculous financial statement -- which they shamelessly aired to discourage participation -- I need money like Pigpen needs a bath. I wouldn't be here without you, so let's choose Friend!"   I argue that a better exchange would be like this:   "Look Opponent, this game is fixed. Based on the math, it's definitely to your advantage to take Foe every time. But knowing this means I know you'll take Foe -- forcing me to also take Foe, and leaving us both penniless. I came on this show to win something, and I think it's better for both of us to leave as winners than as losers. Vote Friend and let's share the loot."   Having calmly explained that you understand the metagame and there's no way he can with without choosing Friend, you then have to mercilessly backstab your opponent by choosing Foe. You   have   to choose Foe every time, regardless of the impassioned speech you gave.  Friend leaves you playing the patsy to your opponent's unscrupulous behaviour. Foe leaves you looking like an untrusting asshole. It's an insipid show with a terrible premise and a talentless host. Game shows are supposed to be   fun  , for Christ's sake -- let's keep it fun and let everyone walk away a winner.  (Please see this  urlLink Wikipedia entry  for more information on expected value.)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Do you suppose the guy that does the movie commercials goes home and gargles with oven cleaner at the end of a long day at work? Or, like, scrubs the inside of his mouth with steel wool, trying to get the bad taste out?   "The best comedy of 2003!"  "Critics rave -- Ashton Kutcher gives an Oscar-calibre performance!"  "This movie will knock your socks off!"   We all know the guy wants to say:   "Look, I'm just doing my job, okay? I'm just thankful none of you know what I look like, because I'm sure you'd beat me half to death for these continuing falsehoods.  "Ashton Kutcher is a dumbass who got to where he is either on his back or his knees. He displays a level of acting talent only slightly better than that of your living room sofa. The film itself lacks any sort of plot or cohesion, but what it does have is an abundance of No Humour -- yes, even for an Ashton Kutcher film, this is the sort of bomb Iraqi weapons inspectors are hoping to find. You'd have a more satisfying experience paying a bitter Vietnamese fishmonger to pound bamboo shoots beneath your fingernails.  "The movie poster displayed outside the theatre is more entertaining than the movie itself. The film's dialogue has all the finesse of a dirty limerick, while the musical score easily doubles as a Turkish funeral dirge. If, somehow, you should find yourself attending this film without hope of escape, be sure to gouge your eyes out with the nearest sharp object, pausing only momentarily to disembowel yourself. The thoughts of your impending death will give you solace as the opening credits roll."   P.S. - this also applies to  urlLink Legally Blonde 2 .
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Man, you think   you're   pretty athi, don't you? Too bad I'm the   athi-est  !  The more references I see to this blog, the more misspellings I find.     urlLink Vin Deisel in the shower  (Vin  Diesel )    urlLink Athiest lectures  ( atheist  lectures)    But there have been some other properly spelled references too:     urlLink Full frontal naked men  (scroll down)    urlLink Body building boobs  (scroll down -- appropriate for me, no?)    urlLink Song about Sibbie  (scroll down)    In this case I don't think I need to take the bad with the good -- it makes me look like an idiot. Moreso.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I just watched an episode of  urlLink Guinness Records Primetime  where a guy flipped  urlLink Smarties  (not  urlLink Smarties ) off his ear into another guy's mouth. There was a burst of applause from the audience each time the second guy caught one of the Smarties.  I need this audience in my life -- they'll clap for anything! Imagine the burst of acceptance and self-confidence you'd feel if you had your own applauding audience following you everywhere you went!  "Look at the size of that poop!"  Clap, clap, clap!   "I just slept for 19 consecutive hours!"  Clap, clap, clap!   "I drank too much and threw up on my girlfriend!"  Clap, clap, clap!   "Hey, everybody! I'm going to jail!"  Clap, clap, clap!   The is probably a project for a  urlLink flash mob , or will become one. But seriously, maybe I should start applauding for everything anyone does. I mean, acceptance has to start somewhere, right?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Weir's the Beef!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Ashton Kutcher.  Okay, the backlash started already, but it still hasn't been publicly pointed out that his neck is thicker than his head. Shit like that was genetically selected against a million years ago. &nbsp;-- Number 13 from the  urlLink Unsexy List 
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh Faithful ReadARRRs, how I pity you -- waiting day upon day for a post to my blog like a child counting down to Christmas. Unfortunately, my plate has been licked clean: there isn't a scrap to be posted these days, and even my last sARRRving was lacking flavARRR. A trip to McDonald's would have been more satisfying; less filling, pARRRhaps, but more satisfying.  Friday was  urlLink IntARRRnational Talk Like a Pirate Day . I didn't get to do a lot of pirate talking, but I did get big laughs the times I did. Blogging about it today fits pARRRfectly with my tendency to jump on fads aftARRR they become unpopulARRR -- also explaining my acid-wash jeans and pog collection.  For next year, then: my  urlLink pirate name  is Mad Tom Rackham, and these  urlLink pirate jokes  from  urlLink McSweeney's  ARRR pretty funny.  Maybe tomorrow I'll want to blog about Debate Club, or something mARRRginally more interesting.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think that guys tend to grow more hair on their face as they lose hair on their head. It must be a verility thing: they're saying, "Ladies -- I might not have a lot on top, but I'm growing hair in places you've never even  seen  before!"  Of course, it might be that guys tend to grow hair in all kinds of weird places as they age. Maybe the chin is one of those places and they just get too lazy to shave.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I must -- simply   must  , I tell you -- post links to  urlLink PoliticalCompass.org  and  urlLink NationStates.net .  My political leanings can be found  urlLink here .  My NationStates nation can be found  urlLink here .  Sorry kids, not much more to say than that.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Why is it that good steaks are 'AAA', but good breasts are quite the opposite?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "The bogus bill -- the U.S. Mint does not print a $200 bill -- bore the image of President Bush on the front and had the White House on the back." &nbsp;--  urlLink Man pays for groceries with bogus bill 
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Does anyone ever stop to consider how funny the word  igloo  sounds? I know I don't.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I needed to phone this Nathan Lane dude today (no not   that    urlLink Nathan Lane , though it would be wicked awesome if it was), and I tried my best to sound oh-so professional. And, as I invoked the name in my  urlLink last post , I shall reproduce this phone call with exacting care in the style of  urlLink Homer Simpson :  "Hello Nathan Lane, my name is Deron Staffen, and I am a professional sounding guy. You can tell from my voice alone that I have all my clothing neatly arranged in drawers in my bedroom, and not strewn about the floor like I'm vainly attempting to hide a dismembered hooker. Why, I'm so professional sounding you think I'm wearing an Armani suit instead of worn out jean shorts with my underwear showing through a hole in the inseam. Listen to the dulcet tones of my ber-professional voice, and rest assured that, no matter the situation, I have it going on like Donkey Kong. I'm sorry that I didn't get to talk to you personally, but allow me to leave my professional-sounding phone number on your voice mail: you can reach me at 586-8914.   (overly long, pregnant pause)   Yes, well, it seems I stupidly gave you my  home  phone number instead of my work number, revealing that my entire professional image was as thin as Karen Carpenter after three weeks in Somalia. I will hastily try to cover my mistake by reminding you that I am employed with a non-profit organization, but it will soon become apparent that this is only because McDonald's refused to take me. As the damage is still not completely done, allow me to ramble about how you could phone me at my home if you so desired, as I rarely get phone calls due to my penchant to speak in the style of Nostradamus: lo, it shall come to pass, when the sun rises high in Virgo, a young man will call out in two voices, one false and one true; and a second man, who masquerades as one who has two lives, will hear both voices; and upon this listening the young man will have the head of an ass, and the tail of an ass, and will be an ass.  Soooooo... ummmmm... yeah. Please call me back. At work."  Also, September 2, 2003 marks my sixth year with SEDA. Happy anniversary to me!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am too self-centered.  I don't mean to be, but it's difficult, you know? This is   my   life, after all.  Hell, this is   my   blog, too.  So I'm walking home tonight and I'm approached by two gentlemen, one of whom claims to be deaf, and asked to fork over some dough so they can buy some grub.  The deaf guy hands me a note, which, in the spirit of  urlLink Homer Simpson , I will faithfully reproduce:  "Hello! Can you help me? I am get [sic] and I   mumble mumble somethingerother   $2 for   booze or chips or something, Jesus, do I have to beg   would be so happy because   my mother's dying in a ditch somewhere on the road to Winnipeg   at last. God bless you."  Maybe I'm just too tight with my cash; I mean, the thought of me telling them that I was penniless while I greedily clutched a roll of twenties the size of a pork roast haunted me all the way home. But that's part of the deal with money, I guess. I'd have had less of an issue if I knew where the money was going, and why they really needed the money.  urlLink The Homeless Guy  wrote once that you should   never   give people money, because it just goes to their addictions, whether it's alcohol, drugs, gambling, eating, breathing, or whatever. Some people will ask you for money so they can buy food, and they're telling the truth -- but it's only because they've spent their food money on cigarettes, or prostitutes, or  urlLink bum fights , or kitschy Star Wars memorabilia.  If I ever become a bum -- a prospect that's looking more and more likely as the days progress -- I'm going to be sure to produce an annual report at year end. That way, when people ask me what I'm planning on spending their money on, I can produced documentation showing how my annual expenses break down. "I see you went over budget in soft drinks and library fines, but you're under budget in clothing and sexual solicitations -- and your administrative overhead is practically nothing! You certainly know how to live like a bum -- here's a  urlLink finsky !" Other bums would quickly have to do the same or risk being shut out by the discriminating financial contributor. Of course, I doubt their annual spending will be as diverse as mine, so their budgeting will be much easier.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      $3.50/beer = a good price. $3.75/beer = a little high, but still acceptable $4.00/beer = quite high, but I'll pay it because I want a beer, damnit! $4.25/beer and up = whoa! Does it come with a blowjob?  whereas...  $3.25/beer = Great! $3.00/beer = I should come here more often! $2.75/beer = I've gone to heaven! $2.50/beer and lower = whoa! Do I have to   give   a blowjob? 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Boss and I were talking today about a certain debate club and the rapidly approaching tournament. She asked if they were bringing a team to the debate, and I stressed they were bringing   a   team. Then I quickly pointed out that I meant a single team and not  urlLink The A-Team . (And as an aside -- who the hell are  urlLink these people ? I mean, really, I don't see one angry, gold-laden, heavily muscled black man among them. And  urlLink German  can be a really funny language -- try reading the first few sentences out loud!)  One thing you didn't see a lot of in the old A-Team episodes is debate. Sure, you were always puzzled by the gang breaking Murdock out and back into the asylum every episode, and you laughed at B.A. being so scared of flying that they had to drug him, and you got to see insane military contraptions built out of pipes and an old lawn mower engine that could take apart a heavily funded squad of guerrillas, but you never,   ever   got to see the boys resolve their problems through any means other than brute force. Wouldn't it be cool to have a roving band of underground debate professionals waiting to be contacted by people in need? I mean, the whole crack commando unit thing has been done to death.  Hannibal would be the clever tactician with full knowledge of the many logical fallacies and how to guard against them. Face would be all style, moving seamlessly from persuasive speaking to dramatic monologue to emotional rhetoric. B.A. would ruthlessly tear his opponents' arguments apart, and Murdock would spin incredibly convoluted cases only he would understand. He   is   insane, after all.  "Help, A-Team! My landlord is raising my rent and I can't seem to reason with him!"  "A-Team, we need your help in deciding if vigilante justice is right for our city. Come quickly!"  "A-Team! My wife has been kidnapped by a South American rebel faction, and they're going to cut off her fingers unless I can present a coherent case against Lucas using Jar-Jar Binks in Star Wars Episode III!"  Wow, I think I've just written the entire first season! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today I was writing  North Battleford Comp.  and I mistakenly wrote  North Battleford  Cop  .  I think that would actually make a pretty good TV show.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       "We did not weave the web of life; we are merely a strand in it. Whatever we do to the web, we do to ourselves." &nbsp;--  urlLink Chief Seattle 
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Places I've puked:    Staff party   Toilet   Kitchen sink   Bathroom sink in department store   Garbage can   Greyhound bus bathroom   Behind a video store   On girlfriend (now ex-girlfriend, but not because I puked on her. Well, not   only   because I puked on her.)    Bonus marks for people who guess which times were due to illness and which to overindulgence.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Way, way back, when I was in university, I was in a deep, deep funk. Funky enough to want my life to just abruptly end, but not quite funky enough to take the necessary steps. Life was simply one weight followed by another, and another, day after day, never letting up. And I was so very tired of it.  Eventually, on the advice of a friend, I went to Student Health to see someone. I remember sitting in the waiting room looking at posters produced by drug companies, and thinking that some drug would be prescribed to me, and how the doctors were paid by the companies to foist these drugs on people, and how much of an assembly line it was: ailment-drug, ailment-drug, ailment-drug.  I wasn't feeling particularly down that day, or nervous, or uncomfortable. I was finally called into the examination room and the doctor, a wonderful woman in her mid-thirties, asked me what was wrong. And in response, I inexplicably burst into tears.  I remember how much I ached as it passed through me; I had never known how I really felt, what I had locked away inside, until that very moment when it all just tumbled out like a tangle of drunken gymnasts. I'm often reminded of the Zen saying, "When the student is ready, the teacher will appear"; I think I was just waiting for the right person to ask me how they could help.  I apologized for my outburst, and after some talking she put me on Paxil, the first of my on-again/off-again romance with antidepressants.  There are a few other things that I took away from my visits with this delightful woman who changed my life: she told me that, oftentimes, people on antidepressants feel "more like themselves"; I've found that it's very hit-and-miss. She also told me to read  urlLink The Celestine Prophesy  and Stephen King's  urlLink Insomnia , as "those guys really seem to know something the rest of us don't." And this, I think, she was right about. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I lost my job today. It was a great six years, by and large -- definitely more good times than bad. I don't know if I can ask for much more than that.  Sorry, everyone.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In regards to  urlLink Kathy Shaidle 's article on the  urlLink Dallas Morning News .   Dear Ms. Shaidle:  I don't know how to begin. As a very left-wing Canadian, I have some beefs with your column; as a Mac user, I respect your Mac.com e-mail address.  What to do, what to do. Well, I suppose even one of the Faithful can be lead astray every now and then.  What I have taken the most offense to is this business of your objections to M. Chretien's actions vis-a-vis the War on Terror. I believe that Canada had every right not to participate in any action the US had concocted; I'm sure you've read MichaelMoore.com and heard his blather about a fictitious war and a fictitious president -- and I firmly believe it's all true. Bush  was  given the office unfairly; reasons for the war in Iraq  were  falsified; the US had no business defying the UN (and the Geneva Convention, but I suppose that's still debatable). I am appalled by the actions of Mr. Bush and his cabinet, and as much as I have sympathy for everyone affected by September 11, the US is acting more like a schoolyard bully than the wiser, older brother we all look to as a role model.  Yes, a lot of Canadians hate Mr. Bush; a lot of Americans do too. But we hate Mr. Bush for losing his "family friend" Osama Bin Laden, and for "Freedom Fries", and for the Haliburton deals, and for "Bring 'em on", and for soft-wood lumber, and for declaring people carrying almanacs as a terrorist threat, and for closing the borders to Canadian beef, and for treating us as second class people instead of his largest trading partner, and for taking offense that we are a sovereign nation, and are allowed to make our own decisions regardless of US opinion. We, as a nation, deserve better treatment from our neighbours to the south; we deserve to be treated with the same respect we give, and so far in this presidency, we have not received this courtesy.  I would also like to comment on the content of your column, which was lacking. What was the point of it, exactly -- that you had hated the US at one point in time, but following 9/11 you now love it? Can you tell us why we would care to know this? Can you provide me with the reasoning that might also change my jaded opinions? It seems to me that this Op-Ed of yours is too little Op or Ed, and too much cheering on of the Bush regime. I read nothing more than "Rah! Rah! Rah!"; we have content requirements in Canada -- is it any wonder you had to reach into Bush's home state to get it published?  All the best to you and yours in the new year.  Sincerely,  --Deron Staffen 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was browsing through the  urlLink Internet Movie Database  after voting on  urlLink Hackers . I browsed my way through  urlLink Angelina Jolie's filmography  to  urlLink Winona Ryder's filmography  -- by way of  urlLink Girl, Interrupted  --  and clicked through to  urlLink Welcome Home Roxy Carmichael .  It was filmed in 1990. Winona looks delightful on the movie poster -- limbs somehow crossed and uncrossed at the same time, a pink dress neatly covering the proper places, big, black boots which are seemingly incongruous but somehow appropriate; this was before all the shoplifting charges and whatnot that stole much of her innocence, charm, and public image. I stared at the poster and I remembered how I wanted to see that movie but never did, and then I remembered how attractive I always found her, and, in particular, how attractive she appeared to me just then in that snapshot of herself, frozen in those boots, in that dress, in that position. And for some odd reason, a huge wave of depression washed over me and I wanted to cry.  Thirteen years. God.  Where has my life gone?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading  urlLink Reader's Digest  the other day -- highly appropriate, I guess -- and they had one of those Dramas in Real Life that they so often put in their delightful publications:  Trapped on a Burning Yacht .  This isn't much of a drama in real life; it's more of a drama you might find on  urlLink Falcon Crest , or  urlLink Dynasty : "I say, Carrington, Lord Wicktenstein's yacht seems to be on fire. How terribly droll." A drama in real life would be more like,  Homeless Boy Locked in Abandoned Refrigerator , or  Four Dollars Short in the Nine Items or Less Lane .  I would   love   to be on a yacht, for any length of time. I'd phone all my friends to come over and check me out. And if it was burning, I would just tell them all to hurry, we've only got, like, ten minutes to enjoy this thing before it's at the bottom of the ocean.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome, everyone, to Lectures on Everything 2004: the same old crap you've been reading for nearly 14 months, but without all those things like  content ,  topical issues , and  insightful analysis  that you'll find in  urlLink other ,  urlLink more popular  blogs.  New in 2004:  Tamara has a mouse.  I wrote the following poem for this  urlLink poetry quiz  at  urlLink poetry.com . They claim it's being evaluated by a team of poetry experts as we speak!   Giant spiders ate my butt! Only giants made the cut. Smallers ones stayed at the back For fear of dying in the crack.   Thank you.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Top 10 rejected names for  urlLink Queer Eye for the Straight Guy :     Mission: Impossible   Queerview Mirror   Fruit Squad   Mighty Makeover Puffter Rangers   From a Pawn to a Queen   Car Full O' Homos   Bed, Bath, and Bendover   Butt Pirates' Shanghai Makeover   League of Extraordinarily Gay Gentlemen   Five homosexuals play dress-up with real straight adult men! (This one is more of a synopsis than a title.)   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Those of you who know me know that I am chronically late for everything. In fact, after I'm dead, I'm positive people will refer to me as the "Late Deron Staffen". I suppose it's possible that somewhere people are refering to the "Punctual Deron Staffen", but that may only be in some backward Bizarro World, or maybe in a Rod Serling-esque alternate reality.  ANYWAY, I went for a job interview today and was told I was early.    Two weeks   early.  Is this a terrifying vision of things to come? At least I still  urlLink go to extremes .  (Some may argue that this should be my theme song; but when  urlLink Ringgo  proclaimed that  urlLink Danger Zone  was  his  theme song, I chose  urlLink Rock You Like A Hurricane , and I stand by that decision. Ringgo thought my choice was "Too airshow" -- unlike his, which was only used in a movie about  urlLink fighter pilots .  In other music-related news, an informal poll reveals that  urlLink this song  from Top Gun and  urlLink this Madonna song  are tied for most romantic song of the '80s.)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My oh my. A month into the new year and I'm already  urlLink drawing the ire  of some nice folks in the blogosphere. And it all centers around  urlLink this letter  I wrote to Kathy Shaidle.  Yes, I know Kathy's reply to me was written on January 10. Yes, I know my reply to her is more than three weeks later. I don't care. The wheels here at Lectures grind slowly, my friends, but they do grind exceedingly fine. Kathy's response weighs in at 306 words, or approximately 30 words/day between posts; my reply is almost six times hers and approximately 70 words/day, so you see I've been working about twice as hard. And I swear a hell of a lot more, too.  Kathy was  urlLink kind enough to respond  in a manner most befitting a respected writer: she asked me what the fuck I meant before calling me a dickhead. Apparently, though, she didn't actually have the stones to write the word fuck on her blog -- thankfully, I have enough to write it twice. She also didn't have the stones to send me   her   e-mail, although I certainly   did   send her mine -- which I'm sure she found in her  urlLink mac.com e-mail account .  Why Kathy decided to pick a fight with me is up for debate. It's not because I dissented against her opinion -- there was  urlLink at least one other person  days before. I don't think she felt threatened by the five people who regularly read my blog -- two of them choose to constantly disagree with me on principle anyway, and regardless, I'm fairly certain they all went off and read the Dallas Morning News story I linked to. (The original article is no longer on the  urlLink Dallas Morning News  site, but it can still be found  urlLink here .) I also don't think it was because I sent "hate mail" -- just as there were no weapons found in Iraq, so too there will be no "fuck" or "dickhead" found in my original post. I had thought someone with  urlLink five years of copywriting experience  would pick that out in an instant.  I think the reason Kathy decided to take me on is because I looked like an easy target. Truthfully,  urlLink her blog  does beat the living piss out of mine, and I haven't been published in anything since high school. She also points out, with great enthusiasm, that she was shortlisted for the  urlLink Governor General's Award  for poetry in 1998, but didn't win. I also haven't won the Governor General's Award, which should put us on the same level of mediocrity -- except that I also haven't won a Pulitzer or the Nobel Prize for Literature! In your face, baby!  Kathy does not even try to rebut my arguments, but instead leans heavily on the  urlLink appeal to authority fallacy : as my poetry is soooooooo wicked awesome, your opinions, regardless of what they are,   must   be wrong. And  urlLink her poetry  is actually pretty good; but still, swearing at me and not following up makes her look like one of those crusty, old women yelling at kids when an errant Frisbee is thrown into her yard: so full of empty rage, it's difficult to believe it's me you're angry with. At least  urlLink The Meatriarchy  gave my letter the old one-two, but, again, didn't really go the distance. Although they've taken some hits, with a good cut man I think my arguments can make it one more round:     There's a Gulf Between Us:  Yes, Saddam Hussein did defy the UN -- but let's not get off-topic! My claim was that Bush defied the wishes of the UN Security Council; finger pointing and cries of "But   he   started it!" are not adequate justification for these types of actions.  During the first Gulf War, the Security Council passed three resolutions regarding the invasion of Kuwait, including one authorizing all means necessary to enforce a withdrawal of Iraqi troops. Bush Senior  then  lead a coalition force on a  wholly defensive mission  to stop Iraq from invading Saudi Arabia, though there was no evidence suggesting that Iraq had designs on anything other than Kuwait. It was after all this that the US Congress authorized the used of force to drive Iraq out of Kuwait. Bush Junior, on the other hand, had no resolution from the Security Council and went on a  wholly offensive mission  specifically to overthrow Hussain. I think the differences in these two situations are clear enough and there's no need for me to spell things out further.     C'mon, Turn the Other Cheek:  Bush doesn't feign a friendship. It's good to hear that he's genuine in his feelings, but there is a certain amount of politicking that comes with the job of, y'know, politician. We're not asking Americans to learn all our Prime ministers or the order our provinces entered confederation. We're not even asking them to stop laughing at the colour of our money or to respect our hockey teams -- but we would appreciate being thrown a bone every now and then.  Maybe Chretien was concerned that Bush would  urlLink implement huge tax cuts for the rich, run up the deficit, and start a war through false accusations . And if Canada has done so much America baiting over the years, as you suggest, why is Bush is the only one to take offense to it? There were 42 other presidents that could have spoken up just as easily, but maybe they weren't spoiled, grudge bearing babies who rode to power on daddy's money. (With the exception of John Q. Adams, who was likely at least one of the three.)     It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad Cow:  We're both aware that the mad cow outbreak was an isolated case and that closing the borders to Canadian beef was an overreaction -- Canadians have been eating beef in   huge   quantities since the border closures and have been going mad for the taste, not because of BSE. And it's  urlLink the cattle industry in general , and not Canadians in particular, that's irresponsible with its feed, so stop stabbing that finger in the air before it gets cut off and ground up into cow chow.     NAFTA, SHMAFTA:  Just because I have my doubts about NAFTA doesn't mean I'm against the reduction of trade barriers; we both know that trade barriers are the least contentious issues behind the free trade agreement, and that reducing trade friction is beneficial to everyone. Regardless, there were few existing trade barriers when treaties like NAFTA and CUFTA were put into effect in the first place, and the main focus of these treaties are not free trade, but shackling governments and granting special privileges to corporations.  These  are the issues lefties like me object to.     25 Million People Can't Be Wrong:  When I say "a lot of [people] hate George Bush", I mean a lot -- not all. I'll concede that there's one person who loves Bush for each person who hates him; hell, I'll give you three to one and six who don't care either way. But with roughly 250 million people in North America, even a tenth of that is   a lot   of people.  Invite them over to your place for a barbecue this summer and you'll have a better feel for what I'm talking about.    Make a Run for the Border:  No sir, we don't buy 80% of the US's exports. In fact, according to the  urlLink Department of Foreign Affairs , Canada only buys about 19% of American goods and services, whereas the US buys a whopping 16.5% of Canadian goods -- only 63.5%  lower  than your apparently well researched estimate. This cross border trade amounts to $188 billion per year, or about $1.2 billion per day. That's   a lot   of money. I mean, it's not a trillion dollar deficit or anything, but it's still a lot.    Kathy, I'm glad you and whoever it is at The Meatriarchy -- Tony, or something -- have found someone -- however misguided -- that inspires you. I'm glad you can find a shred of justification in this crazy war that doesn't make you want to pick your brain out of your ear with a shrimp fork; maybe it's ossified to the point where you need something sharper, like a dental pick, I don't know. I don't understand your attitude, and I probably never will -- but calling me a dickhead and an asshat and then whining about sharing Canada with me are poor justifications for your opinions, although it does seem  urlLink typical of your rhetorical style .  Allow me to provide you with an interesting mnemonic to remind you of our positions:  Left and Right must disagree/always, by necessity . Cute, eh? I just made that up. So, as we stand squarely on opposite sides of  urlLink the fence , I suggest you use your energy   not   to add more posts in your blog about this left-wing fucker (or f***er, as you're fond of writing) who just won't give it a rest, but instead to propel yourself forward to new adventures, and, more importantly, new geographic locations! Go! Be free! Throw off the oppressive yoke of Canadian society! I would be delighted if you no longer had to share Canada with the rest of us asshats.  All the best to you and Tony!  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I feel like a detective. Definitely more  urlLink Encyclopedia Brown  than  urlLink Sherlock Holmes , but I'm not about to quibble over who's better. Leroy does have those cute, boyish good looks, but Sherlock has the cold, calculating demeanor of a serious private dick; I say it's a dead heat, but maybe this is something to be revisited at a later date.  Anyway, sometimes I feel like a detective; it's often when all the pieces of the puzzle have been presented, and the solution finally gels in my mind like... well, like  urlLink Jell-O . Except it's not in a bowl, it's in one of those  urlLink crazy Jell-O moulds , like the breast or pants being ripped off.  Tamara and I went to the  urlLink casino . She comes out of the bathroom and says to me, "Why do you suppose they have those  urlLink sharps containers  in the bathrooms?"  "I noticed them too," I said. "Lots of intravenous drug users?"  We kind of left things in-between that and convenience and went to either lose money at  urlLink $2 blackjack  or screech obscenities at the  urlLink horserace game .  Weeks later, I was at the Bannock Shack and read an article by  urlLink Errol Kinistino  about the high incidences of  urlLink diabetes in aboriginal populations .   Ding , went a little bell. Okay, maybe it was more of a gong being bashed by a heavily muscled guy swinging a tree trunk, but the bell metaphor is so well known -- no one says, "That name causes a gong-like noise to reverberate through my skull."   Fact:  Casino Regina employs a lot of aboriginals; actually, all of their job announcements state that they are designated for people who self-declare as first nation or metis.   Fact:  Aboriginals, as a group, have a high incidence of diabetes.   Fact:  Diabetics need to dispose of needles in a safe and efficient manner.   Conclusion:  The sharps containers in the bathrooms are there for the convenience of the staff, and I am a genius! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tori: "What did you say? Did you say you were good looking?" Me: "What?! I would never say that -- although you   will   hear other people say it."  I think that's called  urlLink modesty .
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It must be difficult having a common name. I hadn't considered it until just recently.  Having an uncommon name is difficult. I spent many of my formative years burning with fiery-hot habanero pepper rage toward a world who could not seem to place the letters of the English alphabet together properly to spell my name. When I was six, I toyed with the idea that the whole world had some mild form of dyslexia (I now know that people are just stupid -- with age, wisdom) -- after all, there are only  urlLink 65000  different five-letter combinations! People could  choose a 14 million-to-one lottery ticket, but spelling my name is somehow a mind-numbing teaser akin to cracking the enigma code? I don't know why  urlLink pirates  and the  urlLink Knights Templar  didn't use my name as a key to their booby traps -- "You know that guy who sat behind you in the third grade? He had messy brown hair and glasses, and he'd rub one of those crappy  urlLink Pink Pearl  erasers on his desk really fast and then smell it? Spell his name, or death awaits thee."  But as the years passed, the correct spelling of my name became less and less of an issue to me -- even though the number of people misspelling my name seemed to increase in direct proportion to my lackadaisical attitude. Why, there were even some people on the  urlLink SEDA   urlLink Board of Directors  who did not know how to spell my name properly,  even after six years with the organization . But I'm not bitter. All I'm saying is, living with an odd name ain't all puddin' and pie.  Anyway,  urlLink last summer  I happened upon the blog of one  urlLink Christopher Taylor . I was delighted that I had found the blog of the  real  Chris Taylor, then saddened that I had, in fact, discovered an imposter. In my anguish, I guess I said a couple of mildly harsh things; he's not going to be able to use my words to scrub those caked-on pots and pans or remove the rust and hard water stains from his toilet bowl, but he could probably use them to exfoliate -- which may be a blessing, seeing what  urlLink The Body Shop  is charging for  urlLink facial scrubs  these days.  Now, it's taken him some time -- I suffer from the  urlLink same problem  -- but he has  urlLink responded to my post   and  sent me the following e-mail:   Subject: I am...   the king of town (and the real Christopher Taylor).  Back to my vat now.  Christopher Taylor  Bennett/Sekuler Vision & Cognitive Neuroscience Lab McMaster University, Psychology Complex 1280 Main St. West, Hamilton, ON, Canada L8S 4K1 905-529-7070 x24489  urlLink http://www.psychology.mcmaster.ca/vislab/   urlLink http://christophertaylor.blogspot.com    I get the feeling he's somewhat put-off by my remarks. I can't say I blame him: here he is, minding his own business, when this rough-and-tumble blog-wielding maniac comes along and threatens his entire existence by saying he's not the  real  Chris Taylor. This is the tragedy of the common name. I know I'd be upset if someone said I wasn't the  real  Deron Staffen -- but in retrospect, I think I'd be able to have a good laugh about how I  thought  I was the real one for all those years, and how many people I fooled. Then, maybe, the  real  Deron Staffen would be run out of town on a railcar, and the judge would instruct everyone never to speak of this again -- y'know, like in that  urlLink Simpsons episode .  I decided to write to the  real  Chris Taylor for some guidance. He provided six criteria which would help me decide who the  real  Chris Taylor was. I'll be totaling the scores in parentheses as we go.   1. Why didn't I know you had a blog?? Here I am, wasting away in Japan, desperate for portals into the world of Derron, and unbeknownst to me, you have been providing the world with a portal into your genius.    urlLink Chris Taylor  knew about my blog before Chris did, so point for  urlLink Chris . Also, Chris spelled my name wrong (curses!), so minus one for him. (1/-1)   2. I took a look into this guy's work. He seems to be doing some good things. I am basically pleased with his apparent knowledge of  urlLink Homestar  and what not. I agree that he may have been left in the vat too long, and felt that his subsequent reference to the vat didn't do the initial jibe the justice it so richly deserved. I think I would have stuck to simply complimenting you on the vat remark, and then spun off into an original self-deprecating remark, perhaps carrying on the boiling and cooking motif, but not directly replying to your work.   Chris likes  urlLink Chris 's work, so point for him. Also, Chris is right about the vat reference, so point for him too. (2/0)   3. He claims that Lord of the Rings deserves its accolades. The real Chris Taylor would never descend to the level of praising fantasy movies or the oscars, but would instead go to an oscar party and act like he hasn't seen any of the movies involved because he is only interested in  urlLink Vincent Gallo  and early Bauhaus experiments in film.   Chris is right about the  real  Chris Taylor's attitude toward the movies, so he gets a point. Although this is about the  real  Chris Taylor, I also agree that Lord of the Rings deserves its accolades and must therefore also give another point to  urlLink Chris . I don't think this point is even arguable. Well, okay, too much with the hobbits and the elves and the ship there at the end of the film, and yadda yadda yadda, here's another thirty minutes of Bilbo dragging his petrified hobbit ass down to the docks while John Williams flails the cellists with a cat-o-nine-tails, trying to extract every last tear out of the audience, and you start to cry, not because of the story, but because every molecule of water in your body has migrated to your bladder and you've been straining against the crushing pressure of that super-sized Coke for the last two-and-a-half hours, and for God's sake, you need to piss way more than you need to see some old dude about as short and hairy as your grandpa wander around shoeless the way he did at your 13th birthday party, etc., etc. But other than that, great trilogy. (3/1)   4. This Chris Taylor seems to be involved in the sciences, which makes him suspect right away.   Agreed. (3/2)   5. If there is a real Chris Taylor aside from this Chris Taylor, it would be the Chris Taylor who has an office at the  urlLink U of R  and his own mailbox in the education building. This Chris Taylor really seems to have things together, based on the emptiness of his mailbox, anyway.   Here, Chris is open to the possibility that he is not the  real  Chris Taylor.  urlLink Chris , on the other hand, proclaims unequivocally that he is the  real  Chris Taylor, not being open at all to other possibilities. Although I can easily believe that I'm wrong, I cannot easily believe that I'm wrong at the expense of Chris Taylor, real or not, being right. (3/3)   6. One good way to determine if a Chris Taylor is the real Chris Taylor is to ask yourself "Would this guy make a good sidekick to  urlLink Erin Weir ?" The correct answer is yes. This blog Chris Taylor does lots of stuff that  urlLink Erin Weir  wouldn't tolerate. Take, for example, the entry where in he mentions that some book is great and that he would review it but he doesn't feel like it. Now, if this guy said that to  urlLink Erin Weir ,  urlLink Erin Weir  would point out that if he had the energy to turn on his computer and write the sentences that he did, he could probably muster three hundred more words to give us his take on the book. And if he can't, he should at least make himself useful by providing drunken anecdotes for  urlLink Weir  to tell of at later social gatherings.   urlLink Weir  doesn't have to say these things to the real Chris Taylor, because the real Chris Taylor knows what is what.  And if  urlLink Erin Weir  does have to say these things, it is because the real Chris Taylor set him up, knowing that the crowd demanded more  urlLink Weir  than other lines of conversation were providing.   The  real  Chris Taylor knows what is what. (3/4)  In a close competition, Chris Taylor beats  urlLink Chris Taylor  by a point, reaffirming that I am right, and that Chris Taylor is indeed the real Chris Taylor. It remains to be seen if the Chris Taylor with the clean mailbox can claim the title of the real Chris Taylor, but as that match-up may shake the very foundation of reality, it's beyond the scope of this post.  Now, all this is not to say that  urlLink Chris Taylor  does not have some merit. I've taken the time to read through his blog again. He's gotten some laughs out of me, and he certainly has an interesting, and eclectic, taste in music. If I have a fault --   if   I have a fault -- it's that I don't listen to enough good music, and I rely mainly on people with broad musical tastes to broaden mine. He reminds me a lot of  urlLink David Mark , who I really had no real appreciation for until I started taking up space in the office next to his. Maybe I just needed to hear the melodic strains of  urlLink Chris 's zany MP3 collection echoing down the hallway to have avoided the vat comment altogether, though I'd then be two posts shy in my blog. And the fans crave content!  I think the moral of this tale is that I jump too hastily to conclusions, and that I was much too quick to deny  urlLink Chris Taylor  his rightful place among the Chris Taylors out there. So kudos to you,  urlLink Christopher Taylor , for being a shining example for other Chris Taylors to aspire to, and for showing me the error of my ways. The only reason I'd suggest you be put in a vat now is to preserve you for future generations, so they could look at you and say, "Hell, he seems like a decent enough guy! I don't know what Super Galactic Supreme Empire Ruler Champ Staffen was making such a fuss about!"  Of course, they would all be blown to atoms milliseconds later for doubting the will of the Super Galactic Supreme Empire Ruler Champ. C'mon, they should have known better.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Crazy, Crazy day.  First blog post in a while. Nothing personal, y'know, just busy with stuff. But I'm getting to that.  Today I ran in my first official race: the  urlLink Regina Police Half Marathon . Now, I didn't actually run a half marathon, I ran a half marathon relay: three of us teamed up to run a half marathon. I ran with guys from the running club, and I was really impressed with their performances. They may fool around a lot at running club, but they put the rubber to the road when it counted. I, of course, continued to batter my poor left knee, but I was okay until later in the afternoon when I twisted it played shinny with some kids from the Regina Warriors Box Lacrosse team. I blame Travis for being out of position.  Then, later today, I was finally invited to become a member of  urlLink Orkut , a community I tried to join from the minute I learned of it's existence. Orkut is members only -- you have to be invited by someone in order to join. This creates an interesting thought line, when you consider that there was initially a core group of Orkut-certified people who expanded the group by adding contacts, and that this, somehow, inexplicably, lead to me. It was probably more than the famous  urlLink six degrees  that everyone talks about, but there is some kind of trail that links me to that core group, step by convoluted step.  Reading more about Orkut, I discover that it's a community to try and manage contacts and make your social life more interesting. Well, there are   a lot   of communities you can join, and   a lot   of message boards to read, but I wonder just how much this differs from, let's say, becoming a regular on  urlLink Fark , or  urlLink Slashdot , or  urlLink Kuro5hin , or even on one of your favourite  urlLink Usenet groups  -- like  urlLink rec.games.backgammon , for instance. This part of Orkut, while important, just seems to me to be yet another community to keep up on -- and if you're like me you're already  urlLink reading   urlLink several   urlLink blogs ,  urlLink Blogdex , social sites like  urlLink MSN Groups  or  urlLink Yahoo! Groups ,  urlLink current news headlines , some interesting hobby sites like, oh,  urlLink GammonVillage.com ,  urlLink Homestar Runner  (on Mondays),  urlLink the Onion  (on Wednesdays), and assorted bits and sundry; if you're current with  urlLink the Economist  that's one more thing, if you follow discussion boards on one of the aforementioned websites, that's another, and if you're reading Usenet with any regularity (but really, I'd be surprised if there's anyone but the old school hardcores like me that hang around on there any more), that's yet another. Orkut adds more grist to the mill, but is it really doing any more than overloading a system already soupy with information?  Following this, yet another exciting thing happened to me -- I was offered a chance to test  urlLink Google's Gmail ! So I now have  urlLink levendis@gmail.com , if anyone wants to find me there. I add this fourth address to my group of  urlLink levendis@yahoo.com , my main e-mail address;  urlLink clamdigger21@yahoo.ca , which I use for zany account sign-ups and rarely check (and which has largely been replaced by the indispensable  urlLink Mailinator.com ), and  urlLink jbananapop@hotmail.com , which I use exclusively for MSN Messenger. Nevertheless, in spite of how I adore Google, and in spite of its one Gigabyte of storage space (which I imagine Yahoo! and Hotmail will match in due haste), I doubt I will be moving from my Yahoo! account -- I've just had it for so long, y'know? It'd be like moving out of the home you grew up in, and we all know how I feel about moving.  Anyway, in the wake of all this information overload, I thought I would apprise all three of you who regularly read my rambling ravings about the awesome array of events that I'm contributing to in these days of underemployment. Once I find a full-time job I'll either need to develop 10 times the time management skills I have now or drop some of my commitments. But we shall see -- I may end up surprising us all!     Shinny Supervisor for the  urlLink Regina Sports Council    Aboriginal Kin Youth Running Club Supervisor    urlLink 24-Hour Relay  Team Fundraising Co-chair   Regina  urlLink KidSport  Committee Secretary   Saskatchewan Summer Games Mission Staff    urlLink Erin Weir's Wascana campaign    General shenanigans and tomfoolery    Oh, and my blog is also 4th overall on MSN when you search for  urlLink ugly boobs  -- and, surprisingly, I've been getting a lot of hits for that lately. Are there some ugly boobs out there I should know about?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I received yet another hit to my blog by someone looking for information on The Bannock Shack. So, to facilitate this continued search for information, I present to you Deron's Official Bannock Shack Post.  The Bannock Shack can be contacted at:  The Bannock Shack 3115 5th Ave. Regina, SK S4T 7T2  Phone: (306) 522-7240  It's exact location can be found  urlLink here . (I normally use  urlLink MapBlast  for my mapping needs, but it choked on the address. Stupid Microsoft.)  If you're coming south on Albert Street, you'll find a Tim Horton's on your right side and a Petcetera on your left.  Avoid the temptation to eat at Tim Horton's!  If you're Vietnamese,  avoid the temptation to eat at Petcetera!  Instead, go one block further south and turn to your right.  If you're coming north on Albert Street and you get to the Tim Horton's/Petcetera intersection, you've gone one block too far. I wish I could tell you where to turn, but the landmarks escape me.  "But Deron," I hear you ask, "how's the food?"  Well, I'm no expert on aboriginal cuisine, but I think it's pretty good. They offer a good array of food, ranging from traditional North American stuff like burgers, fries, and pizza, to things like buffalo burgers and Indian tacos. The burgers, of course, come on a piece of fried bannock instead of a bun. They also serve the popular "bullets and bannock" -- some kind of meatball and potato soup, which I think is delicious, and you can get the 6-pack or 12-pack of fried bannock to go. You can even get breakfast in the mornings, with a good plate bacon and eggs for $2.99. But don't ask me why the Toonie Sandwich costs $2.50, because I don't know.  I've had buffalo at  urlLink Wanuskewin , but I haven't tried the buffalo burger at The Bannock Shack. Similarly, I've had Indian tacos at  urlLink Junior Nationals  in  urlLink Yorkton , but not at The Bannock Shack. I have had the Bannock Burger and fries, which was pretty good. I've had  a lot  of fried bannock, which is very good, but kind of greasy. Nothing out of the ordinary, though, that's just how it's prepared. I'm a big fan of the Bullets and Bannock, and get it practically every time I'm there. I've also had their pizza, but I think it's the weakest food they offer. It was big and thick, like  urlLink Vern's Pizza , but very greasy -- so much so that we had grease dripping down our hands as we ate.  Overall, I recommend The Bannock Shack, and not just because it's awesome to have a restaurant serving aboriginal food. The food there is delicious, the prices are very reasonable, and the atmosphere is terrific.  Now when people search for  urlLink The Bannock Shack  on Google, maybe they'll find what they're looking for.  Please note that I am not affiliated with The Bannock Shack, I'm just a white guy who likes to eat there.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't check my blog, indeed.  I check my blog constantly. I even check the referrers for all the hits I get. I'm surprised by the amount of hits I get from Singapore, though they've dropped off a little recently. I'm also surprised that there's someone in Calgary who remains a faithful reader, though I'm sure I don't know anyone there. My one disappointment is that I don't show up on  urlLink Technorati  nearly as often as I'd like.  Anyway, Anonymous, the problem isn't me letting my poor little blog languish, the problem is finding time and thinking up content to post. I think that's part of the reason why my journal project of 1995 failed so miserably -- not the arrogance or the terrible spelling, though they probably also played their role.  But I find that, like men, my ideas seem to come in spurts. My suggestion is to check back every few days and hope that enough time has passed for at least one interesting post.  You could also check  urlLink Weblogs.com  or something, y'know, to see when I update, but I recommend it only as a last resort.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So. Blogger has redesigned, and I am riding on their coattails. Now, this isn't the template redesign I wanted, but it'll do until I get my sorry ass in gear and finish learning CSS.  Lectures is now Atom-enabled, meaning that all you tech-weenies can get a feed at  urlLink http://lecturesoneverything.blogspot.com/atom.xml .  And -- holy crap! There are now comment tags under my posts! So now you can tell me what I jerk-off I am to my face, instead of leaving those horrific messages on my answering machine.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is Mother's Day. So let me start by giving a shout out to all the mothers out there. Also, word to all the muthas out there. Big ups all around.  I went out for brunch with my mom today. I didn't realize it at the time, but mom and Lindsay already had a location picked out. You know you're eating at a  urlLink quality establishment  when the Mother's Day Sunday Brunch Buffet features  urlLink head cheese .  In case any of you are dreaming of a business making head cheese in your home for fun and profit, or perhaps holding your own Sunday Brunch Buffet, I've included  urlLink this handy link  to a head cheese recipe at  urlLink Remember Mama's Recipes . I can just imagine the other delectable favourites in that household: scab sandwiches, dink dumplings, sock soup, roast groin. Thanks, mom, for cooking me real food in my formative years, so I didn't have to start a website like that one.   urlLink This Red Meat cartoon  also came up in my Google search for head cheese. But I still think  urlLink this one 's my favourite.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, I know I don't post anymore. This shouldn't surprise anyone -- I haven't been posting regularly since I started this blog. Hell, I haven't been posting anything  interesting  since I started this blog.  I took  urlLink this test  tonight and scored 163. Now, I think there are a few people out there that could fry this score up like a side of bacon (I'm looking at  you , Chris Taylor), but I'm fairly satisfied with this score and don't think I could do much better even if I had spent more time on it.  Yes, I am posting this just to brag.  I have had three (and counting!) mysterious encounters with women who may or may not have been prostitutes. Given the propensity for prostitution and its popularity in this place, I posit these people pander publicly to peculiar patrons and perform preposterous pubic procedures for pennies.  My first encounter came as I was walking home. I was approaching two young ladies who may have been having a conversation, but I wasn't aware of them talking. As I passed, one quite distinctly said, "25 bucks."  My second encounter came as I was driving to shinny. I had stopped at a corner to wait for traffic to pass, and a nice young woman came up to the car and offered to let me give her a ride.  My third encounter came while driving to Safeway. I was driving down the street toward a woman who was standing mysteriously in the middle of the block. She was wearing a long coat that was buttoned all the way up, but it had been raining. As I got closer, she decided it was time to stretch her arms up in the air.  Now, none of these are particularly thrilling, but if you wanted thrills you'd be chewing that ridiculous  urlLink soap-flavoured gum . No, instead you want boring stories of women who are obviously prostitutes and how I misinterpret everything as being completely innocent.  You know, I wouldn't have this problem if there were more pimps on the street. What's the problem, exactly? Are they telling their hoes to stand on the corner and make ambiguous sexual advances while they stay home and play Nintendo? They should be out there doing some direct marketing -- selling, cold calls, establishing a clientele. A more efficient business model would allow prices to drop, making prostitutes affordable for the masses and no longer just a luxury item for society's idle millionaires.  But enough of this. I need some sleep. Let's just say the score's Prostitutes-3, Deron-0 and call it a night. Sure, it hurts to be down 3-0 this early in the season, but we've got a strong club this year and we're just going to have to have to rally the troops out there, buckle down, and give 110%. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Reading  urlLink this post  on Defective Yeti, I felt a sense of deja vu. Well, not entirely deja vu, but I don't know much Latin and that's the closest I could get to describing it -- e pluribus unum is something about a salad, or somesuch.  Anyway, I thought I'd posted about this before --  urlLink and I had ! I scooped the Yeti by more than a year! Ha-ha! Well, again, not entirely, but along the same lines. If the Library Guy had actually signed some kind of lucrative endorsement contract, then I would have scooped the Yeti by more than a year! Ha-ha! Just ignore the rambling parts in my post obviously ghost written by some manic street preacher hopped up on goofballs and you'll be fine. That boils my post down to a most palatable four words: "scooped... Yeti... Ha-ha!"  So it got me thinking: how can the regular people in society -- the average Joes, you and me -- capitalize on our disastrous mental illnesses? Why, through advertising!     Manic depressives for before/after ads   Narcoleptics for mattress companies   Schizophrenics for Reynolds Aluminum Foil   Munchausen patients for government subsidized health care   Alzheimer's patients for memory enhancement products   Sexaholics for contraceptives   The uncontrollably violent for sledgehammers or punching bags     So don't just stand there -- jump on the metal illness bandwagon and let the dollars start pouring in! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Sports Council yearbook is finally finished, for good or ill. And there was much rejoicing.  And now, for your viewing pleasure, what  urlLink The Cure  is in each day of the week:  Saturday: Jail Sunday: Drag Monday: He-Man Underoos Tuesday: A Mexican whorehouse Wednesday: So much trouble when&nbsp;their father gets home! Thursday: A second-year chem major's homemade acid trip Friday:  urlLink Love , naturally.   Bonus Post!  How  urlLink Robert Smith  of The Cure is feeling each day of the week:  Saturday: Sad Sunday: Wistful Monday: Blue Tuesday: Somber Wednesday: glum Thursday: Not quite as&nbsp;glum as Wednesday, but still&nbsp;pretty glum Friday: Mopey  (Synonyms provided by the good folks at  urlLink dictionary.com . You guys are really, really, really, really nice.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just made this up.  &nbsp;  Two old men walk into a sauna together and throw their towels haphazardly on the floor. The&nbsp;one old man says, "My God, but that's a long one! And with a nice tip on the end, too!"  &nbsp;  "Yes," says the other, "it's good and solid, and straight as an arrow. Bend over, I'll show you how to use it."  &nbsp;  (Y'see, the first old man was carrying a pool cue. This is one of those lateral-thinking jokes, y'know, where you're given the joke but not all the information in it, and then you have to figure out why it's funny. I mean, why else would two old men be talking like that in&nbsp;a sauna unless one of them was holding a pool cue?  &nbsp;  Maybe I can make a follow-up joke where two women walk into a sauna and one says, "Nice rack!" And then the other one says, "Thanks! I got them on sale, but one of them's a little lopsided and not as round."  &nbsp;  Man, if a pool table in the sauna is as funny in real life as it is on paper, I gotta get me one!)   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Still trying to metaphorically find some direction in my life and my place in the world, I once again make some changes to my blog template. We had a housewarming on Saturday, and I asked a friend of mine, who, after drinking 15 different kinds of alcohol, apparently acquires "strange powers", what my direction in life should be. But in the end, his only "strange power" was to speak completely incoherently and ask me the question, "What do you think it should be?" once for each beer he'd consumed. Which was a lot. Like, the CEO of Molson was popping a boner in his sleep. My other friend wrote "Veni, Vidi, Vomit" on our Wall of Fame, which ended up being a self-fulfilling prophecy. It was an interesting evening.  &nbsp;  Worse, while I've been having this crisis, which flares up every once in a&nbsp;while like a bad case of herpes, I've been reading  urlLink Defective Yeti &nbsp;-- partly because I need something to read while I'm on the john, and partly because the guy is damn funny. But don't mistake those loud groans and cries of "Oh, God!" as me holding my aching sides, because it's actually another part of my anatomy that I'm praying for. And after night of drinking with the SuperFriends -- Captain Incomprehensible and the Upchuck Kid -- there was a lot of heavenly supplication. And on a Sunday, too. I've never felt so holy.  &nbsp;  Then today&nbsp;I rolled across  urlLink this post  on  urlLink Monkey Disaster , which was good for some laughs. And  urlLink the next post  was  really  funny, especially as my head is about the size of, oh, a desiccated peanut. If you think the pro-fit hat is going to to be a pro fit, you, my friend, have just lost your job&nbsp;as a professional hat fitter. And you're also looking at my head through some kind of high-powered magnifier.  &nbsp;  Now,  urlLink Monkey Disaster  is not as funny as  urlLink Defective Yeti  or  urlLink The Morning News , but it's still pretty funny. And John Moe also apparently writes for  urlLink McSweeny's , which is  very  funny; why,  urlLink these lists  alone had me doubled over for hours.  &nbsp;  So, y'know, while John isn't quite the funniest guy around, he's definitely funnier than I am. And therein lies the rub: I need to be funnier. I don't know what the secret is to funny writing. I mean, Matthew seems to just have it pour out of him like a comic sweat -- go pump some iron, write some jokes, have a shower -- the day's done. I have to labour like Hercules just to push out one funny adjective.  &nbsp;   "Uhhhhh... insipid...."  &nbsp;  *frontal lobe deflates*  &nbsp;  "Quick, stick that tire pump in my mouth! And get me the ginko biloba!"    So I don't know what form my writing is going to take, but I'm hoping for an insanely comedic bent that won't cause me any kind of permanent brain damage. If I continue reading&nbsp;Matthew and John&nbsp;and the other apostles, maybe I'll absorb some funny things and I'll actually entertain the Constant Readers who, I don't know, come here when they're on the john.  &nbsp;  Well,  a lot  of them come here looking for the  urlLink Bannock Shack , so I'm very happy I decided to post that information. And really, the john is&nbsp;probably the second place they'll want to go, so some funny reading material might actually help them take their mind off the pain. That and some fiber.  &nbsp;  Oh, and I just found out that Matthew Baldwin is the originator of  urlLink Pizza Party USA , so he is now officially a genius.     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A phone conversation:   Me:  Hi, can I speak to Jerry, please?   Them:  I'm sorry, you must have the wrong number.   Me:  No, I have the right number, I just have the wrong name.  *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Remember when you were little and thought the Leaning Tower of Pisa was really the Leaning Tower of  Pizza ? And you wondered how they kept it leaning, and if the tourists each took a slice, making it smaller and smaller with each passing year? And you wanted to go there someday and see this giant, leaning stack of pizza before it was all gone? No? Well, I hope I have a better memory when I reach your age. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This cost me 75 cents.   Me:  Hi, is there a number for Two-For-One Pizza, please?  Operator:  [keyboard noises] Yes there is.  M:  Okay, is there a number for a three-for-one pizza?  O:  [keyboard noises] Yes.  M:  How about a four-for-one pizza?  O:  [keyboard noises] There's no listing for that, sir.  M:  Is there a listing for a five-for-one pizza?  O:  [keyboard noises] No.  M:  Are there any listings for any pizza places that offer more than five-for-one?  O:  No there isn't.  M:  So three-for-one is my best value, isn't it?  O:  [silence]  M:  Could I have that number, please?  O:  [keyboard noises] Thank you, hold for that number. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>