<Blog>


<date>25,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Karl Popper says that a scientific statement is one that is falsifiable -- there are clear, observable tests you might apply to that statement which would prove it wrong.  If clean, solid billiard balls in motion sometimes collided and then simply stuck together and lay still, instead of bouncing apart, then Newton's Laws of Motion would have to be reconsidered.  Statements like "Rapture is coming" are less scientific than Newton's Laws, by these lights, because no one can ever positively prove that rapture is not, at some point, coming.  You can't make any observations of the future.  "Rapture is coming on January 1, 2000 of the western calendar" is a more scientific statement (and also a provably false one -- everyone observed that Rapture failed to arrive on that day).      Is "Rapture is coming" true or false?  The event about which it potentially speaks is unavailable in the world of the present and its known history -- it lies ahead of us in time.  It's not part of what can be observed.  So perhaps statements like this one have to be simply set aside, when we are interested in truth.  Statements about the future can only be retrospectively true.    Billiard balls have never been seen to collide and then stick together -- yet.  Rapture has not come -- yet.  So aren't they both statements about an uncertain future?  The difference is that one of them succeeds in being true about much of the known past and present.  The other has never applied to anything, and so there is no evidence for or against.  Balls flying apart is evidence for Newton's Laws; each and any time a fast-moving billiard ball sticks to another ball and they both stop moving, evidence against has appeared.  Any strong truth claims, according to Popper, come with this kind of clear specification of what, exactly, would be a disaster for the claim.   But sometimes I think about the problem of verification the other way -- from the perspective of the person who makes a truth claim that they really believe.  When you say that you believe something is true, fully true, you are inviting any and all potential observers to agree.  You are challenging all the inhabitants of the entire future to check your work -- throwing down the gauntlet of what is known, now, before the specter of all that will ever be known, by every new face and facet of the entire future history of observing beings.  It's a brash thing to do.   People know, most of the time, that their perspective is provisional.  When pressed, most people will tend to hedge, and say "I wouldn't bet my life on it, but I think that X," or "It seems to me that X."  Even the expression "I believe," as we use it in English, has a kind of qualification buried in it.  Martyrs and loners, prophets, in that brave act of extending their gnosis as far as it will go, say "This thing is what I believe, and I will stand by it."  The very effort that a believer expends, the amount of nobility it takes to wholeheartedly believe something, is a testament to the unlikeliness and provisional character of being right about anything.     There's a scene in the novel "Contact" where a scientist is asked to place her nose just at the top point of the swing arc of a massive pendulum.  The pendulum is released, allowed to swing away, then back toward her.  Knowing Newton's Laws, she knows that the pendulum cannot -- it cannot -- swing back up and hit her, no matter how much momentum it seems to have.  But the dramatic question of the scene is, "Does she truly believe it?  Will she be struck anyway?"  She does feel afraid, but she does manage to hold still.  I think -- I believe -- that babies are made by sperm and egg uniting, with the sperm actually entering the egg, and the whole mass turning into a human child over the course of nine months.  I strongly believe that this is true; it does not live in the realm of "theory" for me, in the way that plate tectonics is a theory, which might come in for modification at some point.  I don't think the idea of sperm uniting with egg (historically new though it may be) will ever be subject to any modification.  Elaboration, surely, but not fundamental alteration.      But if you put a gun to my head, and asked me again where babies come from, I might admit that I have not actually seen the fertilization process firsthand.  I have seen it on television and in films, have read about it in books from different sources, and have seen its effects in many situations.  I know people who have observed sperm firsthand under a piece of ground glass.    But there is colder wind, a skeptical touch, which makes the whole edifice sway just a little, like a tower seen through a heat haze.   I'm an idealist -- I want to know that the tower will stand forever.      
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A thought about the way that Michel Foucault writes:  Derrida says that he has to explain the "trace" the way he does because of the difficulties of the concept, its special character.  This is a kind of claim familiar from Heidegger, and perhaps it goes back to Hegel.  Last night, the continental in question was Foucault.  Denying that one of your ideas can be submitted to a redaction -- boiled down to an essence -- and instead hinting at the notion, restating it, revisiting it, like Derrida does with the idea of the "trace" and Foucault does with "power" . . . this is, among other things, an excellent way to deny people the ability to paraphrase your ideas in their own vocabulary.  They have to use yours.  In a sense, you haven't provided an "idea", and in fact you probably resist that kind of packaging.  You've provided a set of statements which are cagey about their propensity for adding up, fusing together, into something other than the sum of their parts.    If twenty different places within your magnum opus have to be synthesized, compared, and corroborated, argued over, just for someone to get a bead on what one of your main ideas is, then you're making the work of hermeneutics a primary activity of your readership.  That poring over, that comparing: it makes interpretation paramount, reinterpretation, argumentation.  You're forcing a kind of Talmudic scriptural relationship between your text and its audience (and in Foucault's case, you're succeeding).  How fares the chance for someone to dialogue with your text?  It's reduced.  People can dialogue with each other: your text is above the fray, unplumbable, enigmatic, handed down from the mountain.  It only states; it doesn't know.  And so it can never be wrong.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A haiku by Yosa Buson:   Coolness -- The sound of the bell As it leaves the bell    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      From today's New York Times, about a man who discovered a new Michelangelo drawing in an old box:  "But early in his career Sir Timothy was an assistant curator at the Victoria and Albert Museum in London, working on ceramics. As a small child he collected porcelain and was so obsessed that he used to go to bed with his cups and saucers, stroking them to determine by touch, in the dark, whether he could figure out which factories in France — Sèvres, St. Cloud, Chantilly — made what." 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Reading a history of modern art, it occurred to me that many of the cliches about how the photograph impacted the visual arts are true.  The photograph changed the way people set about capturing images, and what they expected that to do for them.  It changed their ideas about what audiences might want from a painting.    Take expressionism of all kinds (small e).  This is a kind of image-making animated by the idea that, without the pressure toward visual accuracy which impinged on painting for so long, the important point of a painting is to give a visual insight into an emotional state.  This is different from crafting an accurate picture of a selected possible world -- Holofernes having his head cut off, for example -- for no matter how expressive that selection might be, no matter how loosely it might be conjured, there is more emotional veracity to be had in a picture of a non-possible world (or that's the claim).  A brand-new vision.  The urgency is upon the artist to express with emotional charge.  Emotions, moods, colors -- these were always on stage, of course.  They were always more than half the reason for the painting to be there.  But now, in nonrepresentational (or less-representational) art, with the stage taken away, they go barefoot.  Or they stand on stilts.  Or, take the idea a different direction, so that the artist's emotions are not so privileged.  Say the point of a painting is to arouse emotions in the spectator.  Now, we set about figuring out how to affect him; accurate visual representation is clearly not the only way, and in fact, it may be quite a limited way of getting right at him, involving him, engaging him.  All kinds of experiments are tried.  Some general attributes of expressionist (or even impressionist) painting: predominance of color effects, simpler form, tendency to flatness, less interest in space, minimally narrative, more spontaneous.  This has all been said better elsewhere; my point today is that there is an analogy to be drawn between photography's impact on painting and recording's impact on popular music.  The photographic "freezing" (and then the copying, the duplication, the infinite propagation. . . ) has some relation to the recording of an excellent performance of a musical work.    The recording makes the music finished; it makes it distributable.  The musician can play it again, but the recording will persist in being the standard by which those performances may be understood -- the backing paper on which they will be colored.  In a similar way, we can be fascinated by comparing a photograph of a church to a Monet painting of that church, but we can never doubt which is more fundamental.  Monet's vision is idiosyncratic, expressive; the photograph is democratic, and it looks at things the way we generally do.  It's commonsensical: it has a lens.  Monet has a sensibility.  We believe that a photograph is how things look; we believe that a recording is how things sound.  Both of these ideas are mildly fictional in one sense -- technology introduces some turbulence -- but deeply true on another.  Despite the abuses we can see around us, there is really no point quibbling with the basic truth-telling function of photographs.  Even as the photograph makes its way (thanks to digital tools) into flights of fancy, and starts to be unreal, paper money, there's still gold in the bank backing it up.  The currency of photographs doesn't float -- at least not yet.  And the same can be said of recorded music: manipulations abound.  Who knows whether or not Britney Spears really has a good voice?  Or if she even sings?  But outside the studio walls, there are still recorders you can buy, good ones, and you can prove to yourself that it works.  The machine can't tell the whole truth of what a sound is like -- and what would that be anyway? -- but it can't lie either.    Images were, of course, in some sense reproducible for hundreds of years before the photograph, because there was printing.  Musical sound was never distributable that way, until this century.  For music, the printing press and the photograph were invented at the same time: they are combined in the black wax disk.     And what formal changes in the art does this technology give rise to?    There's no such thing as "representational" music, in the way that there is representational painting.  There is no ideal of "accuracy" or "versimilitude" to be shrugged off.  There are, however, other ideals which were indeed shrugged off, around the time of the introduction of recorded music.    This introduction happened in two stages: before the Depression, and then after the second World War.  The period after the War is particularly interesting, and particularly close to home, since it saw the victory of rock and roll and the destruction of Tin Pan Alley.  These events still resonate.  Many sociological factors have been cited in the telling of this story, and it's been well-told.  But it seems important to footnote that story with the idea that, at least on its face, rock and roll music shares many qualities with expressionist and even impressionist painting.    Harmonically, the music is more flat, and simplified in musical form from what was standard in popular music before; musically, it uses primary colors.  It is more emotionally raw, with less formal indirection between lived experience and musical expression than can be found in the standards.  Valuing spontaneity and placing less weight on formal perfection, it more frequently obeys the impulse to authentically reflect the performer's inner state, or to rouse the audience into a powerful singular emotion.  It is participatory, it engages.  It changes the terms of the game, shifting the balance away from melody and harmony, toward rhythm.    One interesting thing about this toy model, this analogy, is that it predicts the success or failure of certain elements of rock music.  It would predict that, by being closer to the core of the musical movement, closer to the idea of expressionism, punk would succeed.  Prog rock would fail, by misunderstanding the basic terms of the game.    This says nothing at all, however, about hip hop.  Since there weren't any really important technological changes prior to hip hop's birth, perhaps its development is purely sociological.  Perhaps it could have happened any time in the hundred years after the invention of the record.    ? 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        I've been thinking about Daniel Dennett's Concept of Universal Design Space, which is closely akin to Borges' Library of Babel.    How can we make maps of human aesthetic creations?  An analogy: Musical Design Space  Take a very simple 12-tone melody, played on a small piano perfectly (collapsing, for now, the difference between musical text and musical performance).  Let's use the first phrase of Mary Had a Little Lamb.   The design space occupied by this piece of music has two axes: you only need two two dimensions to represent the music in Cartesian space.  Along the X axis, time steps, of some standard size.  Along the Y axis, running above the baseline, points or lines which indicate the pitch. A time step without a mark above it is a silence.  Only one note at a time can be played.    In this two-dimensional musical design space, Mary Had a Little Lamb would look like the following (in this rendition, I've put gaps between the notes).     E | -       - - ---- D |   -   - C |     -   +----------------        This set of axes is the whole design space needed to explore all the mini-melodies in the universe.  The "Mary" graph is one shape within that design space; its melody forms one possible constellation, and a fairly strong one, judging by its endurance in culture.  Whoever invented this melody made some "good moves".    The universal set of all (extremely simple) mini-melodies in this particular design space is directly analogous to the set of all books in the Library of Babel.  Here, however, the alphabet has only 13 characters (sticking to notes from one octave, plus silent "note").  So for melodies of 16 time-steps in length (like this one), there are 13^16 possible mini-melodies, or. . . 665 quadrillion.  That is an enormous number.  When I first imagined this example, I was hoping for a tractable corner of the Library of Babel, a little garden whose combinatorics could be managed by the human brain.  But despite the fact that this particular corner of musical Babel is extremely boring -- with a time-step of 1/3 a second, only accomodates melodies of 4 seconds in length -- is is completely unexlporable, within this universe, with any machine, when treated strictly as a combinatorial problem.  From this (and other considerations) I conclude that people do not deal with problems of musical creation as combinatorial problems -- or, if they do, they must encounter design spaces of a significantly different _shape_ than the one I imagined above.  We know empirically that the brain's capacity for sheer computation is quite limited.  The brain could probably not actually perform anything like an exhaustive search, or even a random search, of our mini-design space.    That is, when writing the novel, people do not open the door to Borges' Library of Babel.  Indeed, there must be paths through design space: "a largely invisible set of maze walls -- or channels or railroad tracks -- in the space of apparent possibility."     But I want to flesh out an account of how that might work, formally.   What does the maze actually look like?  What kind of maps or design space are actually possible, maybe tractable?  Forms may seem "emergent" while someone engages in the work of fashioning -- of discovering -- a particular thing, and in retrospect, certain developments _seem_ inevitable.    (But is there any such thing as inevitability?    We cannot know.  That is one of the fundamental insolubles -- a subset of the problem of free will, determinism, Lucretius' swerving atoms, and Schrodinger's dying cat.  Therefore, I'd like to approach questions of creation from the perspective of the creator's timeframe.  I'd like to avoid invoking the concept of inevitability, and stay clear of the tower of retrospection, from which everything seen seems fated.  I'd even like to avoid the concept of emergence, fond of it though I am, until its content can be specified without reference to some sort of determinism.)  I want to explore the specificity of the pathfinding creative process.  In human experience, it's not a railroad track -- it may be 'emergent' in some sense, there may be some sense in which it has reality as a 'trace'.  But is the concept of the trace doing any real work here?  I'm not sure about the utility of positing the existence of entities which only exist in retrospect -- can only be seen from the tower.  The trace may be important as a logical placeholder, but it sounds so strongly unfalsifiable that I'd rather steer clear.  I'd like to think a little bit about what people actually do, in time, faced with the pre-existed design envelopes in culture and in their heads.  What work does the creating mind -- endowed, perhaps, with a certain "energy" -- do within a design system?  In general terms, they encounter the rules, constraints, and customary proportions of the system before them, and they create a form which has a lively relation to those rules and proportions.  This brings pleasure for the artisan and for the audience (pleasure of more and less rarefied kinds, more and less sacred kinds, broader and narrower kinds).  These pleasures are why aesthetic forms exist.    Occasionally, a craftsman so fully understands the constraints of the aesthetic system that sees constraints that had gone unnoticed by other.  Perhaps (in the modernist tale) he wishes to exceed or change them.  Other times, a craftsman does not have a full understanding of the constraints, and his limited understanding leads him to trammel the constraints in ways which turn out, retrospectively, to have been valuable for some audience.  Sometimes people intend to imitate, but end up innovating by mistake.  Fortuitous accidents happen.  In any case, it seems important that, in the process of exploring certain items within creative design space, most of the items conform to the design space most of the time.  Sometimes an item is encountered which falls outside of known space, but it only violates the ordinary constraints in one or two ways.  There are no jazz scales in Mozart.    It also seems important than in the exploration process -- whether ordered or chaotic -- there comes a moment of _recognition_.  The artisan apprehends that some element may be aesthetically useful, and the definition of use-value in the arts is that something may be repeated.  Repetition is at the heart of aesthetic meaning.  An item springs from the void, by chance or experiment; the creating mind recognizes it; and then he intends it.    (It's a bit like eating.  I as a body am made of the materials that I have eaten, materials that were once lying around in the world in complete inanition.  Musical design space, by analogy, is made of elements that have been won from the void, elements that we now know that we can digest.  The second time I eat a thing -- a berry, a harmony -- it is food.)    What might have been accidental the first time (a note played wrongly) becomes incorporated into the artist's whole array of the deliberate.  He may seek out that sound again, later, that strange mistaken harmony, not even knowing that that is the object of his search.  Consciousness is not as important as intent here; artists often describe their flights of creative intuition in terms of hunch, restlessness, and hunting.  The second time the artist finds the weird harmony, there is meaning, and the design system is enlarged -- from the inside.   And even if this particular harmony, new to the artist, is old hat to others, his personal design system has been extended.  This is how an artist takes possession of a design envelope: by intending aesthetic elements that fall within larger and larger tracts of the possible.  Older artists will teach a younger one what they can impart (and what he can accept) of their design system, their set of acceptable harmonies, melodic shapes, what-have-you.  But the most vital of his aesthetic extensions (those that lie closest to his "identity" as an artist, whatever we suppose that to mean), are those which take their root in his own capability to recognize.   Accidents always happen, and are products of historical contingency.  But recognition does not always -- in fact usually does not -- happen.  By recognizing, and then repeating, a certain perceptible notion as though it were an aesthetic notion (an unusual harmony; a song structure; alliteration), someone states their idea of what the aesthetic envelope might include -- and what it might exclude, dispose of.  (Innovation is certainly not the constant dragging of more and more camels under the tent.)  To say the same thing in food terms: by treating some world-thing as an item of food, to be taken into the mouth and swallowed (a live snail, say), someone makes possible a different definition of cuisine, an altered edible universe.  The artist (or their proxy, or their imitator, or their group) introduces the aesthetic notion into a public, where, if it succeeds in bringing pleasure, it can now be more broadly repeated.  But perhaps we don't even need to talk of pleasure now -- if the notion incites the appetite for more repetition among some public, demand may arise to meet the supply.  There are often supply/demand imbalances between artists and a public: there is more supply than demand for jazz fusion.  Artists wish to fashion aesthetic elements from within its design system, and share these, and most audiences do not comply.  I think the same is true of American poetry.    Without a demand, the innovation runs into a dead end, and we (backward looking scholars, ranging over the high-water marks of an entire art or arts) may become their principal life-support system.  Or we may never find out about them at all (as might have happened with, say, Christopher Smart's poetry).    How does design space grow?  Imagine that the two-dimensional musical design space graphed out above was a complete definition of (brief, single-tone) music: 665 quadrillion songs.  Suppose Robinson Crusoe lives on a desert island with some well-tempered 12-tone conch shells.  He sets the shells up in a row.  Never having had much musical training in the first place, one of the only songs he knows is the melody of Mary Had a Little Lamb, which he plays by striking his conch shells with a stick.  Suppose that one day a coconut falls out of a tree onto one conch, just as Robinson Crusoe strikes another conch with his stick.  He is surprised, but he likes the sound.  He finds another stick.  If the conch-chord becomes part of Crusoe's regular repertoire, this breaks our simple design space -- there's no way to represent two sounds happening at once within that system.  So if we wish to create a map of the outer perimeters of Crusoe's musical potential, our analysis of his music must change.  We must have a larger and more complex mathematical system to account for his possible aesthetic products.  665 quadrillion is far too small.  Crusoe has begun exploring a design universe larger than the one he was in before.  Say that Crusoe plays the melody notes of Mary Had a Little Lamb with his left hand, and begins to pair each note with a right-handed harmony conch.  The only way we can accomodate this in our two-dimensional Cartesian design space is to state that Crusoe is playing two different songs.  But since he clearly isn't, we want an analysis that says that Crusoe is, indeed, playing only one song, and that that song is possible within one design space.  The difficulty with this, however, is that the song incorporates simultaneous events, and our two-dimensional graph has no notion of co-occurence.  How can we add this notion?  One way of doing this would be to adopt the MIDI style of musical notation.  MIDI is a way of writing down musical events as a list.  "At time step 1, note F is played.  At time step 3, note D is played.  At time step 6, note F is stopped.  At time step 7, E is played.  At time step 8, note D is stopped.  At time 11, E is stopped."  This list of MIDI events is notationally equivalent to writing out a graph like the following:   F | ----- E |        ---- D |   -----   +----------------   One can easily see that, for more complex music, the graph will soon resemble the sheets that are fed into a player piano.  It also resembles, not accidentally, those illuminated hymnals which monks used to sing over during the early development of polyphony.  But the graph is no longer a simple Cartesian function, pairing one set of axes with one function -- it is two functions laid on one set of axes.  It still doesn't allow a single Cartesian function to describe our music.    Another way to represent Crusoe's altered musical design space would be as as a three-dimensional graph, with one axis pointing out of the page.  From each mark on our Mary Had a Little Lamb graph, imagine a bar sticking out of the page a certain distance (bigger interval, longer bar).    Say that, for every note in the melody of Mary Had A Little Lamb, Crusoe adds a perfect fifth note with his right hand.  The graph we envision now looks like a roller coaster track, or a ribbon, exactly five steps wide.    What if the intervals are not all perfect fifths?  What if they change?  Then the width of the roller coaster changes.  What if one of the melody notes doesn't have a harmony note to go with it?  Then the roller coaster gets very thin, only as wide as a line.  Does this kind of ribbon-graph make any perceptual sense?  It surely does, since human perception is chorded.  We experience many things -- sounds, colors, smells -- by unconsciously adding their elements together.  This faculty is so powerful we're often unable to analyze the compound into its component parts.  (Most nonmusicians can never know which guitar strings are sounding which notes when someone strums the instrument.)  Training or special talent can only partially undo the fact that our experience consists of co-occuring events that are blended into one perception-color.  It seems unquestionable that there are many kinds of co-occuring events which humans are, in fact, neurally primed to understand in groupings.  This isn't even a matter of brain science: it's in the structure of our eyes.  It's in lower animals.  We multitask and filter.  This chording is particularly true of our aesthetic experience, and for a very good reason: artists have historically taken special advantage of those perceptual groupings which humans are least able to untangle.    I'll come back to this later.  For now, we have re-established a complete, if trivial, music, and a complete system for analyzing it.  We know the outer bounds of its design space.  No phenomena are missing from the graph that are present in the music.    But still we know that it's not a reasonable design space.  It makes some reasonable abstractions, but soon Crusoe will be discovering musical dynamics (if only because of the contingency that his left arm is bigger and more powerful than his right), tempo shifts (if only because he can't keep good time), and so forth.    The model, to even begin to be formally rigorous, has got to start growing more, just to accomodate the real conditions under which music is played.  How will loudness and softness levels fit into our graph?  We'll have to add a fourth dimension (hard to visualize -- it could be done by coloring the bar).  What if the two conches are struck with different firmness?  A fifth dimension.    If, for aesthetic reasons of his own, Crusoe fires his musket at the climax of one of his songs, instead of hitting a conch, then he has discovered "found sound".  He consciously invents a dimension along which variations can occur in his pieces of music -- invents an axis for the music-graph to occupy.    Axes can be invented (adding more dimensions to the space); axes can have their bounds extended (adding more notes to the scale -- more conches); axes can also be neglected.    To be continued.    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      >With the advent of the press, the economic bottleneck around reproducing  >texts virtually disappeared, so that a) more people could afford texts (and  >thus found it worth their while to be able to read them). Partly from the  >cheapening of reproduction, and partly from the democratizing effects of  >(a), a greater variety of texts came into printed circulation (notably  >broadsheets), fulfilling functions that had previously been taken care of  >by oral culture. Surely there are creaky points in this historical sweep.  >But to hold the pieces together...  >  >Rock and roll is not an outgrowth of western classical music. It *is* and  >outgrowth of European and African (or Euro-American and African-American)  >folk musics--and its availability as cheaply reproducible and consumable  >mass culture renders it analogous to the early modern broadsheet--a piece  >of popular culture appropriated and transformed by capital and reproduced  >for mass consumption.   Peter --  Think, though, of the typical way that common people (such as my grandfather in London) experienced music in, say, 1935 (or 1895). New, popular music, of a folk or non-classical variety (though it was actually enjoyed by virtually all classes) appeared on the radio, and yet was simultaneously published as printed sheet music (thanks to the printing press). It cost next to nothing to have an evening at home full of hours of music, provided that there was a piano, and a player, and a singer. Even in the working class London of leather tanners, which is where I'm drawing my knowledge from, there were always all three. From what I gather, many, many people from all walks of life spent a tremendous amount of their evening time reproducing popular music for themselves, in groups or singly.   There was, basically, no bottleneck that would restrict people's access to music and musical culture (they were, in fact, up to their eyeballs in the stuff). However, the way that the musical sound was _delivered_ and _shaped_ was quite different from what prevailed twenty years later.   By contrast, your printing press analogy relied on the distinction between mass oral culture and mass written culture -- the latter of which basically was _invented_ once the presses got going. Before that, oral culture was it.   So what I'm interested in is, yes, the Clement Greenberg angle (though I'm not sure who he is) which wants to speculate about the formal and social shifts occurred in popular musical culture when the performance system completed its transfer across the living room from the piano bench to the Victrola. (And kept going, up the stairs, into the kids' bedrooms.)   So my question of "What did records do to music?" does look, I think, much like the problem of "what did photography do to painting"? People had a visual culture by whose lights they interpreted, enjoyed, learned from, collected, coveted, and despised various painted artifacts. But by 1850, one aspect of the use of painting -- its capacity to represent a potential visual stimulus, of a similar grain and tenor to that of actual ocular experience -- was up for grabs. Photography was claiming the same terrain. Photographs had a very similar size and shape to paintings and drawings. All were equally distributable.   Visual culture already existed, and it accepted the photograph eagerly -- and then was changed by it. Other branches of visual culture grew (emotional or expressive applications of painting) or shrank (journalistic drawing).   Thus, I'm saying, musical culture existed, and accepted the idea of recording as a no-brainer. The "new" music took the same amount of time as the old, was played at a similar loudness, for similar reasons, and overall provided a very similar experience. The "same" songs could be played live or from a record. So why should things ever change?   But they did change. The genie that was in the flat black bottle turned out to have its own strange force.   And I think you're right that timbre became one of the big elements in the new music that came out of the bottle. Would it be wrong of me to suggest that timbre is analogous, in painting, to color? We would arrive at the Impressionists and Expressionists fairly quickly that way, which makes my job easy. ;)   Brandon 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Brandon,   Since I have ten other things I should be doing, I took a peek at your blog  only to find--voila--that you had been super active since I last seen it.  Tell your boss you need more work!   Anyway, I was thinking about your theory of rock music (which you have  doubtless by now long forgotten), which I think is interesting but wrong.  Nonetheless, more interesting than wrong.   You compare the advent of recorded music with that of photography, and  consider that rock and roll is analogous to  expressionism/nonrepresentationality as a new genre built on the base (as  it were) of the new technology.   I wonder, though, if you'd do better to rewind to the printing press  analogy, which I think is much more apt for rock music. In the bad old  days, a professional scribal class copied manuscripts for religious and  aesthetic (etc) consumption. They worked really hard, and copying took a  damn long time (and they had to practice their penmanship...do you think  any of us today could hold his own in secretary hand? Anyway, as a result  of the technological bottleneck of manuscript copying, texts were quite  expensive and hard to come by, and literacy was only really useful for  people whose economic station allowed them to consume manuscripts.  Moreover, the high overhead of producing any given text meant that only the  most valuable ones were preserved--unless you were a courtier with a lot of  free time on your hands, in which case you might have the opportunity to  circulate manuscripts of your own verse, etc....but I digress.   With the advent of the press, the economic bottleneck around reproducing  texts virtually disappeared, so that a) more people could afford texts (and  thus found it worth their while to be able to read them). Partly from the  cheapening of reproduction, and partly from the democratizing effects of  (a), a greater variety of texts came into printed circulation (notably  broadsheets), fulfilling functions that had previously been taken care of  by oral culture. Surely there are creaky points in this historical sweep.  But to hold the pieces together...   Rock and roll is not an outgrowth of western classical music. It *is* and  outgrowth of European and African (or Euro-American and African-American)  folk musics--and its availability as cheaply reproducible and consumable  mass culture renders it analogous to the early modern broadsheet--a piece  of popular culture appropriated and transformed by capital and reproduced  for mass consumption.   Of course, what I'm saying does not touch on the Clement Greenberg side of  your argument, that recorded music might somehow express a different set of  musical qualities by the virtue of its medium. I heard someone argue that  music in the 20th century has been not about melody or harmony or even  rhythm (let's face it; the sexiest rock and roll or funk rhythm is not a  particularly striking formal advance from the west african folk musics that  contributed to it), but rather timbre--since particular tonalities can be  reproduced in recorded media, tone color becomes the pallete of choice.   I actually think this cuts an interesting swath across the oral/print  culture picture as well. Print allowed the extensive reproduction of music,  so long as it was codified in a relatively simple design space (see Harvey  2002). I imagine that folk musics that were relatively outside this cycle  of print circulation and music education via print culture could rely more  heavily on timbre. The combination of a) mechanical reproduction of  folk/popular music for mass consumption and b) a continuous rather than  discreet mode of recording music seems to predict an environment in which  timbre is given much play. So Phil Spector or Sonic Youth are the (a  posteriori) predictable products of such a music media culture.   A propos of hip-hop, I think it has *everything* to do with recorded sound,  in its historical development if not in all of its formal elements. Hip-hop  is the collaging of already-produced sound (beats, dub versions of tracks)  with "live" vocal performance--mc'ing, etc. It is the means of  (re)production reappropriated in a popular music practice and resituated.   I keep thinking 'means of production', anyway, when I think about the  relative democratization of the recording industry that has been occuring  at an exponential pace--4 track recorders, sequencing software, etc. Print  culture never underwent such a democratization (until today, perhaps, what  with relatively cheap word processing, production software, internet  publication, blogging, etc), so it's much harder to make analogous  predictions. Any hypotheses?   PJ  
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm now working at the Accenture Technology Labs, in downtown Chicago:   urlLink http://www.accenture.com/accenturetechlabs 
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ** LEARN CRUCIAL THINGS AND BE SOCIAL **  Highlight the whole e-mail. Copy and paste into new e-mail, then change all the answers so they apply to you (it only takes about 4.2 minutes!!). Then send this to a whole bunch of people you know INCLUDING the person that sent it to you. The theory is that you will learn a lot of little known facts about your friends. Remember to send yours back to the person who sent it to you.  You never know what you'll learn. BE HONEST!  **Remember to send it back to the person who sent it to you.**   WHAT IS YOUR FULL NAME?  Brandon Lee Walter Harvey  WHAT IS YOUR PERMANENT EMAIL ADDRESS?  blh22@cornell.edu  WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST PET?  A gerbil.  It died under mysterious circumstances.  WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT FAVORITE BOARD GAME?  Chinese Checkers  WHY MIGHT THIS CHANGE?  War with China, loss of all my fingers, renewed interest in Backgammon,  which is, after all, possibly the oldest game in the world.  WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT FAVORITE MAGAZINE?  The New Goddamn Yorker  WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE SMELL?  Today, I propose that it must be that kind of edible play dough that  they make for children out of peanut butter, powdered sugar, and . . .  what else?  Other things, things that adults think up.  Cream of  Tartar, perhaps.  I think I only played with this stuff once.  WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE WORD FOR BLUE?  Cobalt, I guess.  I could never really get behind azure the way some  people seem to be able to do.  HOW MANY RINGS BEFORE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE?  2.3  WHO IS IT?  It's my mother, and she wants to tell me a recipe.  HOW FAR CAN YOU SEE TODAY?  The sky is absolutely cloudless and the cool air moves through the city  with a long stride, eastward, and holds nothing back.  Thus, from the  36th floor, you can see Michigan.  WHICH WAY IS THE TRAIN GOING?  North, with rolling left turns toward the northwest every now and then.  HOW HIGH?  At the level of the many rooftops, which were built at many different  times and at many different angles.  Nearly none of those times was the  1950's, 60's, or 70's, thankfully, so most of the buildings are made of  natural, sturdy materials, and they exist on a human size and scale.  WHAT ABOUT BUILDINGS FROM THE 1930'S AND 1940'S?  There was almost no building during this period, since first the  Depression and then the War diverted resources away from the  construction of new homes.  The post-WWII building boom seems to have  bypassed urban Chicago, except for some high rises along the water.   This turn of events might have seemed alarming at the time, but it was  ultimately a benefit to the city, which now has a huge stock of  (semi)reasonably priced, well-made two and three story brick  structures, with large windows and wood floors, and neighborhoods full  of mature trees.  WOULD YOU BUY SUCH A DWELLING?  I would buy one.  I may perhaps buy one.  I don't currently have the  money.  I am hoping that the real estate market will experience a  downturn in the coming year.  WHY A DOWNTURN?  Rents are stable while home prices are still rising and home sales are  setting records, which may indicate a real estate bubble.  Once  interest rates go up even a little bit, I wonder whether the tide of  consumer real estate spending will recede, exhausted.  That would be  nice.  WHAT IS THE DRIVER OF THE OTHER TRAIN DOING?  She is leaning out of her cab window, looking backwards over the long  platform, and making sure that everyone is on board.  She is smiling  sideways at one of the platform employees, and she is wearing tight  gloves on her hands.  Then, with one more glance, her mouth clasps  itself up like a change purse and she slips deftly back into the cab,  leaving an empty metal frame around an open window.  There is a pause  before the train starts to move away.  She is inside, driving it.  WHY IS CINEMA NECESSARY?  Because photographs can't grasp a thing like that.  WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE ALBUM?  I think that it is still Jeff Buckley, "Grace".  I listened to it again  today while rearranging the furniture in my bedroom.  WAS SARAH PLEASED WITH THE NEW FURNITURE FORMAT?  She was.  WHAT ARE YOUR FAVORITE FOODS?  I especially like Beef Wellington, lemon rice, Phish Food, cold milk,  cold water, good bread.  CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA?  That question is too hard.  WHAT DID YOU EAT AT POTLUCK DINNER TODAY?  Beef Burgundy, served steaming over white rice, made by Sarah Mesle.   Potatoes hight "Church Banquet Potatoes", made by Kati Phillips.   Leavings from another party, including brownies, carted here by Karen  Pagani.  HOW MANY MILES HAVE YOU DRIVEN IN THE LAST MONTH OUTSIDE YOUR HOME TOWN?  About 4,000.  WAS BURNING MAN THE SAME, WORSE, OR BETTER?  The same.  WHEN DID THE SEPTEMBER WEATHER SLIP INTO THE SIXTIES?  In the third week, it suddenly changed.  You realized, one morning,  that you needed to remember to close the door while showering.  And you  wanted socks.  WAS THAT THE SAME WEEK THAT YOU CAME DOWN WITH A COLD?  It was.  I almost always wake up with a dry throat, since I usually  sleep with my mouth open -- a childhood of ear infections, this or that  mucous membrane gone haywire, trained me to it.  But when the dryness  behind my tongue outlasts morning tea and toast, I know that I am in  for it.  DO YOU STILL HAVE YOUR TONSILS?  I have them!  I have them right where I want them.  WHEN DID YOU START YOUR NEW JOB?  On September 12.  WHY NOT ON SEPTEMBER 11?  The scheduled monthly orientation sessions always begin on a Wednesday,  which would have meant starting work on September 11 this year.  So  they silently changed the day of the orientation.  WHAT IS IT THAT YOU MAKE?  Prototypes and demos for technologies that could, in some form, become  practical in three to five years, or less.  Some of it is software  (kinds of services, systems), some hardware (gizmos, combinations of  existing gizmos).  WHO ARE YOUR CO-WORKERS?  Nerds and cultured nerds.  One wears a turban.  Another resembles no  one in human experience -- no one I can think of -- more than Sam  Eagle, the blue disapproving eagle Muppet. There are neither ties nor  blue jeans in my workplace.  WHAT IS THE NAME OF YOUR FIRM?  Accenture.  WHAT IS THE NAME OF YOUR CUBICLE?  I have tried not to get too attached to my cubicle just yet.  There's a  'hotelling' system which governs these things and makes them subject to  change.  I don't understand it.  ALL WE ARE IS DUST IN THE WIND?  Right.  ARE YOU DIRECTLY RESPONSIBLE?  No, I am in an assistant position.  WHAT IS YOUR OFFICIAL TITLE?  "Experienced Analyst".  WHY NOT PLAIN OLD ANALYST?  Because they decided to give me one year of credit for my previous work  experience at a tiny startup, where I tried with limited success to  inveigle ordinary teachers into digitally scanning their artwork and  publishing it on the Internet.  I made T-shirts myself out of kid's art.  CAN TEACHERS SCAN ARTWORK?  Some can.  Many are simply unable to do this because of technological  or budgetary limitations.  Many would rather die.  WAS THAT AN ALLUSION TO THE PRINCESS BRIDE?  Christmas Carol.  DO YOU LIKE WORKING UP GIZMOS AND PROTOTYPES MORE THAN YOU LIKE MAKING  T-SHIRTS?  Yes, much more.  I am absorbed (for a change) for hours at a time.  It  feels fine.  And I may never again in life come this close to the title  "inventor".  FINISHED ANY GOOD BOOKS LATELY?  No.  Leaving the school system made me, if possible, more ambitious to  read more, and different, kinds of books.  I am now completely  ineffectual.  I have no guidance.  I finish nothing.  PROVIDE TITLES OF BOOKS YOU HAVE FAILED TO FINISH  Peter Pan, Russell's History of Western Philosophy, The Happy Prince,  Principles of Macroeconomics, Archaeology, Process Theology, Herzog,  Cryptonomicon, The Princess Bride, Geek Love, Beowulf, Lives of the  Poets  YOU MUST HAVE FINISHED SOMETHING.  Yes, I did.  The Corrections.  It was damn good.  Not sure that it was  great-great, but it was great-good-solid.  Though depressing, yes, and  long.  But great!  I mean solid.  I am happy that I finished it.   Jonathan Franzen is sweet.  But he needs to move away from the East  Coast for a while.  WHAT WAS THE LAST MOVIE THAT YOU SAW?  A Streetcar Named Desire.  It's utterly fantastic, and I'm not one to  say that.  I am no classic film fan, and never did buttonhole anyone to  try to make them see, say, North by Northwest.  Most old movies require  (from me) so much accomodation, so much indulgence of their little  flourishes and gusts, that you have to hold up some idea of "film  history" between yourself and the movie to try to make it pay off the  way everyone said it would.  As against all that: A Streetcar Named  Desire is still immediate.  WHAT OTHER MOVIES ARE THIS WAY, IN YOUR OPINION?  Night of the Living Dead The Road Warrior Sunset Boulevard  IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON, DEAD OR ALIVE WHO WOULD IT BE?  Ralph Waldo Emerson.  THAT'S ODD.  He's the only one around here with any sense of possibility.  I'd meet  Scott Fitzgerald, but everything he touched was doomed.  WHAT ABOUT THOREAU, THEN?  I think reading Thoreau is probably a lot more exciting than meeting  Thoreau.  AND MEETING EMERSON, THAT OLD PURITAN, WOULD REALLY BE A BARREL OF  LAUGHS?  COME ON.  He was the last enthusiastic man in America who wasn't bitter, insane,  or finally destroyed.  ARE YOU EXAGGERATING?  A little bit.  
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      from Amy.   ate·lier    French, from Middle French  astelier  woodpile, from  astele  splinter, from Late Latin  astella , diminutive of Latin  astula , diminutive of  assis , board Date:	1699 1 : an artist's or designer's studio or workroom 2 : WORKSHOP  
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a fun Monday-morning NYT rarebit about why you, as well, should be playing computer games, or at least kibbutzing about the politics thereof.  I haven't seen the Sims yet.  But the online version they're making will hold 1 million players.  1 million!  This is not uninteresting.  This cannot but be interesting.   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2002/11/24/magazine/24SIMS.html  
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Ellen Feiss: the interview!  It's a really good interview.   urlLink http://www.browndailyherald.com/post/stories.asp?ID=269  
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink http://www.visualthesaurus.com   This is a fun exercise in visualization, though I can't figure out how to make the thing I'm interested in actually stop wiggling around.  My current work is in the realm of information visualization, so this company, along with inxight.com, groxis.com, antarctica.net, is our "competition."  
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This from an old uncle of mine who sometimes sneaks into my house and reads my email.  Here, he seems also to have read the 11/14 post::::  D'you know, I just had an experience which might complicate your theory of aesthetic necessity.  At around noon today, my subway car stopped at a station in the middle of a boomtown, and suddenly filled with scores of deformed, autistic children.  Out of sheer ennui, I buggered every last one of them.  Now call it love if you want, but to us, it was just a good time.  
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This from Peter, in response to my post from 11/14::::  Two quick notes. "Good," according to at least one dictionary, is a cognate of "gather."  In support of your theory: a boomtown becomes beautiful when it becomes a hometown. Think Hong Kong.  I have to think about this more. I think you are pulling a fast one somewhere where love, beauty, and attention intersect. Old Kant would be angry. I'm not sure if I'd move so fast to 'resource allocation'--is political economy really the right register? I don't know why this feels wrong, but it does.  You don't really seem to believe in judgment--if I'm not wrong, your analysis of will is eliminativist. You think that the experience of making a judgment is an artifact of how you have already spent your time. This would also seem to suggest that beauty is completely a subjective phenomenon. Really? I like your weights and muscles metaphor, but I think it's out of key with the rest of your thought.  
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      thoughts from the train, november 13.    ---- For someone to say, “I find such and such a thing ugly” – a room,  or a painting,  or a face – is often simply to say, “I have no intention of spending time with this object.”  It’s largely a statement of how to pursue the course of a life history: a choice,  rather than a judgment.    ---- We evaluate things now – as things that we are living with – and can’t always reach out to the judgments we might give, had we world enough and time.  Our situation is urgent, and so our aesthetic judgments often take on an aspect of resource allocation.    The subway car I am in now, I don’t particularly wish to be in.  From the looks of things, most of the people here feel the same way.  Is it the thin, institutional lighting?  The jerky motion and swaying?  The unvarnished visual feel of backlots, unfinished and untended parts of the city – its calluses – reeling past our windows?    Perhaps, but perhaps not.  There’s a poetry in this, too, and some have sung it: some have called this journey a place, not not a purgatory.  (Think of the marvellous train ride at the end of the House of the Seven Gables.) And they are right: I am on their side.    But today, I call the train ugly, and I am also right, and there is no contradiction.  This train is ugly to me, now, because I refuse just now to spend time in it.  I am, in my mind, lending my time to something else.  (I say lending, rather than giving, because if I could completely give myself over to my private pool of thought (as it’s so easy for children to do), then my physical placement would indeed vanish.  As it is, the residue of this subway world lingers among my ideas, and oppresses me.)  The subway-place is the victim of my wish to be elsewhere: home.   ---- Why is there no contradiction, between knowing that a thing has a Beauty – the beauty of mobility and possibility, the beauty of modernity and efficiency, the beauty of rails and a public, and the beauty of a city, which is a living thing – and suffering from it nonetheless?  It is because the two judgments don’t quite touch each other, in much the same way that the equations of traffic engineering almost, but don’t quite, impinge on the reality of a driver.  They take their truth at different levels.  So things are, really, objectively, human and beautiful, like a train system, can give a subjective sense of suffering.  And rhe reverse case, of an innately ugly thing rendered luminous, is easy to understand: the deformed child, perhaps autistic and biologically incapable of any emotional function: someone loves him.  This is not a fact to be put on television (though it so often is): it’s an incredibly harsh fact, and it’s also a strange miracle of human attention.  The day that child emerged from the womb, someone began to ingest the idea that this, this object, is what their time is tied to.    The parent can freely admit that the strangers of the public world – who have the leisure to consider the object without any urgency – will not find the child beautiful.  And yet the sight of it is a genuine experience of beauty.  We find beautiful what we must learn.  Most grandmothers, most houses, are quite shabby, and most are beautiful, considered from within their circle.    The force of my claim is that these regular eddies in the current of human aesthetic judgment are neither romantic, irrational, or sentimental.  They are proof, in fact, that our sense of beauty is a pact with necessity.    I am talking about beauty and aesthetic judgment as the most practical things in the world; as weights and muscles, respectively.  We may not name them, but we do use them.  Forgive me for naming them.  ---- Boomtowns are places where everyone is moving through a stage, looking to the other side, staying put just long enough to get their and get out.  Boomtowns are the ugliest places on earth.  No one loves them.    ---- Beauty isn’t all subjective.  I suspect there may be a universal beauty.  But, like traffic equations, or the mechanics of crowd psychology, it can only occasionally be invoked from inside the system.  We do sometimes find harmonies, when we’re lucky or good.  People all over the world respond to symmetry, proportion, repetition, and regularity.  It’s in us, somewhere.  But that kind of beauty is a promise of order and possibility – and only a promise.  The deformed child is signed, sealed, and delivered.  Though freakish genetically, socially, probabilistically – murdered in some cultures, sacralized in others – this being IS, and by existing, it spreads a hard and strange experience of beauty.  The bystanders who look away, or the friends who smile politely, are immune to it.  They have made their choice.  They will spend no time.  Life is short.  But the circle of people close around that child, while knowing very well that (for example) regular features are pleasing to every human eye, and that evolution has built us to seek the high promise of the symmetrical and the proportional, can still have the experience of an enveloping beauty by accepting and absorbing – rather than attempting to merely outlast – this lumpish being, this unbeautiful object that their life history has led them to.      
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ps. there was a little organic food shindig going on across the street from the downtown building where i work.  i bought a very cold, hard, red pomegranate for a dollar.  it needed to ripen for about a week before being eaten.  I put it in the pocket of my new wool coat. 
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I bought myself a really good notebook.  It's of a kind called "Moleskine".  Have you heard of this?  It's a kind or brand of notebook.  "It is two centuries now that moleskine has been the legendary notebook of European artists and intellectuals, from Van Gogh to Henri Matisse, from the exponents of the historical avant-garde movements to Ernest Hemingway.  Many are the sketches and notes, ideas and emotions that have been jotted down and harboured in this trustworthy pocket-sizes travel companion before being turned into famous pictures or the pages of beloved books."    Besides all that, it is light, but beautifully bound in black, hard but not cumbersome binding.  The pages are an eggshell color, and there's a ribbon bookmark sewn in.  It has an elastic to hold it shut.  You know how some designs from the earlier parts of last century -- riding the back of the new modernist possibilities but still reflecting a deep-seated wisdom about how people want to make use of things -- became so colossally beautiful that no one has yet managed to re-forge them . . this, anyway, is how I feel about the Leica; the man's three-piece suit; the fountain pen; the ship; the pipe; the novel.    So I found the notebook version of this.  They stopped making them for a while, but they've started again.  
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      An excellent article on file-sharing and piracy from the O'Reilly publishing folks.   urlLink http://www.openp2p.com/pub/a/p2p/2002/12/11/piracy.html   
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a quote from Emerson that Peter found.  It exactly backs up some of what I was trying to say in the post of Nov 14.  For the word "poetry", in the following, substitute the name of some current art form with a wider audience and more cultural impact.  For, as it is dislocation and detachment from the life of God, that makes things ugly, the poet, who re-attaches things to nature and the Whole,--re-attaching even artificial things, and violations of nature, to nature, by a deeper insight,--disposes very easily of the most disagreeable facts.  Readers of poetry see the factory-village, and the railway, and fancy that the poetry of the landscape is broken up by these; for these works of art are not yet consecrated in their reading; but the poet sees them fall within the great Order not less than the bee-hive, or the spider's geometrical web.  Nature adopts them very fast into her vital circles, and the gliding train of cars she loves like her own.   
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Google Labs  is doing some interesting things.     urlLink http://labs.google.com   I especially like the "sets" function.  It gives the illusion of generating -- or rather, it does generate -- a real semantic network, producing items that are near each other in a real-world human meaning system.  It's an illusion because the machine, as I understand it, has no model of "meaning", and no semantics built into it at all.  Such models have always been insanely hard to create (or very specialized, and very hand-crafted).  Much work was done, with no great success.    This "Sets" tool just skips the idea of meaning altogether.  If items are found together in the documents and lists that humans make (the ones they put on the web, anyway), then if we sift the documents the right way, our method can suggest things that might group together meaningfully, _for humans_.  The computer doesn't have any claims to meaning; it just has this method.  And it's nothing but a method, there's no oversight of the results -- they are often bad.  Try typing in  the words "crane" and "shovel".  What works well is to type in a few names; do the names of a couple of jazz greats.  The Google Glossary is maybe less interesting theoretically, but it's actually damn useful.    
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      An Accenture publication called "Centerpoint" just interviewed me, as a new member of the research labs.     Your favorite (computer) language:    . . . has not yet been invented.  But it's going to be great.  Current PDA:     My newest device has a black leather cover, a bookmark sewn into the binding, and eggshell-colored unlined paper.  It's fast, too.  How do you explain your job to your family?      I tell them that I'm an inventor.  My job is to make wiser gizmos, somehow.   What's the worst bug you've encountered (or--gulp--committed) and what havoc did it wreak?    All the really vexing bugs think that they're features.  For example, the message "Abort, retry, fail".  Or that paperclip thing in MS Office.  These are things that alienate people from computing -- they destroy the relationship to a good tool.    Besides your cell phone, which gadget do you use the most?    Cellphone?  Gadget?  Who has the time?  I like a meerschaum pipe, a German car, a good kitchen knife, or a ballpoint pen.  The best technologies are the ones worn down and polished by long, intelligent use.  I might get a cellphone in ten years.     Have you ever persuaded someone--friend, relative, the person next to you on a transcontinental flight who only wanted to sleep--to buy a particular gadget?  Which, and how?    On planes, I try to get people to read Moby Dick.     What was the first electronic device you took apart to see how it worked?  Did you get it back together again?  It was something with a little gearbox inside, full of white plastic gearlings.  And no, those things never, ever go back together again.  It's pure entropy.   Describe (as tastefully as possible) your fantasy convergence device.  I think that the things that make _people_ converge, in physical spaces, are the most important technologies.  Getting people to converge in virtual spaces is fairly exciting, too.  So I'd like a system -- a network, and a set of interfaces to it -- that would do both.  Television, the web, and online gaming are not that system, though they suggest elements of it.  IM may point a way forward.   How would you pitch your current project to someone in an elevator?  We're trying to put a book's worth of information all on one screen, sort of like a really smart piece of microfiche.   What piece of advice would you give to the young people of today?  I had a physics professor who met Einstein once, as a young student at Oxford.  So I'll just relate what he said to me.  "We met Einstein in a hallway.  They asked us if we had any questions for Herr Doktor Einstein, and we didn't know what to say.  So they asked Einstein if he had anything to say to the students.  He said yes.  He said, 'Never believe anything that you read in the newspapers.'"  
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Dear Google ,  I have been very good all year.  And I DO have an amazon.com wishlist.  Please spread the news.    Your friend, Brandon 
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       My new favorite genre   "'The Recruit,' writes A. O. Scott in the N.Y. Times, "seems like a spy thriller, but it really isn't. Sure, there are car and foot chases, some gunplay, a lot of breathless exposition and the frenetic uploading and downloading of files that is a staple of the modern high-tech Hollywood suspense film.   "But for all of its slick, manufactured suspense, and a 'surprise twist' that will come as a surprise to exactly no one, this movie belongs to a very special genre: the Al Pacino crazy mentor picture."
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I have been realizing a little more how deeply linked most progressive ideas are to a belief in inifinite human malleability.  (Once this was called the "Perfectibility of Mankind").  I don't believe in such malleability -- people will keep redicovering violence, war, guile, sexual differences, on whatever field you leave them to play upon.  But I do believe in progressivism.  (I also believe in realizing when you've got a good thing going, and not trashing it.  Are those completely opposed ideals?)  Here's Dan Dennett sifting the same set of problems, trying again to get the Left's head out of its social constructionist ass.   urlLink http://chronicle.com/free/v49/i21/21b00701.htm  
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Michele, in Boston, and things she find amusing or clever.   urlLink http://www.geocities.com/michele_ming_shan_smith/amusing_interesting.htm  
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      David Brooks on why a populist politics is (apparently) so hard to sell to the American public.  "The most telling polling result from the 2000 election was from a Time magazine survey that asked people if they are in the top 1 percent of earners. Nineteen percent of Americans say they are in the richest 1 percent and a further 20 percent expect to be someday. So right away you have 39 percent of Americans who thought that when Mr. Gore savaged a plan that favored the top 1 percent, he was taking a direct shot at them."   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2003/01/12/opinion/12BROO.html  
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       A tiny computer network that uses water as its transmission medium.   Cheeky.   urlLink http://www.coin-operated.com/projects  
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I found my name in the digits of pi.  And you probably can, too.   http://pi.nersc.gov 
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      A letter I'm sending to the New York Review of Books in response to a  urlLink review.    Darwinian Storytelling    By H. Allen Orr  The Blank Slate: The Modern Denial of Human Nature  by Steven Pinker Viking, 509 pp., $27.95   Dear Editor,  The last section of H. Allen Orr's review of Steven Pinker's "The Blank Slate" suffers from a particularly sloppy logical move which brings down the tone of an otherwise lucid, rigorous review.    Orr wishes to chide Pinker for his reductionist politics and shallow idea of history.  Fair enough.  Orr also claims that the idea of the tabula rasa is dead, and Pinker is kicking a dead horse.  And this is fair.  (He does disingenuously pretend that no one holds to the idea at all any more; or perhaps he really thinks so -- if so, Professor Orr should leave the biology quad more often.)  Then suddenly, with no warning, toward the end of his review, Orr rushes to the aid of the tabula rasa idea (which no one believes anyway) -- and why?  Because it has had some good _ethical_ consequences.  He muses, "if [Pinker's anti-blank slate] views had held from the time of Locke . . . [would] the liberal ethic Pinker reflexively reaches for be there?"    Orr goes on to let us know that he thinks the tabula rasa idea is actually synonymous with liberal values _in_general_.  He even decides to call them "Blank Slate liberal values", to coin a phrase in his last sentence.  And he leaves off the review with the very strong implication that we simply can't do without the tabula rasa, because that would be to abandon our values.  This is simply absurd.  Using the same fallacy, any person of faith can argue the existence of God, on the strange claim that without a strong belief in God throughout many of the cultures and times of human history, would love and charity be there at all?  Without Jesus Christ, would "the liberal ethic Pinker [err, Orr] reflexively reaches for be there?"    The idea of God may or may not correspond to something, but the ethical consequences of believing in God have no bearing whatsoever on the validity of the idea.  The idea of the tabula rasa, unlike the idea of God, happens to admit evidence -- and the evidence is getting very clear.  Pinker's book is, as Orr points out, kicking a dead horse (though it's one that many nonscientists in the humanities do still ride.)  It's weird that Orr thinks that to save western ethics he, too, needs to saddle up that utopian pony for one last turn around the grounds.  This is hardly the way to argue with the Pinkerites, or with anyone else, for that matter.   
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Thanks to TJ    Ladies and gentlemen, I bring you...  TimeCube!!!  urlLink http://www.timecube.com   urlLink http://www.satanosphere.com/story/2001/7/28/152548/138     --T 
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Is it OK to despise Bush, and support miliary action nonetheless?  A review of a Kenneth Pollack book called  The Case for Invading Iraq .   urlLink http://www.observer.com/pages/story.asp?ID=6862  
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Motor Car On Every Train is Devoted To the Accomodation of Smokers    A series of old maps and guides to the Chicago L system.  Check out the cover of the 1934 booklet.   urlLink http://www.chicago-l.org/maps/route/#1892 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       On this web page there is some data about how much of different media people are consuming.  (It's not the main point of the (pretty interesting) article, but just look under the heading "Consumption of Information".)     urlLink http://www.sims.berkeley.edu/research/projects/how-much-info/summary.html#consumption     It occurred to me that, moving into the future, the amount of radio people listen to must be fairly consistent, not given to drastic changes, since the time that people spend commuting, or simply driving around, certainly is not going down any time soon.   So in the foreseeable future, the audio market, at least as it's directed to people who are mobile, should be quite safe from the ravages of our visual culture.    The research numbers sort of give the lie to what I said, but just a little bit.  People are listening to AUDIO about the same amount.  But they're listening to recorded audio more, and live radio less.  Radio consumption went down by something like 8% over the period of 1992-2000 (comparable to the shrinkage of newspapers).  But recorded music consumption was up by 15%.   So as an overall, the amount of time people spend getting plain old waves in the ear is fairly constant over that period.    (And that chunk of media-interface-time is 15-20 times bigger than the count of Internet-eyeball-hours.)  Right now, all the techie excitement in audio is around personal devices like the Rio, the iPod, etc -- solitary little devices that make your home library available to you.  Which is great as far as it goes.  Storage will be cheaper; someone will figure out how to do DRM; then you'll have a gajillion songs in your pocket.  In a couple of hops of Moore's Law, we'll have every song we ever heard in our pocket (or every song we can afford).  But that's got to stop being interesting sometime.  These are cool devices, and they're personal, but there's a difference between being personal and being social.  These are not social devices.  People want to hear what other people are up to; being alone in a huge library is solipsistic, chaotic, impersonal.  So I think there's an interesting angle there for the evolution of people on the radio; radio will have to compete with a Borges library.  Or, perhaps more likely, these devices won't attract a truly general public _until_ they have some strong social valence.  (Computers needed email and chat to get them over a certain demographic hump.  Just so . . .  )  The research project I'm working on right now is an attempt to suggest a revamped notion of (at least talk) radio. 
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       A document from Amnesty International on the systematic use of torture in Iraq.    urlLink http://web.amnesty.org/ai.nsf/Recent/MDE140082001!Open    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It turns out that people who are very interested in cars recognize cars with the same brain circuitry that they use to recognize faces.  In simple lab tests, people who know cars very well had a _harder_ time recognizing isolated pieces of cars (they process wholes, as everyone does with faces).  And their recognition process slowed down when they were shown "an image consisting of parts of both faces and cars", suggesting overloaded circuitry.  I wonder what else lies along this route.    I would like to know why blue jeans match with everything.  I think it's because they're the color of the sky.   urlLink http://www.newscientist.com/news/news.jsp?id=ns99993479   
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Children's letters to our President Bush.   urlLink http://www.whitehouse.org/kids/letters.asp  
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Research I came across.     "Noodles are one of the most difficult foods for a robot to handle due to their shape, flexibility and tendency to intertwine. A general method of a robotic aid enabling a quadriplegic to eat Japanese noodles in broth has been investigated."   Noodles handled by a robot   ----------------------------      Too much             3%      Appropriate or less   76%      None              21%   ----------------------------   urlLink http://www.ritsumei.ac.jp/se/~tejima/theme-e.html#noodle   
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        For once, then, something.     Roy Orbison wrapped in cling film.   urlLink http://www.michaelkelly.fsnet.co.uk/karl.htm   
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Great Wall of China is causing plant species on opposite sides to diverge genetically. Sweet!   urlLink http://www.nature.com/nsu/030414/030414-3.html    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't know that Orson Scott Card was writing a column.  Here's one, a lucid little piece on regulation and the (sheerly theoretical) concept of a "free market".  Nothing new, but all (as you would hope) well-put.   urlLink  http://www.ornery.org/essays/warwatch/2003-01-13-1.html  
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       A touching music video.  Essential viewing.  Requires sound.   urlLink http://www.zen15631.zen.co.uk/bb.mpg    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Utah Notes , thanks to Amy E.  The mine where my Dad was an engineer for many years has a web site with some  urlLink pictures .  Kennecott Copper mine, which is the largest open pit mine in the world, is three and a half miles across and a mile deep.  It is located right next to Salt Lake City.   
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Also from the hometown -- the spiral jetty is back!  The level of the Great Salt Lake is low enough that this old earthwork artwork has reemerged.   urlLink see   And a touch of fine writing surfaces from the Deseret News -- that was unexpected.  "The jetty curls into the lake where the water is an eerie lemonade pink because of algae growth. Nearby are black basalt boulders that apparently tumbled down from the adjacent Promontory Mountains. Across a stretch of driftwood and sagebrush, the boulders meet the lake -- and at that point, with the lake lowering, they are encrusted with dazzling white salt.   "The jetty is exposed at the base, then farther out the boulders lining its sides stick up, white with brilliant salt crystals. As it reaches into deeper lake water, waves break on gleaming white lumps of rock. The pastel lake shades from pinkish into blue. Distant islands in Utah's inland sea, and even more distant mountains on the opposite shores, are a pale purple."
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "On June 2, the Federal Communications Commission is planning on authorizing sweeping changes to the American news media.  The rules change could allow your local TV stations, newspaper, radio stations, and cable provider to all be owned by one company.  NBC, ABC, CBS and Fox could have the same corporate parent.  The resulting concentration of ownership could be deeply destructive to our democracy.  "Congress is supposed to guard against monopoly power.  But the  upcoming rule change could change the landscape for all media and usher in an era in which a few corporations control your access to news and entertainment.  Please join me in asking Congress and the FCC to support a diverse, competitive media landscape by going to:  http://www.moveon.org/stopthefcc/  "You can also automatically have your comments publicly filed at the FCC.  "When the folks at MoveOn.org talk to Congresspeople about this issue, the response is usually the same: "We only hear from media lobbyists on this.  It seems like my constituents aren't very concerned with this issue."  A few thousand emails could permanently change that perception.  Please join this critical campaign, and let Congress know you care." 
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Gertrude Stein article in the New Yorker this week.  Written by a Stein novice who doesn't even seem to like Stein's writing, but there you are.  It's confusing, stimulating, and generally good fun to look over Gertrude Stein's bio regardless of the circumstance -- her life was mindbendingly her own creation.    They even made a (negative) mention of Stanzas in Meditation, which is a poem I tried to write on once.  I like this part.   Part III , Stanza X  Tell me darling tell me true Am I all the world to you And the world of what does it consist May they be a chance to may they be desist This came to a difference in confusion Or do they measure this with resist with Not more which. 
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Washington Post Style Invitational contest asked readers to submit  instructions for something (anything), written in the style of a famous person. The winning entry was The Hokey Pokey as written by W. Shakespeare:  O proud left foot, that ventures quick within Then soon upon a backward journey lithe. Anon, once more the gesture, then begin: Command sinistral pedestal to writhe. Commence thou then the fervid Hokey-Poke, A mad gyration, hips in wanton swirl. To spin! A wilde release from Heavens yoke. Blessed dervish! Surely canst go, girl. The Hoke, the poke -- banish now thy doubt Verily, I say, 'tis what it's all about.  This puts me in mind of a little poster that someone put on a bulletin board the Burning Man festival a few years ago.  It was called   The Hokey Pokey   All dancers form a circle, Facing the Center.  1.) the singer will tell you which body parts to "put in" the circle and also when to turn yourself around.  2.) when the singers sing "Hokey Pokey" all dancers wave their hands in the air as they bow to the center of the circle.  3.) during the secions of music with no instruction, dancers may dance "free style" in the center of the circle.  
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Internet!  Some kid videotapes himself trying out some lightsaber moves.  The videotape falls into the wrong hands.  Zeitgeist ensues!   urlLink http://www.teamabuse.com/toxic/stuff/swk.htm   
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Audio signals are an important (and underrated) source of contextual information.  For example, in the case of a complex, multivariable process where you want to be able to detect (subtle or sudden) changes, over time, sound can give you everything you need and still leave your eyes and hands free, e.g. the stethoscope, the Geiger counter, sonar, hard drive chatter.    I've been thinking about applications for sound lately, and it's kind of shame that there's no good way to deliver sound to a single person, except through headphones, which are obstructive and have big downsides for social interaction.  (And loudspeakers, of course, are rooted in a single place; their signal is public and diffuse.)    Here's an article about sound-focusing through a technology called HSS.  Two high-frequency wave signals are sent out in parallel; the different between them, mathematically, is a third signal.  When (and wherever) the two signals interfere, the third sound is produced.    Breathless, but lots of suggested applications  urlLink here .
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Archiving on Blogger seems completely broken for now, but they say they're upgrading their software.  Hopefully in the next few weeks this blog will actually have a continuous archive. 
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Italics added   "William Shatner's ex-wife has sued him for breach of contract over breeding privileges of three American saddlebred stallions. . . .   "'Mr. Shatner's offer to provide semen from the three stallions in question  in frozen form is unacceptable  to Ms. Lafferty,' says the lawsuit, filed in late April in Woodford County Circuit Court. 'Potential buyers of the breeding privileges  do not want the semen in frozen format. '"  
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      At Paignton Zoo in southwest England, six Sulawesi crested macaques (apes) have been at work on six typewriters.  Here is the result of their efforts so far.  They're calling it "Notes Toward the Complete Works of William Shakespeare."   urlLink http://www.vivaria.net/experiments/notes/publication/   Here is a Yahoo article about said  urlLink efforts . 
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Moleskine   These are the best notebooks and sketchbooks I've ever used, in terms of weight, feel, paper quality, paper color.  I like the rounded page corners that don't get bent, sewn bindings, oilcloth covers, a ribbon placemarker, and they're really light.  My current Moleskine notebooks are my day planner and my lab research notebook.     urlLink http://www.moleskineus.com 
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Mu Sing   A program (for Mac OS X as well as Unix and Windows) that you can use to evolve new rhythms.  The program randomly creates rhythms; once you find one you're somewhat interesed in, you spawn a new generation of slightly different beats, mutated versions of that original.  Lather, rinse, repeat.     urlLink  http://www.geneffects.com/musing/index.html  
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Article in the Chron of Higher Ed abt. globalization anxiety.    "In The Silent Takeover: Global Capitalism and the Death of Democracy (Free Press, 2001), Noreena Hertz describes the supposed spiritual Eden that was the isolated kingdom of Bhutan in the Himalayas as being defiled by such awful imports as basketball and Spice Girls T-shirts. Anthony Giddens, the director of the London School of Economics and Political Science, has told how an anthropologist who visited a remote part of Cambodia was shocked and disappointed to find that her first night's entertainment was not traditional local pastimes but watching Basic Instinct on video.   " . . . . It is odd, to put it mildly, that many on the left support multiculturalism in the West but advocate cultural purity in the developing world -- an attitude they would be quick to tar as fascist if proposed for the United States or Britain. Hertz and the anthropologist in Cambodia appear to want people outside the industrialized West preserved in unchanging but supposedly pure poverty. Yet the Westerners who want this supposed paradise preserved in aspic rarely feel like settling there. Nor do most people in developing countries want to lead an "authentic" unspoiled life of isolated poverty.  "In truth, cultural pessimists are typically not attached to diversity per se but to designated manifestations of diversity, determined by their preferences. "They often use diversity as a code word for a more particularist agenda, often of an anti-commercial or anti-American nature," Cowen argues. "They care more about the particular form that diversity takes in their favored culture, rather than about diversity more generally, freedom of choice, or a broad menu of quality options.""   urlLink http://chronicle.com/free/v49/i35/35b00701.htm   
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       It's hard to take the word "hacker" seriously, just as it's hard to take the word "painter" or "poet" seriously.  If it's not being used as a word of abuse, it's often a sign of sentimentality or sloppy mythifying.  Nevertheless, this is good in places.  "What hackers and painters have in common is that they're both makers.  Along with composers, architects, and writers, what hackers and painters are trying to do is make good things. They're not doing research per se, though if in the course of trying to make good things they discover some new technique, so much the better."    urlLink http://www.paulgraham.com/hp.html   
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       More awesome research!  At MIT, a computer game you can play using a stream of urine.     urlLink http://web.media.mit.edu/~hayes/mas863/urinecontrol.html   "Users aim at a series of jumping hamsters, with input position on the urinal corresponding to a target position on the screen above.  A successful hit turns a hamster yellow, makes it scream and spin out of control, and rewards the player with ten points."  
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      From NYT, snapshot of one or two social dominoes falling.    We're in this period where the implications of a few massive societal earthquakes, decades old, are being worked out as a series of little rockfalls, all over the place.  These little slips are most of what happens, most of the time, I suppose.  Have a look:  what a funny century it was, to bring us abruptly cheek to cheek with phrases like "women work" and "death of the suit".  And so men's stores must be redesigned completely.  (But only just now!)  ----------------------------  Analysts point to many men's-wear shops that have either gone out of business or added women's clothes and accessories.   The changes were necessary because of a revolution in shopping habits, said Marshal Cohen, senior retail analyst for the NPD Group, a market research firm in Port Washington, N.Y.. Now, more men pick out their own clothing. Just three years ago, NPD's polls showed that women shopped for 76 percent of men. Now, women buy for less than half of them.   "Women work," Mr. Cohen explained.   And men have a different shopping style.   "Men don't need to see 40 different pairs of black pants, the way women like to see," Mr. Cohen said. `'They want to see three pairs of black pairs, have some clerk tell him what to wear with them, and move on. The stores simply don't need the floor space anymore."   "After a decade of decline, the stores are finally figuring it out," Mr. Cohen said. `'They know men want good service, in a less painful environment."   In the dismal atmosphere that shrouds the clothing business these days, men's wear is usually regarded as the worst performer. C. Britt Beemer, chairman of America's Research Group, which polls shoppers, said the desire to shop for men's clothes had continued to drop: it reported a decline of 8 to 11 percent in shopping for men's wear in the first six months this year, compared with the corresponding period last year. And in all of 2002, customers shopped for men's clothes 4 to 9 percent less than they did in 2001. The numbers vary by region: the falloff is higher in the Northeast, where suits have traditionally sold best, and lower in the South, Mr. Beemer said.   . . .  After the suit died, American men loaded up on chinos and polo shirts -- and made Gap's stock soar. But three years ago, with no clear fashion trend and a souring economy, men and their children, girlfriends and wives passed up buying more khaki and knit shirts -- and Gap's sales fell, along with those of many of its imitators. But now, Gap, which has been steadily raising its percentage of women's and girls' clothing, appears to be recovering. 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I got some new information about the infamous Honda commerical viewable  urlLink here.     "The film took 606 takes. On the first 605 takes, something, usually very minor, didn't work. . .  it took six million dollars and took three months to complete the two minute sequence."  No computer graphics or manipulations were used.  
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Outstanding.   Ted Turner on the SNAFU at the FCC.  "Large media corporations are far more profit-focused and risk-averse. They sometimes confuse short-term profits and long-term value. They kill local programming because it's expensive, and they push national programming because it's cheap -- even if it runs counter to local interests and community values. For a corporation to launch a new idea, you have to get the backing of executives who are obsessed with quarterly earnings and afraid of being fired for an idea that fails. They often prefer to sit on the sidelines waiting to buy the businesses or imitate the models of the risk-takers who succeed. (Two large media corporations turned down my invitation to invest in the launch of CNN.) . . .   "Naturally, corporations say they would never suppress speech. That may be true. But it's not their intentions that matter. It's their capabilities. The new FCC rules would give them more power to cut important ideas out of the public debate, and it's precisely that power that the rules should prevent. Some news organizations have tried to marginalize opponents of the war in Iraq, dismissing them as a fringe element. Pope John Paul II also opposed the war in Iraq. How narrow-minded have we made our public discussion if the opinion of the pope is considered outside the bounds of legitimate debate?"   urlLink http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A56132-2003May29.html   The next step is to contact elected officials, and Consumers' Union has an easy to use database full of useful contact information. They've been very active in promoting the continuation of regulation of media monopolies:   urlLink http://capwiz.com/consumersunion/issues/alert/?alertid=1656736&type=CO   And for reference, here's a library of excellent articles on this topic:   urlLink http://www.consumersunion.org/telecom/owns_news.htm      
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      A new Chicago zineblog -- something, and some folks, to keep an eye on.    urlLink http://www.gapersblock.com/    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Things are Blogger are getting better, but still no archives.  
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another fantastic TV commercial, an IKEA ad by Spike Jonze.  I'd rather point you to a fantastic new poem, but I haven't seen any.  If you have, send me an email.  Go to unboring.com, wait for it to load, and click on the TV set.  In the popup that comes up, select the Lamp commercial.    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Printer ink apparently costs 7 times more than good champagne, and printer cartridges report that they are empty, and refuse to operate, while still 20% full.  I feel that in some indirect way, this must be one of the reasons that (for example) people gleefully trade illicit music on the Internet.  http://www.theregister.co.uk/content/54/31569.html 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The American Traveler International Apology Shirt   urlLink http://www.cafeshops.com/americanapology.6120915?zoom=yes#zoom  
    
</post>

<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The American Journal of Public Health (http://www.ajph.org) has published a study showing that age, sex, income, and other factors being equal, people living in areas of suburban sprawl will on average be six pounds heavier, and have 29% higher blood pressure, than those in the densest communities.   urlLink http://www.forbes.com/home_asia/2003/08/29/cx_da_0829topnews.html  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Inspecting  our new home with a gruff inspection man named   urlLink Robert Herrick  .      urlLink http://home.comcast.net/~sandover2/HomeInspection/HomeInspection.html   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Instead of the art of writing on a surface, which they never developed, the Inca might have stored narrative, historical, and bookkeeping information in knotted strings.     urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2003/08/12/science/12INCA.html  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The ongoing strangeness of the American housing market.  " From Fort Wayne to Rochester to Salt Lake City, the prices of typical homes across most of the country's vast middle have risen just ahead of inflation — and more slowly than incomes.  The cost of homes in the most expensive cities is now about six times that in the least expensive, up from a ratio of three to one two decades ago."    http://www.nytimes.com/2003/08/06/business/06HOUS.html?th
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Important New Holiday!    urlLink Talk Like A Pirate Day - September 19 
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Anita Elberse, an assistant professor who teaches marketing at Harvard Business School, said the last HSX [Hollywood Stock Exchange] trading price of a film before it opens is a more accurate indicator of how a movie will do than any other single measure."   urlLink Itâ€™s Just a Game, but Hollywood Is Paying Attention 
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      More juicy pointers into the world of information visualization.   urlLink Reading List in Information Visualization 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a window into an area of research I'm active in now.  Hopefully the HyperViewer that I'm working on will appear on the following list before too long.   urlLink Information Visualization Taxonomy 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Not new, but still interesting.  A treemap, which is where you take a hierarchy of items (in this case, companies), and fill a rectangle with it.  Then you read it like a map.   urlLink Map of the Market  
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Bookslut  reads too much.  
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Some kind of midwestern Burning Man spinoff?   urlLink The Burning Wheel Site 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Another  fantastic and in-depth review of Mac OS X by John Siracusa, a fine writer and thinker about OS design issues.
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Trends in logo design.  I love stuff like this.      urlLink Graphic Design USA - Feature - Corporate Identity - 15 Trends Taking Shape In Logo Design 
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's an article I wrote about Burning Man, posted on Chicago web mag Gaper's Block.   urlLink Gapers' Block {Chicago, IL} 
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Old Boys' Networks, Long Favored By Robber Barons and the Wall Street Journal Editorial Page, Don't Actually Work As Well as Business Conducted Fairly Among Strangers.    urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2003/12/04/business/04scene.html  
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "As millions more sign up for online dating services, some of the biggest providers are able to crunch some pretty specific data on regional preferences. . .   "Knocking down that longstanding saying that gentlemen prefer blondes, for example, Match.com surveys have consistently shown that gentlemen actually prefer women with light brown hair. Blond hair and dark brown hair tie dead even for second place.  "Perhaps more interesting, when asked about large age gaps between partners, Match.com found more men who said they were willing to date a woman 15 years older than women who were willing to go that much younger."    urlLink http://story.news.yahoo.com/news?tmpl=story&cid=582&e=1&u=/nm/20031201/wr_nm/life_dating_dc     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A high-level intro to the world of RSS, which I'm interested in for its potential to take content out of the web browser.     urlLink http://www.forbes.com/personaltech/2004/02/23/cx_ah_0223tentech.html   As someone who keeps up with between 10 and 20 web sites a day (which themselves might link to articles from hundreds of other sources), I have to build my sense of my my information landscape -- how it changes, when new things arrive, what's interesting to me, what's not -- by manually doing the following.    (a)  formulating to myself my desire for a specific piece of information in a specific genre (say, what's on  Slashdot).  This is a hazy process.   (b)  consciously acting on that formulation, once it's clear in my mind that that's what I'm after (c)  opening a web browser window (d)  typing or clicking to get where i want to go  This process is an interruption to whatever else I might be doing, in terms of where I'm directing my attention.  It takes over my task context, and it blocks out a big chunk of my screen, since web browsers are real-estate hungry.  And yet it might also be unfruitful -- Slashdot might be the same as the last time I checked.  I must do this process for 10 or 20 websites, 1, 2, 3, or N times day, to get a real time picture of what's popping up in my world that I might find interesting.    Tabbed browsers help with this, because they make it easy to open a whole list of bookmarks simultaneously, with each page in its own tab.  You can simply check a page, close it out, you're shifted right onto the next site.    The various sources of information that I want should be woven into something else -- something less monolothic than a browser window or even a separate application.  Something persistent, subtle, and capable of showing the presence of "new" stuff at a glance.  RSS is one way to start on this kind of path.     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Conan O'Brien "threw oil and matches down our national fault line." 		--  Montreal Gazette  "I can't believe this country was successfully baited by a damn hand puppet." 		-- Toronto Star    urlLink http://slate.msn.com/id/2095543/  
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well-done animated & interactive charts showing things like world income distribution over the past 30 years, life expectancy, education levels.     urlLink http://gapminder.org/   
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Visualize the evolution of a  urlLink network  over a time interval.  
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Light transmitting concrete.     urlLink http://optics.org/articles/news/10/3/10/1   What with stuff like this, and the decreasing cost of tunneling  urlLink underground , the world is going to start to look different in our lifetime.  
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A trenchant anaylsis of the "Batman" theme song, courtesy of McSweeney's.  I happen to disagree on a number of points, actually, but it's an OK beginning.   urlLink http://www.mcsweeneys.net/2004/3/12shields.html   
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Type in the name of a few foodstuffs that you have on hand, and you can use Google to find a recipe that includes those things.  I just tried lamb and cottage cheese.   urlLink http://www.researchbuzz.org/archives/001404.shtml 
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      subway systems of the world, presented on the same scale   urlLink http://www.fakeisthenewreal.org/subway/index.html   
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What Uncle Sam Really Wants   This is an amazing book that I've read a few pieces of in the past, and I was thinking about recently, and thought i'd pass along.  It's by Noam Chomsky, the major linguist of the 20th century who also, as you may or may not know, is an active political commentator as well.    The book was written in 1992.  It's a summary of the goals and methods of post-WW2 US foreign policy in the large, based on Chomsky's research into high-level memos from the State Department, Joint Chiefs of Staff, etc. over the last 50 years.  Many of the documents he cites were formerly classified; Chomsky spends a lot of time filing Freedom of Information Act petitions, finding out how US leaders actually make decisions amongst themselves, as opposed to what they say when they're in public.  You can buy the book on Amazon, but for some reason, a little religious website has made the full text of the book available.  Not certain how legal that is.     urlLink http://cyberspacei.com/jesusi/authors/chomsky/sam/sam.htm#_Toc515113637     -------------------------------  [Memo] NSC 68 is the hard-line extreme, and remember: the policies weren't just theoretical -- many of them were actually being implemented. Now let's turn to the other extreme, to the doves. The leading dove was undoubtedly George Kennan, who headed the State Department planning staff until 1950 . . . .  Kennan was one of the most intelligent and lucid of US planners, and a major figure in shaping the postwar world. His writings are an extremely interesting illustration of the dovish position. One document to look at if you want to understand your country is Policy Planning Study 23, written by Kennan for the State Department planning staff in 1948. Here's some of what it says:  we have about 50% of the world's wealth, but only 6.3% of its population....In this situation, we cannot fail to be the object of envy and resentment. Our real task in the coming period is to devise a pattern of relationships which will permit us to maintain this position of disparity....To do so, we will have to dispense with all sentimentality and day-dreaming; and our attention will have to be concentrated everywhere on our immediate national objectives....We should cease to talk about vague and...unreal objectives such as human rights, the raising of the living standards, and democratization. The day is not far off when we are going to have to deal in straight power concepts. The less we are then hampered by idealistic slogans, the better.  PPS 23 was, of course, a top-secret document. To pacify the public, it was necessary to trumpet the "idealistic slogans" (as is still being done constantly), but here planners were talking to one another.  
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       More songs from Eugene, the marvelous crooning child   Internet culture -- I have presented it before, and I present it again before you now.     urlLink http://www.eugenemirman.com/  
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'So began a test run for a game of Pac-Manhattan, a real-world version of the 1980's video game played on the streets of New York and the latest example of a so-called "big game": a contest that uses wireless devices like cellphones and global positioning beacons to track players as they move through the urban grid, turning cities into vast game boards.'   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/05/09/fashion/09GAME.html  
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the IPO documents Google filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission, the exact value of its planned offering is $2,718,281,828 dollars, aka the mathematical constant e, 2.718281828...   
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sure Glad That's Over   Everyone knows that the FBI actively opposed Martin Luther King, Jr., Malcolm X, and others, in a program of covert action against political dissidents called COINTELPRO. (There were Congressional hearings exposing -- and dismantling -- the program in the early 1970's. Some recent discussion on PBS with  urlLink Bill Moyers .)   What's news to me is that the FBI had 2,000 pages on Albert Einstein as well, collected from 1933 to 1955. Because of Einstein's pacifism, his activism, and his socialist sympathies, he became a target for J. Edgar Hoover. In addition to compiling whatever they could find about Einstein, the FBI conducted interviews with informants in a search for "derogatory information."  During the 1950's, Hoover tried unsuccessfully to paint Einstein as a Soviet spy, and there was a serious attempt to get him deported, which Einstein -- who apparently knew the score -- was able to avoid.    urlLink http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0312316097/102-6476082-4381718?v=glance&amp;vi=reviews   "Meticulously researched and beautifully written, The Einstein File details a bleak chapter in this nation's history, when a rogue elephant FBI rode roughshod over civil liberties, including the rights and privacy of one of the world's great scientists."  =----------=----------=  FBI dossiers on other famous people, obtained through the Freedom of Information Act.   urlLink http://foia.fbi.gov/famous.htm   
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Accenture Information Source   That's what they're currently calling it, anyway. This is a project I worked on for almost a year, and it's now live and downloadable at ITPapers.com   Here's some of what our friend Ted Smith at CNet has to say about our work.      =---------------=---------------=---------------=  
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kind of news-houndy, but gives an excellent close reading of how American journalism has fallen down on the job in Iraq.  http://www.nybooks.com/articles/17210  
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More Creative Uses For the USA PATRIOT Act  Federal charges were filed against Adam McGaughey, creator of the popular SG1Archive.com website - a fan website devoted to the MGM-owned television show Stargate SG-1. The charges allege that the website engaged in Criminal Copyright Infringement and Trafficking in Counterfeit Services. The charges were the culmination of a three-year FBI investigation, set in motion by a complaint from the Motion Picture Association (MPAA) regarding the content of the SG1Archive.com website.  SG1Archive.com is one of the most popular fan-run websites among the Stargate community. In addition to providing very active fan discussion forums, broadcast schedules, production news, and episode guides, the site heavily promotes the sale of the show on DVD. As of this writing, direct links from SG1Archive.com to Amazon.com have resulted in the sale of over $100,000 worth of DVDs. Many more DVDs have been sold to international fans of the show through sites like Blackstar.co.uk. Upon hearing this news, Stargate executive producer Brad Wright called the site "cool" - which Adam took as an endorsement of his work.  However, instead of thanking Adam for his promotion of their product, officials at MGM and the MPAA have chosen to pressure the FBI into pursuing criminal charges. Adam was first tipped off about the investigation when the FBI raided his and his fiancee's apartment in May of 2002 and seized thousands of dollars worth of computer equipment. Adam later received a copy of the affidavit filed in support of the search warrant, and was shocked to discover that this document, prepared by the FBI, contained significant amounts of erroneous and misleading information. For example, two social security numbers were listed for Adam, one of which is not his. References were made to a cease and desist letter sent by the MPAA to an email address that did not exist. His online friendship with other Stargate fans across the globe was portrayed as an international conspiracy against the MPAA. And perhaps most disturbing of all, it was later revealed that the FBI invoked a provision of the USA Patriot Act to obtain financial records from his ISP. The FBI's abuse of its powers did not stop there. When they seized Adam's computer equipment, he was given written documentation stating that it would be returned within 60 days. The equipment that they did return did not arrive until more than 8 months later, and only then after much prodding from his lawyer. Much of it was damaged beyond repair - one laptop had a shattered LCD screen, an empty tape backup drive was ripped apart for no apparent reason, his fiancee's iBook was badly damaged when it was pried apart with a screwdriver. The FBI's computer crimes staff is either incompetent (at least when it comes to Macintosh computer equipment) or else they just don't give a damn.  Adam has has received positive feedback about his site from multiple members of the Stargate cast and crew at fan conventions. In addition, a representative of MGM's fan publication interviewed Adam about his website several months prior to the FBI raid. As a result, Adam sincerely believed that the show's creators did not have a problem with the content of his website. Many other sites are currently serving content of questionable legality, without promoting the sale of DVDs or offering a community for fans to discuss the show. Why the MPAA and FBI have chosen to ignore these sites and target SG1Archive.com is unclear.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Internet Archive is a 501(c)(3) public nonprofit that was founded to build an ‘Internet library,’ with the purpose of offering permanent access for researchers, historians, and scholars to historical collections that exist in digital format.  i.e. it has TONS of stuff -- old video; films; documentaries; radio archives ; conferences (such as SIGGRAPH); current media such as the 2004 election.    Very cool.   urlLink http://www.archive.org 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1995 Subaru SVX -- very fine condition - $6500  Red 2-door coupe, gray interior, with 90,000 miles. The car is in very fine condition inside and out.  - 4 wheel drive (of course) - 6 cylinder, 3.3 l, 230 Horsepower - ABS Anti-lock brakes  - Automatic - no rust, very few small bumper scratches  Features: Cassette / CD, cruise control, power windows and locks, airbags, foglights.   First 80K miles of its life were spent in Utah, mostly highway miles. In my family since 58K -- good maintenance records kept since then. New high-performance Dunlop tires put on at 83K &amp; covered by a good warranty. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Over the last two decades more than 200 super-carriers - cargo ships over 200m long - have been lost at sea. Eyewitness reports suggest many were sunk by high and violent walls of water that rose up out of calm seas.      As part of a project called MaxWave - which was set up to test the rumours - two Esa satellites surveyed the oceans.      During a three week period they detected 10 giant waves, all of which were over 25m (81ft) high.       urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/sci/tech/3917539.stm   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The 2004 election has got Sarah Mesle so fired up that she's gone and started her own blog.  It's called  Sarah's Campaign , and it's a compilation of letters to the editor, public exhortations, advice to the candidates, and handy links to interesting things like  urlLink congress.org   .     urlLink http://sarahscampaign.blogspot.com/     You can leave comments there (as you can with this blog as well) . . . I just left the first one.         
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Outfoxed  is OK -- a good compilation of damning clips about a right-wing opinion page masquerading as a 24 hour news news organization -- but what's really interesting is this study which the documentary refers to.  The study consisted of three yes/no questions on matters of fact:  Is it your impression that the US has or has not found clear evidence in Iraq that Saddam Hussein was working closely with the al Qaeda terrorist organization?&nbsp;&nbsp;    Since the war with Iraq ended, is it your impression that the US has or has not found Iraqi weapons of mass destruction?    Thinking about how all the people in the world feel about the US having gone to war with Iraq, do you think the majority of people favor the US having gone to war?    The true answers to the questions are, of course, "no clear evidence has been found," "no weapons of mass destruction have been found," and "the majority of people in the world do not favor the US having gone to war."  The researchers&nbsp;asked these questions to a sampling of people, and also asked those people where they get their news.&nbsp;It's quite incredible.&nbsp; 45% of Fox viewers got ALL THREE wrong.&nbsp; Among ABC/CBS/NBC/CNN viewers, the highest total was 16%.    More data in here, including a little chart of the percentages.     urlLink Media, Misperceptions, and the Iraq War        
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Report from my friend Cole:  =----------=----------=  here are some pretty dreary #s about voter turnout  (i'm writing another yet letter to the editor).  the first drives home the importance of getting out the 18-24 year old vote:   urlLink http://www.fec.gov/pages/agedemog.htm   the second is interesting because it allows you to track who is NOT voting by sex, race, class, ethnicity, income, union affiliation, age, party affiliation, political disposition, &c.   urlLink http://www.umich.edu/~nes/nesguide/2ndtable/t6a_2_1.htm  
    
</post>


</Blog>