<Blog>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh, I'm so freakin' stressed out.  I really need to move out and I made a promise to my bf that I'd find a place in 3 weeks.  Well, I don't know how much I'm making at my new job, and from what I estimating now it doesn't look like I'll have enough.  I'm so upset.... I don't know what to do anymore.  I feel so frusterated at everything.  I'm trying to figure all this crap out and it just doesn't seel like I can't ever get ahead in life.  I feel like no matter what I do I can't win.  Just very frusterated now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone wanta give me $500? Please? 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       They cut off the circulation to my brain! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       If you're gonna have a comb-over.... don't drive a convertable! 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       +19  Total Count: 49 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       +9  Total Count: 30 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       +7  Total Count: 21 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hm,  Well, I decided to start a virus count.  This SoBig.f virus (ok Joe, it's a worm, a worm!) is all over the place.  Today I counted 9 versions of it in my Bulk Mail folder on my yahoo account.  I had a few the day before also...  Virus(worm) Count total:  14 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       10 pennies do not equal $1 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh, I have to be at work at 5am tommorow..... so I have to leave here by like 4:15am...... ugh ugh.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My last day at "the Eagle".   They got me a cake (a little one, like they get everone else).  That made me happy.  Plus apparently the sattalite that runs our music messed up when the power went out, and they where playing modern cool stuff.  Made my night much better. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Wait, I live in Ohio.... and the lights went out at 4:15pm.... ooh well, they went out.  Now they're back on, but soon to go out again, 'cause I'm going to bed.  Good Night! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       The other day, I was joking aorund with one of the sample ladies in my store... she turned to me and said "Remind me when I go home to stick pins in your doll." 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, went to look at the cars, waited over an hour to find out they "don't put out the $88 cars until later".  I had to go to work, so we couldn't wait around all day.  Ooh well.  One more week at Giant Eagle.  I'm kinda sad, I don't really wanta leave.  I'll miss everyone there, they all kinda feel like family to me.   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Going tommorow morning to see if we can find a car for my bf.  We saw signs for a place that has cars for "as low as $88".  Sounds too good to be true, we'll find out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Wahoo!  Hehehe.  Well, they want me to go fo an orientation the 16th.  I'm happy.  Hm, wonder if "The big bird" will want me to stay.  lol, doubt it.  ooh well :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, today's the day of my job interview.  I'm not too nervious yet, but I'll probibly be when i'm ready to go in.  Hm, well, after the interview I'm gonna go get my boyfriend and take him to a few places, and we'll hang out.  That's about it here... bye for now 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       See how tired I was, I didn't even realize that tommorow was already today, last night.  Wait that would be this morning, ooh nevermind.    Ok, my life right now.  I have a job interview @ IGA Monday.  I really hope I get it, I really ned a full time job, and especialy need the cash!  I'm due for a raise at Giant Eagle, which will put me up to $9.75.  That's what I put on my application to IGA, and they still called me back for a 2nd interview.  I really hope they can give me that pay rate.  If I get that, I'll deffinitly be able to get an apartment on my own.  I'm getting really tired of living here.  I miss being on my own.  Ooh well.  I think that's all for now.  If I think of anything I'm sure I'll be back :)  bye for now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I kinda neglected my old blog, so I decided to attempt to start a new one.  I'm gonna try and keep up with this one.  I'll post my first real post tommorow.  I'm too tired to think now.  Good night. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Taking time apart..... I feel so empty..... and lost. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My bf finally moved back with his mom, he moved back home yesterday... So glad, I was getting really concered for him at the other place where he was living... It just makes me feel more at ease... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Tomorrow was supposed to be a happy day in my life.  Tomorrow was supposed to be a day of fun.  Tomorrow was supposed to be my and my bf's 1 year anniversary.  But we didn't get that far.  Just feeling kinda alone...  Halloween was one of my favorite holidays, but not this year... 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I crave an adventure.  I would love to try to get on a show like Big Brother, but I don't have a camera for the application.  Hm.... any suggestions for an adventure? 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Why does everyone seem to be in a crabby mood?? 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, i'm officialy hired at my new job at Tops.  I filled out all the paper work and stuff, and I start Sunday.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Jason, thank you....... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       h e l l o ? 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yet anoyther couples holiday when I'm alone..... ~sigh~ 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Heather baby, I had fun looking at all the streight porn with ya :) hehe  Hope it worked out for ya ~wink~ 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Why do I care so much for someone that has hurt me so much? 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've had my ups and downs with the whole "taking time apart" thing, but I'm ok with it, I guess.  Also, quit my job Thursday, so Now, really bored here..... ugh, Well, I go back to the "eagle" Monday afternoon.  I should get rehired.  Seems good...  I just need something to do around here.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's getting louder... 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       3 days off in a row next week...... PA's calling me..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I hate holidays... well, not really. just hate the  nothing-to-do  when I'm done with the family stuff... I was super tempted to make another road trip to PA, but After figuring out a time frame in my mind, it's just not worth it.  If I had tomorrow off I'd be there right now though.  But with what I work, I have to wake up here at 6:30am :(  I hope work is easy tomorrow.... at least I get to watch SmackDown tonight...  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Happy Thanksgiving... we already ate here... now nothing to do.... lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    urlLink audio post  powered by  urlLink audblog  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Why do you have you have to be a million miles away? 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I finally got to talk to Jason.... I really miss him already.....  ooh well, only time can tell.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Wow I was just so bored I watched most of SummerSlam '94.  Undertaker vs. Undertaker a classic.  And where would Owen Hart be if he where still alive.  Without a doubt multi-time WWE champ... 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       To see you when I wake up is a gift I didn't think could be real To know that you feel the same way as I do is a three-old utopian dream. You do something to me that I can't explain. SO would I be out of like if I said, I miss you. (?)  I see your picture, I smell your skin on the empty pillow next to mine. You have only been gone 10 days, but already I'm wasting away. I know I'll see you again whether far or soon. But I need you to know that I care and I miss you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm bored.  Listing to Madonna "Ray of Light" CD (her best to date) and waiting for RAW to finish taping so I get to watch it.  Missing Jason..... that's about it hehe 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, who wants to take over my life here in Ohio, so I can go and move to PA??  Come on, going once..... going twice..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       oops... I think I left a pair of my unmentionables in PA...... oops i mentioned them 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I blew Jason a kiss right before I turned to get on to the highway, but I wasn't sure if he got it.  Yes he did.  That put a smile on my face.  Arg!  Why can't u be closer?! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I had SOO much fun these past days.  I left Thursday afternoon, and I went to PA to visit my friend.  OMG what a blast it was.  I so didn't wanta leave today.  But I had to, I have work.  But it was sooo nice to be there, and have no worries.  And it was nice to have someone to cuddle with in bed :)  Also his roommate is hilarious (MOM!!).  Love ya Donna. :)    I so wanta go back.  SOON! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Never invite someone out if u don't really wanta to do it.  Or go and judge them before then even make a decision. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I wanta have a date tommorow.  I dunno why.  And I know it's not gonna happen.just wanta have a little fun,  Go to coffee... I don't even like coffee.  Just have someone treat  me  for once... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Been feeling alot better these past few days.... actually after "asshole day" I'm feeling like a weight has been lifted..... So now what.... starting over.... hm....... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       asshole 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       anger... bitter... sad... depressed... pissed off... confused... and 3000 more emotions..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just got a call from my ex bf.... the goodbye forever one..... said he made a promise to his new bf, no skeletons poping up..... so he called me and told me that this was it, and goodbye forever.   Shaking.... crying..... upset...... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       The effectiveness of an answering machine, is greatly reduced when it's  NOT TURNED ON  when u leave the house!!! arg! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just my thought for the day, Stupid people are dumb.  Especially people who think they can mess with my head... but leave their name in plain sight! 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yea, I'm good at that.  Well got his side of it, and everything is ok.  He's just not ready for a relationship and stuff... and I understand, but I guess I was still trying to push things along.  My fault, lol.  But everything is all better now. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So mad and upset now.  Just found out Jason said I was too clingy and stuff.  I really liked him, and I assumed he felt the same way, guess not.  I didn't drive 3 hours both times just for a booty call.  Men suck! 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I saw Justin Timberlake shopping in the mall with his mom, and I went up and asked for an autograph, and we ended up hanging out and he came to my hours and stuff... (now why did I waste the celeb sex dream on Madonna!?). 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, christmas is pretty much over for me, at least all the events of it. My grandmother came over and we ate.  Had a lovely conversation about her bowel movements... that's about it.  Fun, fun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I got a DVD recorder :-D very happy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Hm, just had a dream that I had sex with Madonna.  Odd.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just talked to my ex bf on the phone.  He had called right before I got home, so I retutned his call. It was strange talking to him.  And honestly, I really don't know what to say about it, and I don't know how I feel about it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've been listning to the RENT sound track in my car to and from work... It's comming to Cleveland in January, which someone would take me (hint hint) haha 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just realized that I never got to see the movie Kill Bill...... I really wanted to see it... damn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I think the christmas spirit has passed me by... just don't feel very christmasy this year.  The lack of funds is big part of it, I have no $ to buy anyone anything and that sucks, I love buying stuff for people(which is why i have no $, haha).  Ooh well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       a sence of direction, haha...... (I'm not lost, I'm just not where I wanta be!) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I love the episodes where they freeze the kitchen... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I need more gay friends..... sad, closest I get to gay culture is watching Queer Eye for the Straight Guy (though I  LOVE  the show).  I really only have one gay friend that I hang out with (love ya Joe).  Ooh well.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just found out that my ex bf's father passed away.  I haven't talked to Brett since that phone call.  But I do feel a sadness for him.  I know he was struggling with the fact that his father was ill.  And he said he didn't expect his father to make it to Christmas, guess he was right.  I have the urge to send a card or something, but I'm not going to.  He said to leave him alone, and I will do it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Now, I don't normally get into politics, but this is some great news.  Now we just need to find Osama.......  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Probably something not to be proud of but I'm officially a label whore!!  Well, for underwear only.  I love my 2(x)ist underwear!! just need to find some more... cheap.  I don't wanta pay full price..... Hm, wanta buy me some, e-mail me for my type preference, and size :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I got this in an e-mail from someone I haven't talked to in quite awhile.  Now I'm not one for fowards. I lothe them.  Especially the ones that say something like "send this to 85 of your closest friend, or u'll die by sunset" or something.... this this one really made sence, so here it is...   They call it the "Quarter-life Crisis." It is when you stop going along with the crowd and start realizing that there are many things about yourself that you didn't know and may not like. You start feeling insecure and wonder where you will be in a year or two, but then get scared because you barely know where you are now.  You start realizing that people are selfish and that, maybe, those friends that you thought you were so close to aren't exactly the greatest people you have ever met, and the people you have lost touch with are some of the most important ones. What you don't  recognize is that they are realizing that too, and aren't really cold, catty, mean or insincere, but that they are as confused as you.   You look at your job... and it is not even close to what you thought you would be doing, or maybe you are looking for a job and realizing that you are going to have to start at the bottom and that scares you.   Your opinions have gotten stronger. You see what others are doing and find yourself judging more than usual because suddenly you realize that you have certain boundaries in your life and are constantly adding things to your list of what is acceptable and what  isn't. One minute, you are insecure and then the next, secure. You laugh and cry with the greatest force of your life. You feel alone and scared and confused.  Suddenly, change is the enemy and you try and cling on to the past with dear life,  but soon realize that the past is drifting further and further away, and there is nothing to do but stay where you are or move forward.  You get your heart broken and wonder how someone you loved could do such damage to you. Or you lie in bed and wonder why you can't meet anyone decent enough that you want to get to know better. Or maybe you love someone but love someone else too and cannot figure out why you are doing this because you know that you aren't a bad person. One night stands and random hook ups start to look cheap. Getting wasted and acting like an idiot starts to look pathetic.  You go through the same emotions and questions over and over, and talk with your friends about the same topics because you cannot seem to make a decision. You worry about loans, money, the future and making a life for yourself... and while winning the race would be great, right now you'd just like to be a contender!  What you may not realize is that everyone reading this relates to it. We are in our best of times and our worst of times, trying as hard as we can to figure this whole thing out.   Send this to your twenty-something friends...maybe it will help someone feel like they aren't alone in their state of confusion........     
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       There is no one on-line to talk to, and I'm bored!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Had a dream a few nights ago, and now it's really bugging me, trying to figure out if it really means anything.  I drempt that I witnessed an airplane crash.  Trying to figure out what it means symbolically.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just got back from shopping.  I don't think I fully understand the consept though.  I left the house to go buy a shirt I liked and some art supplies.  Came home with an iced tea and bag of trail mix... hm... something went wrong there.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone wanta give me a million dollars so I can just relax and figure out what I wanta do with my life?  I would like to back to school and get some kinda degree in something.... but that takes $ that I don't have, and if I do go back, how am I gonna pay for my car?  Also, I really wanta go to PA and be with Jason, but I don't know if I can just uproot myself, especially that far. Also, I don't know if I'm ready for a relationship.  After how I was burned with my last relationship.... scared of it happening again.  ugh... what to do, what to do.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just got back home..... it was too soon :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I got new tires and now I'm off to PA.... bye 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       gggrrrrrr I hate cars.  My front tires are worn down more than they should, and with that, my dad said I shouldn't go to PA :(  So I just called the garage to see if I could get them rotated and whatnot.  But my mom said I still couldn't go. :( grrr, I'm just really bummed out that it doesn't look like I'm gonna get to go.  I was really looking forward to going....  We'll see after I get back from the garage. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ugh... it's December already... seems like last December was only a year ago... wow how time flies... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What am I doing..... I really don't have a clue anymore.  Reconsidering everything.  One thing that bums me out is that someone will end up hurt.  I hate hurting people. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, made my decision, and my rose went to Chris, lol (sorry I'm a DORK). 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Now I know how they feel on the shows like the Bachelor, Bachleorette, and Boy meets Boy.  Wow...  Still trying to figure this all out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       dropped off my bf at this Ball thingy he had today, he looks so cute in his tux, he keeps saying he looked like a penguin.   Also he made me smile today, we where listing (and singing along to) RENT in my car, and I realized he was looking at me as I mouthed the words... I looked over at him and said "What?" and he said nothing and just smiled. hehe. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I FINALLY got the free condom I requested thru the Trojan website.  they also sent me a $1.00 off coupon, which expired 12-31-03.... hm.... glad to hear they're on the ball, lol. ooh well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I applied at May Credit.  Some cutie also came in right after me and was filling out an application.  When I gave the receptionist my application she said they would contact me in March.  I looked over at the guy and I saw him mouth "March?!" I just shrugged my shoulders.  Actually not that far away.  I hope I get in. I need something more steady then what I'm gettin right now.  And I need insurance.  I'm not sick right now, but what if I do get sick.  ooh well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        (Well, actually yesterday, but we won't get into technicalities.)   Always make sure u put on underwear when the temp is below 15 degrees outside (Chris!). 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yep, I really do need a new job....  thinking about applying at May Credit, but then I run the chance of running into my ex bf (whom i pissed off the otherday).  Ooh well. I ned a job, and need the $. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Come on  little dude , u can do it..." 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yeah, i got the mail today, and I got $1, hehe came with some survey i gotta fill out (or take the money and run... but not to far it's only $1, lol).  hehe 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well did make it official today, I now have a bf :-D 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, let down my guard and see what happens, I end up dating someone... lol.  Well, it's a good thing, but totaly unexpected.... But we've just seemed to click, and thus far his family seems to like me.  But to be honest I'm still scared, being burnt in the past does that I guess..... and I don't think i was just prepared mentally for this either, lol, but ooh well.  Nice to have someone to cuddle with again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       no new news, just wanted to say good night, lol..... good night :-P 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my neck hurts :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I need some money, haha, a good chunk of change.  lol.  But yet, I don't wanta go to work today, but that's only 'cause I know I'm gonna be bored off my ass.  We don't get a truck today, and where outta stuff yesterday, so definitely not gonna have anything to do.  ooh well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Happy new year...... I wanta go back to bed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The dance was a blast :) had lots of fun there, and danced with my baby all night, it was really fun, and I really really liked slow dancing with him.  Never got to do that before... I'm glad it was with him.  :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, going to my bf's Winter Formal satrday, and neither of us know what we're gonna wear.  I relaly don't wanta decide untill he decieds.... I don't wante be over/under dressed compared to him.  Ooh well, We'll figure it out saturday morning, lol. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You wanta the perfect wat to ruin the mood when you're really getting into sex?  Have you're bf's mother almost set the living room on fire.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had the best like 5 day stretch and finished off with an actual weekend off from work :)  But the 12th was my bf and I's 1 month, and then V-day.  He got me the cutest little crystal teddy bear.  I got him come Cookie Crisp cereal, and real milk, then later I got him some shoes :)  I really love spending time with him cuddling and what not. I just feel so relaxed in his company.  I don't have to put up a front, or watch what I say like my last bf.  He just lets me be me.   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Say it's true, there's nothing like me and you I'm not alone, tell me you feel it too  And I would run away I would run away, yeah..., yeah I would run away I would run away with you  Cause I am falling in love with you No never I'm never gonna stop Falling in love with you  Close the door, lay down upon the floor And by candlelight, make love to me through the night (through the night, through the night...)  Cause I have run away I have run away, yeah..., yeah I have run away, run away I have run away with you  Cause I am falling in love (falling in love) with you No never I'm never gonna stop Falling in love with you... With you...  And I would runaway I would runaway, yeah..., yeah I would runaway (runaway) I would runaway with you  Cause I am falling in love (falling in love) with you No never I'm never gonna stop Falling in love with you...  Falling in love (falling in love) with you No never I'm never gonna stop falling in love with you  With you, my love, with you... na ni na ni na na... (With you, with you, with you, with you)  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yea, I realized somethings today, and wasn't willing to ruin what I already had.  Thank you Joey, and Heather for giving me your honest opinions and not sugar coating everything.  That's what makes you 2 great friends.  Also, Chris, Thank you, for understanding and giving me my space and time to get all this thru my head and figure it all out.  I love you all :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Baby, no matter what I love you, and never forget that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Or would it be half awake? Well, doesn't matter, but my bf was soo funny last night, we where laying down, and he was falling asleep, but he was still talking to me.  He laughed and I asked him what he laughed about and he said "It's not about you or Mike.  It's not about Krissy.  It's about my former treasure for the GSA.  We all had squirrels, and she said her squirrel's butt was too big.  So I said I would bite it off so I was chasing her (incoherent babble) and a car ran over (incoherent babble)" Then he said something else but I forget what that was now. ooh well, he's so adorable. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "They're like joysticks" -- Chris, my bf :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My bf took my shoes last night :(  He gave me a pair of his to wear but I miss mine.... ooh well.   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, my bf now had magenta hair... wow...... it's..... very magenta 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Happy 2 months baby :) I love you 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Holding you make me feel complete. I feel safe when you're around.  I'd do anything to make you happy, and to see that fire behind your eyes. I don't like seeing you hurt. And I wish I could make it all go away like u asked.  But I can't change the past.  I can just be here for you now.  And  now  is all that matters.    One day you will come up to me and ask, "What is more important; me or your life?" I will answer "My life." And you will walk away, never knowing that  you are my life...    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello.  Nothing really to write about, just bored here.  So..... hi. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just a little note to let someone know that I love them and to never forget it.  You can talk to me.  It does worry me when u get into one of your moods and u pace and get all quiet.  It worries me that I don't know what's going on inside your head.  I know a scarey thought... Just remember I love you, and am here for you.  Or i may be over there... or maybe slightly to the left.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I came back from b-day shopping for my now ex bf (she doesn't know that yet) and she asid that I should make a card on the computer for him and she'll sign it, since she didn't have one.  Well, I told her to make one outta construction paper.  Well, ended up using some of the wrapping paper that I got to wrap his gifts (pink... he loves pink... plus it's the color of the day.)  So she coppied a quote out of a anniversy card, and she said "Do you like my home made card, it's my art work" and I said "What are you gonna do now, glue macarroni to it?"....and she did. then she was looking thru the pantry and also glued fome Lucky Charm marshmallows to it.  My mom's on crack. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...birthday to me.  I seem to have misplaced my "happy" 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: eeh  Well, as a result of technical difficulties (namely my hard drive crashing) I was off-line for a few days.  I have a temporary hard drive in my system, but I need to save up and purchase a new one.  So who wants to donate to my "Buy Brian a new hard drive fund"? 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    this is just cute :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: perplexed   Dear Anonymous, Well, I work with veggies 'cause it's all I know.  I've done it for the past 6-7 years, I've lost count.  I think I want to get out of grocery stores, but i may stay in food.  I would love to go into food anthropology but I don't have the $$ for college, wanta give me some?   Well, I guess that's all on this side of things.  (btw, if anyone postes a comment, tell me who you are, lol... even if you don't wanta in the post, e-mail or IM me and let me know...) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: content  I started writing a story, Chris got me on a little vampire kick.  Here's what I have so far :)   As I sat on the roof, I stared at the night sky; vast darkness with tiny pinholes of light, the soft orange city-glow just on the horizon in the west.  I could see my breath, but I wasn’t cold.  It was a beautiful night.  I hate beautiful nights.  I wished for just one cloud.  At least it was a new moon tonight.  I didn’t like the moon’s face starting down on me, eyes always watching.  But tonight there was no moon, just stars.  I could feel the dry blood on my chin.  I liked the feeling of it when it was fresh and warm, now it was dry and lifeless.  It had no meaning anymore, now it was just… blood.  I looked towards the city-glow.  I didn’t want to be there tonight. That’s why I was here.  I did what I had to tonight, then got out of there.  I did not want to run into  them .  I couldn’t stay out of the city long though, they would fine me out here.  Also the city had what I needed.  I felt eyes on me… someone was watching me.  They wouldn’t do anything out here, I knew that much.  I didn’t even try to see who it was.  They knew that I could sense them, that’s what made this sadistic game of cat and mouse more fun.  Only thing they didn’t know was is that  I  am the cat.  I still didn’t move.  I sat until I could see the first hint of daybreak.  I climbed into the open window, closing it behind me.  Drew the shades, and climbed into the bed, pulling the covers over my head.  “Good Morning.” I said to no one in particular, and then drifted to sleep.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: ~smiles~  I saw a rainbow as I was driving home from work.  Another happy sign. :)  Also thanx for everyone who's posted to here, And thank you Scott :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: bewildered  I was driving home tonight from Chris's, and I listened to "When You Come Back Down" by Nickel Creek.  Chris had played it earlier, but I didn't really listen to it.  This time I did, and it made me cry a little, especially the line  My greatest fear will be, that you will crash and burn, and I won't feel your fire  and the line  And I'll be on the other end, To hear you when you call, Angel, you were born to fly, If you get too high I'll catch you when you fall  After that song I just shut off the radio and thought for the rest of my drive home.  When I was almost home, I saw something go thru the sky for a brief second, then it disappeared.  It couldn't have been a plane since it disappeared in mid air, then I realized it was a clear night, so it must have been a shooting star.  I was kinda bewildered by it, but I took it as a song that everything is going to be ok, and kind of put my worries at ease a little.  A little sign that I'm doing something right with everything.  Well, it's time for bed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: sleepy  Had the best evening.  Chris and I ended up just laying on the lawn and watched the clouds roll buy and where deciding what the opens spaces looked like (since there where more clouds then open spaces).  Then it started to rain, so we huddled under the blanket for 5 mins, then decided to go inside.  It was so much fun.  If it's nice tomorrow we're gonna put up his trampoline :-D hehe fun fun 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: peaceful  Decided to put my mood in my blog now.  I dunno how long I'll keep this up. But I can put in a template thingy so It's always there when I make a new post :)  It just started to rain here, and it's nice and cool right now.  Am in a good mood.  Had a decent night's sleep.  Though when I get back from doing a few things I may take a nap, dunno.    Does anyone read this, can someone give me some feedback?  Or am I just talking to myself over here? 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So proud of my bf.  He was in a talent contest today , and he sang My Immortal by Evenesance.  He won :)  So proud of him :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris made this for me while he was "away".  I have it hanging next to my PC.  So I look at it everyday :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris and I in one of those cool photo booths 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris and I&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah! my car is done :) now I just gotta wait for my dad to get home so I can go get it :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love this new Blogger.... :)  unfortunately nothing has happened since I last posted.  My car is in the shop to get my A/C working again, and they haven't called yet :(  I want my car back so I can go see my baby :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, I must be on crack or something... Last night I drempt that I was an MP3 player.  I had a Car CD player implanted in my stomach, and I had LED screens on my upper chest.  Weird.... I don't even wanta try to analyze  that  one! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, this is just cool.  Blogger was redesigned so I got all these cool new features.  Hehe, just to think I was just gonna pop on here to complain that it's hot, and lookie, i get something to play with hehe.  Hm, now i can get comments, goodie :-D 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Like a ghost don't need a key  your best friend I've come to be  please don't think of getting up for me  you don't even need to speak   when I've been here just for one day  you'll already miss me when I go away  so close the blinds and shut the door  you won't need other friends anymore  oh don't leave home, oh don't leave home   and if you're cold,I'll keep you warm  if you're low, just hold on  'cause I will be your safety  oh don't leave home   and I arrived when you were weak  I'll make you weaker,like a child  now all your love you give to me  when your heart is all I need  oh don't leave home, oh don't leave home   and if you're cold,I'll keep you warm  if you're low, just hold on  'cause I will be your safety  oh don't leave home   oh how quiet, quiet the world can be  when it's just you and little me  everything is clear, everything is new  so you won't be leaving will you   and if you're cold,I'll keep you warm  if you're low, just hold on  'cause I will be your safety  oh don't leave home   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Had an emotional past few days.  But all is getting better in my world.  Chris, I love you more than anything I could imagine.  You don't know how scarred I was on monday.  I was so afrade to loose you.    I'm glad everything is getting back to normal, well as normal as it will be for a while.  As I said no one's perfect and I love you with all you're imperfections.  You are my world.  I love you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Down, sad depressed.  I don't know where to stand.  I don't want to be here, I don't want to be anywhere.  I wanta be left alone, but I want someone with me.  I want  my  pain to go away, but I want others to be happy, so my pain must stay for them to be happy.  But then that doesn't make them happy, because  I'm  not happy. Tears roll down my cheeks.  My stomach ties itself in knots.  I'm so tired of being this perfect guy that no one wants.  I'm tired of being a best friend.  I'm tired of being so perfect.  But I'm scared of loosing everyone and everything. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:~sigh~  Just a little message to my bf. Baby don't blame yourself... Things will get better and you'll get your "little brother" back eventually.  Just know I love you, and u know it worries me when u get all upset over stuff. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:goofy  I bent over and picked up a penny the other day, and said to my bf, "Hey Chris, look I bend over for a penny.  You should see what I do for a quarter..."    He asked me, "Well what would you do for a whole roll of quarters?"    My reply "Well just lube me up and spread me out!!" 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:tired  Gravy is not a good subsitute for creamer in coffee. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:happy  Heather, stop following me! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:relieved/happy  Chris found my keys, they where hanging next to the calendar in his kitchen.  So happy :)  Spent almost 24 hours looking for then and they where right in front of his face. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: tired  Lost my keys yesterday.  Actually Chris lost them. but I'm not mad at him. They should turn up today.  I just hope i get them back.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:happy  It's Chris and I's 2nd one month anniversy :)  Very happy.  I'm picking him up from school, then waiting for his friends, then going to see Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.  Then later I'm taking Chris to Steak and Shake, it's where I took him on our first one month anniversy :).  happy anniversy babe, I love you.   Avec tous mon coeur et mon âme, je vous aime plus que n'importe quelle langue peut dire.  With all my heart and soul, I love you more than any language can say.   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: congested  Well, as a result of my Hard Drive going ka-put, i lost my address book.  So everyone, please e-mail me your addresses, b-days (full names incase i don't remember your last name) and e-mail addresses.  PhantomToaster@yahoo.com   thanx all 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: ugh  Well my baby has strep.&nbsp; Rushed outta work 4 hours early to the ER to be with him, then found out it was strep.&nbsp; Kinda wished i had stayed at work, but after i found out about the call I just started to shake and all kinda of thought rushed in my head, so I wouldn't have been albe to really think streight.&nbsp; Ooh well I'll just have to deal with the pay i lost.&nbsp; Baby if you read this don't worry.&nbsp; I can deal with it.&nbsp; Don't think u have to pay me back, you don't.&nbsp; I love you.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Reply to&nbsp;Chris's  urlLink Comment &nbsp;  &nbsp;    Wow.&nbsp;   
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: awake   Yeah, as far as I know tomorrow i get a 3 day weekend. Unless the schedule is changed and I work Sunday.&nbsp; But glad to have a stretch of day's off in a row, I feel like i need a little time to recharge myself, and also next week my manager is on vacation, so extra perk for me :)    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Reply to  urlLink  Comment    &nbsp;  Dear Anonymous,  &nbsp;  I just having had any creative juices flowing lately.&nbsp; Actually I kinda forgot about that story until a few days ago.&nbsp; I dunno if I'll ever write more of it.&nbsp; I know it's a great intro, but I dunno if I want to "ruin" it by adding to it.  &nbsp;  --Bri      
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood: mad at self  From now on I'm just gonna keep my mouth shut. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       mood:happy  Officially proposed tonight :)  Didn't work they way I wanted it to, but what ever does ;)  I love you Chris 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>