<Blog>

<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah so my lastpost was at the library and i'm sure some people are like huh why are you at the library.  I'll tell you why, my mom is so dumb that she said i couldn't use my computer.  No big deal right?   I thought so too.  I just waited until she left the house and then tried to fire up my computer but i couldn't.  She took the power cord out of the back of the computer and hid it somewhere.  This caused me to walk like 3 miles to the library to get access to a computer.  I didn't want to be stuck at home anyway because that is boring.  So today i want to use the compter again and the power cord is still "missing".   Now i think she threw it away just to make me mad.  What she doesn't know is that i can access the internet using her laptop, which I am on now.  Another good thing is that i found another power cord that is supposed to be for some old laptop that doesn't even work.  I think i'm going to take that one and pray that it doesn't screw up my desktop.  For now I'll just go on this laptop when my mom isn't looking and keep snooping around for the missing power cord.   Sorry about all the complaining but i think it is necessary in this case.  Well anyway until nexttime this is zima.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah ok whatever I don't really care where my site is hosted as long as it works allright.  Well that means two things. #1 .tk is great for hosting my site for free and without ads. #2 they suck because the downtime is unbelievable.  As long as my site is up for most of the time then i think it's ok.  On to bigger and better things.  I was thinking of improving my site in many ways but did not know how to.  First of all I was going to add a counter so i can actually see how many people are accessong my site.  Number 2 I wanted to add another section of my website where i can just raqnt and rave all i want becauise i feel the urge to do that a lot.  I could just do that on this page bnut that doesn't go with the funny stories i tell at all.  The theme of the site would be destroyed and people wouldn't know waht to think when they went to nickzima.tk.  That is why i am planning to add another page tyo this blog for me to just yell at people about how my life sucks so much. Robby i need your help on the details and to everybody else sorry about the extremely small amount of funnyness of this post(i'm at the library and some people i don't even know are looking over my sholder to see what i am typing and now someone else has to use this computer so goodbye)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      You dummy Zima, its not my fault your site isn't working. First of all, I don't host any of my sites at my home in beatutiful euclid, ohio. So when something goes wrong its over at the computers in Chekoslovakia were this site is being hosted as we speak. Secondly, the site works fine, the problem is that the .tk domain names are currently down, you can still get to the site by going to http://virtualsws.host.sk/zima/blogger.html . If you can't get onto the site then perhaps you should email support@dot.tk and complain to them about it. Finally, you don't pay for any of this stuff and therefore you aren't even gauranteed 1% uptime. The fact that you have a site for free with zero ads should be something to brag about noty whine about, as most sites have 57 thousand pop-ups on them nowadays.  In conclusion, shut up it wasn't my fault.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HELLO anyone out there why isn't this web site working??  I tried to go to the web site many times from many different computers and it still won't show up when I go to www.nickzima.tk.  This is making me really mad because my pointless life and the pointless lives of the people I talk about should be able to be heard throughout the internet across the world.  If you are looking at this webpage right now e-mail idontknowhowthissiteworkssoilljustblameotherpeople@stupid.com and complain for me becasue I think it isn't fair that my website be suppressed.  If my website is not fixed in a short amount of time I will proceed to do the unthinkable, send out a chain letter.  And that is not all, I will send out a chain letter telling everyone who gets it to send it to addresses of my chosing.  The people on that death list will receive the lettere and any other letters that I will send out in the future thousands of times over.  Your inboxes will be so filled with garbage that you won't even be able to see if you have any real mail.  You better fix my site soon or your life as you know it is over.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now I finally give you the bobicks update.   My Day  So the bobicks trip was scheduled for Sunday, August 17th from 7-9 p.m. Of my mom, my dad, and Chris Simmons, all three knew about the time and place of the event.  Yet, all three screwed me over when the day finally came.  After waking up, going to church, and eating lunch I found out that I had to go to my cousin’s house to wish her a happy birthday.  I thought no problem I’ll be home by 7 because it was only like 12:00 when I left.  I was o so wrong.   It took about 1¼ hours to get there and then my dad wanted to go fishing.  It was okay and I caught a fish after about 15 seconds.  I thought we would just leave then but we kept fishing for like an hour.  After that we went to a Chinese Restaurant about 30 min. from their house.  We were in the restaurant for almost 3 HOURS.  After that long feast, we went back to my cousin’s house and did another hour of fishing.  By this time I was pleading my Dad to let me go to bobicks because 7:00 was rapidly approaching.  He said it’s ok we have plenty of time, it’s only 5:30 and your think is at 7.  I eventually got him to agree to leave so he started rounding up the troops and we were about to leave.  He then proceeded to ask who had to go to the bathroom and that everyone (I have 3 brothers and sisters) had to wash their hands.  This was a grueling event for me because that meant going back inside, waiting for at least 10 minutes for the rest of my family and say yet another entire round of goodbyes.  After that I had to be the shepard and find the lost sheep to herd them back to the car.  After a third round of goodbyes, we finally pulled out of the driveway at about 6:15.  I knew I was going to be really late but my dad refused to believe it.  He said that I would be on time or, the worst case scenario, 10 minutes late.  Needless to say, I was half an hour late and I was really mad when I got there.   Chris’s Day  Now I’m going to tell you about Chris’s day, of which I learned long after the fact.   “Yeah so I’m going over my Aunt’s house on Saturday for a little while so I can see her but I tell my Mom I’m not sleeping over there because I want to be here and I have stuff to do tomorrow.  When she comes to pick me up she asks me where my stuff is and I’m like ‘huh what stuff?’  She says I’m sleeping over so I don’t want to but I go get my stuff anyway.  So I’m over her house and it’s like 11 o’clock and I’m watching TV with my uncle.  He says he has free Six Flags tickets for tomorrow and asks if I want to go.  I say I’ll go but I have to be back by 7 because I am going to bobicks.  He says ok but when we get to the park he says that I won’t be home by 7 to go to bobicks.  By the time I get back home my aunt tells me I’m sleeping over again.  So I’m like what I have orientation to go to tomorrow.  She tells me she’ll drive me home in the morning so I get back home at like 7:05.”   Evil Rob's Day  This part was written by Rob which thus explains it being in first person. So, I get up at about 11.30 and go to the good old 12.00 mass. I've got a couple of hours to kill before Bobicks so I read a book, watch some TV and other randomness. Finally 6.00 rolls around so I call up my good buddy Joe B. to ask him how we're getting there, finally agreeing that he'll drive us there and I'll provide us with a ride home. So then about quarter to seven Eric calls me up and says he needs a ride, so I tell him to give Joe a call.  After all is said and done we leave and get there at about 7. Of course, being youth ministry, nobody has shown up yet, so me, Eric, and Joe sit around at the picnic tables talking for about a half hour about our summers. Apparently th best the Eric and Joe have done all summer is watch the American Pie movie's over Mike's house. Sherry shows up eventually and we talk to her for a few minutes...  Anywho, finally Zima shows up and we go to play some DDR. Now, normally DDR is pretty enjoyable except for when you've got Eric harassing you and trying to screw up your steps. We only played two games b/c I was just about ready to kill Eric anyway. So, Zima decides he's 'in the mood' for some putt-putt. Now, I just wanted to ditch Eric and Joe and go back to the DDR machine, but ended up shelling out 5.50 for a game. What a rip-off!  So, we're on the second hole and who else shows up but Jimmy, Mike Palermo, Erica, and Scott. So we start playing with them but later split so some other people don't have to wait so long for us. After putt-putt we go back for more DDR and more harrassment by Eric, although it stops when Mike agrees to play and calls Eric a "frightened conservative". So at this point me and Joe have to go since our ride has been waiting for a while. And that was that...    At the end of all this I ended up playing some great DDR (Dance Dance Revolution [ urlLink www.ddrfreak.com ]) finishing a really boring game of putt-putt and waiting around for my mom
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just want everyone to know in advance that this is no way an accurate representation of a letter that Chris or anyone else for that matter would, should, or could send to Six Flags or any other establishment for that matter.  This letter was composed for emjoyement purposes only and only after provoked by Six Flags for not returning serious complaint letters.  Furthermore, all of the information in this letter is factual yet exaggerated to be "larger than life" and should not be taken up with Six Flags.  I need not remind you that the view of the writer of the letter may, and in some instances certainly is, distorted in every way, shape, and form.  Without further adu I give you the complaint letter to Six Flags.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               123 Fake St. 								Anytown, Ohio 44444 								August 1st, 2003 Six Flags Ohio Public Relations 1060 N Aurora Rd. Aurora, Oh 44202   Dear whoever is stupid enough to happen to read this, 	This letter is in your hands right now because of  what happened to me when I went to six flags a few days ago.  The whole experience sucked like no other and I was pissed off to the max when I left.  Why does your stupid park have to suck so much?  It makes me sick to my stomach to know what is going on so close to my home.  Why can’t your park be more like Cedar Point or Busch Gardens or Disney World or Universal Studios or Midway Park or Six Flags Darien Lake or any other quality park?  The whole park stinks so bad that the bathroom’s usual stench was a slight relief from the midway.  All the ride operators were slow and many incompetent.  Many employees can be seen standing around talking to several other employees.  I don’t know what is going on in these clichés but I would bet  the rides would run better and faster if people would actually work instead of talking about what nightclub they are going to make an appearance in.  When I got in line for the villain wooden roller coaster, I saw 5 six flags employees just standing there staring at each other.  One of the ladies was writing in a book so I asked her what she was doing and looked at the book as I was walking by.  She responded to my question with the response, “HUH??!!” and when I looked in the book all I saw was some crappy doodles of random things and names of people.  As if that wasn’t bad enough, I got into the loading dock for the ride and there were only 2 people working the whole ride.  Couldn’t the 5 people come up from their discussion group and help the line move faster?  I think they could but they didn’t and the line continued to move somewhat slowly.   When I got into the ride this guy that looked like Stone Cold Steve Austin came up to my seat to check my restraint so I didn’t fly off the rollacoaster and die from the fall.  I was expecting him to check the bar to make sure it would hold a man of my size but all he did was put his hand on the bar and take it off without pulling or pushing.  What if the bar was defective?  I would have surely died from the hills on the ride.  By now I was really pissed off at that dummy but I liked the ride so I was forced to go back again.  What happened next may very well have a lasting effect on me for a long time to come.  After I walked past the gossipers, I went to the top of the stairs and got in the train.  When I sat down in my seat the lap bar fell down on top of me and left me no room to move at all.  I tried to saw the bar was too tight but Stone Cold Steve Austin ignored me and the train started to move.  On the bottom of the first hill, the bar got even tighter and by the bottom of the 2nd hill the bar was crushing my nuts with a force that could sink the titantic.  With all the rattling forces being applied to my already strained body, I could hardly breathe and only enjoyed getting off of the ride because I could finally scrape my torso off of the safety bar.   If I become unable to have children, you will be hearing from my lawyer.  After the bar Villain, I rode some other crappy rides because your less crappy ones were closed.  I wanted to ride the superman but it had a big crane next to it and it was closed.  The texas twirler and silver bullet never opened either.  By now I was so pissed off that I wanted to just leave.  On my way out of the park I saw the batman ride I wanted to go on so I did it.  The 1st part of the ride was good but the 2nd half of the ride had some big design flaws.  Why isn’t there a 0 gravity roll on the batman?  There should be a roll where the boring brakes are and the corkscrews aren’t even that fun.  It wouldn’t matter if there were no brakes in the middle because they only run 2 of the 3 train anyway.  Even when they are running at 2/3 of capacity  there is always one train in the station and one sitting right behind it waiting to get off the ride.  I think the whole 2nd half of the ride is really shady and you guys should replace it.  You should make it into a kick ass ride like the Medusa.    Another thing I totally hate about six flags worlds of adventure is the false advertising.  I saw a commercial the other day that said that the park had more roller coasters, more rides, and more water slides than any other park.  I know for a fact that cedar point has more roller coasters AND rides that six flags worlds of adventure and six flags worlds of adventure has less water rides than any water park across the country.  Six flags worlds of adventure has 7 new water slides and  like 10 old ones.  That brings your grand total of water slides to 18 and if you could count you would know that Dover lake water park has a whole park devoted especially to water rides with a grand total a hell of a lot higher than yours.  If you idiots just took a short drive down to saga more hills you could count the number of slides there and see that it’s more than the number of slides at your park.  So stop saying you have the most and best of everything because it makes me want to vomit.  And after I do, I’m sure it will sit on the midway for at least a day or two because no one takes the time to care about the appearance of the park.  I was walking into a line for the superman to see if it was running and I stepped right into a puddle of puke and damn did it stink.  It stunk just like your park and I demand satisfaction from this ultra crappy experience.  I want you to send me some free stuff to make me feel better.  I want a q-bot for the villain line to get a somewhat good ride and a cushion  to put between the bar and my person.  I want every employee working and the power to dock their wages if I see them slacking.  I want you to make a new commercial that doesn’t say anything about have the most or best roller coasters in the world because that is a flat out lie.  I want to be the 1st one to see the new commercial so I can tell you what fraudical statements you put in it.  I want Stone Cold Steve Austin to check every restraint on the Villain and I want all the barf in the park to be swept up.  If these demands are not met I am going to start a huge boycott of six flags worlds of adventure and stand outside six flags worlds of adventure to tell six flags worlds of adventure potential guests not to go to six flags worlds of adventure because six flags worlds of adventure sucks ass and six flags worlds of adventure employees don’t  work and six flags worlds of adventure doesn’t respond to my letters.  In conclusion I would like to say send me a reply letter or you will pay dearly. 											  											From your pissed off guest, 											Chris R. Simmons   P.S. The villain is an amazing ride and should not be downplayed at any time.  It is the soul purpose for my regular attendence to Six Flags Worlds of Adventure.  I'll get around to the Bobicks update eventually
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well this is my first official post so I'm going to try to make it a good one.  The date is set at August 15th and the place is Lakewood stadium while a highschool football scrimmage is taking place between the Ignatius Wildcats and the Lakewood I don't knows.  But anyway, to the story.  A few days before the game took place, my good friend Evil Rob calls me up and says, "do you want to go to see an Ignatius game on Friday?"  I was thinking why in blue hell would I want to go see a Ignatius football game when I don't even go there?  But then I realized that I had nothing better to do anyway except sit around the house and do absolutely nothing.  "Ok who's in?" i said.  Rob informed me that Simmons was in as well as he and myself so I thought it couldn't be that bad if they knew all the people there and I could meet all these people I've heard so much about.  If you don't know what I'm talking about a trip to chrissimmons.tk might be in order.  Well anyway I said I would go and didn't think about it anymore until I got a call from Rob calls me up on Friday a few hours before we are supposed to go and says Simmons is out.  I'm like WHAT he said he was in a long time ago so I called him up and asked him why he wasn't going and he said it was because his aunt wouldn't let him because the power might go out and then he would be "stranded" there or something.  Anyway I told him to stop being a little bitch and so he did.  When the big day finally arrived Evil Rob came to pick me up and we got to the stadium just before the game started.  As we were finding a place to sit I felt really cool not knowing a single person in the stadium but I still had a good time.  So we were walking to our seats and Simmons sees his speech coach with whom he is unhealthily obsessed named Mr. Fujimoto.  So Simmons being as secretive and strange as he is, doesn't even say anything to the Fuj as he calls him.  We just walked by and watched the game from our seats.  I can't believe the infinitesimal(small for those of you who don't know what that means) amount of knowledge some people have about football.  I swear Chris didn't know what was going on for one minute during that game.  Whenever there was a 1st down or a completed pass or something everyone would cheer and then Chris would look at the scoreboard like it was ESPN or something.  He was thinking where's the replay for all the people who missed the play?  Evil Rob was so obsessed with his digetal camera that he missed 4 of the 5 touchdowns.  I think I might have been the only one there who actually knew what was going on.  At halftime the close game was in Iggy's favor 21-14 so we decided to take a walk down the street to Angelo's Pizza.  On the way there we walked by the Fuj again so Evil Rob wanted to talk to him and told simmons to say something to him.  So simmons walks up behind this speech coach and yells, "heeeeyyyy   Fuuuuujjjjj"  and then doesn't say anything else for the duration of the conversation.  What's this about, why is Simmons so antisocial now?  But anyway we get into the pizza place and we don't know what we want so I start walking around and looking at the drinks in the cooler while Evil Rob waited for someone to give us a menu or a table or something.  So this lady comes out of the back and starts talking to Rob and all the sudden his face starts turning a bright red and he has no idea what he wants.  So he ends up getting a take out menu and sitting there for like 10 minutes complaining about how bad the service was and about how me and simmons screwed him over because he doesn't know what he wants and that he got the wrong menu.  He ends up blaming the server lady and calling her a pizza nazi because she somehow confused him and forced him to get a takeout menu and not get his food.    Well needless to say we left without food and went back to the stadium.  Oddly enough, they never played the second half of the game and just ran drills for a while.  After talking to a few people Rob knew and wondering why Simmons wasn't saying anything, we went back to Angelo's to get "revenge" on the "pizza nazi" for "screwing" us out of getting food in the 1st place.  So we're walking there and Chris and Rob are spazzing out trying to figure out what they are going to say and whos going to say it.  If it wasn't for me I'm sure they wouldn't have even walked in the door.  When we got in I demanded a table for 3 from the pizza nazi and she gave us one after a short wait.  After we ordered our pizza, the nazi came up to us and said something to the effect of, "I don't know what I'm going to do with you."   Well I was amazed that anyone could make that big of a deal over a few very confused high school kids but she did.  After that she made sure our pizza took really long to come out and to have our waitress interrogate us when we said we had to leave after we finally got our food after like 45 minutes.  By this time our ride was about to leave and seemed royally pissed indeed.  On the way home we ate the pizza, which was amazingly good and discussed stratiges for winning contests on the radio.  When I got home I went on Chris's website to see if he had updated it yet.  I was so mad at the inaccurate representations of past events and stupid remarks he made that I asked someone to set up this site for me so I could relay the information as it happened on that crazy Friday night.  I will continue to do so and look for the Bobicks update to come some time in the not so distant future.  ~Zima
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Everything is now up and running...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I was starting to plan a trip to Six Flags on Tuesday and so i found rides there and back and worked out everyone's schedule.  I was ready to go until I got a call from my good buddy Simmons.  So he says he's not going to Six Flags and he's going to a football game instead.  So I call him a bum and think I'll just go without him.  After that my other chum, Evil Rob gives me a jingle and tells me that we no longer have rides because the RTA only runs on weekends.  So I'm thinking I can't believe we got screwed over by the RTA.  After these late breaking developments I have to scramble to go to a backup plan so I don't get stuck sitting on my bum all night again.  So I call up simmons and get a ride to the game.  When we get to the game, simmons does the dumbest thing, he sits by his parents and doesn't want to move. Apparantly, Chris thinks the point of a football game is to just sit there 1 ft. from your parents and just watch the game.  Well anyway, we end up sitting there until the end of the 1st half and then i finally convince simmons to go somewhere else.  So we walk around for a while and see a billion people we know including Joe Chops and Jimmy Palko.  I'm sure simmons will rant and rave about the antics and inferior marches of the Euclid High School band but I really dont care and won't tell you about those crazy bandos.  If you really want to read about the band, I'm sure it will appear at within a few weeks urlLink www.chrissimmons.tk    So by this time Euclid is down 28-3 and I'm like what is going on, Euclid isn't supposed to blow like no other.  So by this time I start to notice some other things at the stadium other than the game.  So I am looking at the sidelines of the euclid side and who do i see?  None other than Jimmy Palko....   more to come at a later date but not a later time.  too tired to go on  Sorry about not finishing that post but I just got bored with this whole blogger idea for a while.  Now I'm back in the saddle because I'm getting screwed over.  I usually like to write almost exclusivly about when I get screwed over.  Anyway the rest of the Euclid game, me and Simmons basically watched Jimmy stand in the very back of the group of players on the sidelines.  About every five minutes either Simmons or I would comment aobut how far back Jimmy was.  After halftime we even went over by the locker room to try to get him to notice us and screamed at him when he jogged by.  He didn't even realize who we were so he went back on to the sidelines and never got in.  In the 3rd quarter, simmons spotted a cluck who used to go to SWS grade school but didn't say a word.  I saw some clucks from my driving school but left the area because they were insane in the membrane.  In the 4th quarter, we had to go back to sit with Simmons' parents and after Euclid lost a close game, we left for the car right away.   Now I'm sure the rest of this update wasn't worth the wait but I promise the next few will be.  Some crazy stuff has happened to me since September 13th and I'm gonna share it, eventually.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok so it was a bad idea to make a website where anyone could post whatever they wanted.  So sue me.  I forgot that everything I make has to be 100% idiot proof.  I'm sure even if I made the website where there were differnet members and everything, someone would screw it up anyway.  If you want proof, just look at virtual sws, debate central, debate central 2, debate zone, and debate core. Those sites were all ruined by really dumb people.  There is no way to stop their invasion.  We might as well just give up and make a big idiot section of every website where they can keep themselves occupied and stop ruining the good sites.  The only problem with that is that the idiot website would get so full and the real website would get so empty that there would be no more real website and the idiots would take over.  As long as there are idiots out there, no website can ever be successful when more than a admin is involved.  Still not convinced?  Just look at any roller coaster site.  All the little sites started by one smart kid never get anyone to join because huge sites like coasterbuzz look like so much fun.  So all these people go to coasterbuzz and post about stuff.  Then some idiots hear about coasterbuzz and are like oh this is great i want to see my words on the screen.  So those idiots go and share their stupidity with all the world and then an awesome site like coasterbuzz is ruined.  So coasterbuzz is ruined and the smart kid's site is ruined because he has no members and no one is happy.  So all the people that hate the idiots from coasterbuzz decide to make a new site and the process starts all over.  And maybe a site can be good for a short time before it is overrun by mindless dummies but when the time comes, it will fall.  And now whoever is reading this is thinking what are you trying to say you big dummy.  And what i'm trying to say is 2 things.  #1 thank you idiots for ruining my website even before it even got good and #2 run for your lives, idiots are taking control of the world.  p.s. You know I'm having a good day when all i complain about is the annilahation of my website.  I actually had a good day today despite having a "life threatinging epidemic".  My football team won today with 1.2 seconds left in the 4th quarter(15-13) and no one came up and bothered me during the game.  I put off my homework until tomorrow(probably going to come back and bite me in the bootimus maximus) and just sat there for a while and did nothing.  I mean doing nothing isn't my goal in life or anything{peter from office space} but it felt good for a day.  There is no imitation ~zima
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a request to explain some of the things from my last story as I was telling it to a few people so I thought it couldn't hurt to clerify a few things from my last post. mole day-  it is the celebration of a number which is immensly useful in chemistry but meaningless to the rest of the known universe.  The number is 6.02x10^23 which is a really big number.  Actually if you had a mole of marshmellows and forced the world's population (5 billion people) to eat 3 marshmellows a second, you would be eating for about 1.3 million years. Now that everyone knows what a mole is I can explain why it falls on october 23rd.  Some scientist who was out of his mind decided to set aside october 23rd for mole day to promote the discovery of what a mole really is.  Now this guy decided to be really witty and use his supercomputer intelligence to make a day where everyone could celbrate this utterly useless number.  So he looked at the exponent(10^23) and said hey let's make the mole day be October 23rd(10-23) and that will be so awesome that everyone will learn and prase the number.  Well I'm not so sure how that worked out but if anyone who reads this knows what the mole is then prove me wrong(coasterfan001@aol.com).  Next order of business is the "wilson" i refer to when talking about simmons.  I say wilson because there is a history book writer named wilson to whom simmons always refers to as a bastard.  Whever I say "wilson" i really mean "bastard" but i just like saying wilson.  When i say lessthenever, it's just another form of levertheness which evil rob says spontaniously   Note: I have stopped using the word randomly and all it's many forms due to a huge debate with a person I don't even know who claims that nothing is ever actually random although I think it can be.   Anyway levertheness is really the word nevertheless only garbled up and spit out somewhat backwards.    Joe Strelnik is a crazy guy who likes to shoot things (hunting i hope) and play hockey excessivly (he must have missed one day of school of every week in the 8th grade year)  Dommy is a dummy who always screws something up or makes a mess of something.  I could post some of the hilarious happings of Dommy and I if i felt like but sadly I don't feel like typing out all that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I know I haven't been able to update my blog in a while with all that important stuff going on in my life.  Well I finally managed to pry myself away from my all important duties to write this new post.  Although I am writing this on mole day (october 23rd)  but the events that are to occur in this update happened a few weeks ago friday.   Well one day Simmons somehow found his way over my house and the story starts, as it invidably always does with him.  So we are playing some DDR and he mentions that there is a big football game coming up between Ignatius and St. Eds.  I'm like ok I'll go I just need a ticket.  Simmons agrees and says all he will need is like $5 to buy me one.  I was thinking ok I'll go and it will be all good. Needless to say I forgot to give him the money anyway because I was so into the awesome game of DDR we were playing.  I need to beef up my combo skills for an upcoming tournament anyway so the steps were the 1st thing on my mind.  After a few days I'm talking to Simmons on the phone and he's telling me he needs to have the money because he has to buy the tickets the next day at school or else they will be sold out.  I told him there was no way I could get the money to him in time and that I would just pay him back.  He agreed to get the $5 from someone and I'd just pay him back.  Well how it turns out it didn't really matter how much money that "wilson" simmons had with him because there was a limit on how many tickets you could buy.  He only could buy enough for his family and not for me.  That bum never thought of giving $5 to someone else and asking them to buy a ticket.  It's ok Simmons because lessthelever it worked out in the end.  So I just got royally screwed by simmons so I called up Evil Rob to see if he had any extra tickets.  When he didn't I knew I qwas on a mission.  It was no longer about the football game, this was a challenge just to see if I could get into the most instense, most popular game of the year with no tickets in my hand 2 days before the game.  I pulled out all the stops and even ended up asking mafillips if he could hook me up.  By the way Mafillips is a kid that goes to Ignatius and thinks I go ther as well although I go to NDCL, which is totally on the other side of town.  So I asking everyone I know how I can get into this game when finally I have an idea.  As a last resort I strike up a conversation with no other than Joe Strelnik!!   I'm sure he was shocked to talk to me since I hadn't seen him since 3 years ago on the last day of 8th grade but he said he had some extra tickets.  I couldn't believe it I was in!!   All I needed now was a ride both ways, some way to collect the tickets in an aread mobbed by thousands of people, and someone to go with now that Joe was offerning me 2 tickets.   Don't worry I didn't get screwed over and just sit on the couch.  A lesser man would have done so, but i was a man on a mission.  I called everyone in my phone book, and started from the beginning again(omitting Dommy of course).  The day of the game arrived and I still had no one to go with.  That is until I called up Joe Basalla one last time and he was actually home this time.  Joe B. was the answer to all my problems.  He siad he could go and even offered to drive.  The game started at 7:30 so we decided to meet Joe S. at 6:15 to avoid the crowds.  We got there about 6 and parked as soon as we got off the freeway.  After a 10 minute hike to the stadium we waited at the gate where we agreed to meet joe s to pick up the tickets.  We waited for about 15 min and still didn't see anyone that looked anything like the mental image of Joe Strelnik from 3 years ago.  After losing a battle with a scalper we found out that there was anoter entrance to the stadium and went down that way.  Sure enough Joe s was there waiting for us to come and give him money so he could give us tickets.  It was kinda weird when we went to talk to him though because his friend was named joe too so everyone was getting confused.  It was some awesome planning and a lot of luck but I was in the stadium.  We ended up sitting on the Eds side because the Iggy side was so jam packed with people by the time we got there that there didn't seem to be room for even one more person.    So we sat there for about an hour because the game started late and then the holy war started.  It was a really close game the whole time and Ignatius ended by kicking the winning field goal with 30 seconds left in the game.  After they were bound to lose the student section on the eds side started chanting "we're not done yet"  and clapping their hands.  At that time joe and i left the game and went home.  On the way home we started talking about the game and we both agreed that it was a sloppy game with tons of turnovers and mistakes.  The halftime show was pretty good but I still like other schools' bands more.  While we were discussing the game and listening to some pearl jam, we came to a fork in the freeway, and took the wrong way!!!    We drove all around Cleveland and had to call Joe's dad to find our way back.  I don't exactly know where we went but I think our journey went something like this:  We started out in Lakewood, drove toward downtown Cleveland but took the wrong way, got off the freeway and drove through industrial valley, turned around and got lost again, got off the freeway again at the zoo exit, drove around toward the zoo for a while, then somehow ended up in parma, i think we were on kennings freeway for a while but then we finally found our way to the freeway and got back home.  In the next few days Simmons and Evil Rob tried to convince me that the 03 holy war was the best football game ever.  hard to believe considering both Joe and I thought it was a close game only because neither team played their best.  Now I have to admit both teams are amazing compaired to my school's team but that game was nothing compaired to great rivalries of the distant and rescent past.  And today's random(yes it is truely random) quote was spoken by the late graet Paul Ruben when referring to the magnetic breaks on Superman:The Ride of Steel.    "It stops you on a dime and gives you a nickel change"
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally the return of the updates that control your lives.  Well maybe not but this is the first new update in a while.  It all started after taking 3 of my 4 in car driving lessons with a real stickler named Norm.  He sucked so I was really looking forward to driving with the “cool” guy named Steve.  So Steve pulled up to my house and I got in the car at 5:00.   I knew right away that this in car would not be like the others.  Steve asked me what I listened to and then turned up the volume on 100.7 WMMS.  As we pulled out of my apartment complex, Steve said, “yeah, just go wherever you want, we’ve got two hours to kill.”  I was like ok whatever, turned left, and kept going strait down Ridge rd. for like 20 minutes.  By this time Steve was getting bored and complaining about driving for 2 hours for no apparent reason so we turned left again onto Route 6 I think.  After that we took the REALLY long way to Lakeland Community College where I had to do maneuverability.  So I did the whole test twice and Steve was talking on the phone with Bruce the whole time.  So after I do it twice perfectly Steve hangs up the phone and says, “Man that Bruce is such a little chatterbox.”  So he’s like you don‘t have to do this thing anymore if you don’t want to, your good enough to pass anyway.   Then he says he wants to go over by a tree to have a smoke.  I’m thinking ok whatever he’s gonna smoke and then we can go drive around some more and go home.  Steve gets out of the car to have a smoke and he tells me I can drive around as long as I don’t wreck the car.  So I’m driving around in this car when I only have my temps and Steve is standing there smoking.  It would have been an awkward situation if I would have crashed in the Drivers ed car without a Drivers ed teacher in the car.  I didn’t crash though and I went back and picked Steve up.  When I get him he’s on his cell phone again and he’s talking to someone and telling them that he had the best driver he’s ever seen in the car.  Well I’d say he‘s in the top 3 and I can’t even remember the other 2 is what he said.  So after that we are pulling out of the parking lot and we see Norm pulling into the parking lot at the same time so Steve Honks the horn at them and yells HEY NORM.  Less than a minute later Steve was honking at the campus cop and then we were on the road again.  So by this time it’s almost time to go pick up the next person who was driving after me and we go to the gas station to fill the tank up before we get on the freeway.  So Steve fills up the tank and asks me if I want anything from inside the gas station.  I tell him I’m fine but he brings out all kind of food anyway.  So we get on the freeway to get back to Willowick from wherever we were and Steve hands me a doughnut.  I’m like ok whatever and keep driving when Steve cranks up the volume on the radio and tells me to go faster because people are passing us.   So there I am driving down the freeway at like 70mph with one hand, eating a doughnut with the other hand in the drivers ed car with the stereo blasting WMMS, and passing all these cars on the freeway.  As if that wasn’t bad enough, I am eating this doughnut wrong and all the jelly comes dripping out the end of it and it’s going all over the place.  So now Steve is laughing and I’m laughing and choking with this doughnut flying all over the car while still trying to drive down the freeway so Steve tells me I have to switch lanes to get off the freeway.  I somehow get off the freeway and make it into another gas station to get all this jelly off of my shirt and my hands.  I get back in the car and go to this girl’s house to pick her up in the car.  When she gets in the car she sits down and lets out a death shriek and Steve asks her if she saw a bug or what.  It turns out that there was a bunch of jelly on the seatbelt and it looked like human blood.  Apparently she was afraid she was dying or something, but anyway she gets in the car and starts to drive.  While still on the back streets I find out that this girl has a fetish for subway and that she gets the same sandwich with a bunch of gay crap on it every time.  She explained it in detail but all I can remember is that it had cheese, mustard, mayo, and chicken on the same bun.  Scary if you ask me.  We got onto the main roads and she kept giving me whiplash on the starts and stops.  Then we were stopped at a light with some guy in a pickup truck sitting next to us and Steve tells this girl that she should look this guy in the eye and nod so he will know that it is time to race.  Of course she does it and when the light turns green she slams on the gas pedal.  The speed limit was 50 on that road but we were soon going way faster than that.  When Steve asked her if she wanted to slow down she said “You can’t get a ticket in the driver’s ed car, can you??” Of course you can so we slowed down and stopped at a red light about an inch behind the car in front of us.  Finally we pull up to my apartment and I get out while Steve is making fun of that chick for liking high school football.  I was left dazed and confused but it was awesome and would do it again if I could.    And now because this site is based off of making fun of Simmons or copying off of his website I give you the quote of the week.  “You can’t get a ticket in the driver’s ed car, can you??”   ~chick who was driving after I did 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think it's time I posted a little bit about a character I know named Tom, Aka Dommy.  This was of course because his dad once accuratly put it, "Ay Dommay, yo bone'ed"  When i was thinking about what to tell about first, I remembered that I had a file on my computer from when I did a speech about a hilarious event that happened last year at a carnival.  So I thought why don't I upload it and embarrass dommy further? Nick Zmina 11-24-02 Block 8 A Dommy Story  I. Introduction    A. Hi my  name is Nick Zmina  and today I’m going to be talking to you about a friend of mine and yours, the infamous Tom Lehman. I’m sure everyone here knows him or at least has heard about him at one time or another.  His notorious reputation precedes him for an other incident that I will not explain at this time because, frankly, no one wants to hear it.  What I will tell you about today, however, is an episode just as funny, but not as well known.  Most people in this room know Tom Lehman from seeing him in the halls of NDCL but I knew him because we went to the same grade school.  Before our high school days at NDCL we used to hang out on some weekends.  One of these weekends went terribly wrong…     B. The fateful night of the Shorgate Carnival was a chaotic one due to the involvement of fear, escape, and sirens.   II. Body    A. Planning errors-how I got stuck with Dommy 	1. I saw the fact that the Shorgate carnival was coming to town so I asked a bunch of  my friends to go with me; Dommy was one of them. 	2. Everyone bailed out at the last minute leaving me to go with Dommy.    B. At the carnival-Dommy getting rejected and then meeting with rough looking chicks 	1. Dommy gets repeatedly rejected by hot girls at the carnival. 	2. He points out some “rough” girls and hooks up with them as I go play arcade games (Simpsons) 	3. Dommy gets phone numbers; we leave    C. Leaving the carnival and climax-shopping cart, and car 	1. I realize we are late, so Dommy has an enlightenment-ride on shopping carts to get across the parking lot faster. 	2. We make great time running across the parking lot on our shopping carts     D. All the action 	1. Dommy has another enlightenment, we should push the shopping carts down the hill to get rid of them because we are at the end of the parking lot. 	2.  Dommy shoves his shopping cart down the large size hill at the end of the parking lot 	3. Car screeches around the corner and smashes into it at about 40 mph E. Escape  	1. I look at Dommy, Dommy looks at me and we run as fast as we possibly can 	2. Dommy gets tired out after the first 3 steps he takes and procedes to walk while in clear view 	3. A dew guys watching us ask Dommy about what he is doing hiding in the bushes.  He replies, “Nothing much, we’re just running from the cops.” 	4. We hear sirens blearing as we take a shortcut to my house    F. Arrival 	1. As we arrive at my house, my Dad is waiting for us and he notices that I am an hour late getting home and that my pants are soaking wet 	2. Dommy opens his big mouth to explain everything but I smash his foot as hard as I can with my heel and say it rained all night long 	3. After staring at the sky for several minutes, Dommy agrees with me and avoids talking about it for the rest of the ride home. 	4. The next day I saw more police cars than I had ever seen in my life III. Conclusion     A. Reiteration-Dommy is a funny  kid because he does so many stupid things like this (in 5th grade he got in a fight over a pen!!)     B. After a crazy night like this, it’s a wonder Dommy has never been in jail  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Usually when I get e-mail I just delete it or read it and want to shoot the sender for giving me a stupid chain letter or ad for their merchandise.  Every once in a while something good comes along and thats when you have to post it on a blogger.  So these awesome jokes are just dropped into my lap and I realize I have to post them or else I would be wasting the only good left in the world and I couldn't live with myself if i didn't do that.  Hey I could post about my stupid and pointless problems but this is probaby funnier.  I guess we'll see after my next few posts.  I still have to tell about the Lake Farm Park and rant about my situation with my cable internet.  But anyway these were pretty good....   A guy from Cleveland dies and is sent to Hell. He had been a horrible man his  entire life. The devil puts him to work breaking up rocks with a  sledgehammer. To make it worse he cranks up the temperature and the humidity.  After a couple of days, the devil checks in on his victim to see if he is  suffering adequately. The devil is aghast as the Clevelander is happily swinging  his hammer and whistling a happy tune. The devil walks up to him and says, "I  don't understand this. I've turned the heat way up, it's humid, you're  crushing rocks; why are you so happy?" The Clevelander, with a big smile, looks at  the devil and replies, "This is great! It reminds me of August in Cleveland. Hot, humid, a good place to work. It reminds me of  home. This is fantastic!"  The devil, extremely perplexed, walks away to ponder the Clevelander's  remarks. Then he decides to drop the temperature, send down a driving rain and  torrential wind. Soon, Hell is a wet, muddy mess. Walking in mud up to his knees  with dust blowing into his eyes, the Clevelander is happily slogging through the  mud pushing a wheelbarrow full of crushed rocks. Again, the devil asks how he  can be happy in such conditions. The Clevelander replies, "This is great! Just like April in Cleveland. It reminds  me of working out in the yard with spring planting!" The devil is now  completely baffled but more determined to make the Clevelander suffer. He makes the  temperature plummet.   Suddenly Hell is blanketed in snow and ice. Confident that this will surely  make the Clevelander unhappy, the devil checks in on him. He is again aghast at what  he sees. The Clevelander is dancing, singing, and twirling his sledgehammer as  he cavorts in glee. "How can you be so happy? Don't you know its 40 below  zero?" screams the devil. Jumping up and down the Clevelander throws a snowball at  the devil and yells, "Hell's frozen over! This means the Browns won the Super  Bowl!"   A new employee, Bet, is hired at the Tickle Me Elmo factory and she reports for her first day promptly at 8:00 am. The next day at 8:45 am there is a knock at the Personnel Manager Bobby's door. The Foreman from the assembly line, George, throws open the door and begins to rant about the new employee. He complains that she is incredibly slow and the whole line is backing up putting the entire plant behind schedule.  The Personnel Manager Bobby decides that he should see this for himself so George and Bobby march down to the factory floor. When they get there the line is so backed up that there are Elmos all over the floor and they're really beginning to pile up.  At the end of the line stands Beth. She has a roll of red plush fabric and a big bag of marbles.  The men watch in amazement as she cuts a little piece of fabric, wraps it around two marbles and begins to sew the little package between Elmo's legs.  The Personnel Manager Bobby bursts into laughter. After several minutes of hysterics he pulls himself together and approaches the woman.  "I'm sorry," he says to her, barely able to keep a straight face, "you misunderstood me yesterday. Your job is to give each Elmo two test tickles."  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was surfing around the files in my computer again and I found a list of cool and funny quotes.  I thought better post this before I format my computer for when I get cable internet in a week(WOOHOO).  So here are a few funny quotes.  Oh and I'm just going to copy and paste so you lazy bums out there wont have to do anything but read and laugh.  I hope your not too lazy to even do that.  So here we go and don't mind the random(sorry evan) order of the great quotes.  Bombs over bagdad Yay I love fighting  Don’t blame me it was the government Peace love and crabs ~Joe’s crab shack I bent my wookie Ha ha  Ay karamba 21th birthday~ French teacher It wasn’t me Mmmmmmmmmmm  ribwich Sir that is an insult, I challenge you to a duel  I have to go to ze lobby I invented the internet ~al gore Ay dommy yo bone’ed So we’re doin’ this right ~dommy Merry Christmas carl Uncle john are we in the ghetto yet Hello jerry	  cut the crap newmen This is shady, shifty, shafty, shifty, shotty, shaggy Some kids just don’t give a crud You are a loser, k, a loser Brrr   it’s cold in here These are eagle eyes I can’t laugh hahahaha He stole my pen I know it Chris that was a vary fraudical statement C’est Gauche Mal eleve I can’t stop shaking, I took 4 caffinnee pills Hey I took me parents car today And the bus was outta control None of the cars have stopped and the light is green.  We’re slowing down and as we switch into the turn lane I hear the loco bus driver yell  Ok cross!!  Give me the bullets or I’ll shoot Hold on marge I’m just nailing out a payment plan How about I give you the finger (flipper) and you give me my phone call Popeye’s chicken is freakin awesome Hey ya made it Erra will rule Is your homework done ~mom What do I need English for, I’m never going to England. Suck it trebeck Here’s jonnie Cock-a-doodle-do ~johnny Kulbus So I look up and I see Nick Zmina riding the tram and I look up again and I see tom lehman riding the tram and I look up and I see nick zmina riding the tram You big jerk You big slug Tu es un grand escargo. Free crab tomorrow We’re going streaking The price is wrong bitch Ohio the heart of it all Thank you, and enjoy your stay here at Cedar Point, American’s roller coast Does anyone know what basta is?  Mmmmm basta I did not have sexual relations with this woman Look at my butt, wow that’s huge ~Andrea Graper  Don’t be giving my daughter any second looks ~some guy who looked like HHH who we met at Six Flags when  Dommy met some girl in the lazy river You could pick off anybody from up here My name is mister truedoe hek hek hek Uncle dommy! uncle dommy! And all this crap comes out eeehh  eeehheeehhheeehh This is pissing me off ~Kevin Hink I really don’t want to do it but I’m going to have to give you a minor Mr K. I want you to know that these guys are idiots and that’s why they are all getting majors Mr. Spacuzza Ok now no one log into their computers yet  ~dumbass Slocombe Actually it actually happens ~shide Oh yeah we’re digging up some dirt on these guys now I could see your face Zima+ Chris= Hitler I em Jourege Boosh Me fail English, that’s unpossible  I’m such a big moocher, I mooch off of everybody I hate the Victor It’s all fun and games until someone gets hurt…  then it’s hilarious Test the whiskey to make sure it’s ok.  More nunoins I could debate you on that Mr zmina says you’re a slacker Don’t just sit there with your thumb up your butt. Gwaa HAAA  HAAAA ~Mr. True do So who did you have for sophomore religion, Scotty 2?? This girl is so desperate that she loses her shoe and these three shady guys pick it up and they’re like can we walk around with you and she says yes because she is so desperate. Sssssssss hands up dirt bag Dummy We can’t go today, its raining rob.  Hey look it’s a cracker barrel Keep you  head back and hands down.  Hands down.  Hands down    hands down    hands down    hands down    hands down GGGOOOOOOOOO For today, we’ll go over the class rules, talk about the curriculum, I’ll punch TJ in the face  and we’ll call it a day  ~current religion teacher Well I was drinking this milk shake and I put it up to my mouth.  All the sudden it all started coming out and getting all over my face.  I couldn’t swallow it all and it was getting all over the place.  There was nothing I could do, it was to much for me to deep throat  ~last year’s religion teacher What do you wash first in the shower? ~Religion teacher from 2 years ago Hello Stanley/Newman/Fargus Good job now squeaky chew through my ball sack  ~Principal skinner Where’s the beef? Those are some kick ass plungers. I’m seeing all these people wearing colored undershirts and underwear.  It’s either white or nothing at all!!!  ~Nazi Nancy No Mack Attack I don’t think so ~Amanda Hoffman Flanlie, we don’t want to hear from you so just shut up  ~Amanda Hoffman AAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH  NO TEACHER Ok I think we’re going to go over this math test,  ehh,  never……   due to the fact that more than half the class got scores better than perfect. These magnetic brakes stop you on a dime and give you a nickel change  ~Paul Ruben DDDAAAAAAAAAMMMMMMMMMMMNNNNNNNNNNN!!!!!!!!!! These judges are screwing me over. BBAAAAAAAA   I’m Zima!!!!!!!    ~simmons GGGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOO   ~simmons as the swede  Now I'm not really sure what this is but it sounds funny now that I read it so I'll include it too.  This is the story of tom dowd.  I think he is wrong so I say tomdowdiswrong and he thinks he is right so he says tomdowisright but I say tomdowdiswrong and that’s what they say.  And after that I say chris is a fraud and everyone says chris is a fraud because his name is fraud.  And then he kills it and the fraud dies and he is chris the un fraud.  And then he kills it again and then they say he is and he says he isn’t and we get the erra.  And then the evil one is evil and he is a fraud again but they do not say fraud and I do not say fraud but he is one.  Then he is not fraud until he kills it again and again he is a fraud.  When he kills it he does back and he is a not fraud.  Now he is a fraud but no one says it.  The evil one is still evil but the fraud does nothing again. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Zima said: I mean here we have Evil Rob running away to the ends of the Earth for this debate fetish he has while Simmons keeps obsessing about this unqunchable thirst for 1st place in speech tournaments.   It seems to me like you have nothing to do on your weekends. I mean, at least simmons and I have found something worthwhile. You know, maybe if you spent your wasted time studying for SATs your score wouldn't be so medeocere, but I mean, thats just a crazy thought.   Zima said: I thought I would go and set up this sweet event on MLK weekend because everyone was complaining about the Youth Renewals of past years. So everything was all good and the bums I call friends said they were coming. But then one by one the "old crew" bailed out with crappy excuses and just plain lazyness. This really sucked because there were perfect conditions for this retreat. I mean there was DDR and no school the next day. On top of that there were cool games planned and a big screen TV for DDR and watching movies. I still went and the weekend was pure sweetness but it could have been even better they had come through. Understandably I was pissed at those bafoons not because they didn't want to do but because they blew me off with fake or stupid excuses that didn't make any sense.   First of all, we both would have had to show up several hours late. Secondly, its a lot easier to go to something like that if you didn't have school on friday, or had to wake up at 6 am on that saturday, following the most stressful weak of the year. So i mean, ya.. I'm sure it was a piece of cake for you, but it actually was hard for some people. And how exactly did I blow you off? I never gauranteed I was going; i said i'd go if i could. But tragically I couldn't. The excuse made sense, i'm sorry it wasn't good enough for you.   Zima said: I know they are busy but come on people you gotta look at what your doing. I can get busy some times but that doesn't stop me from seeing the old crew if they want to do something.   Sadly, the old crew can't live forever. Theres no reason we still can't hang out, but ya gotta find something else to do not involving the old crew.   Zima said: Evil Rob you really have to lay off the debate, it's taking over your life. I don't really see how you could value cutting cards(not playing cards if anyone actually reads this) above anything else but you seem to want to stay home all the time and do it instead of going anywhere.   I can see how you, never having been engaged in the activity, are so quick to attack it. But you gotta realize man, it actually is fun and gives me something to do rather than the same old same old. I told you to try it some time but you basically gave up, so what can i say?   Zima said: I think it just sucks that everyone from SWS is finally seperating after mostly staying together for the 1st half of high school.   Seriously, it was inevitable... who didn't see it coming?   Zima said: I actually have an interview at Mr. Hero tomorrow but I think we can still keep it together man. If nothing is done I'm gonna fall off of the face of the Earth like Joe Strelnik did.   Me too... but you gotta realize that the old gang is moving on. Not that we can't still do stuff, but things do come up.  Thats all I have to say for now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I was looking at this site and I realized that I haven't updated in a long time and I wondered why that was.  It wasn't because nothing had happened to me recently because things have happened(I got my drivers liscense and the mederocere 1190 results from taking my psats).  I think the reason I don't update anymore is because no one wants to read the stuff I post anymore.  I mean here we have Evil Rob running away to the ends of the Earth for this debate fetish he has while Simmons keeps obsessing about this unqunchable thirst for 1st place in speech tournaments.  I thought I would go and set up this sweet event on MLK weekend because everyone was complaining about the Youth Renewals of past years.  So everything was all good and the bums I call friends said they were coming.  But then one by one the "old crew" bailed out with crappy excuses and just plain lazyness.  This really sucked because there were perfect conditions for this retreat.  I mean there was DDR and no school the next day.  On top of that there were cool games planned and a big screen TV for DDR and watching movies.  I still went and the weekend was pure sweetness but it could have been even better they had come through.  Understandably I was pissed at those bafoons not because they didn't want to do but because they blew me off with fake or stupid excuses that didn't make any sense.  I know they are busy but come on people you gotta look at what your doing.  I can get busy some times but that doesn't stop me from seeing the old crew if they want to do something.    Evil Rob you really have to lay off the debate, it's taking over your life.  I don't really see how you could value cutting cards(not playing cards if anyone actually reads this) above anything else but you seem to want to stay home all the time and do it instead of going anywhere.  I think it just sucks that everyone from SWS is finally seperating after mostly staying together for the 1st half of high school.  I actually have an interview at Mr. Hero tomorrow but I think we can still keep it together man.  If nothing is done I'm gonna fall off of the face of the Earth like Joe Strelnik did.  Anyone who reads this e-mail me at  urlLink   to tell me what you think. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well i was having this argument with mike on how long a week is.  I dont know why we coundn't just look at a calendar but I guess that would just be too hard.  The issue is as follows.  Mike thinks Tom came over his house twice in two weeks, both on Saturday.  I think it's the same week.  What you have to realize is that the week doesn't start until the minute Tom walks out of Mike's house.  But anyway if someone is bored and wants to read this and tell me or mike what you think, go right ahead.  I'm sure we can clear up how long a week actually is!!   Coasterfan001: mike?  or is this dommy Viking 0587: mike   Coasterfan001: ok just makin sure Coasterfan001: b/c dommy is over your house like every day Viking 0587: not really   Coasterfan001: well it seems like it Viking 0587: like once or twice a month   Viking 0587: if even that   Coasterfan001: well hes been over your house at least twice this week Viking 0587: what are you talking about   Viking 0587: he came over yesterday and that was it   Coasterfan001: i know because i took him over your house last saturday and yesterday he was talking to me on this sn Viking 0587: that's not the same week   Coasterfan001: yeah it is saturday to saturday Coasterfan001: lol Viking 0587: the week starts on sunday   Coasterfan001: but the visits were less than 7 days apart Viking 0587: saturday to saturday is 8 days   Coasterfan001: lol no its not Viking 0587: count    Coasterfan001: ok saturday to sunday is one day Coasterfan001: sat to mon is 2 Coasterfan001: sat to tues is 3 Viking 0587: sat to wen is 4   Coasterfan001: sat to wed is 4  sat to thurs is 5 sat to fri is 6 and sat to sat is 7 Viking 0587: sat to thurs. 5   Viking 0587: its 8   Coasterfan001: weren't we just counting? Coasterfan001: but ANYWAY Coasterfan001: do you have school on friday Viking 0587: wait   Viking 0587: sunday to saturday is a week  (7 days) plus the saturday before that sunday   Coasterfan001: what time did he leave on saturday Viking 0587: thats not the point.......the point is that it's been 8 adys   Coasterfan001: actually it is the point b/c if he left at say 7 on the 1st saturday and came over at 6 the second saturday it would have been less than 7 full days Viking 0587: first of all it wouldnt be less than 7 days no matter what time he left......if anything it would be in between 7 and 8 days   Coasterfan001: ok this is so easy    saturday was the 1st of febuary.  add a week or 7 days and you get the 8th wich is the next saturday Viking 0587: last saturday wasnt the 1st it was the 31st of january   Viking 0587: what now   Coasterfan001: oh oops then from the 31st to the 7th is how many days Viking 0587: 8   Viking 0587: "oops"   Coasterfan001: yes because i was looking at sunday Viking 0587: proven point-8 days   Coasterfan001: but the fact remains from sat to sat is 7 days Viking 0587: nick\   Coasterfan001: no no no Coasterfan001: i was looking at sun to sun which is still 7 days Coasterfan001: lol Viking 0587: this is 1st grade work   Coasterfan001: yeah i know Coasterfan001: ok lets look at it this way Coasterfan001: su m t w th f sa      how many days are there Viking 0587: 7   Coasterfan001: exactly Coasterfan001: thats how many days are BETWEEN saturday and saturday Viking 0587: 8\   Viking 0587: no thats how many days are between sun-sat   Coasterfan001: between sun and sat is mon tues wed thurs fri and sat Coasterfan001: thats 6 Viking 0587: im losing my mind with you nick   Viking 0587: 1 week =7 days=sun-sat   Coasterfan001: yes 7 days is a week but it starts the minute he walks out your door Viking 0587: forget about when tommy came over or left...........saturday to saturday is 8 days   Coasterfan001: yes part of the second saturday was the 8th day but only after the time dommy left on the second saturday Coasterfan001: how about i post this on the internet and see what other people think Viking 0587: ask how many days is it from sat to sat   Coasterfan001: no im going to post this whole conversation with both our e-mail affresses and see who says what Viking 0587: then dont do it   Coasterfan001: why not Coasterfan001: scared you will be wrong Viking 0587: no its just dumb   Coasterfan001: i beg to differ
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Contrary to popular belief, the old crew is NOT seperating so i don't want anyone to run screaming into the night. Well anyway I did get that job at Mr. Hero so, if anyone wants to come see me, just show up at the vine street location between 5 and 9 and chances are I'll be there.  In addition to the fun of working there....  I'm now saving up enough money to Finally get a car.  I'll type some more later, i didn't see the time.  Oh and of course I have a quote "you can turn your back on a person, but you can't turn your back on a drug, especially when it's waving a razor sharp hunting knife in your eye."  ~Johnny Depp in the movie Fear and Lothing in Las Vegas.  Very screwed up, yet somewhat funny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally for the first time in a long time I actually have news.  First of all i moved to a new house.  Whoopidy frikkin do.  No one cares but it was funny when the cable guys got there and asked what tf they were supposed to do and i was like how tf should I know.  My mom's car died so she was just sitting on her ass at our old place.  Then the movers came and they are like where tf should we put your ass load of crap.  I'm like WTF how should I know where to cram all this useless bull??  So then my mom gets there and starts bitching at me just as the couch gets stuck in the doorway going to the basement.  They ended up piling most of the crap in the garage but ANYWAY.  It was funny because Jack came over and we had to get a new battery for my moms car.  Well Jack has his temps so we went to change the battery with Jacks dad and we "raced" on the way home!!!  My mom's tricked out car topped out at 45 mph and I won.  After that Jack left and there was some more boring crap and then I was like I want to go play ddr and get outta here.  So to make a long story short(er) I borrowed my moms car again and went to Bobicks to play some on a good machine. When I walk in who do I see?  GLOWSTICK from the first yourney Evil Rob and I made an appearance in.  So I was thinking of leaving right away but I was thinking how much I wanted to play. I tried to play on maniac but I realized that once again, I sucked.  Unfortunatly glowstick was drawn to me like a fat kid to a cupcake and he started talking to me.  I was trying to think of something to get out of the convo so I'm like hey the machine's open wanna play?(btw they got a shady new coin line thing where you write your name on your quarter and stick it up there)  So apparently glowstick has been practicing because he is REALLY good. Him and some of glowstick's friends double and triple A'd almost every song they played.  I must have looked like an idiot getting B's and C's.  OH NEWS: Bobicks is probably getting another mix very soon so evil rob keep a heads ^ on Ohio DDR.  Anyway After I played one game the guy came over and put it on freeplay so I couldn't leave then.  I played another few games and then D.J.SarIN(aka glowstick) gave me this really shady Cd and I left.  I got lost on the way home but its all good....  Ok now I have to go hook up my cable modem and hope itworks. school blows and has anyone been to strong bad e-mail lately? I want to see if he used my mail on his number 100 email reading.  note: edited for any bastards from TBBS who think I am the mullet. p.s. HA i didn't go to school on Friday p.p.s. HA i set up my computer p.p.p.s. HA i successfully used a p.p.p.s. oh yeah and a quote i like{disclaimer: not a quote of the update or anything else like that}  by Homer Simpson:"Should I drive home? No, I'm drunk...  Wait a minute I shouldn't listen to myself I'm drunk."  BAAAA I'm Zima 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      First off I have to say that Mr. Brennon is a great guy who makes even boring stuff interesting.  The Q&A session with him was really cool and there were some sweet questions he answered.  Some of Robby’s questions weren't really answered but more like b.s.ed by Mr. B.   Some questions that I thought were funny weren't answered and I just realized that Dommy didn't ask any stupid questions.  Oh that’s right, random occurrence number one was Dommy showing up for the mini course at YM.  Actually he did walk into mass in the last 5 minutes, which was pretty funny.  Random occurrence #2 had to do with Robby.  All I know was that it was extremely random.  After mass Evil Rob walks up to this chick and gives her a big hug.  All I was thinking was oh man Robby.  What a P.I.M.P.  He said he didn't know her and I couldn't decide whether to believe him.  For some reason Robby's personal life is a point of interest for Simmons along with myself.  I just think its funny...   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well last time I was here talking about some awesome night i had last friday.  I could give a recap but whoever knows  me probably already heard what happened. So anyway this Thursday I used the free movie tickets that I won from 92.3.  Yes there is a little ranting and raving to do about getting the tickets but I'll do that at the end, if at all.  I mean i'm high  on life right now, don't sweat the small stuff right...  On Monday I had work so I couldn't do anything that day but  Tuesday I was able to get downtown before 6 to go pick them up.  Lol it was funny because there were some people walking out the door and locking it up just as i got there.  They let me in but told me to tell the guy i got the tickets from  to lock the door.  I did but I dont think he heard me...  I hope that building didnt get robbed because of me.  I don't even remember wednesday, must have been crappy and boring.  Thursday was the day I finally used those FREE movie  passes.  So it was Evil Rob and me and we went into the movie thinking it was gonna be the worst thing in the world because of the title.  The Girl Next Door wasn't THAT bad IMO.  It was funny when we called both moviephone and fandengo and it wasn't in any database anywhere.  For a while I thought the movie didn't actually exist.  Before the movie there were many prizes to be given out.  First you had to look under your seat to see if there was a winning sticker under there. I swear they were just telling us o do that so we wouldn't be witnesses to a murder or something. After that they had the worst trivia EVER. Some of the questions were, "What is the sequel to the Fast and the Furios?" and, "IN this movie rob schneider plays an Animal. What is the movie?" It was cool though because I got free keychains and a free sticker. The funniest part of the night was at the end of the movie when Evil Rob stood up and said, "that was the worst movie I have ever seen." About 2 seconds later some guy in the row behind us stands up and says, "that was the best movie I have ever seen." Well i guess that can be my quote of the post and I can go to bed now. The rant isn't really needed so it wont be posted.  Yo Im out. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The reason why this blog has remained, and will remain mostly unused for the rest of my life is because it pisses me off so much.  I had this huge awesome post about how I won movie screening passes off the radio and had this hilarious personal cheering section when I was playing DDR but the thing didn't do what it was supposed to do when i pressed post and publish and now the world will never know about who I saw at the dollar show and why it was so funny or about what happened after i got kicked out and then won the radio contest.  As of right now I am looking for a better place to put all the crap no one wants to read.  But if anyone does read this and wants to go see a movie before it comes out e-mail me(nzima@hotmail.com) and we'll talk.  I really do hate this thing.  My post was at least 2 pages long!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OOO I finished a story before I thought I was going to.  Why not post this now?  Forget homework anyway.  That stuff is for suckers!! As a remembrance of Six Flags Worlds of Adventure, thrilling a small percentage of the Northeastern Ohio area for the last 4 years I decided to tell the best story I could remember of the good old days of Six Flags.  Of course this story includes a few of the usual suspects.  It involves Dommy, me of course, and Joe Strelnik.  I don’t even remember how we got there or who else was supposed to be in and who screwed who.  That’s ok because we didn’t spend too much time on the rides anyway.  So we were let loose in the park and started walking around and we must have ridden at least a few rides when we got there.  Eventually it got really hot on that blistering summer day so we set off for the water park.  Whoa baby that water park was jam packed with people.  We got into our swim suits and headed for the beach umm wave pool to set up base camp.  Of course we had to go into the wave pool for a while.   While we were in there Joe Strelnik concocted a plan to get some ass that day at the park.  He thought no one would notice if we grabbed while we rode over the waves.  Of course this was not one of the best ideas in the world.  Needless to say it was not successful and Joe's quest for ass continued.  We did make a few unwanted friends in the wave pool however.  There was a group of black kids who took a liking to us and threw Dommy up against the wall for no reason.  I will neither confirm nor deny my involvement with any of the actions stated here.  I’m sure if you are reading this you know already anyway.   But back to the story....  We got out of the wave pool and for some reason I want to say we rode the Big Dipper.  That doesn't make much sense but that’s what I remember so that’s what we did!!  After that it was off to the lazy river where part 2 of Joe's quest for ass occurred.  Joe(or Dommy(this was a long time ago)) came up with the brilliant idea to swim underneath hot chicks to look a them from underwater when they wouldn't notice...  Dommy then swims off with his whale like abilities and when Joe and I finally catch up to him he is talking to this average girl.  He was praising her uncontrollably and she was running away.  Me and Joe were making fun of Dommy being an idiot of course and lets just say I was very sore in a certain region of my body for a few days after she realized what me and Joe were saying.....  Ok back to the boat.  This girl Dommy is "stalking" gets out of the water because she has to go somewhere.  Dommy gets out of the water too and is about to walk over to talk to the girl more.  That is when some burly guy who looked EXACTLY like the wrastler HHH started yelling at all of us.  He had the ponytail and the cannon biceps and everything.  I was like whoa that’s really scary.  I'll never forget what he said.  "You see that girl over there?  That's my daughter!  Don't be giving my daughter any second looks!!!!"  [Insert mean and scary look here]  About 1 second later all three of us took off running and for good reason!!    After that we couldn't get the locker open because someone lost the combination.  I met the most forward girl I've even known.  {PAGE MISSING} Joe started his quest for the 3rd Ashley.  That’s right the girls dommy and I met were both named Ashley.  Wow ~polick   In short it didn't happen and we got ambushed by the black kids again on our way to the Villain.  Joe and Dommy wanted to fight but I reminded them that there was a gang of like 50 ppl right around the corner so we got one last ride on the Villain and got the sam hill outta there.  I believe Rodanne gave us a ride home lol.  Rodanne: Hi Dommy how was the park? Dommy: ok Rodanne: what did you do? Dommy, Joe, Me: uhhhhhh nothing 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw glowstick riding his bike today down Vine Street.  He wasn't riding on a sidewalk or anything, it was the grass and he was on a racing bike not a regular bike.  LoL it was hilarious because I beeped at him from my mom’s car and he almost fell off.  On a more serious note my mom’s car is a piece of crap and broke down just as I was pulling into GLP.  I smelled antifreeze on Aurora Road and by the time I got into the parking lot it was smoking like crazy.  I called my mom and asked if her car was smoking pot but she said no and called a tow truck.  I went into the park and tried to find my crew members but they weren’t on any of the rides I am supposed to be training to run.  To make a long story short I walked all the way around the park at least twice and had to cross the causeway even though it had big gaps in it.  Somehow I ended up at the Dominator and had nowhere else to look so I stayed.  After I rode the sweet ride formally know as the Batman: Knight Flight, they let me run it even though I wasn’t even supposed to be in that area.  After that Bill Spehn came up and rode it, but only after 3 people smashed him into the seat.  He gave a speech to the crew(and me although he didn’t know the difference) about what a great job we were doing and how the ride was named the Dominator because it Dominated the park or something like that.  It was supposed to be inspiring but it was just weird for me because I wasn’t really supposed to be there. Well anyway at the end of the night the TL and the ATL of the ride were going to find where I was supposed to be today so I could go to the right place tomorrow but we just ended up talking to Bill Spehn and Andre some more.  Supposedly I am still going to work the Thunderhawk even though the only training I have gotten so far was on the Dominator.    I got to that POS car at like 830 and there was a tow truck there waiting.  The thing had a top speed of only 60 MPH and didn’t even go that fast.  By the time I got home it was already 930, about an hour ago.  I guess I can’t talk about anything after that because after that is now.  What I’m doing right now is typing up this trip report/blog update while I’m supposed to be reading Animal Farm.  It’s actually a good book and I’m going to go now.  But before I leave, I’ll leak a little inside info: Villain has new trims added on that section that seemed to be built for them and Dominator(FKAB:KF) will be running 3 trains all the time now.  Retracking has taken place or is taking place on all wooden rides and the Xflight train was still in pieces last time I checked.  The new music is AWESOME and the management seems to be competent.  My crew is pretty cool(when I can find them)  and Bill Spehn should run for President of the U.S.  I have homework to do.  $$$ Zima 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I just got of the phone with a Mr. Thomas Lehman and I learned many interesting things about this whole screwy system we like to call friedship.  First let me start by saying working screws everything up.  Eric started it freshman year and by now it seems like everyone and their brother has jobs now.  Even I have been taken to the dark side.   I can never do anything with anyone anymore because I'm always doing something stupid or working.  Actually the only people I can think of who haven't gotten a job yet are Robby and Chris.  You slackers, you dont know how crappy it is to be employed.  Well by a crappy dead end job anyway.  I might have to go back there at the end of the summer but as long as I'm at Geauga Lake its all good.  Robby, your away message is pretty shady and you shouldn't use it anymore.  I bought a car on Sunday wahoo!!!    A little random fact here from GLP orientation.  Craig Rosenthol looks and act just like Dommy.  Apparently it took him 7 tries to pass his drivers test and crashed his car once during it..  P.S. I just signed up for that new email service from Google.  Its not e-mail its G-mail!! P.S. #2 there may be a universal update on this site coming sometime soon.  Watch for it
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       BAAAAA    SIMMONS!!!!   Going to Washington are you?  Fine be that way...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yeah, this is rob, by permission of Zima, i am posting a report of our trip to cedar point on sunday. so zima is supposed to meet me at 8 am mass at st. william and then leave for cedar point straight from there, but i never see the kid show up. then like a half hour later i look back and he's sitting there grinning like an idiot.  after mass i realize i forgot my season pass at home, fortunately its only a 37 second drive from church. anyway me and zima eat bagels and talk to my mom, which ends up wasting another half hour, and then leave. now, zima thought he would get to cedar point by taking route 2 the whole way there. of course, he didn't realize that route 2 ends in lakewood and picks back up in god knows where, so he misses the I90 exit and we have to drive through downtown cleveland, which ends up wasting another couple of minutes.  finally we get back on the freeway and get to cedar point. now, zima works at geauga lake, and i gotta admit, the perks are pretty nice. we saved ourselves 8 bucks b/c employees get to park for free, which is crazy awesome. so i'm looking at the season pass line and it doesn't look too long at first, but after they stamp my certificate, i have to go wait in another line behind the building which was ridiculous! then some dude named stan had to come out and hand everyones passes back. the whole process took about an hour...  finally we get into the park around 11.45 and we head for the cheese on a stick stand, best amusement park food ever. we decide we'd eat our cheese on a stick while waiting in line for wicked twisster, but the line was too short! so we had to get out of line. we figured we'd eat while we walked toward magnum. i was taking pictures along the way since i'm a camera nerd. we get back to magnum which has no line, and ride in the ejector seat (1-3 for those out of the know). Great ride for the first of the season. we get off and head oveer to Top Thrill Dragster since zima still hasn't ridden. that line took about an hour which wasn't bad, except that zima wasn't allowed in line with his glasses, which he just ended up pocketing anyway.  yeah so that was a good ride, although not the best in the park. i think zima's comment was, 'that was a lot of acceleration' or something stupid like that. after that we headed over to the arcade for some DDR, even though having not played in a long time, i wasn't doing so hot. after we finished my feet burned and i couldn't stand up straight.. it was bad. then we walked over to ride wicked twister, which was freezing cold as always since it is right on the beach. that was a good ride, but we were sick of the launch coasters so we walked to millennium force next.  we rode dodgems somewhere in there but i forget exactly where. oh well, screw it. millennium force was about an hour long line but definately worth it, best ride ever. after that we had about an hour before we had to leave so we had to decide between raptor, blue streak, or the antique cards. we opted for raptor which had a 10 minute line. apparently jes moved to geauga lake, that bum. anyway we had plenty of time after that so we rode blue streak which was a walk-on, and then the antique cars, which zima felt all cool giving the guy the geauga lake spiel.  after that it was about 5 so we departed for home, this time not missing any freeway exits. a great way to start of the year at cedar point, hopefully i'll be getting there again soon. i'm sure zima will have some commentary to add eventually.  here's the pictures: http://www.virtualsws.host.sk/photo/cp/index.php  rob
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just wanted to take the time to say WHAT HAPPENED?  This site has totally changed and i dont really know whats going on.  It looks like people will be able to leave comments about my posts now.  Will anyone do this?  It looks like no because this site only effects about 2 people.  They would be me and some Japanese guy who is really bored in the middle of the night over there.  I bet no one was expecting that ^.  I bet all you out there(i know i'm talking to myself) thought I was gonna say Simmons didn't you?  Well i didn't because his computer is broken.  So ha!  I played DDR today.  I blow like no other.  I think this is the result of not playing in like 2-3 months.  Again there were ppl at Bobicks who were friggin awesome and I got schooled.  While they were getting perfect combos on the legend of max, i was hacking up a lung on era.  No glowstick this time, I was surprised.  I got my car yesterday YEAH!!  Man gas is expensive and there are no parking spots left in the school lot but its all good because my car doesn't use much gas at all(1.6L V4 for all you greasemonkeys out there) and the Sr.s are leaving in a week so Im gonna steal one of their spots.  I can't wait until Saturday so I can go back to Geauga Lake Park(GLP).  School isn't cool and I dont want to go tomorrow...  I dont feel to good and I really should be sleeping now instead of doing crap.  Can't crap just do itself?  Damn I really thought that would work but I should go do crap and sleep.  Wait or is it I should go do sleep and take a crap?  Either way, I have to do all 4 anyway.  Wow I'm not making sense but thats ooook.  I had a different post to post but this just came out.  Man this is an incoherent pile of garbage.  Last fairly shallow observation of the day: Every time someone in my family gains access to an additional car the current one(s) break.  For example my mom rented a car so I could drive to work and her car broke.  Now that I have my car, my moms car needs the cruize control repaired and my Dad thinks he needs a new transmission.  It's like I'm destined to get screwed over about this stuff.  The farthest I have driving my car is less that 2 miles at a time.  Come on can the cosmos align or something and let me have the car and drive it too?!?!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wasn't really half an hour late to church...  I walked in 5 minutes late and didn't want to walk all the way up to the front like some sort of a doofus so i sat in the back.  Yes we did get lost in Cleveland but evil rob didn't know where in blue hell he was going either.  But hey we still got there and it was all good, except of course that season pass line.  I cant believe i left my season pass at home.  I really wanted a refund for that, so i guess i could sell it to someone if anyone wants it, my e-mail is posted all over the place.  So anyway we were supposed to meet some people at the Top Thrill Dragster at noon but I finally found a way to flawlessly meet people at amusement parks.  We made a deal before the trip that if we met up it would be all good but if we didn't then just screw it.  The dragster wasn't exactly what I expected but I wont explain why for fear of sounding like a part of the general public.  Lets just say,  "hands down head back and enjoy your ride.  hands down. hand. hands down. ha. han. h.hands down. hands down. hands down" vroooom    The Bumper cars were after TTD and just before twisted wicker.  Right now i just have to say a word about Cedar Point and Geauga Lake so bear with me.  I can't believe how easy those people at Cedar Point have it.  I didn't hear a ride op say a spiel all day.  THey had auto ones on the coasters and they didn't even have to say it on the other rides.  There were something like 3 people sitting in the line of Raptor just controlling the crowd on a ride that didn't need it as opposed to me on the plunge, where i have to send boats, give talks, move boats up, and control the crowd.  I was somewhat surprised that Jes left Cedar Point to come back to the Lake but I was EXTREMELY surprised to learn what position he had gotten at the Lake.  Keep in mind that last year Jes was a first year employee at the Lake.  This year he goes to Cedar Point for 20 days and comes back to the Lake as a Supervisor of a whole Zone of rides.  For all of you who dont know(99.9% of all people) becoming a Supervisor is a 3rd or 4th year posision at the park and usually you become an assistant team leader and a team leader first.  Jes just jumped over all this stuff and got a Supervisor spot, which is INSANE.  Now I'm sorry to all of you who want the last 2 minutes of your life back but thats just doesn't seem right to promote someone that high who has no experience with anything.  Wow I wonder where that rant came from...  Well I guess it's because I might be getting a new atl and tl in the next few weeks AgaiN. Also 2 people from my crew who I really liked left and someone else might get promoted and sent to another ride.  I'm losing my mind with this school thing and just want to be at the park. Wow what a stressful week.  Hopefully next week will be better.  And the trip report goes on!!  After we played DDR Robby was acting really weird and claimed he was stanly.  It was hilarious to see Robby really spaced out and everything.  The DDR machines were moved in the back of the arcade so no more cheering sections for your truely.  Too bad too because I was really tearing it up.  Wow Robby really loves that camera.  It is a cool one but he must have taken almost as many pictures of signs as the rides!!!  I do love the picture I took of robby in front of the Millennium Force sign holding the legal Pepsis though.  Ah an instant classic.  I think the wait in line for the Millennium Force was actually more interesting than the ride but I believe we wont go there.  I did call up simmons in the line though lol.  Apparantly he called up his good chum buddy marchella for no reason and talked for 3 hours about nothing.  Maybe we should bring simmons on here to post his defensive statement.  I'll give you a little spoiler for that post that will probably never happen.  "I was bored so I had no other choice"~probable response from simmons.  If you ask me thats infreakingcredibly stupid.  Oh Robby by the way you might want to consider making that link a link.  I guess I could just do it for you if you turn the comments feature on for me. urlLink cedar point pictures   The quote was above and i'm not wasting any more space on it.  I guess its kind of an inside joke.  Sorry about that I know i hate being out of the loop.  You know what I mean Simmons??  As of right now the word is officially out, people you have to come visit me at Geauga Lake now.  I will be working almost every day this summer at 3 main rides.  They are (drum roll please) the Thunderhawk[old Serial Thriller], the Pepsi Plunge[log flume], and the Merry Oldies[drive them yourself cars].  I'll be expecting a lot of visiters!! 
       
    
    
</post>



<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, today was the day...the day I figured the stalker would begin to stalk me again. One would figure that the stalker situation would get worse b/c of the fact that the stalker hasn't seen my in about 5 weeks. So at about 10:00 AM, I realized that the stalker wasn't there! YAY!   It turns out that this kid from Orange High School admits he's gay, too me! My life truly is full of freaks! So I was very afraid...so I backed away sloooowly. This kid confronted me and Mark several times. One time while we were talking to   THE   Dave Hoover. It was just scary. I wanted to get the kid away, just by saying that he'll place. But believe me, this freak isn't that easy to fend off. It turns out he placed like 3rd in humor or something! I always thought he was a shady kid. We shall call him  Orange freak .  More to come in about the stalker and  Orange freak .  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ignatius has beat Ed's! Now, tomorrow, there will be a full report about my situation when the stalker confronts me.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yes! It seems to be up and running. Bwuhahahaha!  Now to go see Ignatius take on St. Eds!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Rob was correct at everything he said, except for the idiot thing. So, as it's been said, today was the R. River tournament. So of course I always think the same thing whenever I go to a district tournament: don't make eye contact w/ Miss Toothless America if she is there. So Mark, Fuj, and me are the first people there, almost. So we're sitting there for a while, then Hoover, Kocsan, Schultis, and Nayak show up. It's all good, we all start talking.  All is good, Fuj comes w/ our ballets so we can start filling out info. I fill out the first ballet, then I look up...there's Toothless, AT THE TABLE RIGHT NEXT TO OURS! It seems like a 'coincidence' that every single tournament she ends up right around me. I'm terrified, and try not to make contact w/ eyes. So I fill out the ballets, and reveal what has occured. Of course Mark laughed.  Throughout the day, there were many run-ins w/ the stalker. One time, I went to look at where I would be for my next round, and she is right next to me! That really ticks me off! Then she follows me to the award ceremony, w/out me even knowing until Mark tells me.  On a side note, Mark and I did horrible...we'll just leave it at that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I know this isn't my site, but since the domain name and webspace are both registered to me, I figure I have the right to post here. Anyway, so today I'm at the R. River speach/debate tournament and I'm talking to Fuj when I see these two idiots walking down the hall. When I got a closer look I realized its Chris and Mark, so they start telling me about how Toothless is there.  So me and Mark go over by where she's sitting and she seems pretty normal to me... until she turns around and smiles. Yeah, it must suck to be stalked by someone like that, I'm glad I'm not. Luckily I got out of there not too long afterward. I'm sure Chris will have some comment to post sometime tonight. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, the scariest thing ever happened to me today. So it's the first day of concert band, and Ewing is beig an idiot trying to make all the freshman think he's this tough guy and all. So after band, I realize that I have a speech tournament the same day that he wants to fit people for tux's. So I go up to him after class to explain that I won't be able to go that day b/c of speech. So as I tell him, he does the scariest thing to me. I start explaining, so he takes the one side of my coat and starts pulling it. Then he takes the other and does the same, adjusting my coat. I lost my train of thought, ran, and left in horror. It was scary. More to come in later on the situation.  I think it's safe to assume that Mr. Michals is one shady character. Maybe he is a freak. I don't know. But last week, we were finishing weight lifting. So I'm just standing around when he suddenly tells me to do 2 dips! So I'm really nervous, I ask him what a dip is, he tells me, so on w/ life...NOT! I go up for 1, and I here all this cracking in my ribs. Thanks to Mr. Michals, I have been suffering a torn muscle in my ribs for a week now!  More updates as they come in. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday was truly a day to remember. First: stalker updates. The toothless stalker was there. Actually, nothing shady happened though w/ her. Now Orange Freak was there too. Some shady things happened w/ him. So Mark and I are talking to this girl about her speech, which is pretty good I might add, and all of a sudden, Orange freak comes up to us! Mark is now terrified, b/c he tries to adjust Marks tie. Now you just know that things have gotten out of hand.  Just a little bit about the tournament itself. It was long, k, long. All of the Duo and Prose people had the first round off. So it was kind of nice. Mark and I decided that we were going to need more energy than ever to pull off a trip to the state championship. After two of our best rounds, that we felt were, our truly best round came. It was the third round. So theres this kid sitting next to me, a freak I might add. He has this notebook w/ him, in which apparently he has criticism about each speech. It looked something like this: 	  The Stinky Cheese Man and Fairly Other Stupid Tales : As usual. 	Our speech [meaning theirs] 	 Infidelities : Pointless 	 For Whom the Southern Bell Tolls : [I cant remember what it said for this one.] 	 No-Fault Driving School : Annoying 	 The Valiant :  [Didnt have anything written down.]  Ya know? I think thats just bad, considering how bad his speech is. Every speech on there is great except for his and The Stinky Cheese Man and And then to go and call ours annoying. Thats just low. We worked so hard this year to get that skit to work and be good. Well, anyways, now that I got that out of the way, our final rankings, all out of 6, are 5, 4, 4, 3, 3, and 2. So we got better as the day moved on. Unfortunately, we did not qualify for states. We have one more chance, on February 15, to qualify. But I doubt its going to happen.   OK, so we left early b/c almost everyone on the whole team had something to do w/ the play. So me, Mark, and another kid went w/ Matt K. Im going to start by saying that that was one of the funniest and scariest rides in my life. I will never forget it. So we leave, and were following Will and Dave, Dave leading. So we go to this sub place in Parma for about 15 minutes. We then leave again. So were following them, and Matt decides to pass them up b/c they are going slow. So we get to a light, I think on Ridge Road. Matt says, Where are Dave and Will? We explain that they turned a while ago. So he screams this word that can be heard throughout the car! So he decides to turn around at this McDonalds. He blocks the entrance to turn around, cars are beeping at him and everything is going bad. So we get on the freeway, going about 80 MPH, and this cop car passes us right up. So randomly, I say, As long as the Stinky Cheese Man people arent district champs, Ill be happy. So Matt is mad b/c I distracted him and we missed the exit. We got off the freeway finally and got back to school.   What a day. I stayed to watch closing night of the play and went home. I will never forget that car ride. I know I forgot to say a couple of things, but they probably werent important. Well, until the next update, so long.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's been a long time since I've updated the site, so there is alot to talk about. I'll start w/ the movies. The week after Little's, there was no speech. So myself and two other peopel decide to go and see The Recruit. OK movie, I'd give it a B. So we're in the second last row, and there are these old people behind us. They had a comment for possibly every single line in that movie. There is one I remember, and I couldn't help but laughing. So the guy in the movie was doing you know what w/ the lady. So that old lady behind us randomly says, "Oh, God's not going to like that!" Just felt like mentioning that.  On another note, the Big District Tournament had to be the worst experience in speech that I ever had. Mark and I, we go in there pumped, we're convinced that we're going to walk out and come back the next day to qualify for states. I knew I was getting my hopes up. AND IT"S ALL B/C OF CLEVELAND JUDGING! I HATE IT! This is the second time we were at Crestwood and got screwed over. Fuji told us that we were ONE ranking away from going to the next round. If memory serves me correct, that's the same thing that happened to us last time. We were in our final round, and the judge was laughing so hard. He must have been dying, k? One would say that he really liked it. He even came up to us after the round and asked us for our intro. And what does he do? He gives us a freaking 3 out of 5! That cost us 6th place in the tournament. And that is when the Chris and Mark screw-over period began. And it's all b/c of those stupid judges! The screw-over period lasted until Little's, where we got our first 2 since Crestwood. Then what happens at Big's? I'll tell ya what happens at Big's: 3,3,3,3,3,4. That four cost us our trip. How dare that judge.  So b/c of it, I wasted 2 hours of my life while other people were competing b/c they never get screwed over. Well, this is what I have to say. Next year, the judges will see a different side of us. B/c we have decided that we will both do a single's event and a duo event. So Prose people will be in for a surprise.   That's all I have to say, except for the fact that I HATE CLEVELAND JUDGING! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       No speech, With no speech, there are no stalkers to talk about. They might as well be called *idle* right now.   So anyways, I need new things to rant about. How about Biology? Ya know, I can't take this anymore! We had the world's hardest test on Photosynthesis last Tuesday, then we get pounded w/ another test. Luckily, that test was pretty easy. I got a 69/100 on that photosyn. test. Why does this keep happening to me?? Ahhhh!!  BREAKING NEWS IS IN! *Beeps like Mr. Evans* Beep beep beep! What would one do if I said the words "Debate Central" in that order? Why, Evil Rob might yell, "Chris the fraud!" Or Mike Stanley might decide to boycott. Chris (me) might scream out THE MULLET MAN! And Dana and Juliann would see it and say that it's "heading straight for okey dokey land." Here is the breaking news! Debate Central is making yet another return! I do not have the link yet, but once I get it, I will post it! AND IT COULD BE AS SOON AS SATURDAY! For those of you who have never heard of Debate Central, it is where people argue about pointless things, like how people think I'm a fraud (but they know I'm not, I've convinced them!). To take a look at the original Debate Central, click this link: http://members.lycos.co.uk/ worthlessforum/debate/ . Great times. Unfortunately, Debate Central was destroyed, so there is no link for that. But #3 is bound to be a huge hit. Well I'm out for now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I guess the Toothless stalker isn't "idle" after all. I'll get to that later.  Ya know, first photosynthesis, then cellular respiration. I don't know what's up. I studied for the respiration test, yet I still managed to get the same score on that as I did on photosynthesis: 69/100. Tomorrow, mitosis is all mine...  Why do people protest the scholarship drive at Ignatius? Sure we all hate it. But Mr. Popelka makes a great deal w/ our homeroom. He says if we're the top-selling homeroom w/ each of us selling at least 30 books, then we get the challenge boards back. But ya got people who hate the challenge boards *cough* evil rob *cough* mark *cough*. So they go and sell 25. Insane.  Saint Patrick's Day Parade-- March 17, 2003, Cleveland, Ohio. So after we're done marching in the parade, I am told by a certain speech partner of mine that he sees someone. So I've got lots of people on my mind right now. When I hear the words "Toothless Stalker" come out of his mouth, I am totally scared. How is it that every single time I go somewhere, the toothless stalker ends up there. I don't think it's coincidence.  Note! Debate Central is back w/ a new name! www.debatezone.tk .  I'm out for now. Peace. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, after flunking the last two Biology tests, I was finally able to succeed like I used to. Now this is an average Mr. Popelka test for me, but I got a C, and it made me happy knowing that I won't be totally screwed over in that class. Ah, good stuff.   No stalker updates.  As you may or may not have noticed on www.debatezone.tk , the war between the Evil Rob Resistance Alliance (I'm in that), and the Group Against Fraudulent Behavior, there have been some drastic turns. I thought I was launching a fatal blow to the GAFB last night, when I released my own little debate forum, Debate Core. It was modelled after the growing Debate Zone. Well, it ended up hurting me, as I was forced to destroy my site, b/c it was a "copyright infringment." I really don't know. ERRA will prevail. Register: www.debatezone.tk .   On a speech note, Mark and I will be doing Duo for some of next year. So it's good. I'm also thinking about doing Prose as my side.   I'm out now. Bigger updates to come in the future. Peace. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Biology Update   Well, once again. I am conquering y Biology tests, as I got my first B- since the final. I love Punnett Squares. They get me good grades.  On another note related to Biology, my name became one of two guest appearances on the recent test on DNA replication. Apparently, Mr. Popelka feels Mark and I are now qualified to be famous DNA scientists. It's all good.   Stalker Update   Oh boy, something happened on Saturday. It was not pretty on my part, as I was shooken by the event.  So, the bottom of my school shoe comes off on Saturday. That's bad, k? So I tell my mom that we need to go to the store b/c my shoe broke. She informed me that my sister needed shoes for 1st communion, and there is a buy one get one half off sale at Payless. This is supposed to be good. I find a nice little pair there, but there were no dress shoes my sister's size. This means that we have to go all the way to Sears at the Mentor mall. That SHOULDN'T be a bad thing.  We're in Sears. There is one pair of shoes that will fit my sister. But apparently she doesn't like them. How fun! Now we get to walk around a mall that is crowded! Yay! So there is a payless in Great Lakes. We go in it, find nothing. Now I'm pissed off and want to leave because I don't feel like walking anymore. We pretty much walk in circles for a while trying to find a shoe store. So my mom says screw it, we're going to get those shoes in Sears.   Now for the event (s): We're walking back to Sears, and there is a girl in front of us. She looked familiar, too familiar. She turns and begins to walk in a store. That's when I realize it's the Toothless Wonder! So now I'm panicked as we are walking back into Sears. We find the shoes and are in line. I look over and guess what? The toothless Stalker is walking around the store, then making eye contact w/ me! Luckily, I was able to get out of there, lucky to be alive. Scary stuff.   Speech Notes   Mark and I have "nominated" several speeches to be ours for next year. We've got some good ones lined up! Stay tuned!  The New  Quote of the Update   One random quote per update is what I decided to do! Here is your random quote for this update: "K? Apparently Simmons and Ligas here were scoring crack in the mall on Friday after school. I walked out of my room and they're here on the third floor hopping around like little bunnies, K?" ~From the hilariously insane mind of Joe Popelka   Other Stuff    Tell all your friends! Register yourself! Post! We need people! Debate Zone is dead! We need new people to ressurect it! www.debatezone.tk P.S. I believe we banned Em, so don't worry.  Well, that's all I have for today. Peace out.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Biology Update   Now, this makes me sound stupid, as usual, but I am once again happy w/ my latest biology test grade, a C+. This came off the DNA replication test. Now I gotta study for my next test on Tuesday, which is on transcription and all that crap. But it's like Joe says: You might not care about it, but you would drop E  dead if it stopped working.    Stalker Update   Ya know, is the stalker really a stalker? I mean I run into her on rare occasions. Maybe it's only the speech season...   Speech Update   If you go to Iggy, and you're one of those off the campus at 2:50 people, you are a loser, k? a loser. On that happy note, I would reccomend you join the speech team if you have nothing better to do. If ya wanna join, there's a meeting in Fuj's room on tuesday. (NOTE: SPEECH IS NOT ORAL INTERP.) That brings me to my next point. On Tuesday, I'll go up to Fuj's room. Basically, I'll find out what he thinks we should do next year. More to come on that.   Today's Quote   "K? Stand while the bombs drope." ~Mr. Popelka  The new  Bus Criticism   The website is going off theme from freaks and stalkers in my life. Time to bring some of that theme back w/ a new section. In this section, during every update, I will rant and rave about stupid and freaky bus drivers. Once I run out of bus drivers, I will talk about the freaky people on the bus. So here we go.  The Driving Instructor : This bus driver is literally a driving instructor. Basically, they guy says, or teaches, faulty information to this kid on the bus about certain things. The one that sticks out most in my mind is the time he said, "You can arrange words in Latin in any order, everything will make sense." So basically, this freak is saying you can do this (english): as and by a invaded life stalkers. He said that if you do that in Latin, it will mean the same as wording it any other way, if you get my drift. Another time, the guy strongly informed the kid that you musn't talk to anyone that is not in your age group. Kinda funny you say? I say it's a bunch of BS. Until next time, scramble those words!  Well, I best depart now. Peace out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Biology Update   Probably one of my last biology updates ever... So anyways, we recently dissected a fetal pig. Is it just me, or does the smell stick to the lining in your nose? Sure seems like it. On another note, the final is next week. That will be hard, k? hard.   Stalker Update   More to come on that later in this post...   Today's Quote    Credit must be given where credit is due. With that said, the eighth graders' production, Grease, was excellent. Unfortunately, the question that will haunt me in my sleep is; whatever happened to that budget they kept telling us about? Then again, maybe Ditch Day costed as much as Grease did to put on. Yea, and maybe Mrs Lynch was a better teacher than Mrs Garuckas. In reality, The Lynches are the Clintons of Euclid, and although St Williams did receive a jolt of "Grease lightnin", scam is the word.  ~Eric   The Driving Instructor's Faulty Information of the Day   If someone is chasing a bus, then you don't stop until an intersection w/ lots of traffic to let that person on.   Bus Criticism   There are two shady people that I want to mention in today's bus criticism. Yet, they aren't bus drivers, b/c what is about to be read is what many people think about and wonder about. First off: Laughing Sal. Laughing Sal was given her nickname as a result of the constant laughter she takes part in. This lady talks to this other lady (who will be mentioned in a bit) and after everything she says, she just laughs. And it's not this norman laugh, it's an obnoxious laugh, even more obnoxious than the original Laughing Sal from Euclid Beach. Anyways, she apparently doesn't ride the same bus anymore, as she is just randomly spotted downtown, laughing away.  The other lady to be mentioned is the one that talks to Laughing Sal, well, doesn't really have a nickame b/c a clever one hasn't been thought of yet. For now we'll call her the Late Bus Lady. I indirectly quote Evil Rob when I say this: No matter how late the bus is, even two minutes, she calls up the RTA and complains. Or, for that matter, how early the bus is (long story). Recently, the bus has been one or two minutes late, and she hasn't been on. Is she protesting the bus's lateness? To be continued...   Other Stuff   The day was picked to go to the Lake County Captains game : May 23rd. This apparently is the same day that the Ignatius faculty decides to come. And who better to spot doing the 7th inning stretch than Mr. Johnson? But, I'm not going to complain about any teachers. No, no. I'm going to vent about something else, something....stalker-like....  So we're walking around, and all of a sudden, the stalker's one week speech partner is spotted! Just goes along w/ my theory: the toothless stalker doesn't want anyone to know that she's stalking me, even though it's blatantly obvious, so she sends out her hitmen. Also spotted w/ the stalker's friend is another member of the VASJ speech team! An outrage! Unfortunately for everyone but me, there was no confrontation.  That's all for now. Later.    
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Bio, and all School for that matter   It's finally over! It's finally over! As my profile says 8 times...to finish off the year...SCREW POPELKA!   Stalker Update   Nope, luckily she has gone AWOL.   Today's Quote    Mr. Kyle's typewriter doesn't have an F on it. That's why this test says "uck you".  ~Dan Corrigan   The Driving Instructor's Faulty Information of the Day   Today was quite a bus ride in which THREE, yes three, items of faulty informatioin were released. Here we go: 1. If you are drunk and driving on the RTA, you MUST stop in the middle of Veteran's Bridge to show everyone where the concert was. 2. If you are wearing a yellow coat on the bus, you must get off. 3. Never talk on an RTA bus, or there will be severe consequences.  Also, for some odd reason, maybe b/c he was drunk, he was talking to himself in his rear view mirror.   Zima   This, obviously, is a new section, dealing w/ none other than Zima. Zima, don't be mad. I am only stating facts here. K?  At the Captains game, we're walking to Tops, where Evil Rob's parents are going to pick us up. So we're walking and Zima says to Rob, "uhh, you're giving me a ride home, right??" Afetr Rob tells him no due to the length of a trip that would be, Zima runs into the dark! Never to be seen for a week!   That's all for now. Expect a much more detailed update soon.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       What you are about to read is my version of a trip report from when I went to Cedar Point on Friday, June 13, w/ Robby, Zima, and Mark. Lots of freaks and getting screwed over in this one. Without further ado, my trip report.   Cedar Point   We arrive at the park approximately 4:45. We went late b/c we could get in for cheaper. Good stuff; only had to pay $12.50 after 5:00. Once we get in, we decide first that were going to kick off the day on the Blue Streak. This was my first Blue Streak ride, and I was quite pleased w/ it. After that, we decided to go to the Disaster Transport. It had a long line, so we wasted 5 minutes deciding whether or not we should go on it. We decided to, since it was air conditioned inside. After waiting for 45 minutes, we rode. One of the best Disaster Transport rides I ever had. I could tell they did some work on it since the last time I was there (2001).  After that, we went over to the Wicked Twister, and that is where Mark and I split w/ Zima and Robby. I dont think I would ride that anyways. Me and Mark decided it was time to head over to the Iron Dragon. As we were in line, all these people start walking out of it, saying that it broke down. So we then decided to go over to the Wildcat, one of the most intense roller coasters at Cedar Point. We got in line, and we happened to b behind two hicks from Tennessee. Every time the line moved, they gave each other piggy-back rides. They were all over each other. If you are familiar w/ wrestling, they were exactly like Jamie Noble and Nidia. They were probably around our age. So we went on the ride, stuck behind the two hicks. Nevertheless, it was a great ride.  Iron Dragon was back in operation after that, so we went back over. The line was shorter, which was good. As we were in the station, next to get on, the train comes. Ya know how they have those gates that close automatically behind the yellow lines? Well, as Mark was waiting for the people to get off, he waited behind the open gate. Finally, he passed and went on. As I made my way to the car, the gate closed on me and the train left! I tried to get the guy to open the gate, but he wouldnt. By the time I was done explaining why I was furious, the new train came, and I got on. Let me comment on riding a roller coaster by yourself: it is not as fun. So were going up the first hill, and the train stops for a half second. That made my REALLY furious, b/c I thought I was going to be stuck. After the train got back, I met back up w/ Mark, as we headed for the choo choo train. We got on and hit the other side of the park.   We rode the Cedar Creek Mine Ride, easily the worst roller coaster in the park. We got off and looked around for a while for a Junior Gemini shirt just for Popelka. After looking for a while, we went to the Dodgems, but decided not to ride b/c of the longevity of the line. We went to the arcade next, b/c we were supposed to meet Zima and Evil Rob there at 7:30 for DDR. We were early, so we decided to go to the racing horses. It was funny. Mark said that he named his horse Pablo. So I said mine was Paco, just to keep the Spanish tradition running. This Chinese lady got on the horse next to Mark. Mark proceeded to tell her that she had to name her horse. She said that she would name hers Smokey. Mark told her his horses name was and what mine was. She then said, OK, mine is Taco. The lady next to me named hers Gray Bear, b/c it has gray hair just like me. My horse won the race, luckily.  Now this was the most funny part of my trip to CP. It was also my favorite. Mark decided to get some ice cream. So we go to the ice cream stand to get some. When we were walking back to the arcade, about for boys started running after us. They were about 10 or 11 years old. They ran up to me and they were like, Are you that kid from that movie?!?! So Mark said, You bet he is! The one kid then asked, Can I be in a picture w/ you? So I took a picture w/ them! So they question, Are you ??? (I dont remember what name they said. So Im like yep. The one kid said Can I shake your hand? I shook the kids hand. Mark the said, Make sure you see Star Wars Episode III, hes in it! Theyre like awesome! I then told them I had to run, and they were sad to see me go. I feel good and bad after that. Good b/c someone thought I was famous, and their whole world turned upside up. Bad b/c their world will crash down when they find Im not the person they thought I was. Watch, they probably thought I was Franky Muniz.   We finally reached the arcade, and I played a game of DDR w/ Robby, and 2 w/ Zima. Let me comment on the arcade version of DDR. First of all, CP has the best DDR machine around. But its not the actual game I want to talk about. Its the pads themselves. I never knew that at the corners of each arrow, there are little metal plates which bolt the arrows down. I always thought that they were sealed under the arrows. So of course, Im used to that not being there, so I was stepping on those instead of the actual arrows, which made me look pretty bad. I guess thats going to take a little time to get used to, providing I play the arcade version more.  We all decided to leave the arcade and head to some more coasters. While we were walking, we were approaching the Corkscrew and the Power Tower. Robby said that we should ride the Corkscrew. So of course I objected (dont ask why). Then Zima objects, by saying we were closer to the Power Tower. It was then I said that we should ride the Corkscrew. Before I knew it, we were heading up the hill. Id have to say that my first ever ride on the Corkscrew was probably one of the best rides of the night.   We headed straight for the Gemini after that. Gemini was another ride which I hadnt ridden. The ride on the Gemini was, IMO, the best ride of the night. After that, we went to the Mean Streak. As we were approaching, all these people came out and said it broke down. That is why Mark and I didnt want to go on it. We went to the CCMR again, while Evil Rob and Zima rode the Mean Streak. We then met up w/ them at the exit of the ride, and headed toward the MF. We probably stood outside the line for about 10 minutes arguing whether or not Mark and I should go on it, as we finally gave in and got in line.We were in line for about 45 minutes when it started raining. It wasn't raining too hard, so we figured that it would remain open for us. We finally got to about the station when it started pouring. The ride ops told us that we might be able to get on if we wait. LKike 30 minutes later, while everyone is still in the rain, they tell us we HAVE to get out of the line and leave. This made everyone mad, including myself. I spent a good hour and forty-five minutes in that line.   Other than the MF incident, I was very pleased w/ my trip, and another one is being concocted.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Today's Quote   Listen here you pencil-neck geeks. ~In memory of Classy Freddie Blassie   Zima and the Gang   The Parking Garage-May 30, 2003. So its me, Evil Rob, Joe B., and Zima, of course, and we decided that we should go to the Indians game. We took a Laketran bus down, and were going to take it back. The game started after a very long rain delay. The delay was probably about 30-45 minutes in length. The game ended, w/ the Indians winning 7-3. Great game. So we decided that if we wanted to beat the crowd to the bus, we should leave, instead of watching the fireworks. The street we were going to use to get to the bus was closed off, so we decided to cut through the parking garage. Were in there, trying to figure out where to go, when all of a sudden, a huge explosion can be heard throughout the parking garage. One of my acquaintances (I cant remember which) screamed Terrorist attack! Fortunately, it wasnt a terrorist attack. I later learned that they shoot the fireworks off the top of that parking garage. So anyways, after walking around in circles for about 20 minutes, we get out of the parking garage and head home.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Thursday, August 14, 2003, will be a day that lives in the minds of many for the rest of our lives, or not. Many people have amazing stories about how they went through the rest of the day. Others have pretty bad stories, and some have no story. What ever the case may be, I have a story of my own. So I give youBlack Thursday.   Black Thursday   So, at approximately 4:00, I make a call to Evil Rob. We talk for a while, and then all of a sudden, I hear only static. Im thinking its just the crappy phone Im on. I realize, after trying to unplug it, I cant turn the phone off. So I let it just sit there and die. I go into the computer, and the computer is off. Now, as far as I remembered, I fixed the virus shut down thing. So Im wondering what is going on. The phone didnt work in there either. So I go into the kitchen, and none of the clocks are on. Now I think that I blew a fuse of some sort. I call Evil Rob back on the non-cordless phone, and he tells me that the power is out at his house too. Pretty strange. So we hang up and both catch the next bus.  I catch the bus, soon to see Robby boarding the bus. He tells me that Zima was complaining on the phone about how there was no power on in his apartment. So I figured that Euclid wasnt the only city w/o power. On the bus, there was this lady. She seemed very excited about the events that were occurring. She was like, I cant wait to go home in the dark!" She talks for a while until she finds someone else to bother.   OK, so the 39BX gets on the freeway at a different entrance than the 39X. The driver starts to get on the freeway when people start yelling at her b/c she is getting on at the wrong time. So she turns the bus around, almost hitting several cars in the process. When we finally get on the freeway, there are 2 busses next to us. There was this huge traffic jam coming from nowhere. So were sitting there, and Im watching these guys. The one just takes out a book and starts to read it. The other starts talking to himself. Now, Ive only seen one other bus river in my life talking to himself *cough*Driving Instructor*cough*.   We finally get to the East 9th exit ramp. That was probably the longest time Ive ever been on an exit ramp. It had to be like 10 minutes before we actually got onto East 9th. Of course, there is a huge jam at the first light. So the bus has been sitting there for about 6 minutes when Evil Rob and I decide to just walk from where we were to the other bus stop to catch the 22.   Were walking past city hall now. There is absolutely no traffic whatsoever on that street. City Hall was also abandoned. Its like Evil Rob said, Wheres Jane Campbell when we need her? From there, we crossed the street. We are in this flowery area behind the federal building when we pass up the one, the only, hot dog vendor at Saint Ignatius, Dimitri! I, say hi to Dimitri. The next street we come across is jam-packed w/ cars that are going NOWHERE. So we start walking in between all of the cars. Then, from out of nowhere, that crazy lady from the bus approaches us and thinks its funny we got off the bus early too.  We finally get to the bus stop and wait for the 22. We waited about 20 seconds. It came, and it was already packed. People were already standing. So we get on the bus along w/ about 10 other people. The bus driver was REALLY mad the whole ride. She was yelling at everyone standing to move backBUT THERE WAS NO WHERE TO GO! She was yelling and yelling and no one was doing anything. We got to the intersection of West 25th and Lorain when we decided to get off the bus b/c it was so crowded. We watched other people trying to get on the bus, and other people disrespecting the driver w/ certain gestures b/c they couldnt get on. It was quite an event to witness.  Evil Rob and I finally got to Ignatius after walking down the street jaywalking at random times. Actually, it really can't be considered jaywalking, but whatever. Anyhow, we arrived at the Xavier Center. There were three shady kids standing around outside the Xavier Center. We finally entered when Evil Rob randomly says, Hey! The powers out! Thank you captain obvious was the thought going through my mind. When we turn the corner, we are greeted by Trevor Clark, who agrees the power has gone AWOL.   When we enter the main room, we sit down w/ Suzy, Trevor and Becky who are conversing about pictures from band camp. How they were able to see the pictures in the dark I do not know. From out of nowhere, Dave Srsen arrives and we start talking about how stupid it was that we hadnt received our schedules for school yet. Dave, Evil Rob (ER), Trevor, and I then get up to go to the back room. I started to talk to Dave about how the virus seemed to be the cause of the massive blackout. Meanwhile, Trevor and ER go outside. I guess that there was a rumor of some sort that JP had showed up. But when the truth came in, it wasnt JP, it was Mr. Popelka! I never ended up talking to him anyway.  Eventually we all ended up outside, because it was too hot in the Xavier Center w/o air conditioning. ER went to sit w/ a bunch of people while I went w/ someone to the main building.   Anyways, when we got back to the Xavier Center, Beckys mom informed us that she got a call from Julie saying that practice was cancelled. So now everyone thinks they can leave, so when ER goes to ask Mr. Ewing, he tells us we cant leave until 7! Thats another half-hour! Finally, at 6:45,  he let us go. So ER and I went to the bus stop and waited there for the bus for a while. ER went to call Zima and when he got back, these three shady kids walked by. These arent your normal kids either. The girl had a combination of a pink Mohawk and a blue mullet. It was the weirdest hair-do I had seen.  Finally, at like 7:15, the 79 showed up and we got on. When we got downtown, the place was totally abandoned. I hadnt seen it like that since the September 11th attacks, and that made me wonder if this blackout was the work of terrorism. When we got to the bus stop a 39X pulled up. When we looked at the schedule, there wasnt supposed to be one until 8:25 PM. Then, to our chagrin, it turned into a 4! Well thats just great! We had to wait even longer! I couldnt call anyone from the payphone across the street from us b/c it was busted. Stupid payphone.   Like 15 minutes later, so guy comes up to us and asks us if we have a cell phone and if he can use it. We didnt have a cell phone, and if I did, I dont know if Id let him use it. He looked suspicious. THEN, this guy who looked and sounded like Frodo from Lord of the Rings comes up to us and asks us if we have change for a dollar. Neither of us did. THEN AGAIN, he comes up to us. He then asks us if we can watch his bags. Who asks a stranger if they can watch their bags? Obviously, only Frodo. A 38 showed up and then turned into a 39BX. So it was almost our bus, but its destination was the Park and Ride. I wanted a Shoregate bus to show up! Finally, at 8:25 PM, it did, and I headed home. On the way home, since I was so bored, I started writing ideas for this update, which is why its so detailed, but it's all good.  Well anyways, Black Thursday was an interesting day.  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, Im back again w/ another update. Lets just say, Ill be changing a few things in this update. Also, I have a little ranting to do.   www.chrissimmons.tk   Yes, many of us know of the website www.chrissimmons.tk (you should if youre reading this). Also, many of you know the theme of this website has been My Life Has Been Invaded by Freaks and Stalkers! Well, there is going to be a name change, or a theme change, so to speak.  As you may know, the original purpose of this site was to rant and rave about the toothless stalker. Also, I used this site to complain about the freaks who have invaded my life. But then, the website went a little off topic, and still is running off topic. Not too far into the life of www.chrissimmons.tk, I started talking about random and stupid things, like my biology grade, or things the Driving Instructor had taught. You just read about Black Thursday, which, in almost no way, had to do w/ freaks and the toothless stalker. Therefore, after all this, I give you the new theme and name for www.chrissimmons.tk: The Totally Random and Stupid Stories Pertaining to the Life of Chris Simmons.  On to more important things   The Blaster Virus   So, on Monday night, Im checking my email, and I get one w/ an attachment called Cancer (dont delete) by anonymous. I open it and read it. Ten minutes later, Im on a website, and this message comes on my computer telling me I have 60 seconds to stop w/e Im doing, b/c the computer is going to shut down. Sure enough, it does shut down. This happens two more times, and I have had enough of it. I call Evil Rob, and he tells me its probably the attachment I opened. After I explain to him that the person who sent me that email doesnt send me bad emails w/ bad attachments, we knew it was coming from somewhere else  So Im watching WKYC and they have a news story explaining that there is a virus going around the internet, and that its going to use all the computers it has affected and launch an attack on a Microsoft website. Later, at Evil Robs house, I receive information on how to destroy it. Well, lets just say, out of the half hour I spent on it, the only thing I got to stop was the computer shutting down every 10 minutes. Thats all I even want to talk about that. The only thing I didnt say is that its almost impossible to use the internet.   Quote of the Day   (W/ much bass) "GOOOOOOOOOOOD" ~The Szwede  Out for now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, it's been a long time since I've posted. There hasn't really been anything worth posting lately.   The purpose of my website   There's been some confusion over why I actually waste my time typing all this stuff on this website. Here's why I type this stuff out: I type it so that I don't have to tell the story by mouth over and over again. Instead, I put it on this site, so I don't have to repeat myself so many times. I guess I'm just lazy if you look at it that way. Anyways, it's story time.   VASJ vs. Euclid   Alot of people know I really dislike VASJ. There are many reasons for that, but I don't feel like explaining why right now. But the Euclid vs. VASJ game was on Friday night, and I wanted to go to see VASJ lose. After all, Euclid had a good team, so I figured I'd watch them run over VASJ.  I called Zima and asked him if we wanted to go, and he agreed. Anyways, I'm not gonna talk much about the game itself. But what I HAVE to complain about is that Euclid lost! They were supposed to be this great team who defeated the past two teams they played easily. Then they go and lose to a school like VASJ. The final was 28-23. They played alright in the second half, b/c VASJ didn't score, but the fisrt half was bad. The game went into half time w/ VASJ winning 28-3.   Onto Euclid's band. If Fuj saw that performance, he would probably charge the field demanding everyone to get off. There was a percussion break after the first song. What did the band do during that break? They ran around the field like idiots (literally). People were hitting each other w/ their instruments, people were slamming into the goal post, it was mass chaos. Other bad things were that they were off step constantly and you couldn't tell what was supposed to be executed during certain times b/c everyone was off.   I'm done complaining now, I just felt like I had to say some of that stuff.    Quote time   (Referring to the Toothless Stalker) "Hey, Chris, you should bring her to homecoming. Afterall, you'd only have to pay for one meal." ~Fuj  Gotta go. Sorry about the short post. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Remember the old name of www.chrissimmons.tk? Yeah   The Event No One Saw Coming   So Tuesday and Wednesday after school there were speech meetings. We only had to come for one. I decided to go to both. So I headed up to the room. Apparently, Fuj has nick-named me Freck since everyone was calling me Freck. After leaving the meeting, Ligase, Mitch, and I headed to the library and administration floor of the main building. We were talking and were greeted by Dan Neelon. We started talking about Furious Ds nudge toward the board during a quiz to give us an answer to a true/false question. While we were talking, my attention is directed toward the door. There were two girls and a guy walking into the building. I was thinking in my head wouldnt it be funny if it were the stalker? So I take another look and it is the toothless stalker! Wearing a white t-shirt and a tie! I do a Furious D nudge toward her to Mark and he bursts out laughing as they walk into the main building.  Mitch and Dan then ditch us, so we decide were going to stalk the stalker. We started our journey in the admin. hallway, and head up the side steps. We poked our heads through each door to see if we can hear her voice. When we poke our heads through the second floor door, we hear Mr. Brennans voice! We gotta tell Mr. Brennan about this! We listen through every other hallway, no sound. We then get to the 5th floor. We walk through it to the speech room, but no ones in there. We then walk past the debate room, and there she is, sitting in there, talking w/ Mr. Buzzelli. Apparently the guy they were w/ was Mr. Cain (sp??), a graduate of Ignatius, who works as the debate coach at VASJ. Anyways  We head to the second floor to wait for Mr Brennan to come out of his meeting.. We decided to wait a while, but then decided to leave b/c we were waiting too long. We headed to Loyola Hall, and Mark went into the bathroom to change. While he was doing that, I decided to head to the Atrium, b/c I promised Kevin Healey Id meet him there. I couldnt find him, so I see the Swede himself so I run over to his table screaming the stalker is here! So now the whole atrium is looking at me, while Im telling all these people about my story. Jimmy, Paul, and Justin all wanted to see her, but I said theyd have to go to the 5th floor for that.  When Mark finally came out of the bathroom, we went to the Theology office looking for Mr. Brennan, and hes thereWITH MR. POPELKA! So I yell, Brennan, weve been looking all over for you! As I am saying this, Popelka hit his head in disappointment. Brennan is eating his food w/ curiosity at this point. I then say, Youre never gonna believe what just happened, the stalkers here! Then, Mr. Brennan dropped the food he was eating and spit out I tiny bit in shock. Hes like Is she the one w/ the white t-shirt and the tie? When I responded yes, he then said that he thought so. So THEN, Mr. Popelka butts into the conversation saying, K? I got payed to deal w/ you guys last year. Youre on my time now. Now I am sad b/c Popelka only liked me b/c he was paid to.   We saw the toothless stalker leave eventually. When we saw Fuj and told him, hes like, Shes doing debate now. I guess shes found someone else to stalk, Rob.   So there ya have it. I guess the stalker era is over.    How She Came About    For those of you who dont know how the stalker came about stalking me in the first place, heres what happened. It was at the VASJ tournament last year. Basically, to make a long story short, she confronted Fuj after the tournament, saying this to Fuj: Do you have this boy on your team named Chris? Do you have his phone number or email address? Once Fuj told me, thats when the stalker era began.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Once I find something to post, good. But anyways, NEW LAYOUT!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It has been a REALLY long time since I've updated. I've got lots of things to rant and rave about. Things like speech, the stalker, and all that stuff.    Speech   So we're now far into the speech season, and today was the Mentor tournament. Mark and I had some confidence going into this tournament, w/ a two tournament winning streak, in terms of placing.   So we get through the first round, thinking hey, we're doing just fine. Riiiiight. So we get down stairs and the first person I see is ZIMA! Now even though I knew he was coming I was still caught by surprise. So he is going to come to the second round to observe us....   The Second Round   Our second round looked to be a promising round. We seemed to have a high amount of confidence, and we can beat all the teams in this room. So when we get up there, we are as pumped as anyone can be...until I make "the biggest screw up in duo in the history of the NFL." I start to say my line, but then I stop in the middle b/c I can't remember what I was supposed to say! How can this be happening?? So there is literally 10 seconds of silence before it is broken. Mark makes the most bizarre noise, I laugh, then realize we're not practicing, so I say "oh!" We laughed for the rest of the speech (5 mins). And BTW, as soon as I forgot my line, as realized how hungry I was b/c I lost every single ounce of energy in me. If you ever want to see a re-enactment of the event or hear one just ask me and/or Mark to do it when around. Good times.  So we didn't place, thanks to that round.  We did crappy, but we could have had a chance if it weren't for my stupidity. Like I said, good times.   Quote time   "The dream rally of every Ignatius student...a sumo wrestling match...Mr. Davignon vs Fr. Vincent." ~Mr. Hodermarsky  That's all for now. I'm out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        The Toothless Stalker   Many a-things have happened with the stalker since the announcement that she has joined debate. Now, of course, many of us thought the Fuj was joking when he said the the stalker is stalking Robby now...  We'll let "KaPing" explain that himself.    Guest Posters   I came up with an idea a few months ago that there should be guests on the site to tell problems that they are having (problems that have no relevance to anything.). This is why I am now announcing my first guest...Evil Rob KaPing himself. When he posts, he'll probably talk about the stalker and how she is still the stalker.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, its been a very long time since the last time I updatedDecember. Usually when I update, I end up just talking about Speech and the stalker. The stalker is pretty much non-existent now, and speech is over. What can I talk about now? There are plenty things I want to talk about, like the Browns, Zima, Concert Band, candy ropes, etc etc..   The Browns   The Browns had a horrible season last year. They were five and eleven!! It cant get very much worse than that. Many things contributed to this: the fact that the offensive line was plagued by injuries, Kelly Holcomb breaking his leg, Tim Couch having to replace Kelly Holcomb, William Green busted for DUIs, it doesnt get any worse. When Couch started against the Steelers in what I believe was Week 4, I expected him to do horrendously. The fact is, he killed them! This was his best game: 33-13. I thought to myself, Tim Couch might be finally turning into an NFL quarterback. Wrong. That was just about his only good game last season. Another problem w/ Tim Couch is that he cant read defenses. So this off season, Butch Davis has decided to DITCH Tim Couch. The Browns have a new QB! His name: Jeff Garcia! Three time Pro-bowler! I believe this can turn the team around. Hes got good receivers to work w/ (as long as Quincy Morgan can hold on to the ball!), and a good backfield (Green and/or Suggs), the only thing that needs working on is the offensive line. If the season started today, Jeff Garcia would be laying in a grave right now, b/c he would have no protection. Weve got the defense already going for us. BTW, I dont think that signing Ebeezer Ekuban (spelling) was the greatest choice. He averages like 1 sack in every 4 games. We should stay w/ Courtney Brown (while hes not getting hurt), and Mark Word. Back on the offensive side of the ball, the signing of FB Terrell Smith was awesome! First of all, hes actually a FB! Hes not a TE! Hes a FB who can block! Not a TE who can block! The Browns have a real FB now! Hopefully the Browns keep heading in the right direction getting towards the draft. BTW, in the draft, we need to draft, IMO, a cornerback, a few guards, a young QB, and a safety. I think we need those most right now. Im pumped about this next season. And if the Browns dont get close to making the playoffs this year, then Butch Davis is gone (thank God!).   Concert Band   What has happened to Iggys band? I remember the old days when all you had to do was show up to get an A+. Concert band has changed. Whats the newest part? Practice charts. Now, apparently, Ewing doesnt think I (or anyone else) can play a Swearingen piece anymore without taking it home to practice. I dont know. I think its pretty easy, but thats just me. Another thing I want to vent about is these playing tests he is making us do for him now. This is another thing he is using to stop people from getting an A+. Luckily, I am hanging on w/ an A+, but barely. I go in there to play my little scales and circle of 4ths, and I dont mess up. Thats an automatic A+ then, right? Well apparently not, b/c I was out of tune. He took 6% off my grade for that thing b/c I was getting sharper going up my scales and flatter going down them. Ahhhhhhhh!   Adam Higgins   Hello, Adam. Or should I say, Newman?   Sour Punch Straws   Yes Adam, you are the one who has inspired me to create the last few sections in this post. Everyone else may think that this story is random. Oh well. So one day, coming out of that hell hole (the Xavier Center), higgman86 hands me these Sour Punch Straws candies. I dropped them, not knowing it, and I couldnt find them. The next day, they were lying on the sidewalk. The day after they were in a different location. It has to have been 6 weeks now, and they are still laying there! Ahh! They just wont die!   Zima   Ah Zima, Ive been meaning to address you for a while now. Has anyone that is reading this (probably 2 people total) ever been to www.nickzima.tk ?  I must say, that website is a complete copy of mine, also modeled similarly. Zima brings up many random and pointless things, like arguing w/ someone how many days are in a week (the answer to that would be 7, BTW). It used to be that Zima would blatantly lie about me and everyone else. Luckily, it has evolved from that. Sooner or later, it turned into the old gang. The old gang is a group of us from grade school that always hung out. But what Zima fails to realize is that the old gang is dead. So Zima, Im gonna say this to youdont take it as an offense or anything, but its time to move on, the gang died 2 years agoits over. Oh, and also, Zima, the XYZ Affair, contrary to popular belief, is also dead.  Well, after getting most of that stuff off of my chest, its time to move on with the regular sections of the site.   Speech   Its over for a while. No update.   Stalker Update   None.   Quote of the Update   Morgan Freeman?  Shes  hot! ~Anonymous person at the lunch table.  Ha! Higgins! I have this up before 7:00! You now cannot call me Former-Traitor Cinnamon!    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so the social life of myself was lifted from the ground yet again when Zima invited me to Geauga Lake, w/ a complimentary ticket.   Geauga Lake   So Zima picked me up around noon. One of my biggest concerns, now that I was in his car, was, how does this kid drive w/o a responsible adult driver in the car. On the way there, his top speed on the freeway was 70 mph. Not bad, but a little too fast.   So we got to Geauga Lake at about 12:45 and planned on leaving around 5:00. The first thing we decided on doing, after struggling w/ line placement before entering the park, was to ride the Villain. Before we got to the Villain, Zima showed me the new DDR machine, which we decided we would play later. Then, we decided that we would ride the Pepsi Plunger before the Villain. We did so, then headed to the Villain. So we get to the Villain, and, as usual, don't have to wait in line. I'd have to say that that was one of my better Villain rides.   Next, we headed to the Double Loop, which, I would have to say, is one of the crappiest rides I have ever ridden. First of all, the hill shouldn't even be considered a hill..it's more like going straight. Second of all, because of the crappy "hill", there is barely enough speed to get through the loops. It just gets more disappointing everytime I ride it. So when we get off the ride, Zima talks to this ride op he knows. The kid was stupid like Dommy, and looked Dommy, both of which Zima had previously warned me.   All of a sudden, it started pooring hard. We figured that would be a good time to pay the DDR machine a visit. When we got there, there was this kid on the machine...absolutely horrible. He thought he was sweet though. Playing beginner mode, missing arrows anyways. Plus, ya know what I hate? When people are taking steps, then, right after, put their feet back in the middle. That drives me crazy. Then me and Zima played. I did alright for my first time back w/ DDR in like 4 months. I played standard mode. After we were done, that one kid got back on, and did worse than the first time. Then two more skater kids came on, quit after missing an arrow, then it was our turn again. I did considerabely worse the second time, failing the last song..time to pull out the pads at home.  After DDR, we went to get some H2O. We went to a bench, and decided to call Robby. After that, we went to the Geauga Lake employees' club house, a place I never knew existed. I got a lemon chill for only $1.25. Quite a deal if you ask me. After that, it was time to ride a Geauga Lake classic, the Big Dipper. After riding the Big Dipper, Zima wanted Cheese on a Stick. After he bought it, he noted that it was irregularly shaped. To me, it looked like a big white ball of puke. I will never try one of those. He ended up throwing half of it away, b/c it wasn't even melted. Next, we rode the X-Flight, a ride that I had never rode previously. Long wait though. I'd say it was a quality ride though. It lacked the feeling of flying though.  Anyways, after that, we went to the Ferris Wheel, which was a surprisingly short ride w/ only 3 rotations. The last thing we were going to do was ride Zima's ride, the Thunderhawk, formerly known as the Serial Thriller. Before we went on, we talked to this guy Zima knows for like 10 minutes. After riding another crappy ride that I wouldn't recommend, we ended up talking to Zima's friend for another 20 minutes. Actually, I just watched, b/c I had no idea what they were talking about. After that, we were heading home.  Yeah, what happened after the trip was pretty funny. We went to the drive through at McDonalds and had a cap dispute w/ our milkshakes. After that, Zima's not paying attention and nearlky runs a red light! Funny, yet I thought I was going to die. Zima, don't drink milkshakes before/while driving!!!!  Anyways, I'm out for now. Later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wSaturday, March 13...yet another huge gap in between my posts. This site is dying...However, the long hiatus in between updates hasn't really been my fault. Around the time of the last update, a virus hit my computer. All it did was launch adds. There were 10 or 12 popping up at once. Eventually, it killed my modem, and I couldn't get on the internet. Now I'm back, w/ a DSL modem, so it's all good. Anyways, nothing has really been happening to me lately...it's been a boring life. Last Friday was pretty silly though.   The Dollar Show   So last Friday, Zima calls me and asks me if I want to go to the dollar show. I accepted. He called Robby, who couldn't go b/c he was leaving for Nationals the next day for Debate. So thanks to him, DOMMY ends up tagging along. So Zima picks us up in his crappy used car, and we go to see the  Secret Window . It was an OK movie. After that, we went to the arcade, where Zima played DDR. I didn't play b/c I didn't bring enough money and it's been before I sprained my ankle that I've played. Anyways, after that, we head to Giant Eagle, where Dommy buys a SINGLE banana. I never knew that you can buy a single banana. I thought that you had to buy the whole bunch. Eventually, the night ended w/ Zima and Dommy throwing around AOHell CD's in the parking lot. Not a smart thing to do IMO. So there's a totally random and stupid story pertaining to my life.  Yeah, there's not really anything else to talk about. Gotta get a job this summer...I've narrowed it down to probably Blockbuster or Giant Eagle. Anyways...the quote of the update..   Quote of the Update    "If you ever see me at Jacob's Field chuckling during the 7th inning stretch, its because 40,000 people are commemorating a 400 lb fat man pulling his pants out of his crack."  ~Mr. Dan Corrigan    Other Stuff   1. Go Browns. 2. Go Indians (possible playoff contenders if they keep this up) 3. I will talk to Rob soon about getting started my Guest Posting system..where a friend of mine can, for one post, have his/her own account and ramble about whatever they want. Hopefully w/in a week. Paul D. is the first person that will guest post.  Well, after a dull post, I'm out...I'll ahve a much better post next time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, as most of you probably know, I'm a huge sports fanatic. There have been some things going down in Cleveland that aren't cool. I'll vent on this site...post any comments you might have.   Carlos Boozer and the Cavs   Now even though the situation was a little different...remember what Jim Thome did? He went for the money. The Phillies offered more than the Indians. Thome was saying how much he loved Cleveland and he was very involved in the community, yet, he went for the money. Now I was kinda mad about that, as I wasn't following the Indians b/c they SUCKED. Joe Popelka put it best..."K, he's not dumb, he went for the money. If some Jesuit school in PA offered me millions of bucks to teach there, I'd say screw you k? I'm going for the money."   Now, back to Boozer and the Cavs, I don't know. I just don't know. Let me put it this way...anyone who believed Carlos Boozer when he said he wouldn't wanna play anywhere but here is a moron. And to tell you the truth I'm guilty of this too. Paxson and Gund are dumb in not knowing that this could have happened. Now, Booz was like Thome. I love this place I'll never go anywhere. Blah blah blah blah blah. Utah comes along an offers 68 million dollars as opposed to the Cavs' 42 or whatever it was. Tell me something...what are you going to do w/ an extra 20+ million? NOTHING! You will never use it in your life. Ever. He's just another greedy athlete. I expected more from the man. Now, too, he played for Coach K at Duke. You saw what he did. He turned down the money to stay where his heart was. That's a real man. Couldn't Booz do the same? I guess not. I don't know...maybe when he comes to the Gund he's not gonna get BOOOZER from the fans. He's gonna get BOOOOOO___. Anywyas, post your comments.   The Cleveland Indians   Wow. I can almost say they're impressive as a team. Their offense is impressive. Hey Paul D, I remember you were the first person to yell at me when I predicted that the Indians would finish .500 this season. You also were the first to yell at me when I said Ronnie Belliard was going to have an all-star season. The first to yell at me when I said Travis Hafner was gonna have a good season. I proved you wrong buckaroo. You said Matt Lawton was the only guy on the team who had a chance to be an all-star. Victor Martinez, Ronnie Belliard, Matt Lawton, CC Sabathia, and Jake Westbrook are all all-stars.   While I stay w/ my prediction that the Indians will finish .500 this season, my prediction will fall a little short I think. There are 2 things that are holding the team back. Casy Blake's fielding (haha it's bad but it's not holding us back.) OK one thing. If it weren't for this part of the team, we would be in first place now. Yes, the part of the team that gave up nine freakin earned runs tonight against the A's...the bullpen. A disaster since day 1 of the season. We have a few OK guys in there right now...Matt Miller, Bob Wickman if he stays healthy, Kaz Tadano sometimes (even though as of now he's a starter), Rafael Bentancourt, who's hurt, and David Riske, who's gotten his game back. I'm not sure about Rick White right now...he's been a bit edgy as of late. And thank God they got rid of Jose "give 'em up" Jimenez. He's a huge reason we are not at .500 now. It's just something on the Indians w/ closers who's names are Jose. Anyways, I'm done typing and boring everyone out of their minds!   Quote of the Update   "...OIC,  O nly  I n  C leveland."  Remember to comment! Peace.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>