<Blog>






<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ....... waited so long for you to come in my life,  to save me , to see me, to simply understand me. what i would give to see you. To feel the warmth of your kindness. only for the  words that stumble  from my mouth to be feeble attempts to rob your attention. suspended in time, hoping that for just  one nite the world would stop to catch us alone, where there are no boundries, no prying eyes to tell thier tales. To find us wrapped in the seduction of the passion that has yet to be experienced, awaiting for us to endulge into each others pleasures. alas, the world only stops for one person,   screaching to a halt so fast that the clouds are all a blurr,blocking the sun that once showered desire,  to leave a hope that once was, to wait, and wither into emptyness once more.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Revealed In Time   Normally Not to Many things bother me. Because i chose to not let things bother me. But today, has my mind reeling. Normally, i jsut sit and ponder my thoughts about the things that transpire in me life. But anymore even my own instints seem to be out of whack. Reality and Illusion has seemed to have drawn a fine line in my life. Seems everyone in my life has some sort of lie, some sort of thing they feel they need to hide from me. i just dont understand why that is. am i just paranoid? or is everyone really out to get me , lol. Oh well, gonna try to not dig to deep in it. As they say , Everything is Revealed in Time. And the most important thing has been revealed to me today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New Look   Okay this is the new look lol Exciting huh .
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New Begginings   Find My self back on this journal today. at least i know things here will be private. So Much disappointment and selfishness around me lately. Seems everyone around me is so full of shit anymore , just makes me sick. i dont get it. and its not for me to get, or i would get it.  Ever sit back and think about things you have done in the past, feeling regret. i often have. but thinkin about it today, i only realize there are things that i regret that i didnt do. i held back when i should had went for it. i ran when i should had stayed and fought. guess its easier to run . but does running make sense? if you run, you cry , if you stay and fight, and loose , you cry. and if you win, and find out a few years later, there is no such thing as a happy ending , and you cry. so, is it better to not have known happiness?? or is it better to have had it for a short time ?? Is it better to sit here and day dream of what if?? or is it better to sit here and morn the did have's???? Just seems to me, if you stay in the middle, and dont think about the what if's , and never experience the did have's , will life be Grand???  i think its worth finding out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Muaaaaaaaaw&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         BANG BANG BANG On The Door Baby  Ever feel like you are just banging your Head Against a wall? lately seems that is all i do. Wondering will the ride ever end. and would i want to get off once it stopped? i mean honestly. has the self destructive patterns grown to be a way of life. is the only way to feel anything, to feel pain? and how pathetic do you have to be to feel pain to feel alive? i know non of that came out right. But its sad that, not only myself, but i am finding out a lot other, only experience pain and hurt. what makes us so different that we are not allowed to feel love. or be loved. or even to be treated nice by someone who claims to love you. and isnt it funny how the simplest things in life are often soo hard to come by. And wouldnt it be nice that when you loved someone, they loved you back ................
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugggggggggggggggggggg how the hell you use this blogger bot anyhow?????   http://members.aol.com/thebiggirlsstore/me.jpg
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you do , when you love someone and they dont love you How do you move on. how do you live your life when all that fills your head is him, and how he spends his time with her and not you. how she makes him happy, and not you. how do you carry on and  forget when all you want to do is see him. touch him. or even hold him in your arms? how do you  get over the need. over the want? how do you stop caring?  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guess i have pretty much at this point in my life,  gotten over the idea that i am gonna meet the man of my dreams and fall head over heals in love, and him fall for me. The whole nice home with a white picket fence 2 kids, dog, cat, fish senerio is pretty much a fairy tale. LoL , guess to some point it was in the first place. what do i have to offer someone but a vulgur mouth and some thing a step above masterbation. i know, here we go with the pity party right. well kiss my ass, lol.  guess i just didnt realize at the time that what i wish'd for would never exsist for me.  i see others have it. why cant i?????    i have always wanted to do something great with my life, as i am sure everyone else had the same expectations. to aspire to be someone.  Today, i would settle for simple being something to just someone. having someone to share my heart with. mostly someone to talk to. someone who isnt so self centered that they can not hear me speak even when i do.  But what on earth would i even say if i did. its been so long since someone has every been truely interested in what i had to say or what i thought. not even sure know how to really  express myself anymore. i just speak....  and stupid words come out of my mouth.   the funny part is that i actually wish with all my heart, that there was someone there for me. someone to hold me when i cry, or at least hand me a tissue.  Soon i will be passing through my 39th year of life. and as i sit here, and try to seek what contribution i have made to society.  what dent have i made. who would be sad if i left today. lol. but as i sit here, i do realize, nobody would... oh dont get me wrong , i am sure there would be perhaps 10 - 15 people at the furneral. but after they left, i am sure i would never be thought of again.  perhaps whom ever was left to take care of all my shit, more than likely my dearest mommy would. irony at its best i guess. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>