<Blog>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       M33ting the Chromed Sunlight    >  The above line says it all. I am online. And it is a joy. It’s really been awhile since I have been able to get online during the day, been awhile since I have gotten a day off. Just to refresh, I was given this day off from my part in the ITE Army logistics exhibition a few weeks back.  I know I don’t have to remind most of you, but it is so wonderful to be able to get up as and when I please, to take my time to have breakfast, read the newspapers (still have to touch the Hardcopy from time to time), game for a few rounds, then surf and blog.  I took the off today, a weekday, mainly because this weekend will be a busy one and I will not be spending it at home. I have range that would take place over Sat, Sun and Monday if needed be. It will involve having to stay in in camp (which I usually do not) and thus I will not get to enjoy the weekend. It is quite an important event for it will be my last range before I ORD. Therefore it is important to give a good showing so that they will trust me to be able to shoot if I ever need to do so during the course of the rest of my physical life. I don’t think they have much to worry about. I do believe that I may take up sports shooting as a hobby in the future. On the shooting range is one of the few place that I find that I can slow down these thoughts of mine and actually focus totally on the subject at hand, namely to bring down the target. I am able to do this not because I enjoy it or get a high from firing a gun, but because I fully understand the seriousness of the matter. Guns are deadly. A person with one can kill another person in a single motion. Therefore the moral and motive behind pulling the trigger is important. For us, the Army guys, the motive is to protect and defend our country, family, friends and lastly ourselves. Serious stuff and I’m glad that I can focus totally in this and if the time ever comes to pick it up and do so, I want my skills to able to match my desire to defend.  Will not be able to blog this weekend therefore, so keep the keyboards clean and the Datalines burning. I will touch nodes and check in on all of you when I can.   Peace out.   >    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       > Feeling EMO today. Normally that would not be surprising but the fact that I think it is more than my usual shows how abnormal it is. Hope that made sense.  I have an idea of what could be increasing the feeling, but I refuse to allow my mind to dwell on it. Because if it did, it may actually believe it to be true and that would only drive my whole being into a whirring pit of despair. And that would not be nice. For me or the people around me.  Heh. If my dear Agony Aunt   MichWng   were to hear about this, she scold me for being “antsy” again and lovingly bite my head off. Hope she’s not reading this. If you are Mich, I’m sorry, don’t hit me! :)    I’m feeling much better now than in the afternoon. Had a somewhat bad day at work again so I think that’s adding to the depression. Many thanks to   Dex   for ICQ chatting with me. It really made me feel much better.  I have been trying to write out a new technical article to put up here but I seem to keep pushing it back and back again. All I seem to be doing is random postings that reflect the not so calm that my life is in right now. Frankly I don’t think a lot of people would like to read it. Anyway the article I’m planning to right is some tips and hints for new Palm OS PDA users. I mean there are so many articles and reviews about which Palm to buy but after to do get it, than what? How do you make sense of all the programs out there and what programs would make the most of your device? That’s some of the questions that I hope to address. If you would like to read it, let me know. Some aspiration would be really good to get me off my a$$ to finish it.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Report   > Excuses, Excuses. Well, I have none. All I can say that is good to blog again.  First things First: Seems like a lot of people flying to the UK tonight.  Special regards goes out to   Rusalki  , have a good trip and hope to meet up with you when you get back. Don’t worry about   DK  , I’ll keep an eye on him for you *grins* Keep in touch ok? Still need to learn some multimedia and design tips from you….hmmm ever though of making it a career?   To Dear little   Tess  , had a fun time catching up with you on your blog. I still remember the “old days” at  Awake  and will always remember you as that girl from that discussion program where Li-Wen was the host. Come to think of it, I think Rusalki and DK where on that show as well. Oh well. Anyway, all the best and will see you soon. Keep that blog going yah?  Next: To   LadyRaine  , Congrads once again on being honored by your peers for your achievements. Make no mistake, I am really happy for you and that you have found a group that you like and accept you. Sorry if I have not made this clear as of late. Hope to hear from you soon. Oh…one last thing, be patient. I foresee a surprise this weekend.  To   AmberLight  , Hey you! I made another reference to you again on my blog. You better show up here more often and leave a comment or something! Heh.  And Lastly to the missing people: To   Abby  , Have not heard from you in a long while. Wondering if my mails got through. Would really like to know how you are doing over here. Remember what I said, keep in touch.  To the   Ebb Tide  , I just happened to read our ICQ history and it reminded me of all the fun times we had just chatting openly and honesty. Wishing that at the very least I could hear from you more often. I miss you old friend.  >    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Report   >  It been a busy weekend. Had guard duty, and the memorial services going on to honor the victims of 911 had also caught my attention. Also on the Gamer’s Edge, new demos of three games that I had my eye on were released and I felt it my duty (and pleasure) to spend a few nights to test them out. Sorry to have neglected the blog in the meantime.   Guard duty was pretty ok. The guards under me were experienced and so they knew their roles and what was expected of them. The guard commander was experienced as well. I have worked with him twice before, so everything was able to run quite smoothly. As a result, I had time to walk around the camp alone and in a leisurely manner. That’s not to say that I have never walked around the camp before, I have done normal guard duties once if I may remind you. Anyway, the camp I was doing duty for as basically one big carpark and thus there as a good view of the sky without any obstructions.    One of my favorite past times when I’m jacked out of the Net, is to watch the sunset and the moonrise. It doesn’t really matter if I can’t actually see the sun (hard to do so here with our constant city skyline), it’s the clouds that really matter. The way the sky slowly burns then darkens as the clouds past by in their range of patterns and how the stars slowly appear out of the darkness. I simply love it.  To me it is both a joy and a sight to humble me by. Everytime I am able to witness the sunset, it reminds me of how much bigger the world, the universe is compared to us. Mankind always talks of our great our science is, of how much we have accomplished, of how much destructive force we have at our fingertips, of how simply powerful we are. But to make the sun set, the sky burn, the clouds move, the moon to shine, the earth to move and our galaxy to orbit, that is real power. A power that is so beyond us, a power to create such wonders, that have made a creation so  perfect  that to me, is proof that is beyond any doubt that there is a Creator out there.  He speaks to me during those times that I just sit there watching the sky. I like to believe that he especially enjoys speaking to me in these times although He is able to do so at anytime. Perhaps it only at these times that I am really actually listening. Perhaps its only at these times that I can actually hear His answers.  He reminds me of who I really am. Not some lost soul that wanders the empty and haunted corridors of Cyberspace, but a living, breathing, thinking, feeling being. It is in times like these that I actually stop referring to myself as the three separate entities of Net-Icon, Emotion Core and Meat. In those times I am a single created person. In those times I am truly alive.  To all those who find themselves constantly seeking Him. Stop. Raise your eyes upwards. The sky you see, the breeze you feel, the sounds of life you hear, even the very water you drink. He is there. He is everywhere. He is simply waiting, for you to stop and listen. To allow Him to answer the questions you have asked. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        To Whom it may concern: We are Watching  You can hide We will find You You can Run We will catch You We will seek you through the 1's and 0's Your tools will turn against you Your networks betray you Isolation will only protect you for a little while And so as you sit in the cold dark, waiting alone... Remember this,  We are Watching 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Memory Defrag   >..... > Throught most of the day, I was reviewing what my youth leader Calvin and I had spoken about during the Worship team meeting of my youth group at church yesterday. I'm not very good when it comes to impulsive speeches like what I did yesterday, i always seem to come up with better stuff after I have finished.   Basically the "concerns" rasied where something that I think has been hanging overhead for some time. Now I will be the first to admit that I have lost touch with the going-ons in church. The army would be my excuse but we all know that its a lousy one. In any case, I have distilled the problems that are currently facing my area of the worship team, the Audio/Sound Support Team (Or A/S-ST as I like to call it, but thats just my geek self talking again).  1)Commitment - Frankly my team knows the roles and responsibilities that we are called for and we enjoy doing them.But I think there is a problem with commitment. Music practices are important. Not just for the music team but for the sound team as well. However as of late, only a few (err..like two?) members are showing up regularly. I know alot of members have loads of other commitments outside (see above said mentioned = army)but we have a commitment to serving God and the team as well. I think I will go back to setting up a roster where there will be at least two members present at each practice and every member attends at least one very month. Some will have to do more but thats to make up for the lack of manpower. Still have to remain flexible yet still be fair to everyone.  2)Training - I think there is an uneven balance of technical level within the group. This is partly due to the newcomers not having actual training sessions conducted for them. Also links back to the reason above. Will have to look into this and plan a good time to conduct training. And if possible, make it a regular event.  3)Manpower - very important. The basic role of the A/S-ST requires a certain level of manpower, thus I can't help but feel that we are currently lacking. Right now we have only a handful of active members. A few on backup roles and a couple "on job training". All in all, only less than a handful. My constant prayer is that more people will raise up to take up the seemingly "least glamourous" of all the worship ministries.  4)Unity - Not talking about Unity as in within the team itself, but as within the worship ministry as a whole. I believe when it comes to setting up the sound board for each person. you need to know their style, their Personality. And the only way to do this is to spend time with the person. Right now we only meet on sundays and sometimes on Saturdays for practice. Both times it is difficult to actually know their character. Some thing I am praying for as well.   > On a lighter note. I just found out today that I acutally have more days of leave than I thought I did. I must have mis-counted somewhere. Trust me to think the negative of things. So anyway this is very good news has I get to have more full days to study before my first exams in Dec.  > so now I will have to start planning my leave so I can submit it by end of the month. Have to plan well to maximise the most of the time. Boy I can't wait!   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Weekend Scan   > It's strange. One would think that I was going to spend the whole weekend blogging away since this is the first week anniversary of my starting this blog. Then again like  urlLink Tess  wrote, sometimes its not good to be sitting in front of the computer all day long. Now I have been accused of living in Netspace too much of my waking life, but sometimes the Meat needs some actual social contact.  So I was out for lunch with the guys after church. The weather was wet and cold (I love this kind of weather, quite refreshing. I think both AmberLight and LadyRaine would agree with me on this one) so we spent some time walking in the rain and just catching up. We finally ended up at our  urlLink favorite LAN shop  where we had a few rounds of  urlLink DOD  action. I know that in the end I was still in front of a Comp Screen, but it's different when you're interacting with your friends and you are all in the same location. I guess thats the attraction of LAN shops even though  urlLink broadband  is so easily found nowadays. It's gets kinda loney playing online at home without hearing the cheers and groans of your gaming buddies around you.  I guess this explains that the only kind of computer game that really interests me nowadays are MMORPGs or Massive Multiplayer Online Role Playing Games. These games allow oneself to log on to a constantly on-going and ever-changing environment together with thousands of users all across the world. You get to interact with the other users (share, trade or just chat, depending on the game environment) which I find is much more interesting than just playing a set story with just the computer. Here, the story is ever-changing and even goes on without you when you're offline. But best of all is that you get to be a part of the story, that your actions have some effect no matter how small.  I started with  urlLink Anarchy Online  but stopped has it was getting stale, then was looking into  urlLink Earth & Beyond  (I like sci-fi stuff) but discovered that there are alot of locally based MMORPGs coming up, like  urlLink Shadowbane  for example.The benefit of local ones is that most of the other people playing are locals and better to relate and reach out to them. Another reason is that some events in the game are time based and with a local one I can finally have these events take place when I'm awake.  All in all it's a pretty good weekend. Can't wait for the next one...and the next one. The countdown continues.  Happy Surfing!  >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       The News and Media  Inspired by  urlLink her post on her blog , I have decided to share alittle on this topic. First of all, I'm a total news junky. Usually when I'm on the Web, I'll hit all the major news sites and then some of the more obsure ones as well. Of course I ten to stick to technology news, but I have a wide range of interest (and a quite large sense of curiosity) that I'll read about almost anything news related. I believe being aware of whats going on in the world to be important and it's a great way to start conversations and break the ice.    I have a good friend who is in the Media trade as well, been meaning to get her to start her own blog because she's a great writer (I do hope she is reading this, she knows who she is *winks*). One of the things that I shared with her when she started her studies in journalism is that to always remember that media needs to have   Soul  . What I meant by this, is that every journalist or documentry maker, has a responsibility to the public to give an accurate view of the subject or topic. Not just an accurate view but a complete view as well. I believe that the media should not be telling people what to think or believe, I believe that the media should give a complete story for the people to decide for themselves.  While I can comment the American media on accurately portraying the emotions and horror of the 9/11 incident, I feel that they failed to give proper due to the "other" sides of the story. They may have the soul but they are lacking in depth.  However, other the course of the year, I have seen the media starting to "mature" when it comes to this topic. They have spoken of the devistation of the bombing on the country of Afghanistan and it's people. They have written of the knee-jerk response and treatment of the non-extremist muslims. While it may be too little, too late, at the very least, history will show that the event did indeed shake the whole world as the incident has been labeled, and not just one country, no matter what that country may want to believe. In fact I think that they should take some solemn pride that they have shown that when an attack that is against all that is good and just is done on one of us, it is done to all of us as a Race. We still have that faint unity and with it, hope.  Sleep well  >   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       weekend scan   > Today I was at the bits and parts center (Sim Lim), just doing some window shopping and collecting of the latest price lists. Nothing interesting. And I don't think the prices have changed much since last month. But I decided that I should get the most updated prices so I can resubmit my proposal for the budget for my upgrade plan. Maybe I should wait for the prices to come down after the new Intel and AMD processors come out.  Started watching again my "Cowboy Bebop" DVD last nite. This anime has a funky sci-fi retro feel to it. Mostly helped by it's kick ass, almost totally Jazz, soundtrack. There's even a Carol King track in there I belive. All Jazz fans should check this series out. As for how it does as an Anime, it's pretty good. A little slow paced for an action anime, but thats because it needs to set the style that is the trademark of the series. The main characters are deep and realistic (except for one very noticeable exception) unlike another sci-fic/retro action anime "Trigun". "Cowboy Bebop" is Very highly recommened.   >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         I don't want you To give it all up And leave your own life Collecting dust And I don't want you To feel sorry for me You never gave us A chance to be And I don't need you To be by my side To tell me that Everything's all right I just wanted you to Tell me the truth You know I'd do that for you Why are you running away? Why are you running away? 'Cause I did enough To show you that I Was willing to give and sacrifice And I was the one Who was lifting you up When you thought Your life had had enough And when I get close You turn away There's nothing that I can do or say So now I need you to Tell me the truth You know I'd do that for you So why are you running away? Why are you running away? Is it me, is it you Nothing that I can do To make you Change your mind Is it me, is it you Nothing that I can do Is it a waste of time? Is it me, is it you Nothing that I can do To make you Change your mind So why are you running away? Why are you running away? What is it I've got to say So why are you running away? To make you admit you're afraid Why are you running away?      - Running Away by Hoobastank 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       scream 5heet   >     urlLink When Text Messaging Turns Ugly      "SMS bullying is like stalking....It is far more insidious than other forms of bullying" - (Taken from  urlLink www.wired.com )   fAL speaks: One of the largest leaps that technology has given us is the advancement of Communication. Communication is DE most important aspect of humanity (I dare say this because basically Prayer is a form of communication). Communication can build and save friendships, relationships and even lives. But when something so powerful is so freely available, it can be even more easily abused, especially in human hands. While I may seem to firmly support technology (a fact that I believe puts me at odds with some of my fellow Christians), those in the Know understand that I actually support Protecting and Educating about technology. There is a very big difference. I shall speak of this at another time/date.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Rep0rt   >  Today I was helping out in an ITE Students visit to my camp. I am one of the ushers for one of the groups. Basically my job is to ferry them from station to station all around my camp, make sure they reach and leave each station according to the allowed timing and answer any questions along the way. Sounds like fun, but they are hard to control. And with two sessions for today, morning and afternoon, I find myself drop dead tired. I believe even more so than if I were in my workshop doing normal work. Strange.  However it's good to be able to interact (barely, the timings are quite tight) with these up and coming youngers and have an insight into their minds. Mainly they found the whole deal to be boring and a waste of time. Can't really blame them. If I were in their shoes, young and innocent, everything so peaceful and plaicd, I'll find it boring too.  Something twirls in my Headware as I realise that I may not have fallen far from the tree that they find themselves currently on. I may no longer be young, or even innocent, but I feel that I sometimes have blinders on my optic systems. I dont think I have seen enough of the "real world" to be prepared later on, that this island in the Datastream that I call home is really that...an island, sheltered from the oceans of the world. What is going to happend when I finally, trully step up to the Edg3, am forced to open my eyes and look down?  Tomorrow is another two more sessions of ushering. Wish me all the best.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Status Rep0rt   > Well it's the end of the third day of life with a blog and it's still very new to me. Which explains why I keep mentioning it in like every other sentence. Unlike  urlLink her  I think just spending time on my blog and reading other people's blog (as well as to collect ideas) is a good way to ground myself. I've been getting tired of running the  , chasing down my news and other sites of any interest.   As those of you who have been   with me on this blog from day one would notice (yes you...you know who you are), I'm slowly adding stuff as I go along. I'm sure this is the case with any   in the early days but I thought that I should let those people who do read this blog (yes, thank you the two of you again, hands down now...thanks) to bare with me as I slowly add all these upgrades. Still deciding what kind of stuff I should add. That sidebar really looks empty at the moment. Hope to get it all settled down soon but I know thats unlikely. I just love to tweak things. Never really trully happy with some things and yet there are stuff that once I get it the way I like it, I never change it. I think it depends for situation to situation. For example, I never touch my handphone settings again after the first day when I get it the way I like it. And yet i never leave the software on my Rig or PDA alone.I'm always trying out new ones when the old one works fine. I guess it's the want to find something new.  > Netscape 7 looks good BTW, but I think I'll stick with IE6. Pity, I was expecting something more, can't stand Micr0s0ft  >  Or it could be that I'm just weird.....hmmm wired weird...cute  >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Gamer's Edg3   >  Hi All. Just a news update on the PC gaming scene. This one is much closer to home so I figured deserves the honor of being the subject of the the first post in the category.     urlLink Results of Singapore WCG 2002     Counter-strike 1st : GBR Grudg3 2nd : GBR Edg3  3rd : PwA  FCOT 1st : Sisterhood 2nd : GBR Sureal 3rd : Seraphim 4th : Zodiac  Day of Defeat 1st : |-SS-| Team One 2nd : --=GHOST=-- 3rd : Macs  Starcraft 1st : [aLt]duckie 2nd : 4B@Family  3rd : [aLt] NiRvana  Age of Empires 1st : Delin 2nd : Rising_One 3rd : Malcom  Congratulations to all winners.   > FaL speaks: Good to see gaming getting more recognised, since I am a gamer at heart. However sometimes I wonder at the ways and means. I enjoy gaming as I see it as a another form of media, of entertainment. Something like the mainstream standards such as movies and television. However I believe it to be a higher form that those two, due to the interaction and social expects that PC gaming can provide. But as I see younger and younger people move into (and succeed) in these high profile tournaments it looks like some of them are treating it as another way to prove dominance, to boast egos and even as a form of escape. I have nothing against competition (sports are great and can really bring out the best of oneself) but one should not do it to a point that one neglects family, work/school and friends.   >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Monday electric blues    > >  Well lets start this first week off with a review of the last few weeks. Workload has been kinda low. Most of it got pushed back to this month so I'm expecting it to pick up anytime soon.  Still feeling very drained. Not sure why. Could be the office politics going around of late. It totally changes the working environment. Especially when you're caught in the middle.  Then again, it could be my seemingly lack of time management. Plan to sleep early, but always end up having to do one thing or other.  While we are on that topic, it could also be due to my comp giving me loads of problems. Corrupted files and lost chains and links. All due to some beta level software I managed to score to help test out. Tried to anyway, it just ended up total messing up my harddrive. And I haven't made any backups recently. Had to do alot of "zombie" hours to fix things, but its hard to fix what you do not know is broken (hmm...did that come out right?). End up chasing alot of ghost in the machine  this leads to:   Windows 9x Tip/Tweak #1     [[Always make regular backups.At the very least copy your Windows/system directory onto floppy (or floppies) and keep them safe with your Windows Boot Disk. If you have a CD-RW, even better....grab a copy of Norton Ghost and make total complete backups of your harddisk.It my take up a CD per Gig, but if had a total failure on the disk....you will be thankful you used the time to make them. If you need more details or backup help, just drop me a line at my email below.]]     Me gotta get ready to feed the meat. Meeting Da Man for dinner. Need to pass him something.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       STATUS UPDATE   > Just thought I'll bring everyone up to speed on the going on's in my life since I realize that most of the people that will be reading this would not have a recent conversation with me lately.(pings-->all those that are linked to Dex's blog)  Soon I will come up with an actual User Profile page for all the n00b's to the blog, but for now this will have to do.  My Current Age cycle = 23 Standard Terran Years Now this status will be changing....well not too soon but it's not very far away either....will keep you posted.  Currently I'm still serving my National Service on my tiny little island (but it's home nevertheless). The official date is 20021213 but in another 9 1/2 weeks I will be clearing whatever leave I have left over.    >   W00T! yesss! Feel the joy!....  Also another event on the way is the commencement date of my Advance Diploma in Information Communications.  Good to be hitting the books again. Not everyone will agree but then again....pls   >  my current situation.  Other than these, nothing much to report...well nothing I would care to bore you with at the moment. Maybe some day, when I'm low on content, I'll post about my adventures overseas. (Starlight,Starbright...anyone?)  Here are some minor status regs: Food: Still like my western meat dishes but starting to cut down on alot of rich foods like seafood and dairy products (no more ben&jerry sob!) Music: still hooked on my rock,retro, acid jazz....need to find out more about emo....those in the know would wonder what took me so long to get in to it Hobbies: Still jacked into computers, hardware, software, internet and computer games.... of particular note is my love for Palm OS PDA's.  I will write my takes and reviews on the IT stuff and may even post up some IT tips and tricks I come across...of course I can't be everywhere in the Grid at the same time so please post up stuff that you come across. Once again a big   >  out to dex for getting my foot in to Blogging....this one for you bro...  Anyone needs some tech support, feel free to drop me a line. If I don't know it, I can most certainly find the answer...at the very least I will try.   >   oops! Timed out...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        >...   WOaH   That kinda speaks of everything that I'm feeling now as I sit inside my meat on my chair at home, while my  !C0N  is creating for the first time, my very first post on this my first humble blog.  Welcome to everyone with me on this an attempt to share my thoughts, views, hopes, dreams, fears, joys, failures and likes and dislikes on this journey that we call life towards the Edgeless Horizon. In case you haven't noticed, I seem to have written everything in some cyber, uber-l33t sci-fi kinda of style. It is not a theme of particular choice, but kinda something I like to use and sometimes even think in (readme:geek!).  Frankly I have made this as much for myself as it is for everyone else.  Therefore thank you on making my dive through the datalines less lonely....... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3   Ouch….  For those not in the  > I had my second (and last) wisdom tooth operated on today (as in Monday, I do realize that when I post this it would be Tues already.  It hurts. Kinda like a throbbing ache in the mouth, even when I’m jazzed up with painkillers. Glad that this will be the last time that I have to do this. At least I have the whole week to recover from it. Man that bites! (get it? Bites? Wisdom tooth?…oh nevermind. Lame)  In a way this is good timing, as starting from next week I’ll be beginning to clear my leave. I will have two weeks of half days in camp, but that’s ok. I still will have the afternoons to study. The other reason is that I have an assignment due just after Deepavali. Since I have done the research, I have the whole week to write it out. Yaay! Only problem, I’m afraid that I will be so jacked up on the painkillers that I would be rendered unproductive, like today for example. However seeing as I am able to blog past the midnight hour, this is a good sign. I’m a little afraid that I will not be able to finish the assignment on time, but back in my poly days I was juggling three to four subjects and each had their own assignments due barely a week from each other. I guess it’s the getting up to speed on studying after so long that is bothering me.   >        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      In light of the increasing tension over in Australia, I would like to sent out well wishes and prayers to my friends over there. I know that stuff like this are usually overhyped and blown out of proportion. But it is also in cases like this that we should remember our friends, family and loved ones overseas and not take for granted their safety, health and happiness. With our ever shrinking world, it is getting even more and more easiler to contact and stay in touch with one other. Let us make that step to keep the lines open. Peace and Out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3    smoke  program->> Major update here guys. It has been a very eventful week to date. And I'm trying to keep up with things.  Once again we a witness to the mindless horror of terrorist actions. And now it's even closer to home. I had placed my resources and  > to focus on the sniper that has been running wild in Washington D.C. Never expected the next incident to be just next door.  In the meantime lets not forget the so called "minor" incidents that are taking place else where in the region, like in the Philippines. And a reminder people, take a look at the peace around you. May we not take it for granted.  On a lighter note, the newest  Star Wars  novel in the current ongoing   New Jedi Order   series is out. Pity it is hardcover and thus out of my budget, for now. They have however re-released the paperback version of the last hardcover novel from this series that I missed so I got that instead to tide me till next month. For all those wondering, this series takes place 20 years after the end of   The Return of the Jedi  . There is an invasion of an alien race in to the known galaxy and the new and young jedi order raises up to meet them. That makes Luke Skywalker about 41 years old, and he is now a jedi master, an uncle, a husband and most recently, a father. To clear things up, the next Star Wars movie coming out, Episode 3, takes place 20 years before Return of the Jedi. In it we will see how Anakin Skywalker, Luke's father, will finally become Darth Vader.    Star Wars related: The latest sourcebook for the Star Wars pen and paper RPG is out. This one focuses on the Jedi themselves and is a good read. But like all sourcebooks, this one is quite ex.  Managed to get my copy of the MMORPG Earth and Beyond working. Seems like the problem was on Pacific Internet side. But to my surprise, they actually got in contact with the group of us who was having trouble and did their best to help us and got it working. That's what I call customer service. I like to see the other ISP give this level of support. Once again many thanks to Pacific Internet and I have no regrets of the choice I made 7 years ago.   To all those having exams. All the best. Will be keeping you guys in my prayers and when I too sit down to study. It is not been going so good my part-time course so far. It is hard to do two modules at the same while I still have my time taken up in camp. I do hope that I can mug and catch up during my leave, which is coming soon Thank God.  Cheers to eveyone, have a great weekend and my your connection never drop.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       > Quite excited.Been going through the textbooks for my course in Infomation Communication that is due to start in two days time. Man it rocks. The first two modules that I will be doing is basic then advanced Wireless and internet network applications. Just from browsing thru the books I see stuff like xTML, bluetooth programming, WAP content procedures and many other stuff... Basically its all the things that I like to read up on from time to time as an interest/hobby. There is a certain joy when you find yourself having to study something that you have lots of interest in and enjoy doing. I'm sure there are many people who have had this sensation while in Secondary school or Poly/JC. I'm very happy for you and I hope that you will be able to make a fullfiling career out of it. For I believe that getting paid for doing something that you love should be a major goal in anyone's life.   As for me, I don't think I have ever felt so excited about studying ever, and to me, this is the first time I'm feeling the sensation that I talked about above. I hope it last. Hope it doesn't fade away once I get into the bare bones of the subjects and start to find it dry. This especially happends during exam period. Anyway I'm praying for the best. I will keep the blog up to date with my progress as I embark once again in education.   "What was once old is made new again"   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       The 5cream 5heet   Was reading today’s   >  version of  The Straits Times Life!  after dinner and I came across an interesting article with the headline “  Goodbye, and I mean it  ”. It only appears in the   >  therefore I’m unable to provide a link (grrr..). It can be found on page L6, under the  Straight Talk  column by  Samuel Lee .  Basically it talks about how couples who have just recently broken up should have some time apart from each other even if it was done amicably and they want to remain friends. It then goes on to discuss about how it is difficult especially for the guys because we (guys) than to be territorial. We may start out with good intentions but ultimately we just can’t let go. We get all jealous and moody and over protective. In the end it just serves to drive the girl nuts and further away.  So I would like to open this topic up to discussion. Would recommend that you read the article first before jumping in.  To All the guys: Do you think this is true? Are we really that insecure? It is possible to restore a platonic relationship with an ex-girl friend?  To all the ladies: Have you any experiences with this kind of male behavior? How about the flipside, do you think girls find it hard to let go of ex-boyfriends as well and then try to be friends but display this kind of territorial (but more subtle I think) behavior?  Feel free to post to the comments (found below) or the tag-board to the left of the blog.    >    fAl   speaks: “ *raises hand* I’ll be the first to admit that I have been guilty of this. It’s funny. I read up about this long ago and told myself to be aware of it but when the time came, I completely didn’t recognize the symptoms. And now it’s too late. I will not go into detail but I just like to add that this kind of over-bearingness can happen even during a relationship. And if not corrected, there she will go. And after the breakup, if one would carry on with this, it will only drive her further away. To the guys take heed, do not take her for granted, yet do not react with over-possessiveness.   *sigh*      >            
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       > Here is another edition of   Hardware Tips : Wireless Networking.    With more and more households having more than a single PC, together with the cheaper and more widespread use of broadband internet connections such as DSL and cable, home networking is becoming more and more of a highly viable option.  There are many ways of connecting PC’s into a network. With Cabled network (ethernet) being the most common, fastest and cheapest. However, running the cables sometimes takes a degree of planning and may occur additional cost such as having to drill holes to pass the cables through. The biggest limitation however, is that the cable limits the mobility of the PC. Therefore it is not recommended for laptops.  This is where wireless networks come in. They consist of a “base station” which usually has a router build in to share the broadband connection. It is easy to call the base station a “transceiver” and each of the computers in the network a “receiver”. However since the wireless connection is two-way, it is more similar to a set of walkie talkies that are always on all the time.  There are several ways to connect a computer to a wireless network. With the most common devices being an internal card or an external box. The main differences between the two seem to be speed, simplicity of installation and cost. Typically internal cards are cheaper and faster but more of a headache to install, while external devices are more costly and slower but are mostly plug&play.  So in the end, the stuff you need for a Wireless network is: - A ethernet based DSL/Cable modem - A base station - and a wireless connection device for each computer that will be connected to the network  I personally recommend getting stuff from  urlLink Linksys .  For more information, feel free to drop me a line or leave a message on the Board. Or you can refer to websites like :  urlLink Practically Networked    >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Report   “And now you’re back, from outer space…”  Am pretty sure that’s how my blog is feeling after seeing me posting to it again. Heh. Anyway, lets cut to the chase.  Two big unit events just ended for me. It was both long and hard work, but I had off given to make up for the time put in. All in all it was not too bad. Come next week however it’s going to be a new ball game as we all go back to work with lowered manpower (lots of people clearing leave) and under new management. Wish me all the best people, have to make it through this month then I can start to clear my own leave. ORD Loh !! *grins*   >  Been reading a new hardcopy book lately. Picked it up a the second hand bookstore at Funan. For all those who think that I have been slacking off on the Sci-fi theme of this blog (and who find it an improvement), be warned. The hardcopy looks to be able to give me fresh ideas to use here. I’ll speak more about it at a later date/time.  Just be thankful all of you that I’m not a hardcore Trekkie, or this blog would read like a Federation Technical Readout or worse, be written totally in Klingon. I have yet to watch an episode of Enterprise as of yet. I better change that soon.  Speaking of Hardcopy, I just received in the mail my first textbook for my Info-Comm course. I can’t describe how excited I am to flip through it. This is totally my can of coke, I’m going to love studying for once in my short blip of a life. I just wish I didn’t have to juggle the time with going to work. I’m actually have to do two modules for my course and so I’m wondering what had happened to the other textbook. There is a chance that they use the same book because they are somewhat similar, but I have better check with them again.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3    I have been sleeping on the floor as of late. No, my Mom didn’t throw me out of the house and no, I have no girlfriend that is giving me a hard time. Very simply, my bed broke. Nigel sat on it.  It’s kinda nice being on the floor. It gives a new perspective of my most familiar surroundings. It’s like given the chance to have a fresh view on something we take for granted.  For example, I have a few glow-in-the-dark stars pasted on the ceiling of my room. They are centered around the light it my room so that they would get maximum exposure to the light when it is on. But since my bed is in one corner of my room, I don’t really get to appreciate them. There are not that many of them. But now…my mattress is in the center of the room and when the lights go off, I find myself directly under them.   Lying there, I find that it no longer matters that there are only a few of them. It is enough to shine like beacons out of the darkness, to show that I am not alone in this big murky world, to pour out on me the light that was poured out on them until they fade away, having shared with me all the light that they had.  It makes me wonder about the time I gave a few bags of these stars away. I had brought them back from far away. I wonder if they where used as attended or if they were set aside in a dark drawer, never to see and share the light.  A gift of stars is a wonderful thing. Go out and lie on a grass patch, somewhere away from the city lights and just stare at them. Imagine the stars in the sky as gifts, made millions of years ago, millions of light years away, just for you in that one instant. How long has the Light traveled to reach our eyes. And ponder on the stars themselves, as big or bigger than our Sun, yet burning themselves away to shine for us. Just a fraction of the glory of the One that made them for us.  This holiday season, go out and receive the gift that was given from the beginning of Time and so may it remind you of the Gift that was given to you 2000 years ago, born under the sign of a star.  Happy holidays   >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Syncr0ni5e   Just completed my first progress test for one of my Info-Com modules today. The test was conducted on-line and it consisted of 60 MCQ. Not too bad, some were tricky but I completed it way ahead of time. Don’t really know what I was so worried about. I even put off writing on the blog just to study. I guess it’s this studying and working at the same time thing, or perhaps it’s the “so-long-never-study-don’t-know-how-to-anymore” feeling I was getting. No matter, I’m glad its over. I have another test this Sat so I’m not free from the books yet. Not to mention the coming exams. I’ll be so glad when Christmas comes around. All my burdens would have passed away. It may even surpass Christmas 2000 as the best Christmas so far in my life.    This is the final week that I have to report to camp in the mornings. For someone who have gotten used to waking up at 5:30 almost every morning for the last 2 years, 5 months and 1 week, I can’t understand why it’s been so difficult the last few days. I must be totally into the ORD mood. Good in a way, just hope I can last the week.  Was doing some quiet time after lunch today and I started thinking of the Audio and Logistics Ministry that I am a part of in church. I mused on the increased responsibility that awaits me when I join back the ministry in full. As always the lack of manpower is at the foremost of my mind. I am now considering a recruitment drive, most likely after the Youth Camp. Will give this more thought. What you do think?  Been spending a lot of time with my younger brother Nigel as of late. It is amazing how much he as grown in the past year since I returned from my overseas posting. In many ways I am glad that I was able to witness most of it. He has lost loads of his baby fat from daily soccer games, has developed his built with early trips to the gym, push-ups and some light free weights. He even wears the same size shoes as me now. Scary. Now I have to keep watch on his emotional and mental growth. Not an easy task. Since I have to keep a close watch on my own as well. Hmm.. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3   I live! :)  I know it sure didn't seem like it over the last week or so but yes (fortunately or unfortunately) I am still alive and determined to continue this online commentry.  It is back to work for me after quite a long break. Only now I work half days for I have taken half day leave for the next two weeks. This is to allow me to study in the afternoons, and looking at how much time I have left I really need to make full use of that time. However I find myself easily distracted, more so than when I was in Poly. Hoping that it just takes awhile for me to get my studying engine back up to speed.  Another important update is that the Home cell group that is meeting at my physical lair (i.e. Home) has begun. It is good to have people around, to sit around and chat in a comfortable setting, to share and study the Bible. Most of the members are younger than me, but nevertheless it is entertaining to listen to them and be there for them if need be. Of course   Edwin   is always the life of the party, with him sharing with us his jokes and stories. He always has this way of getting everyone to unwind and open up. So anyway we meet up on Friday nights at my house. Anyone interested for more details, feel free to drop me aline.  Lastly, here are some plans that I have for the blog coming up this month. I'm planning to get a Links section up on the sidebar, keep a look out for that. And I am still working on that article about the programs and how I use my Palm PDA, for those new palm users who would like some tips, now that they actually own one.  Here I go, back to the grindstone again. Take care and stay sharp.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       5cream 5heet    >   “Pro-Islamic hackers are escalating attacks against countries backing the U.S. war on terror and its campaign against Iraq, while the "Bugbear" worm and last week's strike on the Internet backbone signal that cyber villains are again on the prowl.  London-based computer security firm mi2g said on Tuesday that October had already qualified as the worst month for overt digital attacks since its records began in 1995, with an estimated 16,559 attacks carried out on systems and sites. “    urlLink Experts: Islamic hackers ready for cyber war, from CNN.com      >   >   Fal   speaks: In light of this report and my other sources, as well as the question posted by   Mil  , I just like to post a warning to all readers to be more careful when online, especially when downloading. Here are some pointers to ensure the security of your computer as well as your data.      Make sure that you have a updated  urlLink Anti-virus software  and definitions. Search for “Anti Virus” for the latest updates.     Check your computer for spyware that may be capturing your passwords and user names as well as tracking your surfing habits. I recommend  urlLink Ad-ware .     Don’t open any unknown files sent to you by email. Be extra careful if you use Outlook or Outlook Express as e-mail virus are designed to target these low security programs, check for the latest security patches. Personally I use  urlLink Eudora , less virus target it.    Scan any file that you download before you open them    Install a firewall into your computer. This step is complicated but would create a high level of security and peace of mind. I highly recommend  urlLink Zonealarm .    I would happy to answer and help if anyone got any other questions. Drop me a line. You know how to get me. Falchion out.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Review and Resolutions    > Here it comes, the end of the year 2002. Am actually looking forward to it. This past year has been the most eventful one yet in recent memory. It started out wonderful, but since then I’ve been challenged and tested emotionally, mentally and even physically. Coming to the New Year, I’m still learning and recovering from what i have learned and experienced.   In light of this, i can only have high hopes for 2003. It can't be as bad as the year i just had and with new beginnings and responsibilities, I can make the best of things.  The first step would be to compile a list of goals and resolutions that i want to accomplish next year. This time around I’ll be sure to keep to it better than this year.(if I remember correctly, I only got one thing done.) no more excuses, have much more time on my hands to get them done this time around.  Here is a sample of the things i have on my list.    Do driving lessons    Learn some cooking and house keeping skills   Improve my programming skills   Forge closer ties with my current friends   Find a well-balanced social group (interest group) that I can be a part of and network from   Improve myself by going regularly to the gym and maybe taking up a sport   Learn some finance and investment skills   Improve my Bible knowledge  and so forth…    Well it’s now official and online. I can’t escape from this anymore. We shall see in a year’s time how I have done, then you all can berate me if I don’t make it.    “CLEO, take note, tag current journal entry for extraction from archive in 12 months”    >  That’s it for me for this post, what could be the last post for 2002. One good thing that did come out from all that was this blog itself. I will continue to update and improve on it in the on-coming year. See you in the future.   >   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Weighted I55ue    >     I just returned from a fairly vigorous outing to the gym at my swimming club. This out-of-character response (I mean how many computer geeks are little more than blobs of misshapen protoplasm with large brain cavities, convex enhanced eyesight and with stubby digits which are only used to manipulate computing input devices and finger food) is mainly due to the recent observations that some people have made about my increase in bulk. Ok lah…they said that I was fat. Especially Nigel who makes in a point to, literality,  point  out this fact to me. I keep telling him to cut his nails but no….  Usually I couldn’t care less what people say about my  >. But it is quite intimidating when you are in the gym surrounded by the regulars with nearly prefect bodies. That’s why I don’t use the public gyms but the gym in my club, where the regulars are mainly middle aged and would only intimidate you with they long stories. Another reason is the price of the public gyms, which are just as intimidating as their regulars.  However one benefit of having people around in the gym is that they inspire you to do more than your body would tell you that it would like to do. Example:  ”…7….8….ok think I’ll do just 10 reps for this….9…come on one more….10 yes!, oh wait….that cute girl on the stair-master is looking this way!…11!…huff puff…12!….13…urgghh!…14…ow ow ow...15…ok she just turned away…sigh”    *laughs* may I remind you that I do not speak from experience…well not really. Anyway, I still feel better with a mouse in my hand than a dumbbell. I mean it’s the brains that count not the body right? Yep! I’ll just keep telling myself that.  Any plans for the New Year? I plan to go all out this year, post ORD and all. Any tips let me know.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Merry Christmas!!   Many blessed wishes to everyone out there  To continue the trend of the last few posts conserning my personality, I thought that this would be interesting. I'm not a big fan of these online personality test, but with the current hype of this long standing series and the strength of the characters in the original book. I figured that this one would be suitable to showcase.  You can find it here:  urlLink Lord of the Rings Personality Test   Here is my result:    You are most like  Frodo Baggins, Son of Drogo  With many acquaitenances, Frodo is deeply attached to a few people, like Bilbo, Aragorn, Gandalf, and Sam. His high ethics come out in his treatment of Gollum and Saruman. Frodo has pity on Gollum and believes that change can occur. You have a strong personal morality. You are committed to relationships and their growth. You tend to be an idealist, believing the best of the world around you. Time alone is important and solitary activities refresh you. You have a tendency to introspection. While providing compassion and being considerate, you may have the tendency of being soft-hearted or even "too emotional" You like keeping your options open. Closure is probably not one of your strong suits.   The Orcs display the evil side of this personality with their lengthy torture methods.  Traits: Empathic, benevolent, looking to the future. On the dark side you could be sadistic.    Happy Holidays once again, may you find cheer and joy in everything and everyone around you. God Bless.  >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       5nowflakes in the 5ystem    It’s Christmas time in the City.  Many season greetings to one and all. Over the last two days, I’ve witness with some amusement the last minute shopping rush that always takes hold this time of the year. However it seems like this year the rush is even greater and not just in the shopping centers and malls. Online shopping rates jumped again since Thanksgiving. Would look like more and more people are turning to online shopping as a way to beat the rush. I think that the delivery service that these online stores provide is the key selling point. They would even wrap and decorate the gift for you. Very useful if you can’t wrap for nuts.  Kinda makes one wonder why there isn’t any good and established online retailer here? Most likely because the market is small and filled with already established big name brick & mortar retailers. So I guess the best way to go is for these retailers to set up their own website to conduct e-shopping services and to provide delivery.  You will have to forgive me. My new course modules have just begun and one of which is on Electronic Commerce technology, therefore I have been thinking in this areas as of late. It also doesn’t help that I don’t seem to be in the Christmas spirit this year. One would think that I would be jumping around in a red suit since this is the first Christmas where I Don’t have to wear green. But with the things in my life of late, it seems that I’m back to wearing blue.  However the tide is changing. I think I’ve been putting myself low for far too long. If there is any occasion to rise myself up, now is the time. Hmm perhaps it’s not too late to regain that Christmas Spirit and do some Window shopping.  *Grins*     Merry Christmas Eve everyone and all.       >   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        A Heart Made Of Glass   I always had a problem in describing myself. Never could seem to find the words to do so. I’m pretty sure it’s a mindset thing but nevertheless… I then look to words of others like in books or in songs to help describe me. But you know that doesn’t work. They can come close, like in the song in the post below, but never accurate.   I’m going to be open here and present something I found that describes a lot of myself. It speaks of a personality trait that is a major part of who I am. Since this blog is mainly read by people familiar to me, it is a clearer picture of something that you may have noticed but couldn't quite put a finger on. (It explains the “Sng Bui (sour plum)” nickname that some use to refer to me.   Of course since this is the words of the author and still not of my own, it is not totally accurate (I would like to believe that I am not as bad as the character.heh.)   But I look at the character in question and I see a mirror. I can’t say the same for the situations that he faces (especially in Chapter 2) but I believe that I would have reacted the same way.  You can find it here:  urlLink A Heart Made Of Glass  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        "If You're Not The One"  If you’re not the one then why does my soul feel glad today? If you’re not the one then why does my hand fit yours this way? If you are not mine then why does your heart return my call If you are not mine would I have the strength to stand at all  I never know what the future brings  But I know you are here with me now We’ll make it through  And I hope you are the one I share my life with  I don’t want to run away but I can’t take it, I don’t understand If I’m not made for you then why does my heart tell me that I am? Is there any way that I can stay in your arms?  If I don’t need you then why am I crying on my bed? If I don’t need you then why does your name resound in my head? If you’re not for me then why does this distance maim my life? If you’re not for me then why do I dream of you as my wife?  I don’t know why you’re so far away  But I know that this much is true We’ll make it through  And I hope you are the one I share my life with And I wish that you could be the one I die with And I pray in you’re the one I build my home with I hope I love you all my life  I don’t want to run away but I can’t take it, I don’t understand If I’m not made for you then why does my heart tell me that I am Is there any way that I can stay in your arms?  ‘Cause I miss you, body and soul so strong that it takes my breath away And I breathe you into my heart and pray for the strength to stand today ‘Cause I love you, whether it’s wrong or right And though I can’t be with you tonight And know my heart is by your side  I don’t want to run away but I can’t take it, I don’t understand If I’m not made for you then why does my heart tell me that I am Is there any way that I can stay in your arms?    By Daniel Bedingfield 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know that this is a week late. But to make up for lost time and because the feelings are still fresh, here goes    ORD LOH!!!!   thank you :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Story of a Computer Guy    Well looks like I have finally gotten my system stable enough to return to normal operations. It’s not 100% but should fit my needs as long as I don’t trip over the newly (badly) positioned power cables.  Basically, close to three weeks ago. My system started getting increasingly frequent lockups, strange Operating System errors and Data corruption. I managed to work through most of them, vowing to get to the bottom of it once my exams are over. However 3 days before my papers, the system suffered a series of crashes that resulted in system memory failure and my hard disk partitions totally corrupted. It was quite a large blow to me as my exam revision includes large amounts of online data, but also an emotional blow as I always believed in myself to be able to troubleshoot these types of problems, especially in such an important occasion as it was. Not to mention the finances used in replacing the RAM module. I took this opportunity to submit a upgrade proposal to my sponsors as it was passed in the last meeting that upgrading was needed. However current budget constrains did not permit it at the time. I had to make do with what I had.   I had assumed that the problem was caused by the faulty memory, but after installing it, I found out it was only a part of the problem. Midway through reinstalling my programs and data, the whole system crashed once again.   Something else was wrong.  I spent the rest of that week trying to chase down the problem and finally narrowed it down to a power problem, one of the most overlooked and arcane of computing problems. I replaced my power supply with a newer, more reliable brand and proceed to reinstall.  After 30 hours, the problems resurfaced.  I was at my wits end. It left only two other areas that would be the cause. The power strip that supports my workspace, or the wall socket.     Well to cut a long story short (actually I think it’s a little too late for that) I bought a new power strip and it didn’t really work. It was better but not good enough. In the end I had to stretch the power cables to my other power strip that would result in my cables tripping up people if not careful. I’m praying that this is only for awhile until a more permanent fix is found, such as installing a new wall socket closer to my workspace.  After all this I am back online and it looks like I have a lot of catching up to do. Bare with me everyone, FalchionEdge is back.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       ...Continued   Quite a cool thing today was witnessing  Dex  playing around with his Lomo camera. Thing looks like a toy (but I guess thats partly from Dex's choice of transparent for the color) but it actually a really funky fully functional 4 lens camera. The most interesting about it is the strange color effects that might occur after the picture is taken. I read about it when I was overseas and thought that it would make a cool gift for the arty type of people. Still do. May decide to look into it as gifts for some friends as their birthdays comes along. Thing is not cheap though, but not as expensive as I thought it would be.  Speaking of  Dex , I didn't really want to add on to the emotions that he and  Milton  are already going through. But it would be unjust of me not to mention them before they leave. Both of them have actually been huge influential factors in two areas that I can recall. My interest in playing drums and in having a blog. Sad to say that my interest in playing the drums is for more than my actual talent in it. Lets hope that this blog doesn't go that way as well. Then again, if you want to blame anyone for this blog, now you know who to go after. Good for them that they are leaving heh.  But  Dex  has been a very good friend of mine for a very long time. We basically grew up together in church and while I had a more wayward time before getting involved, we share the same memories of some of the best times we had in church. Recently our paths have diverged somewhat and I'm sorry that I haven't gotten to know better the Awake and now Sonic Edge guys and gals, especially his rocking Pension State Band members. Hopefully after  Dex  leaves, we would still have a common connection. Keep in touch bro. You'll be sure that I will keep bugging you if you don't.   Milton  has always been a big feature in the Crossover youth. He came in with a bang and has been banging away on that drum kit ever since. Apart from missing his quick licks and lighting chops, his huge laughter and corny jokes that rank right up there with the best like Danny and Sean and  Dex , his presence will be missed as well. I'm sure his closest friends are reminding him that they are going to, and will be, missing him when he leaves. I just like to add that they will not be the only ones.  Godspeed my Friends and brothers. I'll see you soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       5hout 2 the N0rth and the S0uth   >   Well, according to the reports that I have seen. Most of the Internet problems over the weekend was caused by a worm exploiting the latest in  Microsoft  security holes. Good news that the attack doesn't seem to be malicious, but nevertheless it been giving huge denial of service worldwide. While it seems to be easily fixed, I'm wondering why this 6 month old hole was not fixed earlier? I'm not sure if this is an oversight of the server administers  or of  Microsoft , but at the risk of sounding bias, I'm sure you can tell where I am pointing my finger to.  Work Update: I managed to finish off one assignment, just have to reorder the reference list thats all. I am however waiting on the other assignment, still not all the details are in yet. I did get updated about the oncoming tests the weekend after the CNY, so looks like I'll be busy for next week and the week after as well. Starting to look like there is a pattern to how my school works. They like to dump on us last minute stuff especially the two weeks before the one before the test. Guess I'll have to be more aware for the next module. Good think I only have one to do after this two, but I have to study all three for the exams in April.  Aside from school, I did manage to learn something new in the form of installing and running basic desktop functions in Linux, that a good thing. I should learn a new skill every month for this whole year. Wonder what I can do for next month? Maybe finish off by learning the server side stuff of Linux, or hopefully Windows XP Pro. Of course lets not forget about Driving.  Hmm That should be kinda cool.  Gotta get back to work now. Will update again later.    >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Br3wing over a h0t cuppa t3a    Oh my freaking head...      >    Sigh...been laid low the last few days of the weekend due to some strange bout of stomach flu. Seems to be the only type of flu I get these days. I always seem to find the best times to fall ill. The last time was just barely a week before my tests last November and now it's during the time that I need to focus on my assignments. Get a feeling that I'm going to be very busy this week. Better blog now in case I don't get a chance to later.  It's strange but only last night, at the end of flu symptoms, did I remember a helpful remedy. I know it's sometimes considered an old wives' tale (heh. Sorry. Detected some irony in the last few words) but honestly, a hot cup of honey and lemon rocks. Makes your breath fresh too! (*winces* yet more irony there)  Gadget News: One of the items on my wish list has just gotten an upgrade! The new version of the  Creative Nomad Jukebox Zen  now comes with USB 2.0 support. Prefect once I upgrade my system. It still can hold 20Gigs of musical goodness and still support 14 hour playback. Speaking of my wish list, perhaps I should post it online...nah, don't want to seem egoistical, or materialistic for that matter.   Col Se  and gang in church have been having some problems with their  Clié's  as of late. I spoke to him about giving me some details so that I can check for them. Have yet to get a response since I wasn't in church yesterday. Will email him again. It's important to help out my fellow  PalmOS  users. I always believe in community in software, hence the Linux. It's quite sad to see that something designed to be simple to use still requires technical support. But it's the way with all devices. Makes me wonder about the more “advanced” PDA's .  Well looks like it's back to work for me. Hope to update again soon. Looks good if I can keep this darn headache at bay.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Maj0r Updat3      >    Well it's been a busy last few days so far. The big update is that I have changed my working system to a Linux OS. Basically Linux is another type of computer operating system, sorta like Mac OS and Windows. It has not been an easy transition. Installing and running it is not a problem, it's getting all the applications to work thats the problem. I think part of it lies in me wanting to get it to work like Windows. It's hard not too. I have been using Windows for a very long time. Before that was DOS and how having to go back to a DOS like environment, it's like taking a step backwards. But where it lacks in flash, it makes up for it stability and function. No more random crashes. Which makes me wonder again about what was the problem on my old system.  The biggest complains come from    >   of course. Not easy getting used to the new environment and getting all the applications to work. But as you can see, things are much better now.  Of course I still keep my Windows around. Games still run better on it and since gaming takes a big chunk of my processes, all the more that I should still maintain the best performance for it.  In other news, I've been hitting the books hard since sunday, need to make up for lost time suffered during the migrating of OS. On top of that, I have to make time to study for my driving test this friday . It's only basic theory, which I have passed in the army, but I shouldn't take it lightly. Better get it over and done with.     >        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3   Happy Birthday to me :)   > has been alerting me to the incoming  birthday greetings on the Net for the last hour or so. So many thanks to all who have wished me well. What would we do without ICQ's birthday reminder service eh? Heh  Right now I'm trying to get my contacts from my Palm to Sync with my new PIM/Email client. Going to spend some more  time on it...will give a bigger update soon.    >
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Statu5 Updat3    >   Welcome to a brand new year! Well things have been going fine lately, all in all a good start to the new year. Studies are coming along although I’m a bit behind, especially in assignments. I booked my driving theory test, should be a piece of cake since, in a way, I have passed it before. Been exercising regularly and feeling good.  However there are a few low points; if you recall I have been getting strange computer freezes for the last two months or so. Now this is not healthy, for the computer or for me. I have narrowed down the problem to two areas, the power supply or the mainboard. But I needed to test my theories. So I moved the system outside to the main hall and used a power point there. Since I have already changed the power supply inside the system to no avail, this was the only other alternative. I then tested the system for 8 hours and it suffered no random crashes. My fears come through; there is a problem with the power supply from the wall socket of my room. Now I’m in a fix as to how to solve this. Should I just get the electrician to check the wall socket in my room? Or should I get him to install a new one closer to my system so that I don’t have to use any extension power strips? Any ideas?  Another low point was when I answered a somewhat personal question untruthfully on impulse. I consider the person who asked it to be a good friend and I had no intention to be dishonest with her. I just answered the first thing that came to mind, as it caught me by surprise and it was the easiest answer to give. Now I feel that I need to clear the air with her although she is unaware of my error. Perhaps I should call her.   > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Gr33tings Pr0grams!   Just a quick update here before I launch myself back to work. Ever been in this sense of limbo where you are totally happy about something and you want to enjoy that feeling, but there is a little something that puts a damper on it? Yep…I feel that way right about now.  I got my new  > up and running and it’s a sweet machine. I would have gotten it up earlier if it wasn’t for the fact that I need to swap the video card, hard disk and even the power supply with my old rig. The installation of Windows XP Pro was smooth, the easiest OS install I ever had frankly and my view of Microsoft has improved just on this fact alone. The OS itself is fantastic and I’ve grown to like it. However it is still Windows and some stuff bug me, like how a high powered rig is needed to run it well, and all those annoying Microsoft apps that I can’t turn off (damn MSN messenger, go away! Stop eating my resources…), well not yet at least.  The damper on the party is that I can’t use all the security features that I wanted unless I use the NTFS file format. But silly me, I was in such a rush that I didn’t do that. So it looks like I would have to reformat and reinstall to get it. Oh well. Good thing I found this out early on but I can’t do it right now since I need to finish up my assignment first. Sigh. Just consider this a learning experience I guess.   >  Wonder about today’s Tag Line? Check out  urlLink Tron 2.0  a follow up on one of my favorite movies, Tron (comes just under Star Wars). The special effects was Way ahead of it’s time back then and the soundtrack is very cool (cyber-orchestral I call it, if there is such a thing) and it’s the only DVD that I own at the moment.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       fa5t Updat3   Just a quick one to introduce the two new blog users that I have added to my links. They are both local blogs to sorta make up for the lost of two other local blogs which have now become overseas blogs.heh. All the best over there you guys.  Firstly we have  urlLink Lianne  who I feel writes with a simplicity and honesty that is embodied by the layout and desing of her blog, with a healthy dose of cynicism that gives her words an edge.  Next we have  urlLink skinthrills  and a lovely pink and functional blog. Love all the links and features on the sidebar. Most importantly, she writes with a style that is smooth, causal and lighthearted. Worth checking out  I hope everyone welcomes them and take the time to check out their blogs. It's good to encourage people who have taken the time to share with us their thoughs and feelings and willing to open them up for discussion and new insights.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Pick of the W33k   What an interesting start to the week. I have been planning to take it easy this week since I just finished a round of test. I still have an assignment due next week but since I have the whole week it’s not a big rush. So now I can turn my attention on the matters that I have left alone during the last two weeks. Apart of which is enjoying myself. To that extend I have spend the last two days catching up on my movie/tv watching list.   Lets see, I started on  Sakura Wars: the TV series  and have already caught up to about halfway through the series. I know it is currently showing on TV but it’s hard to catch every episode everyday. Besides there seems to be a greater understanding of the main theme and plots when the episodes are viewed in close succession. You should try it. Pay close attention on character plots, you can really notice the growth in some of them, which is not apparent with a week long break.  It is not really the case with movies however. They are mostly designed to be self-contained. Even the trilogy type movies, all you need is a basic understanding of the plots from the previous movie to see you through the next one. That being said, one of my greatest times I had was when I sat through an eight plus hour marathon of the  Star Wars  Episodes 4 to 6.  Our movies that I caught up with are  Shanghai Knights  staring Jacky Chan and  The Sweetest Thing  staring Cameron Diaz. ( Cameron Diaz  rocks! She is a big favorite of mine and it kinda scary that she keeps reminding me of someone I know, I think it’s the high cheekbones and mannerisms.)    >   Other items I got done involve the blog. I’m looking into moving it onto Pacific Internet for the time being. I don’t really need fancy CGI scripts (at the moment) and at most I’ll add pics, which they have support for. I guess I’ll move again after a few months to a new domain name where I can use software like  urlLink Movabletype  to design and implement a new layout. Perhaps in time for the one year anniversary of me starting the blog?    >   Some good news. Looks like the   >  to upgrade my computer would finally be coming through during the next few days. It’s much reduced from the original amount but hey!…I am happy for what I can get. I will have to top up some of my own cash but since I’ve been saving over the last few months, it’s ok. I’ll most likely take the weekend to get everything up and running again, and by then I’ll have to focus on my assignment, so updates will slow down then. But it’s all good…expect me to be back brand new and better than ever.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       turn it up & tune it d0wn   Yesterday (seeing how it's past midnite now) was the first time that the  Crossover Ministry  held it's service in the newly constructed  Youth Hall . Very exciting time it is. We as a Ministry have been praying for a place of our very own for a very long time. Before this we would always be sharing space with other services which would result in some difficulties, such as the sound and worship team only having 15 minutes to set up and soundcheck. Now with our own place, we don't really have to worry so much about such details of where we are and instead can focus more time on what really matters, the people.  However there is still some work that needs to be done. The sound system is not totally complete as of yet. Still missing some cables, floor monitors and effect boxes. Not to mention our own drumset. And the sound team is going to take some time to get used to the acoustics of the new hall. I estimate about a month for us to really settle in. In addition, the sound team now has greater responsibilities, not only for the audio equipment, but now the instruments as well as the whole Hall itself. Frankly I'm looking forward to the challenge.  In any case the very first service there was a blast. There was this new energy and new joy that just spread throughout the people as the musicians played. This is not to say that we only praise Him when we get new stuff, but sometimes it is indeed good to see change in how He provides and cares for us. Of how prayers can be answered, even after many years. The unity of the ministry is growing, not just because we are closer physically while standing in the hall, but because we have been given a greater sense of identity. I can only foresee this unity growing.    >   I had a blast today hanging out with the guys at our favorite LAN shop. It's not been often lately that I get to hang out with them, especially with the “kid”  Jst  Lm  who so happened to drop by today to have lunch with us, or so he claims *grins*. I don't know why I still call him “kid”. Must be because I still remember him as that young, wild spirited , impulsive kid that I tried to take under my wing and mentor him even though the age gap is only around 2 to 3 years. Sorta like Han Solo to Luke Skywalker. Heck, I've had a girlfriend who is as old as him, which, taking the nickname I have for him, would make me a...p...i don't even want to think about it. (and if  Lady Raine  reads this she would kill me, but then again how else can I get her attention these days? *heh* )    >   I know this has been talked to death on the tag-board already. But it's too funny and ironic (to me) to pass up. Just after typing all that I wanted to on the board, I went off to read the latest issue of NewMan (a more local, smarter and less offensive mag than FHM Singapore). Lo and behold what would I find within it's pages but an article about how guys should deal with getting dumped, for a lack of a better word. There...I'm not ashamed to say it anymore. First my best guy friend who sometimes has no right to talk about acting rationally when it comes to relationship trouble. Next the actual ex-GF in question, who is so nice and thoughtful to take the step forward even though she had her reservations about how to deal with me and at the risk of her own emotional state (horrible fake hokkien though *grins*). Normally that should be enough for one to realize that it's time to get up and get moving forward, but no! Someone up there understands how bad I can be when it comes to things like this and sets it up that even a “stupid” Men's mag has to tell me to get off my a$$. All within the space of a few hours! I was laughing the whole way through reading the article.   Yes, it may still hurt, yes i may stumble with the memory from time to time and yes it will take some time. But I have learnt from it, I am better from it, and I know that I had some good times that I will always treasure. The future awaits and I have to keep moving forward to meet it. To continue to live on the edge if you will. “Come what May” it was sung. So be it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       5tatus Updat3   I noticed that I was lacking some important personal information in my profile, so I added some of that in as well as updating the other fields. On top of that I have added some more links to other blogs. This one is long in coming since  Da Man  (no no…not that DA MAN) is so featured on this blog, especially in the tag-board. Of course it’s only justice that I include his better half in my links as well. Happy now D?  I’m also looking to add more links to other bloggers. So my old friends, if you have one that I am not aware of and don’t mind me adding it here, let me know. In the meantime, I’m also looking at other interesting blogs of people that I do not know. Will start off with Singaporean ones first. Will let you know when I do so.    >   On the personal side, I currently seem to be on some sort of emotional balance scale (you know, those things we used in physics class to compare the weights of objects? the lawyers would know what I mean). On one hand I have closure to questions that I have been wondering almost the whole of last year, and I have affirmation and encouragement of my character and the demise of one of my greatest fears. It’s great to be released of these burdens.  But on the other hand, the outcome of the situation doesn’t seem to reflect the good things, and the speed of and change to this current status is something that I cannot fully wrap my mind around.   Is it “How can everything be so right and yet seem so wrong?” or “How can everything seem so right and yet Be so wrong?” How can I find the answer to the question if I’m not even sure which one of the two is the question?   How can I be so encouraged and uplifted yet be so alone and empty? How does one praise someone and yet move to a state what puts that person in a negative light?  *shakes head* this is going to take some getting used to. And the answers can go longer be given, but have to be found. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Port Scann1ng     >   Here I am once again, stuck infront of my  > going through my notes for my upcoming test end of the week. Same thing as last week it would seem. At least this module is much more interesting and therefore easier to adsorb.   It was an interesting weekend I had, firstly I was quite happy to get over and done with my test on Sat, however the mood to celebrate was lost in the reality that I didn't have anywhere and anyone to celebrate with. It's rare that I get impulsive urges to...well enjoy a night on the town, usually I'm content with simple (and less expensive) pleasures. Therefore is was sad to see the feeling go to waste.  I was helping a friend out over the weekend as well, she was looking for tenants for a place she was renting out in  Melbourne  and inquired if I knew anyone who would be needing a place since this is the period that a lot of overseas students would be going over to start their studies. It was kinda last minute but I did know of some that fit the bill. So I helped to link them up. Perfect example of the type of  Networking  that is so heavily touted as the new  road to success, business or otherwise. For this reason that I quite regret not having closer links with my old classmates. As I think back I don't know why I didn't try harder to keep in touch. Even those as late as my Poly friends, I am in contact with a bare handful. Think I need to start to keep closer links, I mean thats one of the reasons why I carry a PDA, so I won't lose contact information. You never know when knowing someone would come in handy. Especially the likes of doctors, lawyers, computer and automobile technicians, journalist, real estate agents and a whole range of support industry types.  In light of this then, that it was a welcomed surprise that I bumped into an old primary school classmate of mine in church. I had found her familiar at first but  didn't think too much into it at the time, and neither did she, but after listening to my ah...unique manner of speaking, she deduced my identity. It was great catching up with old times, I have nothing but fond memories of my time at Tao Nan and she shared the same sentiments. We were both eager to hear more of what became of our classmates and while she was still in contact with some of them, I had to disappoint her with my lack of knowledge about the others. We did agree however that we should try to round up as many of the ones that we did know and have a reunion of sorts. Well heres a shout out to  SuLynn . Hope to see you next week. We can trade more stories :)  My time's up...back to the books I go.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Taking my own advice   Well...remember what I was saying about doing more emailing? Well this morning I wrote a quick one to another overseas friend that I have not heard from in sometime and guess what? Within two hours the person came online and we chatted over ICQ. Which is rare, as this one is in a stressful and busy enviroment.  I have another friend that I need to catch up with too. If I can get her away from work that is. I had better mention her before she finds out I forgot about her in yesterdays post and takes my head for it  ”There can be only One”  Word to yah D.C.  This email thing seems to be working out so far. Guess I better keep it up. Looks like there is more to email than just for mailing list, newsletters, subject updates, and infrequent questions and greeting cards.  Well...back to work. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       5tatus updat3   Today I managed to get in touch with an old friend of mine. It was really good to hear from her again. Although it was marred by the fact that she didn't call me even though she has been back for almost two weeks and that she forgot about my birthday.  *tsk tsk*  No matter, I forgive her :) I can't say that I've been very active in emailing, so my bad as well. We had a good conversation and I'm glad that we can communicate so well after so long. I've always enjoyed talking to her as she has this certain humor and joy in the way she speaks and we seem to be able to talk about anything. Everyone should have a friend like this. I'm looking forward to meeting up with her soon.   This reminds me of another, even older friend that also just came back, this time from Melbourne. I will have to remember to set a time to meet up with her too, if the boyfriend lets me that is. Especially difficult with V Day coming though.   Seems like Feb is the month to catch up with old friends, especially those returning from overseas. It's a pity that Feb is also the month that I have all my test and assignments due. Better make sure to plan my time well.  In hindsight I guess I should start emailing people more often. Even local friends. Usually my only online form of communication is this Blog and ICQ. But I can't assume that people will read this, especially with my irregular updating schedule. As for ICQ, not everyone would be online at the same time that I will be. With Email, they can't escape. Heh.    >   Just finished reading the latest  Star Wars: New Jedi Order  novel. It's a good continuation of the ongoing story line, but I feel that some of the characters seem, well out of character. Also missing was a few other favorite characters that were featured in previous books. Here is a very good quote from the book:   ”There's no right or wrong way to tread; the rules are made up as you go along and can change without warning...trust me when I say it makes being a jedi look easy.” - Jedi Master Luke Skywalker, on relationships.       >   Seen the latest  Matrix Reloaded trailer ? Man it Rocks! You can find both trailers at the  urlLink website . I can't wait for May, have to start watching the first movie over and over again to prepare for it. Sorta like what I did for the  Lord of the Rings  movies by reading the books again. This is going to be a big year with the ending of the Matrix movies in November, the ending of the above mentioned Star Wars series also in Nov and the last LOTR movie in December. It's going to be an interesting year ahead.  For now. Let me get back to work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Earth and Bey0nd   It is with a heavy heart that I write this. This past 1 of Feb, the dream of thousands was shattered and put on hold, and for the 7 member crew of the Space Shuttle Columbia, ended.  I always had a fascination with Space. As a young child I would read up on the subject and would stare at the night sky for hours, a habit that I still continue today. In primary school when the Yong Scientist  award scheme was introduced, I tried out for 4 different fields but only managed to get the award for astronomy. It was in this interest that I naturally branched out into reading Science Fiction.  I remember that faithful year. I had just turned 7 and it was to be a sign of a life changing year for me. The space program had been going full force with the shuttle project after a successful run on the Apollo program. Morale was high and a fleet of shuttles was commissioned after the successful testing of the Enterprise. Two shuttles had already been put into active duty with another 2 on the way. It was the second shuttle that I watched on TV that day as it climbed into the sky only to end in a fiery 3 part fireball. The Challenger disaster. It was also a day of firsts, the first teacher was on board and a first step into making space travel more open to the public.  Now the first shuttle has followed it's sister and it took along another first. The first Israeli astronaut. In what what was to be a great symbol for peace and unity, ended in a blaze of fiery flame. It does not bode well for mankind. Nor for the space program. With the hope of a space program to Mars in 2010, there was a hope to take our minds off the troubles on Earth. Of famine, of fear and of war. I had imagined to be able to see mankind living off Earth by the time of my grandchildren, and perhaps have my ashes sent towards the edge of our solar system, in the final eternal journey of discovery.  Now it looks like the space program would be set back another 40 years. And with growing tensions planetside, we may never leave earth orbit again. We may never live among the stars nor be buried in the fields of space, like the heroes before us, who have made it all possible.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       The 5creamSh33t   From Wired News:  SINGAPORE -- Male. Obsessed with computers. Lacking a girlfriend. Aged 14 to 34. Capable of sowing chaos worldwide.  That is the profile of the average computer-virus writer, an anti-virus expert said on Tuesday. "They have a chronic lack of girlfriends, are usually socially inadequate and are drawn compulsively to write self-replicating codes. It's a form of digital graffiti to them..."     gosh. I better get cracking then. I wouldn't want to be left behind. ;) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm sure by now everyone is rooted to the media on the conflict in the Gulf.  It has finally began, and therefore I won't go into my reasons for why they should or should not do, I have been putting off writing them as a matter of fact. And frankly it doesn’t matter anymore now.  What matters is to pray for the fastest and best resolution to this situation. May God watch over those who are involved, on both sides and  especially  the ones caught in the middle.   May God forgive us all. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       The E1eventh H0ur      Trace the shape of my heart, till it becomes more familiar to your eyes.  I've been lost without you, cold without your love. It's taken days and nights to make me realize.  Rescue me from hanging on this line. I won't give up on giving you a chance to blow my mind. Let the eleventh hour quickly pass me by. I'll find you when I think I'm out of time.  Take the place of my heart, till I become a stranger to my life.  I've been down without you, wrong without your love.  In time will I be what you're thinking of?  Rescue me from hanging on this line. I won't give up on giving you a chance to blow my mind. Let the eleventh hour quickly pass me by.  I'll find you when I think I'm out of time.  I've been wrong without you, cold without your love. In time will I be what you're thinking of?   - By Jars of Clay       this is dedicated to all those who need to believe in miracles or if that they do exist. Of special note is  urlLink Lianne  and her report, "the title says it all"   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Plann1ng Ah3ad     "Cleo, report..."  >    Already been a few days since the server move and I've added some new functions, mainly to test out the things that I can do on this server. The Jedi gif is cute, but gets old after awhile, I should start looking for others. But it does pave the way for real pics coming to this blog soon. My family will be acquiring a digital camera within this month or early next and I'll make sure to have a go at learning and using it. Of course it will be a family item and not a personal one, so it's not a model that I would have chose (I.E. it's not a Sony) and I will not have access to it all the time. But on the other hand, it will fall under family expenses and not my own so that’s good. *grins*  Other plans for the blog, is to expand it into a real website. Start of with adding pages that have the same theme as the blog but contain other information such as a real bio page and full links page. If I really get ambitious (or finally get off my lazy ass), I might put up some of my own written works, stuff like reviews (movies, TV and a whole range of stuff) and short stories (mostly Fan Fics). Watch for it. I hope.    >   A bit under the weather over this weekend, have a sore throat, cough and some major headache. Think I caught it from Nigel, he's been sick earlier this week with the same symptoms. Kinda reminds me of my army days where when someone in the bunk gets sick and all the rest one by one catch it as well. Terrible.  Guess I'll just take it easy, do my readings and messing with my stuff. Like for example, I just got a new 128MB Memory Stick for my Clie, think I shall go find stuff to upload to it, maybe a dictionary (to help my spelling), a new e-book and even some MP3s. Of course once I move some of the big files on the Clie there will be more space to install new programs, so I guess I'll go look for some of those as well. Yay! Wee! *laughs*   Neat. I feel better already.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Updat3: Move Complete   Well as you can see the move has been completed and is sucessful. Except for the Archives it seems. Trying to do something about that, but so far no go.... it's a pity...I consider the archives to be an important part of a blog. Not only for others to catch up with whats going on, but also for oneself, to go back to read what I once wrote and reflect on how far (or how low) I have gone since then.  In the meantime enjoy the faster loading, and I hope to have some pics/graphics up soon because...well frankly...because I can *grins*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Updat3 : Moving to new server   Just got a reply from Pacific Internet regarding my personal domain name. So now I can start to bring the blog over to their system. Ideally it should be faster and easier for people to remember the URL. So that means everyone please update your links to point to the new address.    urlLink www.Falchion.per.sg    I'm going to try to move the blog soon, but it looks like blogger is having some problems. Will see how it goes.  I'll see you all on the other side!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Start1ng 0ff a brand n3w day   Situation: Start of a brand new month and week. Status: doing fine!  Yes. Life is good. Sometimes. But that is also good. For if life was good all the time, then we wouldn’t appreciate the times that it was actually good. I hope that made sense.  In any case things are looking good now. I finally got a stable and fully functional  > after 3 long months. I have some new software and games that I can enjoy and get lost in, no more deadlines, no more tesst. Ahh Life  is  good.  Of course it not all fun and games. Can’t totally slack. I’m behind on my reading for my current module and I still have to review my last two modules often so as to prepare myself for the exams next month. I’ve also picked up some learning material for Windows XP Professional. If I’m going to be working in the IT industry like I hope, it would be a good idea to know as much as I can about the most used operating systems. Normally I would like to learn with self-taught hands on experience. But I’m kinda tired of just messing around with stuff on my own. Things are getting more and more complex nowadays that it’s good to have some sort of guide otherwise untold damage can be done. That being said, one can learn a lot from taking things apart with one’s hands and trial and error. Oh to go back to simpler times.    >  Some other things that I would require to focus on include helping some people source for PDA’s. Can’t keep them waiting for too long. And I still have yet to get around to that article about PDA’s that I was planning to do up here. But you know what they say, no demand, no production.  My church is acquiring some new computers and planning to link some of them up in a network for the study room. I offered to help and give advice on the setting up. Time to put that new book I bought to good use.  And in the mist of all this I have to find time to start on driving lessons. Still don’t know why I’m resisting this fact of life. Guess the information on how much the COE and car prices are keeping me getting excited about it.    > Such a great joy today to get into one of my all time favorite computer games that was once thought long gone.  urlLink Ur-Quan Masters  is the remake of Star Control 2 and features all the same gameplay, deep and rich story, fast-paced yet tactical action and huge doses of humor. Many new features have been added such as remix soundtrack and speech, makes this a must for fans, short of a true sequel, since Star Control 3 was made by different people and thus doesn’t count. Looks like sleepless nights are here again. *grins*  I shall close with this regularly uttered quote from the game:  "Yeah! tonguing! The tonguing is the best!" - The Zot-Fot-Piq talking about their  Sting er ships  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       *stretches*  Well, that's it. Another round of exams over. Not totally happy about though, but I don't think that I'll fail. Yeah... think ...  Wandered around the City Hall area after my paper, went to check a few things out, windows shop for a bit...pretty boring...  Was kinda looking for something fun to do...I mean it's just after exams so it's only natural, but on top of that I only have a small window of time for R&R before I jump back into the fray with that project due early May. Kind of worried about it. I barely have two weeks to do it and yet it counts for like 90% of my marks for that module. Worse of all I have no idea how to start it. Looks like I have to contact my lecture and throw him some questions.     >   Once I get through that however, it should be an eventful month. Lots of new stuff coming out and I intend to start a new hobby.     >   Got a call from an old friend, RthCk , just before the exams. Haven't heard or seen her in a long time...more than a year I believe. Hope to squeeze in some time to meet up before she leaves on a business trip in May. I tell you that girl is always busy. Another old friend I need to meet up with is  SLyn , very fun to talk to her and get all nostalgic about our primary school days.    >   Well time to update the links and layout...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       *sigh*  Another 10 day gap between posts. I got to go back to writing more often.It's been quite a busy week studying for my on coming exams in less than 2 weeks time. I could have gotten a better head start on it if it weren't for the fact that I was busy studying another module which I though would be having it's exam around the same time, only to find out that it's a non-exam module.  grrrr . Wish they had told me earlier. Yes I know how it can seem unusual, but I assumed that all modules had exams and wasn't told otherwise at the beginning on this one. Yea Whatever.    >   Downloading the latest  urlLink Matrix Reloaded  trailer now.  Rocks!  I can't believe that it's almost a month's time away. Seems like I've been waiting so long for it. It almost seems a lifetime away seeing as how I had enlisted, lived overseas and gone through a relationship during the time since the first movie.     >   Picked up the highly acclaimed PC game  Battlefield 1942 . It really ups the ante on first-person online multiplayer games with the biggest feature being seamless interaction with vehicles and defence placements. Didn't have time to spend too much time with it but I did get a chance to try out the Desert Combat modification which updates the game to modern day headlines. All in all a pretty cool game, but my interest in it seems more on it's innovations than it's gameplay.    >   Now that  Smallville  has ended it's first season run, Channel 5 is bringing in the sister series  Birds of Prey  in the same timeslot. It's from the same producers of Smallville and is also a twist on a DC comic, in this case  Batman . I realize that I may have spoke of it before but since it's actually coming to our small screens this time I guess a recap is in order. Basically it is a strange combination of the Batman movies, animated series and comics. In BOP, Batgirl is Batman latest partner after Robin and Nightwing left. On top of that, Catwoman has reformed after giving birth to a girl, who turns out to be Batman’s daughter. The war between Joker and Batman reaches a tragic end and the series picks up in the aftermath of that event. The whole thing is linked together by the visions of a young meta-human (think mutants in X-Men) who has traveled to Gotham City. Keep an eye on actress  Dinah Myer  who plays Barbara Gordon/Batgirl/Oracle. She plays the role very well and true to the comics, it helps that she is quite a knockout too :)   Well, hopefully It won't take me another 10 days to post again. heh.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Allow me to speak about the news, since there is so much of it now and so many people looking for it. However lets not speak what's  on  the News, but  the  news itself and how it effects (my own) lifestyle. Back in my poly days I was a big news junkie. Part of my daily routine would include spending an hour half to 2 hours just hitting all the news sites on the Internet, followed by another 45 minutes of reading the E-mails I would get from the newsgroups that I had subscribed to. Even my girlfriend then, towards the end of that time, was going to (and now is) study journalism. When I enlisted, part of the problem early on was similar to a "News cold turkey" which came from being cut off from the outside world (and the above mentioned girlfriend of course). Would "waste" away my precious weekends just trying to catch up on the week. And it only got worse when I was posted overseas.  The other subject I like to touch on seems off tangent, but I will link it all back later, is radio. My interest in radio has waned much since the growth of digital music and the trend of personal music that arose from it, which I am a firm supporter of.   However since the module that I'm learning now focuses on media and broadcasting, I've started to regain more respect for radio in the fact that it's actually the most up to date media in the area of News. It's a wonder why I never thought about it before and even if I did, why didn't I implement it? Like my module states, radio is still around because it's so pervasive, it can be found anywhere and is cheap.  So perhaps I should look into getting a small hi-fi or standing radio and keep it on the news radio channel whenever I'm at my desk, that should allow me to ease off the need to "waste" time getting   >  to search my news sources. Of course, I still have to get my Tech and Gaming News but that should still cut down on time significantly.   Maybe all this could revive my interest in the News, which has waned considerably over the last year or two. I wonder why? Perhaps it's the need I found to focus not so much on the things or people around me and focus more on my wants and desires, of which I found to be lacking of late. Selfish? Perhaps but that's for another time.    > 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally I am an owner of my own personal digital camera. Now I can join the league of arty photo-takers who post seemingly abstract shots on their blogs like  urlLink tess  and  urlLink jon   *grins*  . All I have to do is to find someplace to host the photos and link them to here.  Another league I believe I can officially be a part is the gadget freaks. I mean take a glance at the list: mobile phone, MP3 player, Sony PDA and digital camera...I'm practically a Harvey Norman. And one would think my level of "geek" couldn't get any higher. Guess I just "leveled" up ( *heh*  another geek reference).  Well, we can look at it in two ways. On one hand, it fits in with my future line of work in IT. I would need to be familiar with the product in order to properly advice and troubleshoot for people, and what best way to get to learn about than to actually own and use it?   And the other end is that, perhaps I will take it up as a real hobby and more time will be spent outdoors and away from my desk and computer. Goes well with my new bicycle that I just got now that I'm starting to learn how to cycle finally after all these years.  Whichever the outcome,  it's all good . 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      OhKay...a little late on that review. Heh. Have been trying to cramp in 3 weeks of C++ programming into this whole week. Didn't go as smooth as I expected.    >   Right.  The Matrix Reloaded . Let's get the obvious questions out of the way.  I liked it.  I know there are alot of divided views on it and about how it doesn't live up to the hype and that the story is too messy with too many holes and gaps in the plot.  But I liked it nevertheless. Why?   Because I know that  Reloaded  is only a part of a full story which includes at least two episodes from the  Animatrix , the video game  Enter the Matrix  and of course the to be shown  Revolutions . Of particular note is the game  Enter the Matrix , written and directed by the same two brothers, which leads into and takes place the same time as  Reloaded . Alot of plot holes and questions are answered in the video scenes in the game and they help to develop and explain the other characters and events that appear in  Reloaded , but are not focused on. However, all this branching out makes the movie seem empty and the story fragmentated.  I knew that we would be getting more of what we have seen in the first movie. I didn't expect the same degree of awe and wonder as the first one, but instead a continuation of a story already in progress. I'm glad that they answered questions from the first movie such as how Zion looks like, the other ships and their captains and crew and what Neo can do.  I especially like a story that already has an established beginning and end, unlike most movie sequels and many TV shows which only tact on stories when needed. This allows for compelling storytelling such as foreshadowing, build-up, red herrings and plot twists. I believe that writing so far ahead requires and allows research that enriches the overall experience and story world. I enjoy discussing stories and discovering whatever meanings and little points that may be. I believe in respecting the effort that the author has taken in crafting the tale, especially in this age of instant entertainment, were it is experienced and discarded just as fast.  Lastly, I just love the concept of  urlLink The Matrix . It has alot of elements that I find intriguing and cool such as martial arts, oppressive machines, computers and it's programs, the human struggle against an overwhelming foe, mirror shades, the philosophy of realism, Plato, religious concepts and guns, lots of guns.  Yes it may be not as innovative as the first one but I'm enjoying every minute of it as it reveals the story to the climax in the upcoming movie, just have to hang on for the ride. For now, let me get back to work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a week it has been. Quite a fruitful school-break if you ask me. Managed to spend time with some of the guys, seeing as how their school terms have ended and they too are pretty much free at the moment. Of course all this going out and eating out is a drain on resources that I am trying to conserve. But seeing as how I'm only free, more or less, this week, I guess it's ok to indulge. Next week onwards I can let my bank, as well as my friend's pockets, take a break.    >   Noticed that my posts are always too damn long. If I post more regularly I guess I won't have this problem. Anyway, I shall focus on movies, in this case one in particular.  Caught  X-Men 2  early in the week and once again I am presently surprised as the franchise takes superhero movies in another step up. The first one re-introduced to people a type of comic book based movie that is intelligent, deep and mature.  This latest release in the series expands on that by balancing pace with characterization and yet allowing the key roles to shine. The actors do a better job here and now seem more comfortable and relaxed, even the new ones. This is a trend that I hope is maintained for the next round of movies.   Interestingly enough, all these new movies are all from Marvel, which is strange to me because the reasons that I seem to have that compels me to prefer DC comics over Marvel comics are the same as the ones stated above. Which makes one wonder how much better movies could be made from a DC license. But in the end I guess, it all depends on the writer and the director. However, it is not an easy job for them. Comic books usually have a lot of history and changes in them since they are such long lasting series. In some way I guess the writers are hampered by the history. What to leave in? What to throw out? And what to change?  I hope that this level of chair and respect for source material not only continue in movies for comic books but for any work based on another work from a different medium, be it books-to-TV or movies-to-computer games. Don't just follow, copy or port over blindly, but tell the hidden story, fill in the gaps, use what was thrown out. Respect the story in all it's forms and consumers will respect it as well.    >   I (of course) caught  urlLink The Matrix Reloaded  over this weekend. More than once actually. Will share some thoughts about it tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *sigh* After reading  urlLink  DebbieC   blog I really feel bad about not posting in so long. Really do deserve to be beaten about on the head for it. I mean I know I tell myself I only write when I have something really to write, but looking at my last few posts, well there is nothing really outstanding about them. They are not long essays on the decay of our world's moral fibre or things along those lines. They are simple observations at that point in time from a guy who just simply wants to share it with people. It is something that can be done at almost any point in time. So why can't I?  I guess everyone who has a blog has one point or another wonder about why we bother to try to update it. For me it's a little different. I know why I want to. But I wonder at why I don't do so. Is it some commitment thing? Not surprising coming from a guy, but I never thought I would have a problem in this area since one of my goals in life is to be comitted, for life, to someone. So why can't I be committed to such a simple thing as putting a few lines up here? If I can't even commit to this, how can I reach my goal?  It's not the first time I have started something and lost steam along the way. My first web site was abandoned after a month and left to rot for almost 6 years. I didn't even take it down until I moved the blog to this server. I have tons of unfinished stories and ideas for stories, incomplete designs...all flashes in the pan. I can't even complete a computer game from start to end anymore and books I blaze through in the fastest time possible, ignoring other stuff, only to set the book aside and never touch it again when I'm done.   Things need to change. And I'm glad I can see it.  But the focus shouldn't be just on me. Everyone who is committed to something should wonder..."why am I doing this? Is this what I really want? Or am I doing so out of obligation or resignation? If It is out of duty, then do I still believe in it?"  Knowing what we want is hard enough, reaching it is even harder still, but even if we take the first steps towards it, may we see it to the end, not only to the end of the goal, but to the end of our best that we put in it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Written on date 20030614:   I'm writing this as I sit in the cafe of my hotel here in Bangkok, awaiting breakfast on the second day of the trip. One of the things I enjoy the most while on these kinds of trips is the intercontinental breakfasts. I guess I have a soft spot for having orange juice with bacon and eggs in the mornings, something I don't do while at home. After this, we will be taking the "skytrain" to some other popular shopping complexes since we have already spend quite some time with the one next to our hotel.    >   Now I am just taking a short breather from exploring this huge department store. Feeling kinda sheepish, there is a larger verity of some items here that I was looking out for rather than at the place where I had already bought. Guess I need more experience in the art of shopping. I'll do better next time. Should learn from my mom, this trip after all is a business-shopping trip for her to stock up on her side venture.    >   The weather here in Bangkok can be summed up in a word: Hot. Throw in the dust, crowds and the constant heavy traffic and it becomes dreadful. Good thing that this trip is mainly a shopping expedition which allows us to be indoors some times. On the other hand, since it is a shopping trip, I have not gotten much photo ops. Will try to get more.    >   Back in my room at the end of the shopping day. Getting ready for bed soon. It has been great walking around, digging for bargains and exploring the night markets and so forth, but a part of me is looking forward to returning home, even if it is just to enjoy the spoils of the trip. Also the reminder that I have a project and two new school modules awaiting me, drives me to get them over, done and out of the way as fast as possible. Exam results, and so forth all have to be faced. Guess I got to make the most of the time I have here then, and look forward to enjoying the stuff I bought. Going for Jap-Korean buffet tonight, should rock…    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I just finished packing for my trip to Bangkok tomorrow morning. It’s just a short trip and I will be back on Sun(15/6).   Somewhat looking forward to it. It’s been awhile since I have been on a holiday out of town. Then again this should be concerned a working holiday since I will be helping to haul large loads of clothes for my mom’s home business. She mainly deals with female apparel but she’s looking into picking up some men’s stuff this time around. Anyone interested? Drop me a line. Maybe I can talk her into giving discounts :)  Another thing that has me excited is that this would be a great opportunity for me to make full use of my “new” digital camera. In fact, I remember making sure that I will get the camera especially for this trip. Will be sure to post some of the better shots when I get back. Really looking forward to getting some fancy and art shots over there. Will have to keep my eyes open.  Hoping to have a good time shopping. Clothes, games, little nick-nacks, anything goes. Of course I must remember to get some stuff for my friends as well. I know both  FeLee  and  LadyRaine  have made their requests quite well known.  *grins*  don’t worry guys, I won’t forget.  So until then…Have a good week and God Bless.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         finally got around to posting this up...         Click here to check out my online photo album    Opps..as of Feb 2004 I have stopped using the above link to host photos..so sorry    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      At least, not yet.  Even as I write this, I am still hacking away at the pile of work that I have had for this month, which consist of 3 projects plus 3 reports. All of which are not yet completely done. And they are all due within the next two weeks. I just seem to keep getting stuck whenever I focus on one, thus I have to keep jumping from topic to topic. The problem lies in that all three projects are based on some form of programming and to even start to code requires some time to learn the different languages and their quirks. Needless to say, it’s this learning curve as well as troubleshooting that have really taken up a lot of my time.   I’m afraid that I may not meet the deadline for the last project and I’m not sure what kind of extension, if any, I will get and what kind of grade penalty I’ll receive because of it.  *Sigh*  In any case, it’s all my own fault really. I think I spend too much time running into brick walls when it comes to my projects then stepping back and thinking about how to find another way around them and not feel frustrated. It’s strange. I am usually not the kind to be so incapacitated by my emotions. I’m usually in far better control over them. And yet I wonder where all the time as went. In the last 25 days I’ve only been out of the house 9 times. It’s insane. I put aside everything, all my other outside commitments and yet I still can’t do 3 simple projects.  *sigh*  this doesn’t bode well. If such a small workload is killing me, how am I going to handle real working conditions?    This is turning into a nightmare, and it may only get worse. If I do fail the module for the 3rd project because I miss the deadline, I don’t know what is to become of my course schedule, will they let me continue into next year course? or will they require me to wait until I retake the module, which is the problem since I believe the next time this module is conducted again is in next April.   Guess I just have to buckle down, ride the storm and put my nose to the grindstone. And after it’s over, I’ll have to take a nice long look at how I handle my emotions, my time and my responsibility to my work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      A little late with the update this week, so lets jump right into it.   Going through the news while listening to the  urlLink Black Eyed Peas  makes for an interesting read. Basically I have no longer the need to make one-off comments like I usually do. The soundtrack speaks for itself.  As we go headlong towards the anniversary of that faithful day that started it all and the faithful days that have followed it, it is easy to lose sight of common goals that we as a species I feel we should strive towards. As I look at the  urlLink night sky  this week, I ask myself how much better it would be if all the resources, human and otherwise, time and energy that we have been using recently to respond to as well as create, the various situations that we now are in, was directed towards that one goal. Or any other common goal for that matter. As long as it takes us away from ourselves and gives us something to work towards together. Yes indeed, how much better it would be.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Been putting in some time touching up some minor things in the blog. Formatting, updating links, re-configuring archives and so forth. Still looking into new hosting options and other blogging tools. Should I consider Blogger Pro? Or go for the web host and use Movable type? Also came across a new blog host/tool site TypePad. It looks very interesting, especially the photolog services.    >   Here are some links and reviews that I have come across recently.   Computers  Lots of news of the MSBlast virus going around. Wasn’t effected since I patch my windows often and have firewalls, e-mail virus guard and spam killer all standing by.    urlLink ZoneAlarm  and  urlLink Kerio  Two free firewalls out on the market. Although they may not be all powerful, it sure beats surfing naked through the Net. Learning curve on how to configure them may be abit high but once done, it becomes much less a nuance.   urlLink Pacific Internet Spam Guard  One of my local ISP’s new offering. Frankly speaking, I think all ISPs should integrate some form of spam filter for their customers, and not charge for it too. But it’s good to see the first steps taken over here.  urlLink  Mail Washer   Interesting little program. Checks your mail for you and shows you what could be spam based on a constantly updated list. And with a single click, you can blacklist other addresses that slip through. Once all the mail have been filtered, then only the “real” ones will be downloaded to your mail reader. Cute. Highly recommended.   urlLink Avant Browser  Combines the best of Mozilla and Internet Explorer. Makes surfing much faster and easier since it’s able to juggle many different windows at the same time. I would use it full time if it weren’t for one major bug. Still do give it a try. It’s free after all.   Entertainment   urlLink Television Without Pity  Funny website that does totally critical reviews of the latest television shows. Very useful if you miss an episode of your favorite show and want to catch up on what happened.   urlLink MegaTokyo  My latest webcomic craze. Beats out all expectations one would have gathered from other webcomics. Beautiful art and a truly multi-layered plot with romance, action and lots of humor that doesn't try to go for the joke of the day tactic. Only fans of anime and gamers need apply and please read the archives or be totally lost.  First site to beat the three link limit in the sidebar.    urlLink Megapixel.net  One of the first websites I came across while doing research on digital photography and what camera I should buy. Lots of breathtaking photos and in depth reviews of the not so latest cameras.   urlLink Friendster  The latest Internet fad, since the time of when ICQ first came out and the “six degrees of Kevin Bacon”. In fact, friendster is mainly popular because it combines the two together. Worth checking out and if so, do drop me a message :)  Lastly, I cleaned up and updated the link and information in the side bar. Take a look around. More updates soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Time:2:39am Mood: Much calmer and generally better than I have been in the last two weeks.    Been slowly moving back into attending to the things that I have been neglecting as of late and it's really quite therapeutic. It’s good to be able to kick back, address issues one at a time, and focus my attention. Guess I don't work well under pressure after all. Thought I would have that figured out by now.  And thus I now, once again, find myself at this time of the day, sitting in the dark bathed in only the illumination of my computer monitor. Except this time I'm kicking back writing this, a beer in one hand and changing CD-R's in and out of my computer while it is backing up all it's hard drives. Ahh...the Zen of living the digital life, who said beer and electronics don't mix? Just don't actually add the two together unless you want to find yourself in  Electric Dreams  .  But after so long, I still find myself suffering from that age-old holiday syndrome, where I still have to find for myself things to do or be bored out of my wits. One thing that I should do is catch up on my reading. I have these thick books to finish that are just lying around the place. Some of them are textbooks, so that’s most likely the reason why I’m so reluctant to get into them. Oh well, I will have to anyway, before things get busy again. Perhaps after I get done doing some packing that I also have been putting off, like equipment and clothing colored green…   *Yawn*  well the backup is going to finish soon, so I guess I’ll pack up here, get a nap and post this later in the morning. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally I'm able to let go of that which have been bordering me the whole of last month. However all is not well, for the outcome of the project is very much in question, not the kind of situation that one would like to be in at the start of one's holidays.   There are many reasons why I now find myself in this predictement, "I didn't have the proper background", "I had to learn it from scratch", "I had two other projects to handle". But, as it is for most of life's lessons, I am not without blame for putting myself in this spot. so, as it is for life's lessons once again, I will have to pick myself up again, and carry on.   Which of these is the good part or the bad part, I am unsure.   One thing is for sure though, as I approach the first anniversary of this blog, it looks like my plans to move to a new web host would have to be put on hold. Life lessons are rarely without a price, so finances are going to be tight for the next few months.  Something tells me that I should just focus on posting regulary.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Over the weekend, I had the fortunate experience of attending a virtual “Meet the author” book club meeting held in  urlLink Second Life .  urlLink Cory Doctorow , the author of “ urlLink Down & Out in the Magic Kingdom ”, was gracious enough to come in-world (although he doesn’t “play” Second Life) to give an interview and to field questions based on the ideas and topics raised and touch on in his novel.   I managed to read though the novel a day before the book club and I find it to be very much to my liking. It falls firmly in what I consider to be  CyberPunk , in which instead of technology being the basis of bigger and faster action like in  Star Wars  and  Star Trek , it uses technology to bring to light the essence, strength and overwhelming frailty of Human nature. I have nothing against both  Star Wars  or  Star Trek , but sometimes I just need a good dose of a more gritty type of science-fiction.  And what a concept the book paints, a world were reputation is currency, where death is defeated by “back-up” booths and forced-grown clones, where computers are implanted and all set against the backdrop of  Disneyland . Yet with all the technology, humans are still subjected to the roller coaster ride (if you pardon the pun) of emotions such as failure, disappointment, betrayal and boredom.  In the end the book comes highly recommended. If you like you can download a full copy of the novel from  urlLink here .  All in all one of the best events I have attended in  urlLink Second Life  in some time. Looking forward to the next one.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Right, on to the rest of the week (last week). A few days after the day spent with  Nigel , I met up with  MchWng , an old friend who incidentally is only free on school holidays even though she is working. And that’s when she’s not rehearsing for a new play. We don’t meet very often, sometimes once every 4 or 5 months.  I have to say that I was quite presently surprised when I saw her. First of all it was actually daytime and I didn’t know how “new” it made things seem.. usually we only meet for dinner and we were actually debating when was the last time we had met up and seen the sun.  Next, she was dressed more…casual than I’m used to seeing her in since she didn’t come down from school. It was a nice change.  We sat down for some waffles, chatted and later went for a walk down past the riverside. Apart from a call from  FeFe  asking questions as he was sitting opposite us during the waffles that threw me off, I had quite a nice time just hanging out. Truth to be told, its been a long time since I had an outing of this sort. However I do find myself somewhat more uneasy being around  MchWng  than before. I guess, it’s because we’ve known each other for almost 5 years and she has seen me in my bad times and my even worse times. She’s sorta like by  Aunt Agony . But I told myself sometime back that I shouldn’t just treat her as just that. As I have always taken issue with others taking my friendship and me for granted, I shouldn’t do the same to her. And since how that both our situations have changed recently, it’s like starting anew again. I guess that’s not so bad, but only if I get myself out of this funk and start treating her like everybody else and not as my  psychiatrist . I mean I don’t treat  FeFe  as my lawyer or  DaMan  as my doctor.   Perhaps we should break the 3-4 months per meeting routine…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a pretty interesting “holiday” week this past week. Actually it’s  Nigel  who is the one on holiday since I technically don’t get any unless you count those self-declared couple of days I try to squeeze in between modules when they are not overlapping.  Anyway, I was starting out the week pretty much the usual, studying and reading mostly, when  Nigel  gets the wild idea for us to find a network game to play to past the(his) time. He had just burned himself out on  Unreal Tournament 2003  (again) and therefore had the idea to give  Rise of Nations  another go seeing as how it is about the only Real-Time Strategy game that we both can actually stand to play ( Warcraft 3  so being NOT the one). So we sat on down and proceed to get our a$$e$ served to us in what turned out to be a 5 course meal.  Next day we decided to recover from our defeat by spending a nice quiet afternoon fishing, which turned out quiet nice actually. It had been a long time since I can just take in the sounds and the breeze of the sea. I had forgotten how much I had loved being on the top deck of the cruise ship I was on almost 5 years ago. Truly made for some conducive studying.  Pity  Nigel  had the misfortune of losing his fishing weight and hook…again. He would like to claim that he lost it in an epic battle of wills and determination between teen and fish, alas it was a simple really ugly miscast that snapped the line. Perhaps lighter weighs are in order…  In kindness and, well…pity, I took him to  Australian Outback  restaurant for some aussie style food. Of course before I go any further, I must submit a declaration that “I do know it is hardly comparable to Real aussie food but it’s the closest I can find over here” before my friends who are Down Under declare me a heretic and nuke my mailbox. Hey guys? If you want me to sample the real good food you guys get sent me the ticket and I’m there ok? ;)  In any case I was craving for a huge steak dinner and  Nigel  as been bugging me about the beaded mushrooms that I keep telling him about. So we sat down to two 28 ounces sirloin steaks, one grilled to a medium rare and the other well done. Followed by a bowl of hot breaded mushrooms with spicy ranch sauce. It’s so rare to have a nice civilized meal with my younger sibling without the toilet jokes and insults. I guess the endless refills for our huge drink mugs helped keep him pacified. I do wish we had spoke on more serious stuff than just in-line hockey and school but I guess we can save that for the next time.      I also had an interesting outing with someone else on “holiday” during the week. Will talk about it soon once I get my head to it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was talking to my friend  CC  from  urlLink Second Life  and she mentioned something that stuck me. Not so much so that it was surprising or unexpected, but in that it forces me to realize somethings that I may not want to.  She told me that from the first time that we had met, she had felt a sense of sadness from me and that she continues to feel it each time we talk and she was wondering about it.  Now I will not be so bold as to deny or agree with her straight off, but what really bordered me was that she was able to gather this sense through an electronic medium, from the other side of the planet, with nothing to go on but the words that I type, and to a lesser degree, the actions that I do in the Second Life world. You have to understand that no matter how realistic  urlLink Second Life  tries to be at times, the 3D avatars that are your stand ins when in-world do not perform any body language or show any emotion unless you want it to. And I’m sure I didn’t.   This lends to the second thing that disturbs me. If something whom I never even met face-to-face can detect it, what does it say about the friends that I have and do meet on a regular basis? Has this sadness become such a part of me that they can’t tell any difference anymore? Or they do know it but feel that they we are not close enough to me to talk to me about it, is my relationship with my friends that shallow? Either reason is something I would want to consider.  And lastly, it brings me back to the question Am I really sad? I will be the first to admit that I’m not completely happy with my current state in life, but then again, who is? Life needs a degree of bad times for us to appreciate the good times. True I may have been in instances where I have been badly hurt, but those times are neither uncommon nor recent. And I have been believing that I have been moving away from those times and carrying on with my life. Or is in the process of doing so. Read back the archives that show some part of the road that I had to take. But now this forces me to ask if I am really doing so. Am I still stuck in that rut? If so, have I once again wasted years of my life wallowing in something that I cannot change and even if I did, would the outcome be any better or different? If it is true then where is my faith? In things that would be better and good for me?   And to top it all off, I just had bought a new CD and I just took a look at the lyrics for a one of the tracks that caught my attention.      I'm so tired of being here Suppressed by all my childish fears And if you have to leave I wish that you would just leave 'Cause your presence still lingers here And it won't leave me alone  These wounds won't seem to heal This pain is just too real There's just too much that time cannot erase  When you cried I'd wipe away all of your tears When you'd scream I'd fight away all of your fears I held your hand through all of these years But you still have  All of me  You used to captivate me By your resonating life Now I'm bound by the life you left behind Your face it haunts My once pleasant dreams Your voice it chased away All the sanity in me  These wounds won't seem to heal This pain is just too real There's just too much that time cannot erase  When you cried I'd wipe away all of your tears When you'd scream I'd fight away all of your fears I held your hand through all of these years But you still have  All of me  I've tried so hard to tell myself that you're gone But though you're still with me I've been alone all along  When you cried I'd wipe away all of your tears When you'd scream I'd fight away all of your fears I held your hand through all of these years But you still have  All of me  (My Immortal by Evanescence)    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been scouring the Net for this book,  urlLink Plowing the Dark  by  urlLink Richard Powers . I heard that it is similar to  urlLink Snow Crash  by  urlLink Neal Stephenson  in that it talks about a virtual Cyberworld where people worldwide log-on to and interact with others and their environment in real-time.   I’m a big fan of Stephenson and of his peers,  urlLink William Gibson  and  urlLink Bruce Sterling . If you haven’t realized this yet, then you haven’t been looking around this website enough  *grins* . I remember reading most of their old stuff but never actually owned them until recently, (I think I dug them out of some corner in my primary school library or something like that) and would like to read Power’s take on this genre. Well it looks like I will have to access a library for a hardcopy of the book after all as I have not been able to find an e-book version.  Talking about the “Metaverse” or the on-line virtual world that is the basis of both of the books mentioned above, one should look into  urlLink Second Life . It is the closest form of a “real” virtual cyberworld I have seen yet. In fact, I have been participating in the beta test ever since I heard about it in April. In short, all I can say is that it is a very intriguing concept that uses state of the art technology. Being able to chat and interact with people all over the world in real-time and a realistic looking environment really brings to life all the ideas that one can imagine in being a virtual world where almost anything is possible. Events are constantly being held in-world, users buy land and build houses and shops, sometimes in a group as building in-world is done in real-time with everyone seeing the results at the same time. Users take a lot of effort to make their in-game avatars looking surreally like how they are in the real-world and even upload images to be made into clothing. Any fans of ICQ/IRC chat programs and enjoy messing with 3D design programs will totally feel at home there. If you do decide to take a look, remember to let them know that  urlLink I sent you .             urlLink       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Late update once again. I’ll really trying to keep to posting at least once a week and within 10 days at the most.   I really love the latest run of local newspaper columnists recently. Yet another thought-provoking article in the Life! Section last Tuesday. Speaks on a topic close to my heart. I know it is once again about relationships and talking about that can get old very fast. Heck even I’m sick of talking about it, but beats all the computer stuff that no one else cares to read or understand here right?  The said article talks about the Columnist’s experience and reason for wanting to remain friends with her ex boyfriend and she talks about why would she want to, why it’s something that more people should do and the obstacles she had to overcome. Now I would love to reprint the whole article here, but since I don’t have permission, I shall have to resort to just highlighting certain points that she made that I agree with and summarize it.  The writer notes that it is not easy going and requires “maturity, patience and several misfires”. She recalls that it was difficult when her ex had to run off on a date during an outing with mutual friends, how a hug or a pat on the shoulder can bring back painful memories but they “peter out over time”. But even with all this she carries on, in part due to the idea that past relationships help make one become stronger as a person and as an individual. Over advantages she notes includes being able to quiz him about what she did wrong so that she won’t make the same mistakes next time and how he can be used as a “pseudo Gay Boyfriend” in which with all the sexual tension over with, they can just “hang out without feeling self-conscious”. Lastly she muses over how her ex and she now swap testimonials on  urlLink Friendster.com  and that he remembers her birthday and sends flowers. She feels that they are more “saner” as friends and that everyone deserves a second chance.  I’m quite glad to see good writers on the payroll of my local newspaper. It’s good to see them being able to stretch their talents and speak on personal experiences as well. I’ve always had firm respect for journalist and this just reinforces it. Of course not everyone can be a Dave Barry, who is more humor based then anything, so it’s good to have a good balance of insight as well as whim.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I had an interesting chat on the phone last night. It was very good to hear her voice again. And, truth to be told, good that she was the one that called for I had resigned myself to the possibility that things were only going one-way down a two-way street for some time now.  It was a good chat. A lengthy one. And while she may have felt that she dominated most of the conversation, I didn’t notice, nor would I mind.  It went quite smoothly except for one awkward occasion. My fault really…it came from one of the few things that…well…I still don’t understand. But I must remember that  understanding  is not a prerequisite for  acceptance . Such is the way of most things in life. Of what is called   Faith  . We may not fully understand how electricity works, or how gravity works or even how God works. But all these are accepted. They are facts. Likewise when dealing with people. Especially when their actions, directly effected or used to effect, you.  It all takes time really. Just like so many things once again. I believe I may be limited in my thinking, that I’m not getting the big picture, that there is a piece of the puzzle missing in my mind. I don’t intend to dig up past issues, I’ve gone way past that, and may well be my biggest problem previously. No, I think I’m missing a current issue, and it’s my hope that when I do bare witness to it, everything will fall in place.  So are you seeing the big picture in the things and people around you? Or are you so caught up on your own limited view of issues?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It’s interesting to note how I seem to find the most profound articles in the newspaper nowadays. I have to say the column writers are an interesting bunch, when they are not trying too hard to be funny of course. But the ones in my local paper have been coming up with some thought provoking stuff recently.  Just last week there was a female columnist who was remarking about how most of her family and friends still consider her to be unwed even though she has been legally married for close to 4 years. Just because she didn’t hold a church wedding or a wedding dinner to go along with the signing of the papers. She was talking about how the Chinese wedding dinners especially, have become such as sideshow serving no other purpose other than to show off and to pacify external family members with free food.   I may not totally agree with all her points, I for one feel that a church wedding service is the bare minimum, but I do think she is on to something. Young couples nowadays have so many expenses to deal with, let alone to throw a dinner party that can go into the tens of thousands. Especially in the slow economy that we are all facing these days. I think that a series of small, intimate dinners with groups of people who actually know each other would be enough.  And today, another columnist wrote something that touched me as well. It seems like fairy tale-like lover stories do happen in real life: boy and girl meet, love at first sight, they go out, they have problems, they break up, apart they realize that they do need each other, they work out their own individual problems, they get back together, they get engaged.   On reading it, it started out as a reminder on how my own “fairy-tale” didn’t have a happy ending. But on the other hand, I’m really happy for the writer and his partner. To have worked things out and come out of it stronger gives much hope to others who are having problems or are afraid.  However the one thing that stuck me the most, was something that I too have said to others before. He wrote that the best way to find that someone is firstly to be happy being single, to be happy being alone. For if one tries too hard to search, one’s vision is easily clouded by one’s desire. But if you are truly happy being by yourself, you would be able to clearly see the good and bad points of the person and take them at their true value.  To have this written in a newspaper is sort of like saying that yes, there is still hope. Just hang in there and learn to be happy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *Whew* Just finished handing up the report for my module on Broadband Commuications. Thats the reason for the lack of updates this past week and a half. You know...I really got to give some fair warning before I dissapear like that. Otherwise the people who do read this (mainly digital crickets I think, but hey...you never know) would think I'm just irresponsible and lazy. And I wouldn't want that now do I?  On a related note. I got back the results for my three project modules. The big surprise is not the good grades that I got for the first two, but the fact that I didn't fail the last one as I had expected. Frankly speaking I would have failed myself if I was doing the grading, but failling that module might have derailed my entry into the final year of my degree for as much as 9 months. Now that I have scrapped through on a passing grade, there should be no delay.  I am totally grateful for this unexpected blessing...best of all its just all the more reason to celebrate!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now Usually I’m one who takes some time to get into the Holiday Spirit. Which is strange, for this time is usually the busiest, what with Church events to help out in, cards to write, shopping to do and Christmas dinners to eat. But over the years, I find that I only start feeling it at the last minute. Therefore there is always a rush to write cards and gift shop and then…it’s all over too soon.  I guess part of the reason why I’m so Scrooge ( Bah! Humbug!)  about holidays at times, is that I somehow always found it lacking in some way. Must be the romantic in me that has this set vision of how Christmas should be and of course it never turns out like that. One year in particular was nearly perfect, but only served to raise the standard, so to speak, that only make the following years feel even less pristine.  But now we come to this year, and somehow the old holiday spirit is kicking in extra early. And so I sit here and ponder why. Maybe it’s the really cold weather that we seem to be getting over here this year. Been doing a lot of sitting in front of my window studying as of late, with the chilly breeze a constant companion. So much so that it drives me to distraction with illusions of Winter and of such. Another reason could be because a friend was sharing their enthusiasm for the holiday, complete with tree decorating ideas and gift buying plans. Or it could be that I’m so sick of having exams cut so deep into the holidays that my mind would wander across rivers just to find something to occupy itself with rather than the topic at hand.  But like the plot for any tragic character, it so happens that this is the rare time where I actually  want  the spirit to kick it late. Mainly because I want to focus on said exams and furthermore, I’m flat out broke. So all these ideas and holiday urges… I can’t act on them!   Frustrating I tell you.  Here’s hoping your festive plans are doing better. Season Greetings.       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been once  hell  of a week. And I mean it that way. Really, one hell of a week. Worse one I had in more than a year, even worse than that time I was rushing that Visual C++ programming project. The problem lies with some details about my degree course final year that I would be starting next year. It’s all my fault really, and I’m not pleased with myself for making such a big mistake. I already don’t think very highly of myself, no need to actually go out there and make it come true! In any case, I’m hoping very hard that this issue can be resolved soon.  On top of that, I have to go and  lose  my waist pouch with both my handphone and Sony Clie in it. Made a police report and everything, but I guess whoever found it, was not nice enough to return them. Can’t say I blame him, it takes the best of us of turn down a free handphone and PDA. But nevertheless, it is the right thing to do. Guess not everyone can place himself or herself in the position of the other person who has lost it. In any case, to whoever it was who “ found ” my stuff, if you’re somehow reading this: enjoy your windfall, cause you’ll get what’s coming to you, someday. Oh and I hope you found a way to charge the Clie, the sucker drinks batt power fast.  Thankfully, my parental unit (i.e. Mom) still has her old Motorola V60 lying around, so I’m using that for the time being. Unfortunately it’s going to take some time to get used to the different interface. Some of the Motorola interface is quite troublesome, or perhaps I’m just too spoilt on Nokia.  So with the need for a new phone pushed down the priority list, the next in line would be the PDA. So digging into my savings, I sprang for the new  urlLink Tungsten E  from  urlLink palmOne . It’s the most value for money handheld that they have and after using it for a few days, I’m very pleased with it. Just wished I had gotten it under better circumstances. Now with my savings drained, looks like I’ll have to wait longer for that  urlLink Creative Nomad . Or anything else for that matter. Hope my old player can hold out that long.   So a gentle reminder to myself is in order, always check your stuff, don’t be careless and don’t take what you have for granted.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally got around to putting up some additional pages for the blog. It's quite a big step. After one year, this is no longer just a one page blog. It's now a full website with blogging features of course.  In anycase, I put up the  urlLink Writings  section with one story for a start. I'm looking it fill it up with some stuff over the next few weeks. Hopefully it would look filled out before the start of next year where things really get busy for me over here.  In any case, if anyone got feedback on the stories, feel free to drop me a line.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quick note. Have two tests staring me down this week which are delaying me from putting up the new pages to the site for my writing section and so forth. Will get them up as soon as I'm free from study.  Been spending time with   Da Man   and   Nigel   over the last week. One is out of leave, which is always a momentous event with his work schedule, and the other is out on school holiday. Being a good friend and brother, I felt it was only right that I make some time out from studying to spend time with them. In fact, I was with them on the first show for the Matrix Revolutions on opening day.  Speaking of Matrix Revolution, I will need to post up my views and full review of it and the Trilogy as a whole. The critics and peer reviews have been really bad and scalding. While I do think it is a little disappointing, nevertheless it is a must see at the very least as a form of closure and a fitting end to first movie.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Feeling kinda chipper today, which of course is unusual knowing me. Factor in that I have been playing  urlLink Max Payne 1 & 2 , in which good things like falling in love is made bad and the bad things made, well...worse, it’s a wonder why I’m so hyped up.  One of the major reasons is, of course, that  urlLink Matrix Revolutions  opens in less than  urlLink 22 hours  and counting. Finally the best movie trilogy to come around since  urlLink Star Wars  comes to an end. And I’m pretty sure that The Matrix will have the same impact on future methods of storytelling and on pop culture that it had.  Other factors include, the shiny new floor of my room. No more decayed looking carpet and thus much more travel when rolling from end to end in my chair. It also helps to improve the acoustics of the room and as a sound guy, that’s something I can appreciate.  I have also recently finished a   short story  , my first one in years. It’s been a really long time since I’ve written anything but it kinda came to me one night last week. After much prodding from some friends in  urlLink Second Life , I finished it in very short order. Right now, I’m looking into adding a page to this blog to host it, so look for it when it’s officially up.   All in all I have to say it’s been a pretty good week. Just wish I didn’t have two tests waiting in the wings of next week, otherwise I could start another short story, poem or fictional story universe. The writting bug seems to have bitten. At least I don’t have to worry about my reservist call up, I got everything already packed anyway.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been a fun holiday season that is now fast coming to a close. Christmas eve was stressful but the marathon session of  urlLink Chez Geek  afterwards more that made up for it.  Christmas morning was quiet, with visits to immediate family (whom we always have to visit as soon as possible during any major holiday, hence the name) and some small gift exchanging. Got a metal CD case from Mom, nice considering that I don't use CD's anymore, oh well, should be good to store harddisk backup CDs I guess. Boxing day was spent across the border with the highlight being the off-road biking tracks and the outdoor bath. The bath was a refreshing experience, at night; one can really feel like part of nature. It reminds me of my NS field camp but with better soap.  Since returning, I’ve been busy getting things ready for start of the new school year. The timing is a little off this year so it looks like some school shopping is still in order. Stuff like note-taking paper and the sort. Wish I could go paperless this year and pick up that  urlLink wireless keyboard  for my  urlLink Tungsten E , but that would depend on how much note taking there is going to be. Hopefully I won’t have to sit next to a power supply to keep my  urlLink Tungsten  juiced while typing.     >    And so it brings us right to today. Had a nice quiet lunch with  AbglCh  who is back in town on break for just a month. I was happy to be able to catch her on the day she came back but plans fell through and after which the rest of her friends and family caught up to her. So we did meet up today, but she was feeling somewhat under the weather and thus couldn’t stay long. Pity really. She is fun to talk to, is funny and is the best source for finding out how living in the US is really like. Hope to be able to meet up with her again before she goes.  All in all, a pretty good way to end off 2003. So lets all raise our glasses in the air and say:  “Hooray for the New Year! We into it without any Fear!”   Heh.   Have a good one people.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
          May your day be bright, the company to your delight Let not your belly be empty, or your eyes filled with envy, at the presents oh so shiny, given out by your parents or your auntie. Instead let your Spirit take flight, to the Joy that is the Light, and may in your mind this day be famous, and never forget this Christmas!       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of my most found childhood memories involves sitting outside the gate outside my house at the time (before I was living in an apartment). I was sitting there reading a book, which the title I cannot now remember. I was happily reading when I noticed the darkening sky. Distracted, I stopped to watch the clouds move overhead, increasing in number, dark shapes slowly moving across, driving the light away as they go.  The wind had picked up while the clouds moved, seemingly, into position in the sky. I could see the trees swaying, leaves desperately trying to hand on to their branches, their very lifeline. Of those that had failed, they were scattered across the ground, marking the very passage of their bane, allowing the invisible to be seen.   Suddenly all was still, the wind a fading memory. The dead leaves were still, the very emptiness deafening in their silence. Slowly an echo is heard, then more, increasing in number and tempo, like a marching army approaching. Looking down the road, I see a wave of raindrops coming towards me, leaving a trail of slick in their path. Glancing in the other direction, I saw that it was still dry, yet untouched by the oncoming onslaught.  Mesmerized, I stay where I am, vulnerable book still in my lap and let the rain overrun me. After which, I set the book aside, it’s lines wrinkled, and took a long slow walk down the road, becoming one with the rain.  Since that day I had a new appreciation for the weather, rainstorms in particular. I know no other greater example of the beauty and awesome power of the Creator. But yet, it’s been a long time since I have walked in the rain, or when I am forced to, to enjoy it. Now I’m afraid for the items that I carry on myself and how the rain may spoil them, or likewise even for my appearance.  How I long for those carefree days to enjoy the rain. And I am sadden by the fact that it is my ownself and the things that I take on that prevents me from enjoying one of the greatest experiences in the world.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man time does fly. It’s already been 10 days since I last posted. This last month of what turned out to be quite an interesting year is just pasting me by. I have to admit that I’m a quite sad to see it go. Although I may have not been able to accomplish all that I had set out for myself to do this year, I have enjoyed it; even with all the unexpected ups and downs.   Speaking of unexpected ups…I had the delight of attending a secondary school classmate’s wedding dinner over the weekend. It seemed like a school reunion with all the old familiar faces showing up, although there were many that were…missed.  I find it unfortunate that I was not able to catch up as well as I would have liked with everyone who was there. I guess one reason was that huge dinners like these are not really conducive to speaking what with all the eating going on. Or it could be that I was constantly interrupted with discussion of my “antics” in the good ole days. Regardless, it was all agreed that we never thought that our schoolmate in question would be one of the first to get married. Time flies indeed.      >     Holidays are here again and it’s good to be able to kick back and enjoy it. Lord knows that things are going to be ramped up come next year, so I had better enjoy this one as much as I can. While I do have some major items to look into the next few days, I’m looking forward to about 2 solid weeks of festive celebrations, complete with shopping, outing and Christmas right smack in the middle of it.  I plan to make it a good one. Cheers! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Figured it was time to do some restructuring of this place, so I was slowly going over the source codes last night. Decided that a good first step would be to try to make the place compliant with the HTML 4.01 Transitional standard and eventually work towards XHTML transitional compliance. So that means removing some tags and replacing some with another tag that basically does the same thing. It’s a good thing because I intent to keep this site around for sometime and even when I do move to my own web host, it’s going to use some lines of code from here as a reference so it’s good to start planning for the future. Besides, I need a reason to practice what I learnt during my website creation module earlier this year, although all I really learnt was focused on XHTML and just a little bit on scripts using  .jsp  and  .asp .  Speaking of website scripts, I’ve added some links to more blogs as well as removed some dead ones. One of the new blogs, is from  urlLink Beverly , who is one of the few females I have come across who is a wiz at the  Perl  scripting language. I know I’m generalizing but there doesn’t seem to be many females who are good or even like to code. I know I have met some in  urlLink Second Life , and I’m sure there are a fair even share of female graduates from computer based degrees that can code well, but to actually like it? Now that’s rare I think. And brings me to the question:  Why can’t I meet more girls like that??!! .  It’s saddens me to think that while I do know  C  and  C++ , I can’t say that I’m good at them and my frustration at the whole programming process is sapping any joy that I used to derive from writing code. That being said, I should learn  Perl  as well as  .Net . Maybe I should ask  urlLink Beverly  the best way to get started on them.  Another blog, I’ve added is from a fellow “ practitioner ” of the fabled art of    urlLink Palm  Fu  ,  urlLink Gordon . I actually know more “ practitioners ” in the  urlLink group  I used to run around that  urlLink Gordon  is also a part of but I seem to have lost touch with them. Oh well.  urlLink Gordon  is a fun and loud character to trade “fixes” with but he does have his soft side as seen in his blog.  And lastly,  urlLink Tamara . I have lost touch with her many many years ago and it’s a testament to the usefulness of things like  urlLink Friendster.com  to reconnect with long lost friends. In this case its especially meaningful cause  urlLink Tamara  did play a signification role in a point of my life. I guess I can call her a   Childhood Sweetheart  . She’ll probably smile at that. But now she has far better things to smile about for she is recently engaged! My most heartfelt congratulations to her and to her husband-to-be. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Continued from Part 1     Snapping up the magazine, I learned that Sequencers are the heart of the digital studio (of course the computer it is running on is equally important) in the sense that it also involves recording, adding effects and even EQing and final mix-down. In other words, almost like a full studio that music producers use.   Immediately my thoughts turned towards my  church  audio setup and how a program like this could  benefit  it. With talk of doing recordings, a Sequencer plugged into the hardware mixer would be able to record the whole session into the hard disk and then allow a whole range of post-recording work such as adding effects and cleaning up some of the tracks to be done before mixing down and burning from the computer’s CD burner. Now that’s at the most basic, but going a little deeper, individual instrument tracks could be recorded and burned out on it’s own for…lets say a new guitarist who is trying to  learn  the songs? Could burn for him/her a CD containing just the guitar parts for various songs all played by the current guitarist, which they can take home to listen and practice at home. And this could be done for every instrument (with exception of the drums since it’s not miked up).   Another area would be the Sequencer’s ability to take classical music notation and display it a MIDI overview for play back and study. It can even take notes inputted from a MIDI keyboard and change it to classical music notation, which can then be printed out for distribution. This would be very useful for music  composition .   With all this very interesting ideas, it would be good to find out how much actually obtaining it would be. But even this was hampered by the fact that audio software doesn’t seem to be sold off the shelves here. Therefore I was forced to email the local distributors requesting for price lists. Looking at the prices online in US$ and Euro, the price ranges from a little over 1K for the high end products, above $500 for the mid-level and around $300 for the entry-level stuff which are limited in certain areas such as the lack of the ability to handle classical notation. All it all, it kind of reminds me of the price difference between levels in most personal electronic devices such as handphones, PDAs and digital cameras.   In the meantime, I just settle with learning from the demo versions, and about the other types of audio software such as soft synths were one can create new sounds and sample mixers where bits of different audio samples are mixed and tweaked to form complete tracks. Useful for when one feels creative and would like to actually have a finish product to actually listen to and enjoy and even distribute to others.  Phew! There is so much more I can talk about this, but I already had to spilt this into two posts and I’m learning more each time. Guess I better end here. But I shall leave some links if anyone wants further information or if anyone knows more about all this, I’m all ears for tips and new areas to discover…who knows? Maybe in a few months time, I could have some of my own stuff to post up here. Just hope I don’t end up cranking out the usual techno crap.   Links:  General guides and information  urlLink Tweakheadz   High-level Sequencer   urlLink Steinberg Cubase SX 2.0   Entry-level Sequencer  urlLink Cakewalk Home Studio 2004   Loop-based live performance software mixer  urlLink Ableton Live 3.0   Software Studio  urlLink Reason 2.5    Free software studio  urlLink Buzz machines   Leading Magazine  urlLink Computer Music  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Very late post again. Meh.  Guess since this was so late, i shall make it a long one. Might just occupy one enough until the next one.  What I have been busy with over the last week or so, is research into my latest hobby/fad/craze. Yes yes, I know you have heard it all before. Like whatever happened to all those photos that I was to take with my digital camera? Well I do take them, just haven’t really gotten around to finding a good place to host all of them. Not to worry, the camera is still being put to frequent use. On top of that, the research is not just for selfish reasons, as I will explain later.  It all began with an  urlLink article  I came across in  urlLink Wired.com  middle of last year. It spoke about how this “world-famous” (only if you like techno I gather since I have never heard of him before) DJ was using Mac G4 laptops and, in particular, software called “ urlLink Ableton Live ” in his sets. I found it interesting that software had reached a point where techno music composers where using it, but then again, they have always been known for using sounds from almost anything that beeps into their stuff. Since I don’t like techno, it didn’t arouse my curiously that much, on top of that, it was running on a Mac (not that I have anything against Macs…oh wait, I do…) which are way out of my price range. So I made a quick link to the  urlLink Ableton  website but didn’t visit it then and, of course, I promptly forgot about it.   Fast forward to late November, and I was just going through my favorites links folder when I came across the link to the  urlLink Ableton  website. I said “what the hay!” (Cause I felt like horsing around) and visited the website. I took a tour of the features of the Live software and listened to the samples of what it could do. In short, I was totally blown away. I never knew that audio software had reached such a level (and best of all it has a PC version) and could be such a factor in what I always thought was dominated by hardware. So I grabbed a download of the demo version tried it out a few times and once again forgot about it. This time school distracted me, so that’s not really such a bad thing. But the software had made an impression on me and I told myself that I had to go back and look deeper into it when I have the time.  Late December, always a busy time of the year, and I was presented with News that I was to fully take over the handling of the  Audio and Sound Ministry  in  Church . Scary. But that’s the case for any increase of responsibility, just have to take it and run with it the best you can. First thing that came to mind was how to improve on what we already have, of course first focus was on how to make full use of the hardware we already have, but my thoughts turned towards the software side and what better time than now to find out what is really out there that can help. Boy was I not prepared for what I would find.  After searching the Net for sometime (finding dead ends at all the Djing and beat mixing sites) I came across  urlLink this site , which focused more on the recording, composing, editing and producing areas of music. Very much more my can of coke. But going through the “guides” and reviews, I was overwhelmed by the load of information. There seemed to be different categories of software involved, combined with obscure hardware modules and its own brand of jargon that is not really explained. Usually stuff like this is no problem for me, I mean I find it equally relaxing and entertaining going over the rules and concepts of RPG books and reading a normal novel. And anyone who knows RPGs know the sheer amount of jargon that goes along with that as well.  So even as I went through the information put forward in the website and in the accompanying forums, I decided to keep a look out for other sources of information. A chance visit to  Tower Records  at Suntec, because  Da Man  wanted to buy the “ Love Actually ” soundtrack to go along with his “ Love Actually ” screenplay novel (it’s strange how I completely blew past the hype surrounding the movie, I guess my romantic spirit has taken a more cynical and less naïve outlook on relationships), had me stumble across the magazine section, where I came across the  Digital Music Maker  series of special edition magazines that focus on one particular software at a time. In this the first issue, the focus was on  urlLink Steinberg Cubase SX 2 , which from my research is said to be one of the most popular and well-known software Sequencers currently on the market.    Continued in Part 2  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's a sample of the various birthday "well wishes" I heard over the course of the day:  "It's your birthday again? Man that was fast..."  "Dude! Happy 23! Enjoying the good life?"  "Err..I'm 25 now" "Really!? wow...that sucks..."  "Welcome to the downhill slope towards 30!"  "Quarter of a century already. So what have you done with your life?"  "So you are now on the wrong side of the twenties like I am. Enjoy!"  ..Sigh..
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once again, the one thing I am reminded to learn from the start of this new year, is not to take things for granted. Time is not kind to any of us and if we are not careful, it can overwhelm us, overtake us and leave us alone and bewildered.  Take a good look in the mirror of your heart and soul and realize that you should not take yourself for granted. If there is something you see there that you don't like, take steps to change it. If you don't see anything wrong, then challenge yourself, upgrade or start something new. Take a chance.  Take a good look at the people around you, putting off that outing? Haven't spoken to in months? Pick up the phone, buy that lunch. Especially for the people overseas of which I'm sure we know many. The long months can be brutal.  Take a good look at one's family, there are there for a reason. We are to learn alot from them, one way or another and don't just remained focused on the ones near you. Be thankful for extended families. Do not be content on seeing them just once or twice a year.  And lastly, remember those that are no longer with us. Smile in the memories that we have, but use them to move forward to the future. Take what we have learnt from them and put them into use. The best way to honor their memory.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Major update time again. I keep saying that if people where to complain more about me not updating this, I’ll be all the more driven to do so. This does not seem to be the case this week with  IrsSm  being the one to make noise about it. Maybe it’s just her :)   Nahh..just kidding. It’s good to have readers again. Yes all three of you. Once again I have to tout the usefulness of  urlLink Friendster , however, while for most it allows them to make new friends, for me it seems to be more limited to catching up with old ones. Not that I’m complaining of course. I have always been more concern with losing old ones than making new ones.     >    Finally closed the deal with  urlLink Nigel , he is now a proud owner of a  urlLink Sony Ericsson T610 , while I have a freshly signed new 2 year contract with  urlLink M1  and have taken over his 9 month old  urlLink Nokia 6610 . For those of you who think that I have been dealt the short end of the stick here…  …you’re right. But it’s all good.  urlLink Nigel  cares far more for handphones than I. To me they are simple communication devices. I leave the personal assistance, information and entertainment applications to the far more capable  urlLink Palm OS PDA . But to him (and many others I’m sad to say) it is the one-stop portal to social contact and iconic status symbol. Therefore the more things they can fit inside, the more things he can make it do and the lesser he has to pay for all of that, the happier he is. Me, I’m happy as long as people can contact me when I want to (and even when I don’t want to), I have good call reception, able to fire off an SMS when the thought strikes and have good standby battery life. I have no need for a sub-standard camera in my phone and  Bluetooth  is only useful if my PDA is equipped with it as well (which it is not at the moment).  Bottom line. I believe that devices should be made for a specific purpose and made to do it well. Then people can mix and match what devices they need to carry around according to the situation instead of being forced to carry one device that can do everything, but not as well, and be put at the risk of not being able to use any of the functions if the one device where to malfunction or (horrors!) run out of battery.    I hope to see in the future a device that is no more than a battery compartment that acts as a  ‘skeleton’  that the user can plug various ‘modules’ into as the user sees fit. For example, going on an outdoor trip? Then plug in the 5 megapix camera module to take pictures, the screen module for viewing the pictures that you take and to show the GPS location, the GPS module so you don’t get lost, a memory module to store your pictures and a software module containing the GPS software, maps and outdoor survival todo list. Just going to the zoo instead? Swap out the GPS module for the MP3 player module with the headphone jack.  Simple. But knowing the device companies, they will take years before they agree on a standard interface for the modules and the software that controls them all (even though the Palm OS would do well in this area).  Oh well, one can only hope I guess.     >  Other updates to take note. My  urlLink MIDI controller keyboard  that I got off  urlLink Ebay  arrived today. Haven’t had the change yet to test it out though. And I have been approached to DJ for the  urlLink Second Life  Internet radio station called “ urlLink SLive ”. More news on these later but first it’s back to the books to study for my test this Sunday. Stay tuned.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      How did I spent my V/F/S Day evening? Watching   JnY   play  urlLink Gunbound  on one of the computers in Church.  Somehow I got nothing to complain about.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Never really one to follow the Lunar calendar, I am however tickled that this is the year of the monkey. I mean, who would name a year after such a chaotic creature due to the very fact that they are the smartest animal around? (arguably the smartest if you take humans into account...actually now that I think about it...) Or maybe it's because I just find monkeys funny. Well whatever the case it seems to me that you're just asking for trouble if you call anything "monkey". I'm pretty sure even the monkeys take offence at it.  In light of this, the Chinese New Year celebrations passed without much trouble or fanfare. Other than the fact that it is exceptionally early this year. Not that I'm complaining of course. Celebrate the New Year twice in the same month? No Problem! Not that I would actually go out and party...that would be so unlike me.  At the end of it all, I realize that I should spend more time with my cousins. I seem to learn something new from them every year. Simple exchange of information that would point me towards a useful resource or idea, I hope to make sure that I'm able to give a useful piece of advice myself each time.  Speaking of spending more time with people, I'm finally settling down and getting to know my fellow coursemates.Of course there will always be the odd cliche here and there but all in all it's a pretty good group. Of note is the fact that more than half of them are forgien students, mainly from Indonsia and Malaysia, which means I'm actually exposed to different cultures and countries without having to go study overseas like I originally planned. Not bad. I hope to be able to get to know them better for we all may not continue taking the same modules throughout the whole year.  As the schoolwork piles up and the projects, assignments and tests approach, I will have to start focusing more firmly on them. This does not bode well for my new interest in Computer Music and production for it also requires a substansial amount of time to be invested in overcoming the learning curve. Oh well, we will have to see how it goes. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally updated the  urlLink Writings  page with a work in process and some other ideas that I have flying around in my head. Currently working on   The Cure   in between whatever free time I got between studying and assignments. But I think it would be good to gather some feedback on what story to work on next after I’m done with this one. All the better to plan ahead with. Lord knows I need it. Would like to focus on trying a hand at making music using the digital tools at my diposoal, but it seems to be a far more time consuming method of expression, so I'm not totally eliminating writting for fun.   Anyway go to the  urlLink Writings  page and check out the short synopsis for each story and let me know which one you would like to read more about and I’ll focus on that one. Feel free to use the comments link below.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       quick update   Guess I spoke too soon. I logged in into SecondLife this morning, bumped into my friends and they were able to talk me through testing my setup on the test radio server. I was one of the easiest thing ever and soon they could hear my Winamp playlist going and even my mike setup seemed to be fine, maybe a bit loud but thats better than being too soft.  Now armed with my password and login, I'm all set to start Djing, all thats left is to find and book a good time slot. Easier said than done with the time difference and my oncoming workload. Just have to play it by ear, pardon the pun. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       sigh.  Looks like the DJing gig for  urlLink Slive.net  in Second Life is dead in the water. It’s been increasingly difficult to meet up with the people who run said station to discuss details. I would like to conduct it as soon as possible in order to circumvent the assignment deadlines and tests to study for that are pilling up this month. Oh well, at least I got permission to play songs by  Pension State  if I ever do get the gig. Thanks PS guys.     >    Right. I’m going to speak on a topic that would most likely alienate half of the people who read this (yes that’s the two of you). But I’ll try to bring it back onto something that would actually make sense to “normal” people.  Now everyone I know whom actually cares, have played and completed the hit PC game,  urlLink Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic . All the votes are in, the hype spread and the Game of the year awards handed out and yet I uninstalled it over the weekend to free up the huge amount of disk space that it takes up. Uninstalled that is, uncompleted.  Now this is not to say that I’m lazy in completing the games I play, I did pay $50+ for my copy of  urlLink SW:KOTOR  and I did complete  urlLink The Sands of Time . Instead, this about how although I find it a fantastic game with a fantastic story, it just didn’t capture the “spirit” of what I look for when it comes to  urlLink Star Wars .  I’m not one of those die hards that stick only to the movies in the face of all the extended material but I guess, for me,  urlLink Star Wars  is more about the characters and the actions that they did in the movies, than the whole   “universe with jedi and lightsabers and the Force”.   I would like to play/read something that not only is fully based in the  urlLink Star Wars  world as seen in the movies, but also has references to the main characters, their actions and even their future and history.  So in terms of the game  KOTOR , there are just too many things that seem different and even “break” the history that has already been establish during the movies. There are a few bright spots where they detail some history mentioned elsewhere but these are too few to hold my interest at least. I still stand by what everyone else is saying about how good it is, but while I don’t think I would be replaying it, I do have one request to the developer of the game. Give me a  urlLink Star Wars: NJO  game already and make sure there is interaction with the characters from the series and situations that took place.  Now how does all this geek goodness relate back to “normal” stuff? I guess it’s a call to take a closer look at your favorite books and television shows and perhaps play more attention to the stories and characters about why the writers make them the way they are and go through the things they do. It will be no longer a matter of who they are and what they do that is cool, but why they are that way and why do they do that that becomes the center. While it may take up more time and more interaction than normal, I’m pretty sure you will find your level of enjoyment of the series of books or show will increase. And if you’re already a fan, how can that be a bad thing?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been more than a week since the collapse of Nicoll Highway over here at what marks to be the first major disaster of the year. I’m not sure about the rest of you guys, but over the last few years I noticed that there will always be an incident that "marks" the year in our memories (and of course the media doesn’t help) and sometimes there will be a mark for the first half of the year, and another in the last half, sort of like a way to distinguish how the year in question moved from bad to worse, or from bad to better.  I’m sure all the advertising, media and sociologist reoriented people are interested in finding out the factors that contribute to having people collectively remember a subject in identical terms that is then linked to form an opinion of another, but that’s beyond the scope of this post (or my brain of that matter). You know, I think there actually is a term for this kind of "massively inducted memories". Someone care to enlighten me?  As mentioned above, the last few years have had their fare share of incidents that has affected lives here, but this one for this year is different. While the previous ones such as less people traveling and health awareness because of SARS and bird flu have had a direct effect on our economy, the Highway incident is something more inconspicuous and yet the effect could be more long-lasting. In this case, it affects the infrastructure.  While the closure of the highway is at best a minor inconvenience many, especially in the east, felt its effect. This only hints at what possible widespread effect could occur and how fragile our infrastructure actually is. The possible problem is further cascaded with the incident affecting the whole new MRT line, with the project being held up indefinitely as safety checks and new plans are drawn up. While not having the new line itself is not much of a problem, the fact that all the construction that has already been started would be left open and thus compound the weakness of the infrastructure for a much longer period. For the very nature of building something, dictates that the item in question lies in a weaken state until it is completed.  I guess we can only hope and pray that the situation is still under control and that we would not be caught in this "limbo" while it drains our reserves and undermines our infrastructure. The circle line MRT project was perhaps pushed too hard. Maybe more restraint is needed. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm. Now this is kinda interesting. As a long time user of blogger I have just been given my own  urlLink Gmail  account from Google. Of course this is the very same Gmail service thats been making the rounds in the Tech news because of the 1Gig worth of email space as well as the controversial google supported ads appearing along the side bar that are based on your emails. In other words, the system would scan ones email that is stored in the servicel and then show advertisments that match keywords found in the emails, thereby creating personalized advertisments which some people feel is an invasion of privacy.  I'm all up to testing it for a couple of months in this close beta testing period. I have already listed it here on this blog as the email address to contact me with and I have forwarded my secondary email accounts to it. However, I'm reluctant to forward my main mail account to Gmail, for the simple fact that most of my mail is spam anyway due to using it to subscribe to too many mailing list and newsletters over the past 7 years. Really should have gotten a secondary account for all that back then.  Quite pleased that I managed to get an account, I remember being one of the first testers for Google back when they we still in beta. Always had a soft spot for Google since then. It does help that they are now the search engine of choice.  All in all...this should be quite interesting to see how things turn out. The only problem I forsee is that I somehow forgot to change the default Gmail email address given and now I can't change it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heh. Pardon the pun of a title. But yeah, I just finished my most dreaded Advance Database exam yesterday. No more having to deal with lost updates again. Hopefully.   Speaking of which I am somewhat surprised that I actually found it to be not as terrible a paper that I thought it would be. As I walked out of the exam room, I had this uneasy feeling that I must have done something wrong, because it just didn’t register to my mind and fit what I expected it to be.  I have had this sensation before, but never this profound before. Once again I’m reminded of how much someone upstairs must like me. Once again it’s not by my strength but by His. I should never forget this one fact.  So now it’s on to a well deserved break. Will be looking to updating here more often. Got lots of thoughts I should be putting up here. If I can remember them all that is.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      *bleah* long long gap between updates.  I just finished up a round of two tests and a mega irritating assignment. Still got one more assignment to finish up by mid-week then I'm all done and can settle down for a short break over the Easter weekend.  Really wish I could have spent more time studying for my tests than working on the assignment most of the time. Looks like I won't be getting those A's like I did last year. Funny how back in poly my final year was the best year for me, and not in just grades. Oh well, whats done is done. Must focuson the exams next.  And thats all I got to say about that. I really got to stop talking about school and work so much. I mean I'm sure no one wants to read about that. Thats why I have always used "selective posting" and only post when I feel there is something to discuss and not the boring daily drudge. For thats what my life is like mostly, a boring daily drudge and thats never interesting to read about.     >    Ok. On to the good stuff.        urlLink Trillian (and Trillian Pro)         - For quite some time now the trend has been not to stick to just one IM but to have several open at one time. The point of them taking up too much CPU processing is a moot point now with high-end CPU processors at an all time low. Nevertheless I like having all my contacts in one place and not having to jump between program windows. In this case, I can't say enough how about how good Trillian in in this aspect. Only one contact list for all my contacts, a standardized message window, being able to write more than one line in MSN and no more ICQ ads and useless buttons from both. Recently upgraded to the pro version and I'm falling in love with it all over again.         urlLink okcupid.com         - Coming off like a more focused  urlLink friendster , the interesting thing about this site is the use of personality test and questions to further give depth to someone's profile. It can come off as a little cheezy and questions themselves can be a racy, but the underlining humor and personality profiling tricks (which I always had an interest in) makes it an interesting place to visit.           >    Well here are my own results from the above mentioned okcupid.com test. Big props to  LdyRne  for putting it up on own friendster bulletin.     The Boy Next Door  Random Gentle Love Dreamer (RGLDm)   urlLink more details at okcupid.com test results     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once again this week has totally just flown by. Generally uneventful, there were some interesting happenings.  Dropped by the airport early in the week and was once again reminded of why I once enjoyed that place. No other place I know where it is both crowded and yet has quiet places, has wide open-spaces and yet have long empty winding corridors. Helps that it opens till late and is only a quick bus ride from home and back. However there are some sad memories that may have kept me away, but I understand that there are good ones as well. Things are changing.      >     Speaking of change, my congrads to  Iris  for taking a huge step of faith in both heart and mind. All the best and perhaps more of us could benefit in taking similar steps as well :)      >     I had a good afternoon meeting up with my old friend  LdyRne  earlier in the week as well. We finally caught a movie after such a long time, which was kinda awkward since we were like almost the only adults in the theater and was surrounded by school kids on all sides since we had center seats. Remind me not to get tickets of an afternoon show for an animated movie after school exams again.  We adjourned nearby for tea, and while it took some time to get going, we had an enjoyable conversation. I'm glad that our friendship has come to such a point. Like I mentioned to someone earlier, I'm not the type to burn bridges and would try to keep friends as much as I can. We have both grown much and it makes things new as well as keeping the familiarity that have already been established. It also helps that she looked great that day! Makes me hope that I had asked to take a photo or that she would agree to it. Man I hope she's reading this, or all that energy spent keeping tongue-in-cheek would have been for naught :)      >     Speaking of which, there are quite a few people I need to catch up with.  Ebb Tide  is back in town and, God willing, she can find time to get back to me. Somehow I don’t think I should hold my breath about it though.   MchlWng  is finally on holidays, I think. She deserves it I feel, whatever the case may be. Hope to be able to see her; she’s always a joy to hang out with. Pity that we do that rarely.  Then there are my classmates. Sounds strange I know since I see them almost everyday, but I rarely get to spend time with them outside of school. For example, they were up in JB a few days back and I wasn’t able to attend. Another reason is that our modules will be different come next term thus I won’t be able to see them as much.  Last but not least are  NcoWng  and the rest of my NS understudies. They will be ORDing soon and thus they owe me a dinner treat  *grins*    Hmm…maybe I should get around to dropping the rest of the people on my Friendster friends list testimonials, good way to get them to write for me too. If friendster is working that is. Maybe get them to read this blog too. And with that, I have brought all this post back full circle.   Have a good week! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On a whim, I decided to drop by the airport on my way back from class today. It was still kinda early and I was feeling to groove because of the good music mix from my Nomad but most importantly because I happened to have my Cybershot with me. Been awhile since I took any new pictures and had forgotten alot of techniques and settings tips. But I think they turned out pretty ok.    urlLink    Of Steel and Glass      urlLink    Loney Walkways      urlLink    The Endless Search      urlLink     At the Plane beyond  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Attended the first Church produced music theory-training lesson two days ago. Was surprised that I actually remembered stuff from my drum lessons during my poly days at the great old Suntec Music Plaza back before they moved. Good memories. Especially the time where I ran into  DaMan  there when we both were with our respective SO at the time.   Heh  . So anyway the lesson was just basically a refresher course but it was good to see the younger ones that are really new to music theory have a go at learning it. Quite fun, I hope they will keep at it. Always have a place for new instrument players, and if they don’t make it on to the Worship team, well my Sound team would be more than willing to take them in.    As for myself, well…I think I need to talk to  CrlSh  about what I want to get out of the lessons. I’m mainly in it for the theory, but don’t mind picking up some keyboard skills. However I’m not looking to actually play up on stage, its more for me to experiment with at home, to know what notes sound good together and what should follow after each note.  In the meantime, I’ve did some searching on the Net for stuff on music theory and came up with an interesting link.   urlLink Musictheory.net   It has a series of lessons done in flash that are quite in depth. Some of them even has sound and there are trainers to help test one's knowledge. Haven't had much time to go throught it yet. Wonder how much I can pick up on my own.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink       Well it's the start of a whole new week as we barrel straight towards the end of the month. Can't believe it's almost already the middle of the year. Time really files fast. Sometimes I feel like I'm stuck in the past.  On that note, after last week, my mind is starting to finally open up to new possibilities and outlooks. But somehow I'm left feeling like a guy on a huge coffee craving but only has one Starbucks in his town...and they only have tea. Where do I even begin searching?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man...the surprises from blogger just keep coming. After re-vamping the whole interface and adding much sort after features like comments. They then throw in a photoblogging service that allows photos to be posted with just a few clicks and no html. Just like the one in the post below.  There are other additional features to the service as well that is pretty cool. Such as direct connection to your friends to share photos and chat with them about it MSN/ICQ style. So no more trying to find ways for  DaMan  to show off to me his photos from his latest holiday (all 9megs worth), we just both connect using the  urlLink hello client   and he can show me each photo at time, discuss them while both of us are viewing the same picture (so no more misunderstandings) and I can then op to save to my disk which photos I want.  Totally cool. If there is anything that can get me back into using my digital camera more often, this would be it. I highly recommend this to anyone with a digital camera, don't forget to add me to your list. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Breakwater&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For some strange reason, this has been at the back of my mind over the last few days. More so than usual. And now I discover... How long? two? four? No notice and no further follow up offered...for good? and what about the other? left behind?  Too many questions, not enough answers... now flying in my mind.  I don't want to dwell too much. I can't dwell too much. I can't afford to dwell too much. I won't allow it...I just can't.  It's time and yet I don't hunger. I'm not afraid of the answers, only of not having them at all...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Picked up the latest copy of  urlLink Computer Music Magazine , the other day and was quite pleased to see that it was a special beginners issue. It wouldn't be out of place if they had called named it with this above title.  Basically what this issue does is to give a detailed introducing to the world of using computers to not only record but also to create, mix, produce and even master music for personal use. In most cases the stuff done can also be applied to professional studios as well.  Now as I have mentioned before ( urlLink here  and  urlLink here ), at the start of the year I had taken up to learn more about computer music as an extension of my duties as a sound engineer, to find ways to improve or booster the sound equipment in Church and for personal enrichment as well.  But things have not been working out as well as I have figured, there are tons of information that need to be understood and compiled from many sources, too many choices in hardware and software and most things assume knowledge in music playing and theory of which I have…well…none. It’s all very disheartening. It also doesn’t help that all the solutions that I discovered to help out in Church is mainly only possible with a sizeable budget, of which I have none.  So I have not been keeping up to date on the scene much with school and such keeping me occupied. But I guess with this issue a fresh start can be taken. Perhaps I shouldn’t rush headlong into trying to figure out the higher end stuff and perhaps start slow towards the low end first. I am taking some basic music theory courses and so that would hopefully arm me with greater know-how to make better use of my MIDI keyboard instead of just banging away at it.  Basically it comes down to making the most of what I have at the moment and not worry too much about other stuff. These things take time and so I just have to stick to it and then I’ll slowly see the benefits as I build up my foundations.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well the one-week break practically flew past and I'm already at the end of the second week of my new school term. With some of the modules requiring weekly assignments, this term looks to be a killer. But then again I always say that at the start of each new term.    >   It has been awhile since i last beta tested for something, so I took some time off awhile ago to try out some new online game worlds. Of the three I’ve tested, only one seemed engaging, which is totally normal for these sort of things. This is because for all the concepts they can come out with; only a few companies have that formula where they can balance all the factors during the development and conception phases. This does not even include the stability and gameplay issues that may arise from Live 24/7 gameworld uptime. How with all of the game companies currently gathered in L.A. for  urlLink E3 , the annual exhibition for Electronic-interactive Entertainment, it will be interesting to see what new concepts and developments will be announced. I feel that the industry has just reached a new level of maturity and we will see a new mindset when it comes to future games.    >   But yes back to what I was saying. The new online game that is actually  Interesting. Well some of you all know that I used to be a big fan of American superhero comics. Especially those from  urlLink DC comics , like Batman, Superman and Wonder Woman. Even have written up some comic book characters some time ago.  So the whole concept of a online game where you can take on the role of a super hero, band together with other people who are super heroes and go against groups of dastardly villains with their army of minions and plans for world (or City) wide domination, is totally engaging to me. Sounds cheesy I know, but it fits the whole style and concept of the four-color comics. Of course, like I mentioned above, even with the best of concepts, if the execution is flawed it will not retain interest for long.  But it is in this area where developer Cryptic Studios and publisher NCsoft really shine. By constricting the game  urlLink City of Heroes  to a heavily streamlined set of features, they have captured the essence of what makes comics fun. Fast paced action, detailed and twisting story plots plus colorful and interesting environments. Believe me, in the area of online games, this is a wonderful breath of fresh air.  So anyone looking to get in on to massive online gaming, this comes highly recommended due to it's user friendliness and quick paced action. Of course, it does have a monthly payment scheme past the free trail, which is usually the main reason for the lack of popularity compared to server based online games, such as Warcraft, Counter-strike, Gunbound and the like. But this may be changing in the future, when new payment schemes are tested or even made free. I’ll be sure to keep a watch as things progress. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well. I've changed some things around. It retains the look of the original template, but I think the feel is different. It's more me now.  I'm very pleased that each post has it's own page now. Makes things all so much more neater and easier to implement other pages with the same layout. But that means I'll have to go back through all of them to correct some layout problems. Irratic font sizes seem to be the major problem at the moment. I'll have to dig through the style sheets to figure out why it's happening.  Of course I'll still have to put up all the links that I used to have on the old layout. That will be the next item to be added soon.  So tell me what you think of the new layout and test out the new comments system while you're at it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well. How fun. Here I am preparing a post about how I used the web page validator at www.wc3.com and what does Google and Blogger do? Completely revamp the service, including new templates that meet all the latest standards. Boy does it save me alot of time but it does force the need to implement changes like well...now.  This template is only a placeholder for the moment, I quite like it but think I will need to add my own touches to it soon, like a little less blue. Of course the old tag-board and comments are gone. No big lost really. The tag-boards keep crashing and having pop-up appear and the comments were practically unused. Will be using the new Blogger comments system but I don't think I'll be putting the tag-board back.  As for the profile, writting page and links. I will work to getting them up as soon as I can. Lots of stuff to adjust and learn. Would be fun if I didn't already have some stuff on hand to do.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        My hopes are so high that your  kiss  might kill me. So won't you  kill  me, so I die happy. My heart is  yours  to fill or burst, to  break  or bury, or wear as jewelery, which ever you prefer.  Hands down this is the best day I can  ever  remember, I'll always  remember  the sound of the stereo, the dim of the  soft  lights, the  scent  of your hair that you twirled in your fingers and the time on the clock when we realized it's  so  late and this walk that we shared  together . The streets were  wet  and the  gate  was locked so I jumped it, and I let you  in . And you stood at your door with your  hands  on my waist and you kissed me like you meant it. And  I knew  that you meant it, that you  meant  it, that you meant it,  and I  knew, that  you meant , it that you meant  it .     -Taken from "Hands Down" by Dashboard Confessional
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I spoke to some of the Techs at  Pac Net  and it seems like they have fixed that error 400 redirecting problem that have been plaguing the blog over the last few weeks. So far so good, so major upz to them for fixing it.  On that note, I just realized that the renew date on the personal domain name had indeed run out, but  Pac Net , having good customer service, has automatically renewed it for another year. So it looks like I won’t be looking for a new web host anytime soon. Maybe towards the end of the year, when I have gotten my money’s worth of the renewal fee and itching to expand the site again, then I’ll bring it up again.  Till then…it’s good to be back.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well for more than a week, an error would have prevented most people from visiting this blog. Not that there are alot of visitors in the first place.  I had figured it to be a problem with the re-directing service from Pacific Internet and that they would fix it after a few days. However as it turns out the problem lay with how they handled the URL to be directed to, which required a change in the settings, of which I only discovered today after much testing. However it seems like this only solves the problem for a short while, then it pops up again. Really looks like a problem server side. Hopefully they will fix it soon but in the meantime I’m looking into finding a new web host for the site. Having trouble coming up with a good domain name though. Any Ideas anyone? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Coming off the restlessness that I was feeling over the weekend, I decided to pick up again, book 5 of the  Harry Potter  series,  The Order of the Phoenix . Having watched the latest movie last week, and realizing that I had only read the book once on the day of its release, guessed it wouldn't hurt to go through it again. Well other than the fact that I need to catch up on my school reading, do my weekly journal and get ready my army stuff, it shouldn't hurt. Yeah Right.  About halfway through the book already, I'm reminded of some reviews that I had read about the book. While I may agree that the book is a little long-winded, and the pace somewhat off at spots, I don't agree that it is the weakness in the series. While it may not be as good as  The Goblet of Fire , and the plot not as strong as  The Prisoner of Akzaban , it is not as weak as  The Chamber of Secrets , the weakness of the series in my opinion. Good thing that the movie done it good.  Speaking of which, its only natural that I found the movie for  Prisoner of Azkaban  to be the best of the lot, having a better overall plot, much stronger acting and a style of directing that fits the new direction that the plot heads towards. I can't wait to see the movie (or movies) that come out of  The Goblet of Fire , still my favorite book. Another good thing about the whole series is that hopefully people would follow the spelling of my real name as given in the books. It’s one “L” not two.  *grins*   Well hopefully i can finish off the book by tonight, get my fix and then get on with the business of school and service to the nation. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Came down with some flu today and feeling quite urgh about the whole thing. No mood to do anything really. Hate it when I’m in these sort of moods. Hopefully it will pass by soon. I’ve got magazines and textbooks to read, games to play and a bed to sleep in, yet I’m struggling to write out something here.      >     On another sad note, former US president Ronald Reagan  urlLink passed away  last night. Being the first US president that I remember while growing up, Reagan will always stand in my mind as the idea leader of that country. While his politics may not have been agreeable with everyone, his leadership skills and presence, I believe, has seen no equal since. Truly an end of an era, but in a way there is relief that he no longer has to suffer through such a terrible and heart-wrenching  urlLink disease .          >     Caught game 5 of the  urlLink Stanley Cup  finals that are going on now. Never really had the chance to sit down a watch a proper Ice Hockey game from start to finish, so it was a real trill. Helped that it was a terrific game as well.  So my interest in the game got pushed back up a notch. Maybe I should look into getting a copy of the NHL 2004 game. But more importantly, maybe its time that I take up sports again. Doesn’t have to be hockey since I don’t think the leg injury I got while in the army can withstand the punishment, but I don’t think cycling, swimming and gym once in awhile is enough. On top of that, a team sport would be good way to expand my social circle, as  Someone  so “helpfully” suggested I do. As if I didn’t know that and am not trying. Still the question remains as to what sport to take up. Knowing my taste in the exotic and unusual, as well as the mentioned injury, finding something that fits would not be easy.   Then again…perhaps  urlLink this one  may be a good place to start.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       " Yet another sign that the End of the World as we know it is approaching"       Yep you heard it right. I have doomed us all.  I have turned my back on my brothers and have fallen into the  White .    Yes.I have bought a Mac product.    An iPod actually. 20Gigs, 4th generation. All white plastic and shiny chrome.  It's simple to use, does what it's made for well, turn on;plug in; forget it's there.    It's good. Not perfect. But good.    Yet I don't see what all the hype is about. Haven't made a Mac convert out of me. Heck it doesn't change my views on computing towards the Mac mindset either. Frankly I was more "enlighten" when I bought my first Palm PDA.    That being said, have to give credit due to Apple for a nicely made piece of tech.  If this is the device that makes people more aware of the joys of digital music, so be it. We could do alot worse.    Well I did say that I would talk about my issues with Apple if I did end up buying an iPod. Not everyone wants to hear it I know, but at least it will allow me to actually put down on paper my views. I'll try to do it soon.       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Over the last few days I have been taking a close look at  urlLink Mp3 players  as I have been in the market to replace my aging  urlLink Nomad II . It’s amazing; the little thing has been with me for almost 8 years now. It predates all my hand phones and PDA’s, most of Poly and all of Army. It even outlasted two girlfriends.  Now that’s what I call loyalty.  So the best that I can do is find a suitable successor and finally put the little guy down to rest. Seeing as how it came from  urlLink Creative , it’s only natural that they are my first choice for a replacement and that only a hard disk based player with gigs of space would justify retiring the Nomad.  However over the years, the products from Creative have been intriguing but somewhat lacking. The first jukebox series seemed like the CD players of old and the Zen series, while being a big innovation, just seems like an external hard disk. Not to mention that they all lack the easy one-handed operation of the Nomad.  How about the competition?  urlLink iRiver  and  urlLink Apple  being the only alternatives worth considering.   iRiver contains the best feature set but at extravagant prices when compared to the amount of space they are offering.  As for Apple? Expanding from my general resentment of their views on computer culture and product development, I find their offerings to focus too much on style and design over technical aspects and compatibility for such a premium price.  So back to the present, Creative is coming out with their new player and it looks they finally came up with something that is usable and not too big. Of course they did this by copying almost full scale from Apple, so they lose points there. And what’s with the vertical touch bar? I not sure if that would be easy to use.  And Apple? The  urlLink iPod minis  are cute and have the right idea in terms of navigation but are not value for money. Then I saw the new  urlLink 4th generation iPod  and I have to admit.  I am  impressed .  Seems to me with this, Apple have finally fixed what have, in my eyes, been wrong with their whole line till now.  No more awkward placed buttons, now they almost match the configuration of my old Nomad. And of course the touch wheel is still there, a trademark of the iPod and somewhat gimmicky to me, but its a tried and found to be practical method and I'm all for practicability. Better battery life, which Apple previously ignored to maintain the seek look of the old iPods, yet another decision of theirs that I disagreed with. And finally, Windows and USB support right out of the box, so no more ignoring the bigger percentage of computer users.  In short, I’m actually considering buying a Mac product.  I know. I'm as surprised as you are.  My one consolation is that it seems that this is the most disliked iPod among current Mac users. They call it a step away from what makes Mac a Mac, that it is too mainstream. But that is actually the reason why I like it.  It strikes me that I should explain the history of my dislike for Apple one day. Especially if I do end up buying an iPod.  Till then, the first salvo in the digital music battle for my money has been fired.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "Understanding is the first step to acceptance, and only with acceptance can there be recovery"   - Albus Dumbledore "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire"   It's amazing how this simple step gets overlooked or is denied us at times.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I’m glad to finally have back on air, about the only “reality” TV show that I can stand to watch hence my favorite,  The Amazing Race .  However it looks like  urlLink this season , it’s going to go to extremes. Either someone screws up so badly that it becomes the highlight of the season, or it’s so unmemorable that no one will bother about it weeks after the final show. Of course it’s only the first episode so as yet anything can happen.   However it’s the people that make the show and compared to last season, this season’s 2 person teams almost seem normal. Sure, we have the requisite young, good-looking, comprised of at least one model, couple (or two, or three, or four!?) and the network tried to spice things up by throwing in mothers, pilot, twins and a midget but they are still lacking compared to the clowns, blondes, virgins, gays and surfer dudes of  urlLink yester season .   Now I’m not saying that it’s gimmicks that sell the show, far from it. I’ve always believed that it’s how the teams run the race that matters. In the first episode, the teams already seemed “blessed” by lousy vision, stronger than the norm ability to follow written instructions and copious amounts of backstabbing that didn’t serve any purpose. In contrast, the above-mentioned red-nosed wonder clowns ran a near prefect race. They were eager, quick to move, hardly missed a clue, were good at almost all the events, rarely argued, were nice to other teams when it mattered and was actually funny to boot. It was only by a single mistake that led to their exit late in the race but they still remain my favorite team in any season.  So here’s hoping that these teams improve on their race skills, but I think they will have an easier time trying to show some character. Until then I’ll be honking my bright red nose at them.   urlLink Here is  a good site to read the latest episode recap. Beware that it can be bitingly honest of the team’s performance. More so than even I can stand to be. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...at least it sure feels like it. 2 weeks between posts. Not even the excuse of being cut out from the Net due to my Internet router failing and having to be replaced sounds good enough.  That being said, I'm totally enjoying the new router that I picked up today. Heard alot about  urlLink Netgear  products but never had the chance to try because of their much higher price. But nowadays prices for networking devices are so low that they are all about the same level anyways. Best thing is that it came bundled with a laptop wireless card, which I passed to my mom, for only a small sum.     >    It's deep into assignment/project time here in my 2nd term at school. (heh, not only is it my 2nd term of the year, but it's also the 2nd last term of my course). Of which I have completed a presentation and a programming assignment. These two have been the reason for my lack of presence here as well as my lack of sleep, all due to pretty last minute crunch time work done on them. Thus next time, for the remaining assignments and projects, I'm going to start early so as to hopefully prevent another similar occurrence. But with all the due dates close together, as well as the amount of study and research needed to even attempt them, I foresee future sleepless nights.  Still, no excuse to repeat another 2 week long blog absence. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>