<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Let me just start by saying that I am officially on vacation.  What's that, you ask? I'm not sure, but ask me in two weeks and if I have figured it out, I'll let you know.  In truth, it's impossible for an attorney who is running her own firm to truly take two weeks off without any contact with the office whatsoever, but if my staff (who is absolutely awesome, I must say) can keep the office running to the point where we only communicate by email at the end of each day, I'll consider it a successful two weeks. :)          I'm learning that some clients have unrealistic expectations of what a lawyer is and isn't, so I thought I'd take this opportunity to give the general public some tips on who we are, what to expect from us, and what YOU need to do to ensure a smooth, positive working relationship. (By now you're probably thinking " What do you mean 'what *I* need to do?  I'm paying you to do things for me, not the other way around!")  Ummm...yeah, but if YOU fail to do a few things to make MY job easier, we BOTH get screwed.  So, pay attention. :)          1.  Attorneys are human beings, too!  Believe it or not, we laugh, we cry, and most of us really care about our clients.   We make the best decisions we can based on the information that you give us, and on whatever evidence we get our hands on.  We CANNOT guarantee results, as we are not only at the mercy of the law, but we're at the mercy of the mood of the judge. :)            2.  When you hire an attorney, you are an integral part of the Attorney-Client relationship.  You are protected by the Attorney-Client Privilege, which means that I cannot tell the other side ANYTHING you tell me that is not discoverable through some other method.  That means that if you're being sued for adultery and you confide in me that you did it, but they have NO evidence, then you're home free, because I can't tell on you!  So, guess what that means?  TELL ME EVERYTHING- the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth!  Do NOT guess, and do NOT withhold information, because if you do, I cannot protect you if the other side finds out the truth and then slaps us with it in court.  If I know the whole story, I can prepare for any scenario.  Your duty as a client is to divulge anything and everything that could affect the outcome of your case.          3.  Attorneys do not control how fast a case moves through the system, especially if it will definitely end up going to trial.  We can do our best to request trial dates and hearings, but we are ultimately at the mercy of the court coordinator.  Remember that the courts are backlogged with cases, and try not to yell at your attorney too much when it takes her three months to get a date for a trial setting!          4.  Your case is not the only case your attorney has.  Your attorney has to work their caseload in accordance with what has been scheduled by the courts and what deadlines are looming.  They will not touch your case every day, and they will not call you every day to give you an update.  Attorneys are very busy, and if you don't hear from your attorney for two weeks, that usually means that nothing has happened with your case that needs to be reported to you.  That doesn't mean they haven't looked at it at all, it just means that there is nothing new to report.  Attorneys charge for their time- if you call them every day to request the status of your case, you're going to have one really big bill, because thay are going to charge you for our time.  Please realize that your Attorney is working for you and doing their best.  Calling your Attorney once every two weeks to check the status is okay, but any more than that isn't necessary.  Trust me, we haven't forgotten you. :)          5.  Please pay your bills on time, and if a lump sum is due that you can't afford, then call and work out a payment arrangement and stick to it!  Attorneys have bills to pay, too...we have to pay our staff, our rent, your filing fees, our utilities and phone, etc., and if you don't pay your bills, we can't pay ours...and we'll most likely withdraw from your case. :)          Hopefully, this little semi-rant will give you a little insight as to how you can make your experience with an Attorney a positive one.  And, I'll post more tips as they come to me, but right now it's time for VACATION!!!!    
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Welcome to the Lamenting Lawyer!&nbsp; This will be a plethora of musings, articles, and rantings regarding the legal profession.&nbsp; Grab some java, get comfy, and get an inside look at the wonderful world of lawyers. :)     &nbsp;    DISCLAIMER: Nothing in this blog will constitute legal advice, and absolutely NO ATTORNEY CLIENT relationship exists between myself and anyone who reads this unless there is a signed, written contract of employment executed in my office.&nbsp; ALL CONTENTS OF THIS PAGE ARE COPYRIGHTED BY ME UNLESS STATED OTHERWISE, so please ask permission before republishing.&nbsp; Thanks! :)    
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Let me preface this whole rant by stating what may not be obvious...I'm NOT a Texan. :) I know, I know, I'm scum, I'm a blashphemer, whatever you want to call me.  And, before you ask WHY I'm in Texas, I'll just spill the goods.  I'm a native Louisianan, and let's just say I ended up here in humid Texas because at least the laws here are in a language most people can understand...of course the logic might be WAY twisted, but it's readable. :)Also, you can blame my presence here on my husband- he thinks that anyone north of I-10 is a "Damn Yankee." :)      Today, I'm going to rant a bit about what I think are some of the STUPIDEST laws in Texas, and I may throw in some of the greatest miscarriages of justice I've ever heard of.  First, let's start with the new "license plate cover law."  Who the HECK cares if you have a plate frame from TSU, OSU, or the name of your local car dealer framing your plate?  I'm sorry, but Texas plates are so distinct that any moron can figure out it's a Texas plate.  And here's the kicker- they want to charge you $200.00 for committing such a serious crime.  C'mon, don't you guys have REAL criminals to catch?!?!?!?      And while we're on the subject, is it just me, or does it seem like our legal system is backwards here?  I see cases every day where some small time thief/drug user gets 40 years in the slammer, but a murderer gets out in 3 years.  I'm sorry, but the taking of human life is far more sinister than screwing up your own brain.  This isn't rocket science, folks...      Andrea Yates...you either hate her or feel immensely sorry for her.  I subscribe to the latter view, and I happen to believe that her sentencing was the most extremem miscarriage of justice I've ever witnessed.  This woman needs MENTAL help- you don't get that in jail!  Nobody in their right mind drowns their children...that in and of itself smacks of severe psychosis.  And yet the jury in Harris County, in their infinite "wisdom," chose to send her to jail, where she has NO hope of any significant recovery, instead of locking her in the psych ward where she truly belongs.  And WHY was her husband not charged?  I'm sorry, but her husband was an Engineer, a man of science.  Any man as smart as he is KNOWs that when you have a wife that suffers increasingly severe episodes of postpartum psychosis, you do NOT continue to get her pregnant!  And you sure as heck don't leave her alone with the kids...      ...and that brings us to Dr. Clara Harris,  the heroine of every wronged woman.  Her husband makes a public spectacle of her and what does she do?  She runs over him with her car...a crime of passion, right in the heat of the moment, and she gets TWENTY years???  Drunk drivers who kill people get less time than that!!!  Of course, it is an interesting sidebar that the daughter changed her story rather quickly when she realized that stepmom's conviction would make her a rich little girl in civil court...          Don't get me wrong- I believe that in the right circumstances, our system works for us.  If I didn't believe in justice, I wouldn't be here- I would not have taken the oath.  I believe that there are still those in our profession that are good, honest, noble...sadly, our profession has been inundated with those who are in it "for the money."  Those of us who aren't will never be rich, and we'll be paying on those doggone student loans for the rest of our lives, but we will dedicate ourselves to taking cases where we believe that our client deserves to win.   
      
</post>


<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Welcome to the insanity that is my world. In time I'll get some entries on here worth reading. For now I'm just getting used to having a my own Blog. :)     &nbsp;   Okay...so now it is two years later, and I STILL haven't gotten in here and posted.&nbsp; Hmmm...am I losing my marbles?&nbsp; Nah, I've just been BUSY!!!! urlLink http://www.fultonlawfirm.com &nbsp;- this is what I do in the real world!    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I suppose I must digress a bit. They say every person has their defining moments- those fleeting few moments where decisions made will define who they eventually become. Looking back, I can honestly say that I had more than my share. The hardest part has been coming to terms with all of the crap I've been through. People ask me often "How did you survive?" The truth is that I simply do not know, from an emotional standpoint. I know that God was there, even if I wasn't really wanting to listen to Him, let alone talk to Him. Either way, I have to say that is it were not for God, I'm pretty sure my home would be six feet under with the worms and the maggots...and yet here I am. Anyway, back to the story...     I did sue the doctor for playing God with my body, and after a 6 month ordeal, it was over and I had won a whopping $35,000 dollars. Yeah, you heard me right. In Germany, they place values on body parts, and deduct from that if you've acheived some benefit from that body part. In plain English, I could have won about $50,000, but since I already had two children they reduced the award because I "could take solace in the fact that I had children." My story had been in the American paper and the German paper, and I felt like eyes were on me everywhere...I just wanted to go home- back to the US, and away from that very sad chapter in my life. To this day I feel immensely guilty about how disassociated I was from my baby boy those first few weeks...and I wish he knew just how much I adore him and have the highest hopes and dreams for him. He's a wee bit impulsive (okay, okay, so he's REALLY impulsive), but a kinder heart I've never seen. His older brother is quieter, calmer, but quirky all the same, and I adore him as well. They're both part of me- what's not to love?!?!?! ;)   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 1993- It would be a bittersweet year, and the birth of my second&nbsp;son would turn out to be both&nbsp;one of the best, and one of the worst days of my life.&nbsp; The&nbsp;sequence of events that led up to the day of his birth were nothing short of a comedy of errors.&nbsp; Those of you who are well-versed in military history will recall that 1993 was the beginning of the "great downsizing" of US troops, especially overseas.&nbsp; At the time, we lived in Erlangen, Germany (it was a bit Northeast of Nurnberg).&nbsp; My then-husband was in the Army, and I was slated to deliver our son in the Army hospital in Nurnberg.&nbsp; At the last minute, they sent the troops to the field, and I was sent to a&nbsp;German doctor.&nbsp; I was quite overweight at the time (I was somewhere around 360 pounds) but my health was good and I had&nbsp;not had any remarkable problems during my first or second pregnancy.&nbsp; I had even mader it clear to my OB/GYN that I did NOT want my tubes tied.&nbsp; I had even made that clear to the German doctor during our visit.&nbsp; A few days later, I went in to the hospital in Nurnberg to have my son.&nbsp; over there, they did not yet do spinals so that you could be awake during a C-section birth.&nbsp; I was given general anesthesia and was knocked out during my son's delivery.&nbsp; When I woke up, I knew something was wrong...I was in the recovery room for hours and it was at least three hours after the birth before I ever saw my son.&nbsp; I kept asking the nurses&nbsp;if my baby was okay and did I have a boy or a girl.&nbsp; I vaguely remember my husband coming in&nbsp;and he seemed upset that they had not let me see my baby.&nbsp; The next day, I found out why I'd been in recovery so long.&nbsp; During a conversation with my doctor, he casually mentioned that he had done the tubal ligation&nbsp;"that my husband had discussed with the CHAMPUS advisor."&nbsp; WHAT?!?!?!?!?&nbsp; I had made it crystal clear that I did NOT want my tubes tied, and I repeated those words to my doctor.&nbsp; His reply?&nbsp; "Well, you're very overweight, and a future pregnancy will not go well for you.&nbsp; One day you will thank me for this."&nbsp; With that, he left.&nbsp; Thank him???&nbsp; He had to be on&nbsp;drugs...yeah, I'd like to thank him by breaking his fool neck!&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I was in a haze, but somewhere in the haze I remembered the words "your husband" and it hit me that my doctor was alleging that this was done at my husband's request.&nbsp; That wasn't possible- we had decided together that we didn't want that- it had to be a mistake, didn't it?&nbsp; I asked for the phone and called him and told him what had been said, and he was so upset I think half the staff heard him yelling.&nbsp; He came to the hospital right away, and it became clear to me that the doctor had decided to play God and cover his ass by blaming it on my husband.&nbsp; Incensed, I demanded that they release me from the hospital on the second day (I was supposed to be there 5 days- that wasn't happening).&nbsp; I was angry, confused, and my gorgeous baby boy suffered the most.&nbsp; For the next 6 weeks, I couldn't barely even hold him without associating him with what happened.&nbsp; It wasn't his fault, and I knew that, but I was heartbroken.&nbsp; I felt like I had been raped, and in a way, I had been.&nbsp; That so-called doctor violated my body and took something precious from me.&nbsp; He WOULD pay.    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        WARNING:&nbsp; Although I like to joke around, I am a writer/attorney, and I do copyright my writings, so please, respect my work and don't try to steal any of it (psst...it's not worth much anyway!!!) =P~&nbsp;     &nbsp;  I'm sorry for the two year delay, really I am!&nbsp; It's just that right after I created this little corner of the world, I got sick for a while, and then I got better and had to do what real people do (WORK) and then I got sick a gain, and, well, it's an ongoing yo-yo. :)&nbsp; Oh well, the great thing about having my story out in the open is that I'll won't ever be a target for blackmail, cuz I'm an open BLOG!!!     &nbsp;   Anyway, I promised you the dirt, so I suppose I should get to it.&nbsp; Let's see, I was born a poor deprived coal miner's daughter...errr...nah, too cliche'.&nbsp; Truthfully, I was born, I lived, and I probably should have died, but God has had immense mercy on me, or else he has a really twisted sense of humor.&nbsp; Either way, I'm proud ot say that it is comforting to know that there is a better place waiting on the other side of this insanity that is known as my life.&nbsp; I couldn't survive this world without my faith.&nbsp; Strangely enough, there was a time, not too long ago, when my faith was shattered, and I became so, very, very lost...     &nbsp;   (next post- 1993- How it all began)    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        1994- The Void...          I thought that 1994 would be the beginning of a new time for me. We were back in the USA, in Kansas, a place I REALLY loved even though everyone told me that it was dull, boring, and there was nothing but miles of endless ...well, nothing. :) My then-husband and I had weathered the storm surrounding the unwanted and unwelcome tubal ligation and the ensuing publicity and trial, and despite the insinuation that my husband had been somehow involved in what happened, we had grown closer. I was happy to be back home in the USA...closer to my family and friends. The worst, I thought, was over.          We had arrived in Kansas in early January after an extended vacation with our families after our arrival from Germany. It was good to see my parents and my brother again after two years. Before my time in Germany, I'd never gone more than 2-3 months without seeing my family. It felt good to be back home. Of course, I was in a wheelchair, thanks to my klutziness a few days before our scheduled flight home. I managed to tear every ligament in my ankle when I misstepped of of a sidewalk and found a deep hole. Hey, there are reasons my family called me "Grace." :)          My brother had been having a rough year...he'd been in a couple of accidents and was having bouts of depression. My parents were worried about him and I urged them to get him some help. He also had a girlfriend who had been playing a few mind games with him, and he was unsure how to handle it. During our visit home, he and my then-husband had talked at length about women, the things they do, and how he should deal with it all. By the time we left, he seemed better- focused and determined not to play the games. I thought he might be okay.          (Next Chapter- The Darkness)   
    
</post>


</Blog>