<Blog>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

       
      This is my first post! yay.. hahaha. I finally got a more professional-looking blog after I kept sticking to making my own. I got tired of it and decided to let other people do the harder work and now all I need to do is type and type. No more coding! Hahaha. Bye!!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

       
      My template finally works to the way I want it to, but my archives don't quite work, yet. I'm not sure why not, but I'll figure it out later. Right now I'm thinking of what to do with my pitas and my about my life entries. I might just put them here in my archives section.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

       
      I'm back.. yes, I am. Now I need to test if my new template works or not.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
          BIG JOHN (KERRY)  Every mornin' on the Hill you could see him arrive Standing six-foot-four, weighing one-twenty-five Kinda' scrawny at the shoulders and lacking a spine And when he spoke at all, it was mainly to whine. (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John.  Nobody seems to know what's in John's soul His 'beliefs' are based on the latest poll Though he'll say what it takes to get your votes It's the leftist agenda that he really promotes Big John.  Some one said he came from Boston town Where he joined the Navy and gained renown 'Earning' three purple hearts and one bronze star The home folks said, "This boy will go far" (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)  Then came a day back in '71 When he renounced all the medals that he had won Then turned against his country and his Navy friends And sold them out for his own selfish ends (Big John)  He appeared before Congress and on left-wing talk shows Giving aid and comfort to America's foes It was clear to see whose side he was on Some say he helped cause the fall of Saigon Big John. (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John).  He claims to be for the working poor Yet he owns 5 mansions from shore to shore He never had to work a day in his life 'Cause he learned it helps to have a wealthy wife! Big John  Now he wants to be our next President and Commander-in-chief of those he resents: The American soldiers who fight and die To give him the freedom to tell us his lies (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)  Thousands have sacrificed their young lives To help ensure that our nation survives A vote for Kerry is a slap in the face To all the brave soldiers that he's disgraced (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)  I found those on the internet.. haha funny. ^ 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      I'm somewhat frustrated right now... I just went to go get my classes with Ms. Hunter, and she messed it up at first, and didn't even give me one of my IB classes (drama). Instead, she put something like technology lab for 2nd period instead. Interesting. Anyway, she gave me Belcher, then I asked for Lamb, and she said ok. Then she changed it back to Belcher though, after asking Mr. Diskin, meaning that all the other people she changed will probably go back to Belcher as well. I told her that Belcher doesn't want to teach spanish 5 ap and he told me so, and she got all angry about it and talked to Holmes, but I had already previously talked to him. Anyway, I'm stuck with this schedule: 0 TOK crisci 1 SPANISH 5 AP belcher 2 THEATRE STUDIES karr 3 ENGLISH 4 IB underberger 4  COMPUTER SCIENCE A AP tufenkjian 5 IB MATH HL hildreth I hate it.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      I realized that I actually quite like Blogger... I don't know why I stopped using it about two years ago. If you think about it... LJ (Live Journal) does not give users enough customization, with only a few ways to change and tweak the template. Xanga is extremely popular for its "easy usage" reasons, but once again, to change stuff, it can be extremely annoying. Blogger is the only one left where you can actually get rid of the nasty ads on the top of the page, and allows full access to the template itself. You can even have several users and stuff.. I just think that's really cool. Anyway, my schedule appointment is tomorrow.. ahhhh.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      I'm testing out Google's BlogThis! option.. publishing right from my toolbar!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      I got my wisdom teeth yanked out yesterday.&nbsp; Fun stuff.  The doctor told me the procedure would take about 45 minutes, and I would be unconscious the whole time so he could drill and stitch in peace. Essentially what happened was that my four wisdom teeth needed to be pulled out because my mouth was "too small" to fit them... and they were still under my gum and so I needed surgery to get them out before they caused more trouble.  The nurse attached those clasps-like things to both of my arms to keep track of my hearbeat in those heartbeat line monitors where a ~~~~ is goood, and a ----- practically means you're dead. &nbsp;I also had those tight heart pressure thingies attached to my left arm. My right arm was reserved for the UV pipe that stuck into the veins of my arm, and I could actually feel something fluid-like going into my arm. It wasn't painful or anything, but it was discomforting.  The next thing I knew, I woke up. The sneaky doctor had injected the medication without saying a word, so I had already been unconscious for 50 or so minutes, and I finally woke up. I was unstable on my feet at first, but it got better. There was also intense bleeding for about 2 hours, and now it's gone.. which is considered pretty good, I guess, because the bleeding is supposed to go on for 2 days, then wane out.  The only bad thing is that I'll probably be limited to soggy and soft food. Sigh, goodbye fast-food places.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>