<Blog>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i want to change to this one so i can keep it exclusive to friends and only people whom i want reading my blog.  but bah. i cannot resist the call of my few seconds of fame.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      argh. the template for this isn't turning out that well.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the real blog is  urlLink here . i'm just reserving this for a future move.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       untitled  nb: not being cliched here, really have no idea what to title this. suggestions?  never like this before  this dull ache,  heart squeezed and tears bled dry.  slow, asphyxiating folds gasping in their grasp   pain passes, time heals all,  gut wounds aren't fatal in this time and age.    what fools they are to slather rhyming lies on maimed limbs and try, in their secure comfort to  reach out  and  heal your pain   why can't it be like it was before,  with the apathy dripping through the iv drip,  like morphine, ether, chloroform leave oblivion in agony’s wake and blank silence in pain’s place  but addicts grow ever hungrier our doses ever larger  phish the iv bag has burst  and leaving all behind  is harder.  this is draft one. have decided to go eliminate the first few stanzas and expand the iv drip metaphor, might be an interesting perspective.  will post here and on footloose when done.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Come down to my house Stick a stone in your mouth You can always pull out If you like it too much  Make a whole new religion A falling star that you cannot live without And I'll feed your obsession There'll be nothing but this thing that you'll never doubt  A hit is hard to resist And I never miss I can take you out With just a flick of my wrist  Make a whole new religion A falling star that you cannot live without And I'll feed your obsessions There is nothing but this thing that you'll never doubt This thing you'll never doubt  And I'll feed your obsession The falling star which you cannot live without I will be your religion This thing you'll never doubt You're not the only one You're not the only one  Bow down to me  Bow down to me  Bow down to me  [Now I want it too much Now I want it to stop Now I'm lucky like a falling star Fell over me] Bow down to me [Now I want it too much Now I want it to stop Now I'm lucky like a falling star Fell over me] Bow down to me [Now I want it too much Now I want it to stop Now I'm lucky like a falling star Fell over me] Bow down to me [Now I want it too much Now I want it to stop Now I'm lucky like a falling star Fell over me] Bow down to me  [Now I want it too much Now I want it to stop] 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Drag him out your window  Dragging out your dead  Singing I miss you  Snakes and ladders  Flip the lid Out pops the cracker  Smacks you in the head  Knifes you in the neck Kicks you in the teeth  Steel toe caps  Takes all your credit cards Get up get the gunge Get the eggs  Get the flan in the face The flan in the face  The flan in the face Dance you fucker dance you fucker Don't you dare Don't you dare Don't you flan in the face Take it with the love is given Take it with a pinch of salt Take it to the taxman Let me back let me back I promise to be good Don't look in the mirror  At the face you don't recognize Help me call the doctor Put me inside Put me inside  Put me inside  Put me inside  Put me inside I keep the wolf from the door But he calls me up Calls me on the phone  Tells me all the ways that he's gonna mess me up Steal all my children  If I don't pay the ransom But I'll never see him again If I squeal to the cops No no no no no no no: Walking like giant cranes ah With my x ray eyes i strip you naked  In a tight little world and why are you on the list? Stepford wives who are we to complain? Investments and dealers investments and dealers Cold wives and mistresses Cold wives and sunday papers. City boys in first class Don't know we're born little Someone else is gonna come and clean it up Born and raised for the job Someone else always does always pick it up Get over get up get over Turn the tape off. I keep the wolf from the door  But he calls me up Calls me on the phone  Tells me all the ways that he's gonna mess me up Steal all my children If I don't pay the ransom  But I'll never see him again If I squeal to the cops So I'm just gonna' 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You're cynical and beautiful You always make a scene You're monochrome delirious You're nothing that you seem I'm drowning in your vanity Your laugh is disease You're dirty and you're sweet You know you're everything I need  Everything you are Falls from the sky like a star Everything you are Whatever ever you want  I wanna kick at the machine That made you piss away your dreams  And tear at your defenses  Till there's nothing there but me  You're angry when you're beautiful  Your love is such tease  I'm drowning in your dizzy noise  I wanna feel you scream  Everything you are Falls from the sky like a star Everything you are Whatever ever you want  Everything you are Falls from the sky like a star Everything you are Whatever ever you want  Everything you are Whatever ever you want Whatever ever you want  Whatever ever you want 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you sent me down when halfway through your cooking that there was no belachan left. and curry would taste funny without belachan you said, stuffed five dollars in my hand and shoved me out the door.   go to the shop behind the ntuc. you know, the one in the wet market, which sells dried goods.  you can't miss it, it's the only one there.   walking there in slippers; i wince at the thought of the grimy floor and strange smells mossy bricks and dirty ice red flesh on steel tenterhooks parts i will not name dripping foul liquid perhaps i'll lie and say it's closed, take refuge in the aircon'd supermart  thank god. it's closed. but fairprice's belachan is all wrong. solid, not liquid, you tell me over the phone it comes in blocks. not bottles.  now for a tour of indian shops. which one will have belachan. the first, i hope. the sooner the better. no strange songs or chants to haunt me in those quarters.   why didn't you try the malay shop first they'll definitely have it you lah, never buy this kind of thing, that's why you waste your time looking in the wrong place.   they have belachan! praise the lords! (five times a day, facing mecca) but how much do you need for cooking curry. a lot i suppose. if i buy too much, it can keep, right? whatever. just buy.  this is belachan right?  yes girl. $3.  (oh. ok. cheap.)  you bought too much i think. but never mind. you never buy belachan anyway.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tonight I can write the saddest lines.  Write, for example, 'The night is starry and the stars are blue and shiver in the distance.'  The night wind revolves in the sky and sings.  Tonight I can write the saddest lines. I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.  Through nights like this one I held her in my arms. I kissed her again and again under the endless sky.  She loved me, sometimes I loved her too. How could one not have loved her great still eyes.  Tonight I can write the saddest lines. To think that I do not have her. To feel that I have lost her.  To hear the immense night, still more immense without her. And the verse falls to the soul like dew to the pasture.  What does it matter that my love could not keep her. The night is starry and she is not with me.  This is all. In the distance someone is singing. In the distance. My soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.  My sight tries to find her as though to bring her closer. My heart looks for her, and she is not with me.  The same night whitening the same trees. We, of that time, are no longer the same.  I no longer love her, that's certain, but how I loved her. My voice tried to find the wind to touch her hearing.  Another's. She will be another's. As she was before my kisses. Her voice, her bright body. Her infinite eyes.  I no longer love her, that's certain, but maybe I love her. Love is so short, forgetting is so long.  Because through nights like this one I held her in my arms my soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.  Though this be the last pain that she makes me suffer and these the last verses that I write for her. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if only i could stop turn back and speak to you again to tell you something different  to touch you deep inside  if only i could tell you, ask you,  hear you tell me: [yes or no?] if only i was not such a fool and knew what i now know  if only i could strip bare my soul downtothenakedcore if only i could tread the splintered ice and not fear the water dark beneath  but cowards flee from that which they fear so i must live with my little pains unless you come  for me.  i found an old poem in my blog archives, and revamped it. it didn't have a title, and had my old horrid habit of too many runon lines. the language is cliched and the structure far from original, but strangely enough says exactly what i wanted to say when i wrote it.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damnit. i had the first few lines of something and promptly forgot them.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       milk -- garbage  (excerpted)    I am milk I am red hot kitchen And I am cool Cool as the deep blue ocean  I am lost So I am cruel But I'd be love and sweetness If I had you  I'm waiting I'm waiting for you I'm waiting I'm waiting for you  I am weak But I am strong I can use my tears to Bring you home 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       dreams   for those of you who dream (like me) we do not sleep we do not sleep  a short three liner to those who dream.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       6 months (well and truly over)   i once said that there was tension between the both of us. you laughed it off and told me that prizefighters feel it too.  i remember the thoracic spasms, your awkward breathing, like mine. surreal sorrow and magnified pain echoed over fibreglass lines and digital bursts of light.  ok. this is really. really. bad. stop there, stop there.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       shanghai’s homeless   cardboard boxes lie ashamble  torn newspapers flying  alleys littered alleys dark back streets body strewn   she’s empty, deserted barren, bleak [the destitute prostitute] such are these godforsaken slums  of shanghai, once great dynasty  who will dare to live among her streets and speak in tongues of old (now dumb) who will read the volume of her lustrous history and remember what was writ within?   now shanghai’s homeless they’ve left her once warm homes to settle in far off unknown lands and have their children culture-less.  for who could care for roots a century removed or bother since others don’t. that’s shanghai abandoned, shanghai disowned for the glories of EIC’s shores.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      flippin hell, something's up with the guestbook.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here we are now here we are. i was thinking of moving a whiles back but i'm too used to hubmind so i'll just use this to post poetry. it's got a nice warm feel to it. ok, fine it's got a nice pink feel to it. nice change from goth.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      letsseeif urlLink links areobviousintext
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      undergods   have you heard the wind sough in the trees  or the leaves rustle on concrete pathways  and wonder, for all his majesty  would god do these mundane things?   we live in nooks and crannies  one of us for each of you  doing our prosaic godly deeds  in silence, underneath.   god's here for all those  displays of majesty  columns of fire and so on.  (but here we are the undergods  we tidy sacristies.)   we are the humdrum undergods  uninspired and uninspiring  but when next you see the sunset painted  in glory, red and gold  remember the work of the undergods  and thank us on your way. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This: sliding under skin of human being searching folds of psyche and taking unconscious apart; looking, for monolith Truth- falling.  This: is my body speaking Me Me, in imperfection trying to tell you what You is; but putting You, in terms of Me, is making infinite estimates of You.  This: is all I only know when beating drums call too Loud for my me to escape my body- no perfect separation,  transcendence cut short, fragments of Me can find  only This- a new me, in This.  in This for a time:  there is no the, but This.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in a valiant attempt to rescue this blog, i am posting my entire cap portfolio- if you've been reading my work regularly and for a while, only one of them will be new. also to let you lot grumble and so forth, i've appended the shoutbox from my main blog here. comment, if you so wish.  struggle for the words, and then give up.    shanghai’s homeless   Cardboard boxes lie ashamble  Torn newspapers flying  Alleys littered alleys dark Back streets body strewn   She’s empty, deserted barren, bleak [the destitute prostitute] Such are these godforsaken slums  of shanghai, once great dynasty  Who will dare to live among her streets and speak in tongues of old (now dumb) Who will read the volume of her lustrous history and remember what was writ within?   Now shanghai’s homeless They’ve left her once warm homes to settle in far off unknown lands and have their children chinese-less.  For who could care for roots a century removed or bother since others don’t. That’s shanghai abandoned, shanghai disowned for the glories of EIC’s shores.     on graduation day   how many suns have traversed from east to west, how many moons have waxed and waned in four years of journey, dawn to dusk hand in hand, foot in mouth hand-to-mouth existences,  living like there's no exam tomorrow.  this will i remember our mad laughter, mocking parodies gnomic hilarities, inside jokes bursts of insane song and dance only we would screen (illegally) disney reliving childhood dreams of tales as old as time only these white corridors will tell of demerit points, libellious news firing teachers, raising hell shakespearean near-tragedies in missing daggers, unseen props laboratories for briefings long, timed practicals with unknown specimens sleeping in toilets, perfectly shaped cubicles  cradling much fatigued bodies in escape from realms of kong zi shuo*.  a person blinks twenty times a minute. 60 minutes in an hour  24 hours in a day 7 days in a week 52 weeks in a year 4 years to our chapter here multiply so many times and you will find these memories were not made for us within the blink of an eye.     in ways i never saw   There is a moth inside my room. It beats upon thick panes of glass, crushing paper wings  on harsh cold concrete solid walls, the rhythmic shudder of them beating, beating, beating on.   Then it stills upon the window frame  Emaciated body lifeless in silence.   Perhaps I should catch it in this instant of stillness have it struggle 'neath my hand in claustrophobic terror screaming  noiseless insectile screams. And I would take it through the open window and set it free in ways it never saw while blinded by transparent glass-  Yet this moth is feverish in its fear no sooner do I fit hands about it that it spirals upwards, upwards, upwards and begins again, that hopeless beating of wings against cold glass.  I leave the room, altruism spent the futile inane struggle causing more noise than I could stand Only but to return in passing  and find that same moth gone.  Be unbound and fly away in ways I never saw, dear moth you are, as ever, free.     Minor Complaints   Your ribs ache. I am trapped within them emptied into your emptiness, with only the ache for company. We’re quiet in here, really with the nothingness of your body.  Do I burn within you, cauterising with serrated edge? Moving inside you, forcing you to take me on my pain- Your torment is all your emptiness feels.  His void is my shadow and I am plunging through his		blanks lost in mid plummet abruptly he shows me which end is up.     danse macabre   I again bodies falling, sweeping arcs of stunning curvature lifting, folding sweeping evanescent elegance, in simple, beautiful, movements  this is dance, you said speared en pointe?  impaled on leaping jetés contorted figures, faces convulsed this is our dance choreographed in morbidity erasing past perfection no longer dance, but danse macabre of you and i 	--pas de deux   II you and i, watch indeterminate fencers circling in fixed trajectories of step, step pause, step slide 	irrhythmic. unsound. one feints, one starts begins anew thrust parry riposte slight movement hit. score. lights go off.  are we not these faceless, shield'd dancers, white in body, black in face subtle, succinct movements these are the games we play, masked as we are opponents.  save we wear flesh, and in this form our masks mock the deadly serious battle, engaged not in foils, but words said; unsaid actions left undone.  hit. score. blood, no lights.     I/instructions from a ballet guide/   one count ; one bar  one count ; one bar one count ; one bar one count ; one bar  facing barre  commence: 3rd position, hands on barre  release front foot to cou-de-pied devant en fondu with stretched foot close 3rd devant stretching both legs repeat derriere release front foot to cou-de-pied devant en fondu with stretched foot extend to 2nd a terre stretching supporting leg hold close 3rd derriere fini   II/geometry/   strokes and rulers, pencilled grids straight-edge boxes, regular lines,  circles, which don't fit.  (she drew these lines to box you in but realised they trapped her instead)  lines are for walking on stripes; to caution dashes to divide lanes. lined lanes which draw into 2 ½s those coming; going the beginings, ends today, tomorrow daylight, dusk life, death you. I.   III/muse/   she watches now. sylph, wraith waryeyed foe?  she is draped over my windowsill. more falling without, than lying within  i am tired, rest me awhile  i plucked feathers in my dream and woke to find her wingless; pinned in silence 'gainst the glass.   i set her free to fly without her wings  she nailed her hands to the windowsill.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Flowers- in your arms overflowing the crook of your elbow The lilies spring from you, the arranged blooms become you: You hold the measure of your glory.  You are slightly tilted you head arched backward The line of your jaw. Proud creature- sleek, slink, sneak, flash your feather boa of magnificence into my face Because You Are So Splendid In Glitter.  In this moment you are a You, not a She- because you are alone, and mine to watch alone, alone. You exotic creature, alone, alone. No moths dallying with your flame for now. Alone, alone. Tomorrow you will be scrubbed free of your sequins.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in all banality, i ask you to drink tea. i want to give this amber-cooled stream to the cracked furrows of you and run it through you, brown and chilled and liquid, natural and normal.  you must not pay attention to these things anymore, the smaller flavours that peer at you for notice because your mouth is full of   a bitterness i have never smelt and cannot guess the taste of.  pour it on, this golden remedy, and let its amber sheen of liquid be all that is between  your body and the world.  ---  rather unlike my usual style. this is rather atwood-y. and the second stanza reminds me of st paul's letters (the sentence structure). this would be a b-side. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this blog is sorely neglected indeed- i had some grand scheme of putting up good poetry i came across, but i never seem to read poetry. music is another matter though, so the lyrics of some good songs up here. have a listen to them.   the good old days -- the libertines   If Queen Boadicea is long dead and gone Still then the spirit in her children's children's children  It lives on  If you've lost your faith in love and music  Oh the end won't be long Because if it's gone for you then I too may lose it  And that would be wrong   You know I've tried so hard to keep myself from falling Back into my bad old ways And it chars my heart to always hear you calling Calling for the good old days Because there were no good old days These are the good old days   It's not about, tenements and needles And all the evils in their eyes  And the backs of their minds Daisy chains and school yard games And a list of things we said we'd do tomorrow A list of things we said we'd do tomorrow   The arcadian dream has all fallen through But the Albion sails on course So man the decks and hoist the rigging Because the pig mans found the source And theres twelve rude boys on the oars  --  better lyrics than you usually get. and the rude boys ref is smart. (there's a reggae bassline.)   rock and roll -- the velvet underground   Jenny said when she was just five years old You know there's nothing happening at all Every time she puts on the radio There was nothing goin' down at all  Then one fine mornin' she puts on a New York station She couldn't believe what she heard at all She started dancin' to that fine fine music You know her life was saved by Rock 'n' Roll Despite all the amputations You could just dance to a rock 'n' roll station  Jenny said when she was just five years old My parents are gonna be the death of us all Two TV sets and two Cadillac cars-- Ain't gonna help us at all  Then one fine mornin' she puts on a New York station She don't believe what she heard at all She started dancin' to that fine fine music You know her life was saved by Rock 'n' Roll Despite all the computations You could just dance to a rock 'n ' roll station  And it was alright.  ---  i love love love lou reed on this.
    
</post>


<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   his  urlLink latest post .  a summary of that: homosexuals are homosexual because of an imbalance of masculinity and femininity. those overly feminine are "bottom". those overly masculine are "top".  there seems to be something wrong with that argument, and not merely in the science of it. its so entangled that i cannot pinpoint what exactly. 

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   www.abidingtruth.com 

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Actually, Miss Urfe, TT doesn't call himself a part-time journalist because he writes odd letters to various publications but because he is, in fact, a part-time journalist. I don't know for which publication. I'm trying to find out and then discover some nuggets of horror that are his articles.  He also is a part-time chef. Again, I can't tell you where he practises his chef-ing, but I do know someone (whom  he  barely knows, having never seen each other before, and whose number he harvested from a blog) he has smsed late at night, asking him whether he'd like to have dinner with him. Probably to partake in some gastronimical delight he invented. Stupidity Flambe perhaps?   He is, however, a full-time idiot.  It's very interesting actually, when enquiries into the AC population are made. My sister's classmates, for example, have all heard of him and his blog and are utterly disgusted by the fact that he pervs on AC swimmers. Someone else has been added to his friendster thingy and bombarded with both messages and tags by TT on his tagboard without having ever met him.  I can't remember what else, but I think TT is damn fascinating haha sorry, I know I'm supposed to be all 'Oh I don't think the word "commit" used in his latest post is very appropriate because it connotes some criminal activity etc' but I'm not feeling up to it this bright and shiny morning.  However, before I go, I must say 'homosexual activity is a waste of time and resources' is one of the funniest things I've read this year. Goodbye! I'm off to consume an unprecendented amount of resources and time leading my boring, yet incriminatingly homosexual, life. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   once again the amazing stupidity of tim tang. go and pract crit the latest post yourself. suffice to say it is hilarious. if a little tedious. ok fine. a lot tedious. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   the cause we are fighting for (bloody freedom fighters :)   - the invigorating fervour that some of us, myself included, slap off the frivolity of others' sans-logic arguments - but what for, really,  what for?   The government has not been entirely unkind, and progress, though slow, is progress. Bearing in mind the traditional Asian values that have governed our society, having events like nation04, gay-themed plays etc. is a milestone in Singapore's history of acceptable changes in the sexual dichotomy.   on the other hand, (you have different fingers.)    The stigma may have wavered a little, but it remains, after (un)dying and valiant efforts to tear the wall down. The ramifications of certain decisions remain demonstrably considerable in many cases.   to tell your best friend in secondary school,  to declare before enlistment, to step out of the closet, to be your real self in a real world.  aren't you tired? i am. i be and am, and i don't feel the need to justify myself anymore. it is abominably tiring. other than the fact that i have homosexual proclivities and indulge in the fulfilment of them, i am law-abiding. i cheer madly at NDPs and sing the national anthem with pride. my homosexuality, which although some apparently perceive as the core of my being, remains merely one fo the facets of the me that is. i'm singaporean. i can speak chinese (albeit terribly unfluently). i like literature. i am a guy who likes guys. i go  huh  at e.e.cummings. i have ten fingers, ten toes, a nose. why concentrate on the one part of me? explain cummings to me. count my fingers. send me for chinese linguistics tuition. but chastise me?  if you are insecure, don't be. there is no need to justify and at the end of the day, (for me) i only need to be accountable to myself. some of you may have your deities or gods to answer to - then so be it. it is your choice for your own religion, and i am so tired i can't continue explaining that you who have chosen your religion chose the path you will take and your ambivalence and torment is   (you guessed it.)  a matter of your choice, to my friends who have lived so terribly.  maybe,   One day we will learn to love ourselves.  The fat ones will stop dreaming of chubchasers,  those fauns who hang from love-handles.  The skinny ones will dare to wear tight tops.  The old ones will stop claiming they look  at least five years younger, over telephones.  The young ones will walk into pubs and  not feel the need to be needy.  We will learn that muscles are like doorknobs  that hint nothing about empty rooms.  We will learn that a big cock is a miracle,  but only of hydraulics.  Just because a body has been pierced,  tanned, or landscaped with tough flesh  does not make it an armour.  Just because a body has not been touched  does not mean it is eager for lessons.  When two people kiss there is the possibility  of love, not its confirmation.  When three people kiss there will always  be one who feels left out.  When two strangers fuck the healing  they do is the unstitching of old wounds.  One day the closeted boy jacking off in his bed  will know that guilt and shame are just  the body's fatigue at hollering to a world that is deaf.  One day someone will walk up  to the paunchy white man at the party  and genuinely ask what his name tag stands for,  GWM4LTR, worn like a prison code.  At Raffles Place the shophouses will catch fire  and expel the smell of catpiss, and rotting beams.  The shadows of men will grow tall in such an inferno.  Loners will stay back at Fort Road for sunrise,  even if rays will illuminate pockmarks and scars.  In broad daylight two men holding hands  will mean nothing, but a symptom of daylight.  (anthem, TIM)  i lost my point somewhere. and incoherence takes over. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Unlike most of you here, I didn't  always know  I was gay. To be sure, I'd always suspected, but at the time I wasn't sure how I could possibly  be gay . I didn't have any role models. I didn't know anyone who was lesbian. I certainly hadn't heard of 'successful lesbians'. I didn't think it was possible to have a relationship with a woman.   Fast forward to today. I know now it is possible, there is now no shame, it's no longer the little secret I have with my lover while we continue to see men at the same time. I fought tooth and nail to come to the place where I can say here I am, I love a woman, I am a woman too - and if you don't like it, screw you, and no, I'm  not  going to screw you. Ever.  Embracing my sexuality was, for me at least, a politically-charged turn - I shudder from the word 'decision'. I didn't  decide  to be gay. But being gay, for me at least, also meant rejecting the prescribed way of life I am supposed to take as a Chinese Singaporean woman, and in the larger scheme of things, rejecting what 'being a woman' is supposed to mean in today's world. I was a staunch feminist for no reason other than that I saw no reason I should allow injustice to be done to me on the grounds of what I may or may not have - I was going to stay out as late as a boy in my family was allowed to, I was going to do whatever they were allowed to do, I was going to render impotent any male my family thought might violate me. I could protect myself, and I can protect the woman I love now - not necessarily in the physical sense.  My relatives show me wedding shots of their proud children, who will soon be wed in holy matrimony. It's always the same: the makeup, the studio pictures, the customary "Western" shot followed by the "traditional" costumes. I'm looking at these pictures and I want to feel happy for them. I really do. But I also cannot help but feel a tinge of envy - that their love can be blessed, sanctified and legitimated,  no matter what . And that mine never can be, at least not in the eyes of church and state,  no matter what . But I'm not going to be bitter about it. I don't believe in giving in to 'destiny' without putting up a good fight, so I'm going to take these matters of matrimonial happiness into my own hands, God willing. And I'm not going to let fuckwits like TT convince me otherwise. "Trying to sightread what our fingers can't keep up with, learn by heart what we can't even read".  An excerpt from Adrienne Rich's "Transcendental Etude" -    "I am the lover and the loved, home and wanderer, she who splits firewood and she who knocks, a strange  in the storm, two women, eye to eye measuring each other's spirit, each other's limitless desire, a whole new poetry beginning here."  

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "There are three kinds of gay people. The first kind decides to live with his real self, but in a false world. The second kind decides to live with his false self, but in the real world. The true gay man is born in the third kind: the one who is ready to show his real self to the world. It is this third kind we must stop." â€“  Asian Boys   *   religion, sexuality and conversion    I am a seventeen-year-old non-Christian Singaporean-Chinese boy studying in a local junior college. I like other boys.    Judge me if you will.   I can also permutate the information provided above with other variables.  "Hi, Iâ€™m a 24 year old dude who is deeply religious, Singaporean-Malay, working in the finance sector, and I have a girlfriend that I plan to marry, by the time Iâ€™m 28."    Will you then love me and embrace me and deem me fit to engage in society? Forget celebrating the diverse milieu we live in, society has no need for deviancy.   Deviancy, the very word sounds devilish, no?  I donâ€™t claim the full rights that a mature individual is entitled to. Despite the exponential growth of self-awareness everyday, I donâ€™t quite think I am ready for many things, nor do I subscribe to the notion of immutability in humans. The actual permutation of the variables in the information is not an impossibility. Some day, I might find myself taking up a religion in the future, when I realise that I need faith for strength. (This does not indicate that I treat religion with frivolity.) Some day, I might find myself being attracted to a girl down Orchard Road, her femininity embroidered in a lovely pink ruffled skirt, her long hair flowing in the breeze,   encompassing something I can ejaculate to.  But today is not that day, nor can I or will I give you guarantee that that day will come. I donâ€™t know because of the vicissitudes of everything we know, I myself don't know about my self.  and then you come along, with your surge of self-righteousness, but who are you to dictate my heart and how it should love? Who are you to impose your will on who I will my heart to?  Are you God? Are you not a man?   I claim the right to feel, . . . I claim the right to mean, is that right obscene?  (Ng Yi Sheng, A Loud Poem to be Read to a Very Obliging Audience)  During an act of insubordination towards teachers, my classmates and I sat together and discussed religion during a PE lesson that we promptly decided to give a miss. Being cynical about it, I questioned whether any one of us would return and change our religious views after the discussion. What for? But a female friend noted that while it is fine to think of our religious opinion (or the lackthereof) having primary validity, it does not bestow upon us the prerogative to discriminate or devalue other religions.  To each, his own.  We listen, share, and do not impose.    So, why cannot we allow people such as TT to thrive on? Some friends plainly stated,  youâ€™re just giving the stupid fuck the attention that he wants.  Au contraire, weâ€™re giving him the attention, to listen to his largely uncorroborated views because he canâ€™t be that easily ignored when he encroaches into and impinges on our personal freedom of thought. Hence, it is the survival of my opinion or his.   And it has come to this. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i've never really thought much of the issue of being who i am, and i've never really articulated it. as in, i'm sure i have, in a strange way, or other, but always indirectly, like 'oh my god this guy is so fucking hot. i want to get into his pants.' not so much as a 'hi, i'm gay! wanna get our eyebrows plucked?'  and the good thing about mr tim 'i'm to damn smart 4 my own good' tang's attack is that it has provoked a reflection of sorts on my part on what it means to me to be gay.   there, the word. i've always hated it, a strange label on a stranger thing. i've always wondered how gay men and women could use the word as some sort of rallying point. to me it's always had such a queer meaning (oho. another word!), and a decidedly and precisely derogatory one. c.f.  faggot ,  homo ,  cocksucker  and so and so forth.  but i've always known it. i was a fucking precocious child, i knew that i liked boys since the early days. i mean, we had the obligatory crushes on girls in primary five, and i did like the girl i so-called 'had a crush on', just not in that way. i knew that there was always something more. something that mainstream society did not cater to, nor care to acknowledge.  imagine my pleasant surprise when i found jeanette winterson's marvellous little piece  oranges are not the only fruit . i have something so tangibly in common with her, our experiences: the world is so full of people who are willing to ignore what is truthful for what is convenient. and full of those who do not have mixed feelings, who approach everything from an absolutist perspective.  now i realise that what genet said applies directly to me: 'i chose to be homosexual in the sartrean sense of the word chose, like i chose my eyes to be blue.' it was a choice insofar as it was a recognition, something that i realised only in the last four days. mr tang does not realise that, when he says that he says that homosexuals are incomplete, emotionally-unstable things (yes, things, not persons), that these undesirable imbalances (because in mr tang's world human beings are perfect, healthy and happy organisms) are an effect, not a cause of homosexuality.  and they are effects only because modern society has deemed homosexuality unacceptable. (of course, the christian church, in their smallminded splendor, has had much to do with this, but i blame equally the rise of modern education and the politicisation of the right.) as such, from a young age, children are conditioned to perceive gay as wrong, gay as bad, gay as unclean. consequently, how might one expect young people -- not things -- to be emotionally stable in coping with knowing that they are different when they are taught that difference is downright dirty?  many homosexuals are emotionally unstable, many homosexuals are incomplete. many heterosexuals are emotionally stable, many heterosexuals are incomplete. it is not a homosexual condition, it is part of what i would like to believe is the human condition. despair, anger, hatred, these exist, but so does joy, peace, love. the only way to expel emotional instability is to adopt a forsterian stance of connexion, of spreading goodwill goodwill and more goodwill.  when the Conventional Family Unit and the People Who Love and Fear God and the Conservative Right-Wing try to protect themselves against the pinko-leftie-commie-faggots, they often lose sight of what is true and venture into what is imagined. there is no pink plot to undermine the Traditional Values, whatever they might be. there are merely those who are not the same and who are brave enough not to live the grand lie of the status quo. there is often a need for enemies, and if it isn't the homosexuals it will be those bastards who have the cheek to live off welfare because they can't break out of the poverty cycle. and if it isn't them it'll be someone else. who knows maybe one day the CFU, the PWLFG and the CRW will turn on themselves.  and hopefully the world will be a nicer place to live in, if not at least more polite. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Actually, on second thoughts (after I posted the last entry), I'm starting to think that he's just a very confused young boy too young to make his own decisions who does things like this in order to hear people tell him more about himself since he wouldn't know, otherwise. It's just a very bizarre way of getting therapy for free.  Which is a very stupid thing to do since it effectively means that he'll never be able to find himself any man (since the gay community is so small) nor any woman (since he is a well known misogynist), and he really has to hold true to his vow of being asexual forever and ever. I think we should all take a minute to step back and feel sorry for him. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    So Predictable I Could Cry   I'm not gay. I have a fridae profile and a gay blog, I hate women, but I'm really not gay. Really. I'm not gay.    "Please la.. it was for research." - Easy cop-out. Just like "I did drugs to gain a better PoV from the perspective of drug abusers, in order to help them more."    "I am an amoeba." - he is FUGLY?   "I intend to be asexual and single for the rest of my life" - nobody wants to sleep with him. Actually, scratch that, it's not always about sex. Nobody wants to be his friend.   "Sex is a waste of time and resources" - since when people are having sex, he's busy twiddling his thumbs thinking up flamewars, for lack of choice.    "You insisting I am gay actually shows you think homosexuality is a negative thing." - No, you twat, we don't think we're exploiting the 'fear of homosexuality', we're simply interested exposing in the blatant hypocrisy.   "More people love me than hate me" - this reeks of self-validation.   "I have a MENSA score of 130 so I am not talking rubbish on my webpage" - I will quote him on this, taking a very great leap of faith to assume this to be true:  intelligence without rightful application is useless . Somehow I'm not inclined to attribute intelligence to him, but I did say I was going to take a very great leap of faith.      Other Things That Make Me Wonder If I Should Cry or Laugh  He wants to win the Nobel Prize. It's not so bad being accused of being more asinine than Bush, because after all, Bush was nominated for the Nobel Peace Prize? He wants to write a book. He writes at all. That anyone can be so blatantly in love with the sound of their own voice - "witness my sheer glory" - I think we all know  bona fide  writers, and despite their brilliance, there have been none so pigheaded. He thinks he's a 'freelance journalist' because he pens strange letters to various low rate newspapers about things nobody gives a flying fuck about. His pretensions towards prophesy. He needlessly uses the name of the Lord in vain to suit his agenda, and does it badly as well. His pretensions towards being the upholder of social causes, and justifying his hatred by saying that 'time and resources' can be devoted to more 'meaningful' things - flamewars and hatredmongering are very meaningful things indeed. The English.. oh my goodness.  This is all I can think up off the top of my head, his idiocy does not easily translate into words. Add more if you like. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    She goes about organising her crimes against righteous and justful good hearted social workers with the help of her legions of gay   urlLink anti-anti-gay   royal subjects.   The Anti-Anti-Gay Brigade indeed! Perhaps it would be fitting to move the discussion to other avenues. The anti-anti-gay royal subjects have relocated to stopstopgays. But first, a few words - what do we hope to achieve? We all know this arose as a direct response to the inane, mindnumbing diatribes against us, and it is perfectly reasonable for us to have felt a need to mobilise. But satire would be giving him more of a voice than he deserves. Mockery would only indicate we stoop to his levels of indignity. Tearing his arguments apart, while not difficult, would induce many migraines. We all know he has no grasp of logic and no talent for the English language, certainly much less talent in constructing a viable argument in it - these are givens, and there is no need to push it.   Perhaps instead of responding with tubthumping vitriol in response to whatever hallucinations of arguments he conjures of, we could do better. "Flipping" and going berserk were understandable in the first instances, but at this point I don't think anyone has the capacity to be surprised and more appalled than they already are. While the main objective at this point is to debunk his lies and his idiocy, what would be more meaningful (and less of a waste of 'time and resources') would be to see this stand on its own against  all forms  of homophobic bigotry, not only those coming from him. I don't want to concede any forms of victory to him, and I'm not going to let him think he's managed to rile me; it shouldn't rile any of you either. The deluded have a talent for believing that all opposition to them stems from a subliminal concession that they are in fact, correct (recall Mahatir saying last year that the international community speaking out against his anti-Semitic remarks indicated he was in fact correct).  We have bigger enemies than Tim Twang Twat - his drivel will be ultimately self-defeating. Neo-conservatives with their pseudo-scientific "evidence" and ex-gay crusades are far more dangerous even if they seem less malignant now. We should all remember that we are doing this in response to him because his drivel has reminded us how dangerous it is to allow blatant hypocrisy and pseudo-religious moral sensibilities to run unchecked, but to dedicate too much airtime to him would be playing into his hands. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   whoever's writing the shit at www.stopgays.blogspot.com should immediately stop.  you will NOT believe the amount of rubbish that's offered on the site, pretending to be evidence and truth. it is hard to believe that in this supposedly post-rationalist age of ours, such true idiots still exist.  oh my god.  postmodernist criticism do not apply here. how do we know what we know? well, there's no way we can find out objective truth, unless that truth involves this person's, supposedly tim tang's, ignorance and idiocy. for in that there is certainly no doubt. this stupidity could be institutionalised.  here's a sample of the sheer madness that masquerades as madness.  --   "Homosexuals require affection and Love as we have already established that."    excuse me, but i think that pretty much everyone requires affection and Love. this is redundant, as most of your logic is. the stuff that is vaguely acceptable is only logical because it is generally true. do not fool yourself into thinking that you have established fact, when what you have done is just to repeat it. just because you know that 1+1=2 doesn't mean you invented or established it.  (i don't know why Love is capitalised, maybe to this person Love is an abstract concept that is alien and unfamiliar, and thus is a proper noun, like, you know, Peru, Marlon Brando and Intelligence. i wouldn't be surprised. it would be hard to Love someone like this.)  --   "Therefore we can see that homosexuals always have in mind a perfect wonderful person who is flawless and perfect who can easily fill in any inadequacy they may have."   i think we all strive for a love which is perfect and flawless, a vision of combined Agape and Eros. of course, i could be wrong, but from literature we often do get a strong sense of searching for that perfect love, for example, auden's search for someone he could love and could love him back, donne's ideal love combined spiritual and physical, petrarch idealised laura to an unbelievable extent.  that is, not only homosexuals (of which auden was one) but straight people (donne, petrarch) want someone who is flawless, perfect.  no one, however, wants someone who is stupid and, if that weren't enough, aggressively so.  --   "Homosexuals want to make themselves better as everyone else. They want someone that they can relate to, who else other than someone like them, someone of the same sex who acts like them, thinks like them but better than them. Logically to say homosexuals become homosexuals for this reason."   logically to say that you are unfamiliar with english idiomatic expressions.  logically also to say that you are not saying anything. what reason is this? i do not see a causal link at all. there is no logic exercised here. can't a person of the opposite sex act like oneself, think like oneself and is better than oneself?  logically to say that tim tang would have trouble finding love, because no one wants someone who doesn't act like them, can't think at all, and is better than no one. except for, perhaps. the toilet bowl.  --   "Straight people on the other hand think that they are already complete and sometimes more, so they seek out a different kind of person, a different gender to compliment their personalities and characteristics."   sylvia plath was straight. she felt intensely inadequate compared to ted hughes. phillip larkin was straight. he never found much love, although he loved porn. some of my schoolmates are straight. they'd never find love even if it came from behind them and took them up the ass.  what the hell then do you mean by this? how is it that a person of a different gender is immediately different in terms of personality and characteristics? i know of many girls who like boyish stuff, but are not lesbian. i know of many guys who like girly stuff and aren't gay.  your sexual stereotypes, tim tang, are egregious and frankly, belong in the dark ages. like your brain.  --   "But as to how homosexuals seek out their goal is a different matter altogether. We may see their attempts to get what they want as being selfish and ruthless at times or even greedy."   what goals do homosexuals seek out? let's assume emotional needs. but straight people need love too. there isn't a pink plot going on to convert X number of straight people do gay people on a year by year basis (let's call this gay GDP). no such gay GDP exists.  what other goals. hmm, let's see. sex. but that's just an ordinary, daily concern. straight people concern themselves with sex too. so if you aren't getting laid tim, you might be the exception to the rule.  selfish and ruthless at times or even greedy? isn't that human nature? some gay people i know are total bitches. some are really nice people. statistically, by the law of large numbers, different people have different characteristics, regardless of their orientation.  so i'm sorry that you're damned dumb. __   "I hope this answers any doubts as to why homosexuals become homosexuals."   well, you've not answered anything at all with your lousy syllogistic technique. and by the way, there never was any doubt anyway: studies are underway to prove that homosexuals are merely born with a larger front anterior cortex (i think it's called that, i could be mistaken) or it's something to do with the amygdala.  freudian views of a weak father, and jungian views of an unintegrated shadow, and many other forms of unproven psychobabble have been largely discredited.  like you.  --  so please. don't pretend to be really smart, because you really really aren't. i suggest you stop writing frivolous and lousy articles on your blog. it's getting a name for egregious stupidity.  so get a life. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   just to see if we can stop the stupidity by counteracting with intelligent, sensitive discussions. 

						
</post>





</Blog>