<Blog>


<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to take the plunge. I am a grown-up and figured it was time for my daily thoughts and small rants to reflect that. A few of you may have known my, far between, lj entries "The Pink Fit." Now...you can find me posting on Loft 31. This will be space for the world to see, read, and enjoy.  Ok...now I am going to get back to watching Liza's Biography.  -Miss S
     

    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Matthew you should name your band after the scientific name instead and have people wondering what it means.  My lovely scientist boyfriend informed me of the meaning of Amorphophallus titanum.  I'm not sure I want to post the meaning up on here...  I'll keep my posts clean.     P.S.  But you should definetly look it up...you'd probably get a laugh out of it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's now official...the name of my next band is going to be CORPSE FLOWER.  Extremely tough and dark sounding while also being sensitive and fragile.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out this  urlLink link   When I was at UConn, I had wished this would happen when I was there.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blurry, but I guess that's "artistic" or something.  nice vivid colors though.  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      amy and I in for the food and tv night tonight.  she's up at the office working for a while, but we'll try to get over there around 7:45 or 8.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just to let you all know Me, Cyndi and Sonia are going to make dinner before Six Feet Under.  So if your interested in comming let us know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cyndi and I just went to Samuri Sams and it wasnt half bad.  Thanks for the recomendation on it Mathew.   If you are down to hang out tonight give us a call.  Additionally there will be a viewing of Six Feet Under tommorow so we better see you all.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Join us tonight for Blow Out and Queer Eye starting at 8 p.m.    And I'm making cookies!!!    See you guys tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      matthew and i won't be at 6 feet under tonight, because i am dragging him with me to day break while i study. ssshhhh! i don't want to hear it! he's coming with me and that's final. mwhha ha ha ha!   we will, however be over for queer eye for the straight guy, if that's still on?  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, I hope you all had a great weekend.  It was a very pleasent surprise to see Sonia and Jackie sneek up on us when we got home. Cyndi and I thought we were about to be gunned down.    Well, Six feet under is on at 9 tonight so come on OVER!!!!  P.S.  Sonia i put a link to the Best week ever blog under links
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone...did you guys know there is a "best week ever blog?" yay!   well i am off to the movies with the fabulous miss jackie.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey thanks for the invite Chris. My stupid home phone was turned off, so I can only get online at work now. That's the reason I've taken my sweet ass time joining up and all. Now maybe I won't feel so out of whatever loop there might be. I haven't been doing much of anything lately aside from working...so yeah. awesome! Jake
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have a good weekend all.  I will post what time Six feet under will be on Monday.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh Matthew you got the Sims?  It is sooo addicting.  That's all I used to do last year.  It was bad.  And I sucked for awhile too until I figured out all the cheat codes.  But I will keep you in suspense about those too (because I can't remember them right now, ha!)  I hope nothing happened to you in this accident that you're leaving us all in suspense about.  Wine bar tonight if you can make it out...then you can finish the story.  I'll post a time for tonight some time today when I find out or we'll just give you a call.    Hope to see everyone there tonight!  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry I missed your call Chris.  I didn't get the message about Chimy's until just a few minutes ago.  So yeah, I'm back in town, and I have a story to tell everyone.  When I was just south of Post, this suburban pulling a camper flipped right in front of me...  I'll leave it at that and let the suspense build so you will all want me to tell you the story the next time you see me (or something like that).  sad sidenote: I'm addicted to The Sims. even sadder sidenote: I suck at The Sims.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa Chris!  How did that happen?  Are you just trying to steal my identity?  Then we could be on those identity theft commercials and you can pretend you're me.  Imagine that.    Let's try this again...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thats weird Cyndi posted under my name last time.  I wonder how that happened.    Just a reminder:  Tonight Blowout and Queer Eye at my house.  2001 28th St Apt A. Festivities start around 8. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Sonia I saw that Who's the Boss was having a marathon but I stayed away because I needed to finish my homework.  Who needs homework when you can watch Who's the Boss all night long?  I used to love that show along with TGIF.  They need to bring that back.  My friday nights just haven't been the same since.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cyndi and I are down.  Just let us know the time.    Look at this insane email I just got from Yahoo: You are currently exceeding your Yahoo! Mail storage quota by a very large amount. You are only allowed -2048.0MB of storage but you are currently using 0.5MB of storage. Your account has been temporarily disabled from receiving new messages.  These guys need to get their heads on straight. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok...as we are all working to revive our "old group" jesse and i were talking about all of us getting together to a trip to chimmy's. any takers?   also for you old school teevee fans...there is a "who's the boss" marathon. ahhh yeah!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay. i'm on! now what to say, what to say. dang. got nothin'. sorry I won't make it out to the brewery tonight. but i assume jesse passed his thesis defense since everyone's going out? well, someone drink a brew for me (even though i don't normally drink them). over and out. (can i say that?)
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You still alive Jessie?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Six feet under is on TONIGHT.  If you want to come by and watch it at my house the address is 2001 28th St. Its a yellowish green duplex with a huge stockade metal looking fence.  If you can park behind the house or on the opposite side of the street from the fence.  If you need to call me: 239 4482.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay Sonia!  After a few tries you are finally in.    Chris maybe you shouldn't diss on Mac users.  Ahem.  For you lovely...better than PC...Mac users you can use  urlLink this  to upload pics and then just paste the link it shows for posting in journals.  Just an idea, but I'm sure there are a million programs out there that will work.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi kids...i am here! finally! it's like in gym class and you aren't the last kid picked for dodgeball. finally i am a winner! i too have joined blog-mania 2004. my spot is called loft 31. i don't quite know how to add people...so if you guys could help a sista out feel free.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, if you are interested in posting pictures on here go get  urlLink HELLO  from picasa.  You can use that to post pictures.  I am sorry to all the mac users cause it wont work on your computer.  You will have to do it the old fashion way.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Matthew, I'll be waiting for the dance moves...and Jesse you should really try and come.  Good luck and try not to lose your mind.  There will be no reason to "take it like a man" because I'm sure you'll do well.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I empathize with ya Jess.  One of the most stressful times of my life was when I had my defense.  I had been up for 48 straight hours, eating only BBQ Ruffles 3Ds, and drinking Code Red Mountain Dew.  It was not pleasent.    You will do fine though, I am sure of it.  Just remember, if it does get bad you just have to bend over and take it like a man.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nice...last time i went to the wine bar, i had quite a few glasses and showed everyone my usher dance moves.  so, yes, count me in for tonight.  jesse, during my thesis defense, i just got used to saying, "yes dr. conrad, you're right and i am wrong."  and the sad part is that i wasn't being sarcastic.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its final,  Im dreaming about my defense now.  Im going crazy, so I might be up for a little wine later on.  Chris I tried calling Dr. Pope and no answer.  I sent him an email too.  If he calls back should I invite him to the wine bar.  Yeah, that would be a blast.    Adios,   Raul
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9 tonight.  wine bar.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Would anyone like to go to the wine bar or do something else tonight?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think we're officially addicted.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cyndi and I wanted to start this blog we thought it would be nice for all of us (friends and aquintances) to have a place to talk about things that are going on in Lubbock.  We used to have one of these a while back but it ended up dying out as people moved away or became too consumed with work/school.  So we are giving it another try.  It was nice because it provided an open forum to talk about whatever you like such as things going on , things  we don't like, upcomming hang out sessions, or just whatever the hell you want.   This is suppose to be a happy place for all so don't get excessively crude or mean.  If you do your posts will be deleted and you will be banned.  And just as a reminder to any of you who may be newbies:  make sure when you write a post to not only post it, but click on the "publish" button as well.    
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      to Mrs. Avila!!!  Thank you Sonia for putting the scavenger hunt together.  It was the BEST!!!  UPGRADE!!  HUUUUGE UPGRADE!  I already can't wait for the next one.    :)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi everyone...  1. i have always enjoyed listening rev. al. don't you guys think his mouth opens and closes like beaker from the muppets?   2. i will have to postpone the scavenger hunt. i can leave the clues though, if you guys want to still have the great hunt tonight. i couldn't get out of the 50th bday festivities for my mom. geez! colorado here i come!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know what everyones political beliefs are but I found this quote from Rev. Al Sharpton right on point. I didnt think I would have ever quoted him in my life but........        "     The issue of government is not to determine who may sleep together in the bedroom, it's to help those that might not be eating in the kitchen."          - Rev. Al Sharpton, 2004 National Democratic Convention, Boston  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi gang...  the hunt may have to be postponed. there is a possibility that i'll be going out of town this weekend and leaving thursday afternoon. is there anyother night that's good for everyone? i am taking nominations now. :)  like a stormteam doppler member...i'll keep you posted on any new developments.  -s
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i had to miss out on QE last night, but i'll be there for&nbsp;sonia's l-town scavenger hunt this thursday! i'm so excited. i've also been wanting to see monster and i missed out on that too - shoooot. matthew won't watch it because he thinks it will be too disturbing, which it probably would be. did you guys like it?   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all,  Do to the fact that I need to return Monster tommorow, I think we should watch it.  I'll even make some pop corn for all you willing participants.  The movie will start when you all get here.        
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HEY ALL.    Sonia you beat me to it.  QE will be at the casa de chris, nagles, mozzy, missy and indie.  BE HERE!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey cyndi...is QE at your house or a la casa de chris?  sonia  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't wait for the scavenger hunt.  I bet there are a ton of surprises.  And I want you on my team, Sonia.  ;)  Anyway, today is Tuesday.  You all know the deal.    See you tonight!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bring your sneakers, a digi camera, and a partner!  the first annual "lubbock can be cool" scavenger hunt will take place on thursday, july 29th. (this is subject to change).  more details to come...  invite others...!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey All my phone is going to be temporarily out of service so you can call my house at the landline     765-7643      
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My last entry was a joke.  Chris = a good time all around.  Yay!    In other news, what does everyone think about having a potluck or something of the sort tonight?  I'm not sure who's planning on coming but today is such a good day for friends to get together and cook.  :)  Call me or Chris if you're interested.  Now to continue on with the great job hunt...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Lubbock is beautiful on days like this    I love the rain. Today is the kind of day i have been hoping for for a long time now.   Its days like this that wash the miseries away from the daily living here in Lubbock.      Anyways Six feet under my house tonight at 8.      Adios !  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You suck!  Good times are only had when you're not around.    Good fun night with Chris = watching a TERRIBLE movie called Cabin Fever where all the kids spit blood everywhere.  Ho hum....
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY!!   I am back home.   It sounds like i missed out on a good time last night.    We need to hang out tonight too!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey cyndi...how did the test go? "rosa" was all i could remember from your notecard making. haha. count me in for a dose of "whatever."
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All of my tests are finally done!!!  After a hard week in school it's time to party.  What's going on tonight?  Thursday nights always seem to be "whatever floats your boat" night.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink George W. Bush and John Kerry sing Woodie Guthrie's "This Land Is Your Land."   Thanks to everyone for coming out to the last PFL show.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sorry for my last post.  There is no Tuesday night lineup since its Cyndi and Mathews last show.  You better be there  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Tuesday lineup for tonight is Plan for Landing at the new Tokyo Joes.  I hope everyone will be there for our final show.  :(  Make sure to bring your box of kleenex to wipe away the tears.  Haha.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have yet to go to sleep since 6 am yesterday.  Oh what i do for the love of science.  haha i am a nerd.      I hope to see you all tonight for the Tuesday night lineup.      And check this story out  urlLink CLICK   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey kids...you can always count on me. i am sure that's a slogan for something, but i am sure it applies to bbq. what shall i bring?! i still can't believe last nights 6 ft...that guy deserves an emmy nod.  in other news...i don't care for the new "belle" on days. she doesn't even look like the old belle black. sheesh! who cares as long as they keep patrick right?! haha
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Christina, don't forget to click publish post after you post.  I noticed you had a post that is being saved as a draft.  Unless you  meant to do that...  I don't know.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A potluck&nbsp;BBQ sounds great. I like to cook. It is tooooo much fun! And I've been wanting to see if I can make a pasta salad like my Mom used to because pasta salad is perfect for summer.  &nbsp;  Just let me know!     
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Jake sorry we missed the show.   I didnt even realized you had posted until just now.      Did any of you besides Jeremy Sonia and Cyndi catch six feet under.  It was an amazing episode.  It left you feeling all stressed out.  Poor David.  Not only does the guy get beat up and robbed but he is forced to smoke crack and then gets busted in the face and left in the ghetto.      Cyndi and I would like to have a potluck BBQ soon.  Any one interested?        
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello.  &nbsp; tonight at j&amp;b at about 8 if you're interested.  &nbsp; it's me, morgan, and jared from the conversation.  it will be $3 just to get jared a little gas money word, b'bye jake 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the blog Brian and Christina!!&nbsp; :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a reminder Six feet under is on tonight.  So come on by to my house.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cyndi and i went to go see Farenheit 9/11 last night with Brian and Christina and the movie was amazing.  I know that there is the Moore slant on alot of the information portrayed in that movie, but still its impossible to hide the corruption and the fear that our government is instilling in the American people.  Throughout the whole movie Cyndi and I were just getting more pissed off the more that Moore kept showing and uncovering.  I strongly reccomend this to any of you who havent seen it!!!!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Now it's time to party and we'll party hard (party hard)    Let's get a party going (let's get a party going)    When it's time to party we will always party hard   &nbsp;  i have to deliver a birthday present to my friend jamie tonight, but other than that i'm down for hanging out as long as it is cheap or free.&nbsp; i mean, i'm all about the benjamins, obviously, but a brotha's &nbsp;gotta be thrifty.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets do something tonight dammit!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, We are going to be watching I love the 90s and some other stuff tonight at Cyndi dearest's apt tonight.  We are going to order some Chinese Food from Summer Palace so if you want some let us know in advance so we can phone it in.  For directions please call me on my cell:   806 239 4482.  For all that missed it six feet under last night was DAMNED GOOD!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey kids...  i have missed you all. the world is just not the same without all you. i am guessing that everyone had a fun holiday. down here it's been really humid and pretty much typical san antonio....busy, busy, lots of mexicans (haha). i've been busy at the job fair, doing a pharamaceutical observation, and the all important pedicure. i tried to email you chris...to send you and cyndi a hello but it emailed it back to me. to quote jackie "meh."   so i am dying that blow out is over..and i missed it! argh.  well count me in for bbq fun...at this time tomorrow i'll hit lubbrock like a hurricane.  also...be prepared i've been working on the scavenger hunt!  well i am off...i just had to reconnect with the world.  oh yeah one more thing...i found fisheries jobs...odd huh?!  -miss s  shout out to: jackie, cyndi, chris, peanut, matthew, amy who wears fast socks, the newly official maxx, indie, mozzy, nags, missy, and everyone else who reads the blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, I hope that you all had a good fourth of july.  Cyndi and I did.  Is there anything going on this week?  Just to let you know that next Tuesday that there will be a new Queer Eye (in England) and the season finale of Blow out.    Cyndi and i are thinking of having a picnic bbq potluck jobbie this weekend.  Anyone interested in that?  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just finished creating a new photos section for the Plan For Landing website.  i really should have been packing instead of doing this.  anyway, check out the new photos section at  urlLink www.planforlanding.net .  Happy early 4th of July to everyone, since i won't have access to a computer for a few days.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey chris...  i can leave and return whenever. i have no schedule.  -sonia
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Hey guys i hope your week has been going well.  Hope Target is treating you well Jeremy.  Sonia and Jackie I need to find out what time you guys will want to leave and what time you need to get back from Hell Paso  this weekend.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been a long long long day guys.  Sorry to stress you out beanie.  I am excited to go see Cyndi this weekend how about you all?  I am very proud of you killing her with kindness bean.  I wish i could have witnessed it. There is going to be no way i am going to be able to do somethign tonight but maybe tommorow or THursday.  WE will see.  Good luck jeremy at Target and i will give you and Sonia tomorow.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jeremy...i have placed the call to get your number. i have no plans tonight though. i do know that jackie is closing...so no fun for her. i do agree that we should somehow make chris have fun. we'll try! and cyndi i am having the worst time finding a gift for you. i bought something but i am affraid you won't like it. in fact i think i am going to return it. argh! decisions. decisions. decisions.  -sonia
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wanted to hang out tonight Christopher!  But thats totally understandable...I don't really care for crunch time, but we've gotta do it.  Good luck though, I'm sure it's going to be great.  So Sonia and Jackie, do you guys have plans for tonight too?  I'm about to go to Lamesa to have lunch with my mother, so give me a call in a little bit and we can chat.  Actually, call Cyndi or Chris to get my number, I don't think that you have it, and I really don't want to put my phone number on the internet.  No mas prank calls for Peanut!  I hope everyone is having a good day!  I'll talk to you guys later.  Good luck again, Chris.  ~P 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is probably not a good thing that I stress out over the work YOU have to do, Chris.  Someone needs to get Chris away from his work and make him have fun for a little bit this week.  mhmmm...  I'm not sure when Jeremy's shift starts (but maybe he'll read this and post it...if we're lucky).  But I definitely think pictures should be taken.  I wish I could be there.    Today, Tomorrow, Hump Day, Thursday, FRIDAY!!   I can't wait any longer.  P.S.  I killed my bro's gf with kindness last night and it was the best!  Just thought I'd add that in there.  ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Regretfully i am not going to be able to hang out tongiht.  I have run into some major problems with some of my models that i am presenting in Wisc. in a couple weeks.  I need to get them finished in order to make a presentation and practice it several times before we go so i need to get the errors corrected as soon as possible.  So unless something changes I wont be able to hang out.  I will keep you all posted though.  Sorry, 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks Cyndi! What can I say Lubbock isn't as bubbly without you. I think the LBK is missing your laugh. So I am curious...when is Peanut's first shift? Maybe I should immortalize the moment in a photo.  -Sonia
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really really really miss all of you.  :(  My days just aren't the same.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First of all, Congrats to Sonia for getting a job interview!!!  I'm so excited for you.  I couldn't express how excited I was on the phone earlier because I was in the middle of Target.  Ha!  Second of all, that bitch is going down!!!  Yeah.  If you don't know who I'm talking about, ask me.  :)  Woohoo.  Thirdly, Jeremy starts working at Target wednesday and I can't be there to witness his first day in a red shirt and khakis so everyone should go in my place!  And I'm now alone at Aalon :( so Jackie, I left you message and you should go fill out an app. and pretend like you don't know Jeremy.  Haha.    Fourth...I can't wait till Friday when El Paso will be taken over by the dynamic duo with a side of Chris.  I'm ex-super-cited!  Love, love, love from ME!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sounds good to me Christina.  Have a good trip too!  Call us when you get back in town.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone! I just wanted to say have a great time in El Paso Cyndi. I won't be in Lubbock for our birthday either, but we definetly need to have a party when we are both back in town! I'll be back the 20th so anytime after that is good for me! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'd know that hiiiii anywhere! hey peanut...welcome to the blog. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the blog Jeremy! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lookie whos here?!?  ME!  btw: I look like caca in that picture Cyndi, we need to take another one. :o)  Your boobs look good too. ;o) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a que tiempo es...taco tuesday?   haha (no translation for that)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone...the blog looked lonely so I thought I would post a few tuesday thoughts. oh...sorry about that pic cyndi...i should have cropped it. i didn't think about it. oh and the radio show was fun to listen to. i have a nomination for your name...maybe the word star in some other language or something else asian inspired. just ideas.  ok now for my rant. i know there has been some maroon 5 in the ears of lubbockites lately. has anyone seen the video for "she will be loved?" ok...i "love" this videa. now it's not all interesting and creative like say the modest mouse or franz ferdinand vids but this is like a mini-movie. it's a four minute movie that i will (a) not fall asleep during, (b) do not have to pay $4.50 for, (c) has no coming attractions to sit through, and (d) don't have to deal with people eating popcorn loudly next to me. but anyway..it's very Mrs.Robinson, but I wonder which lady ends up with Adam?  What time is Taco Tues?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa could my boobs look any bigger.  Woohoo!  Goodness.  Hmm...I don't want to write my lab report...but someone's gotta do it.    Taco Tuesday tomorrow my lovelies...and of course Queer Eye.  See you all tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I am posting this for Miss Sonia since she cannot.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha just kidding. I am thinking of having a small cook out tonight at 4ish?  Who is interested?  Can anyone bring anything?    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>