<Blog>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        You should be a Bunny!    urlLink   What Should Your Halloween Costume Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Actually we are dressing up as masquerade people. All black formals with gloves and harlequin masks. Very cool!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      John Kerry. International Man of Mystery? Is Kerry Making Stuff Up Or Is There A "Deep Throat" At The U.N?   KERRY CLAIMS TO KNOW OF SECRET PRE-WAR DEAL . . .   April 2, 2003: Claims He Spoke To Number Of Foreign Leaders But  Doesn't Name Names. "In remarks in the basement of the Peterborough  Public Library Kerry … said `I talked to leaders of a number of  countries … that told me they lost all confidence in the  administration.'"   urlLink (James Pindell, "Kerry: $8 Million In The Bank," PoliticsNH.com Website, www.politicsnh.com, Accessed 4/3/03)   October 20, 2003: Claims Bush Administration Refused To Work With  France And Russia But Doesn't Offer Specifics. "I talked to [UN  Secretary-General] Kofi Annan the Sunday before the president decided  to go to war.  And I knew at that moment in time that the Russians  and the French were prepared to, in fact, make a further offer."   (MSNBC's "Hardball," 10/20/03)  October 21, 2003: Says I'll Tell You Later.  "`I have it on the  highest authority' that the French and Russians were prepared to make  an offer at the UN, but were rebuffed by American officials intent on  going to war, Kerry said. `I'm going to talk about it more publicly  at a later time.'  [Kerry] would not disclose details of the position  the countries, which opposed the US-led military offensive, were  prepared to take or identify the source of the information."   (Patrick Healy, "Kerry Won't Elaborate On Missed Deal," The Boston  Globe, 10/22/03)  SO SECRET, ONLY HE KNOWS?   EVEN FRENCH AND RUSSIANS ARE BEFUDDLED  October 23, 2003: Assertions Disputed By France And Russia.   "The  French and Russian ambassadors to the UN, in separate interviews  Thursday, said they knew nothing about any private offers made by  their governments to the US on the eve of the war.  The envoys told  the Globe that the only concession made was a public proposal to  extend weapons inspections in Iraq by four months before military  action could begin. … Kerry questioned whether the two ambassadors  were fully apprised of the proposals that top officials in Paris and  Moscow were prepared to discuss, however."   (Patrick Healy, "Kerry  Presses Assault On Bush," The Boston Globe, 10/25/03)  A Publication of the RNC Research Department   Paid for by the Republican National Committee.  Not authorized by any  candidate or candidate committee. 310 First Street SE, Washington, DC 20003 - www.gop.com     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you ever had a really bad headache, then you took some tylenol (or excedrin migrane in my case since I knew it was a migrane coming on) and then a few hours later your whole head tingles? Mine is doing that right now, and it feels totally funny but a good funny. Like I don't want it to stop. hee hee. I'll be back later with some real news. I swear I haven't done any illegal substances....not yet anyways.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing pisses me off than offering something only to have it snached away. Long story short, I invited the  urlLink madponies  to KC for Jessica Simpson. Well, the station didn't have a venue and when they got one, boom, they wanted the show 18 and over. Grrrr.....so Lauren can't go. Pisses me off. I hate when they do that. They alienate 30% of our listeners. Makes me mad!!!!!!!!!!! Why? So now I've got Stacie Orrico tickets, at Orlando's. Tammy wants those and she's gotta sit in the front row and scream. I'm gonna make her.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sunday Morning Barf Bag!   So I wake up this morning, an hour late because of daylight savings time (remember to change your clocks) to find a fresh pot of coffee (yes!) and cute little moron George Clooney on CNN's  urlLink Reliable Sources . Now I'm all for people promoting their movies and all but it really didn't surprise me that Georgie the liberal idiot was on the leaning so left it walks with a tilt CNN because he had things to say that people care about. I care Georgie, really I do but come on hunny. When was the last time you had a hit movie? Ocean's 11. This last one doesn't count because Catherine Zeta Jones is in it and everyone's going to see her anyway. Thankfully, I only saw the tail end of the show where they talked about all around cool guy, urlLink  Mr Bill O'Reilly  and his repeated requests to have George in a tet-a-tet on the O'Reilly Factor on Fox. George's response? Well, if CNN and Reliable Sources were more reliable, I would post what he said verbatim but unfortunately, I can't find it at the moment so I'll sum up. He accused Bill of only wanting him on during sweeps and that he would talk to him on Larry King, and only Larry King and when he wasn't selling a book. Excuse me, Mr Clooney, but aren't you promoting a movie called Intolerable Cruelty? Pot, meet black kettle.   Also got a chance to check out George Snuffalupagus and the "new all fancy, we're trying so hard to be like Fox" This Week Sunday News show.  How fun. Cute as he is, he can't help but be stupid, huh?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, it's offical. I'm obsessed. I can't help myself. I've watched Lord Of The Rings: The Two Towers again. I need a serious intervention   But Viggo Mortensen is hot!!!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Interesting stuff...   Q. What occurs more often in December than any other month? A. Conception.   Q. What separates "60 Minutes" on CBS from every other TV show? A. No theme song.   Q. Half of all Americans live within 50 miles of what? A. Their birthplace.   Q. Most boat owners name their boats. What is the most popular name? A. Obsession   Q. If you were to spell out numbers, how far would you have to count until you found the letter "A"? A. One thousand   Q. What do bullet proof vests, fire escapes, windshield wipers, and laser printers all have in common? A. All invented by women.   Q. What is the only food that doesn't spoil? A. Honey   Q. There are more collect calls on this day than any other day of the year? A. Father's Day   Q. What trivial fact about MeL Blanc (voice of Bugs Bunny) is the most ironic? A. He was allergic to carrots.   Q. What is an activity performed by 40% of all people at a party? A. Snoop in your medicine cabinet.   Q. What word has over 400 definitions? A. SET   Did you know...   The first couple to be shown in bed together on prime time television were Fred and Wilma Flintstone.   Coca-Cola was originally green.   Every day more money is printed for Monopoly than the US Treasury.   Men can read smaller print than women; women can hear & smell better.   The state with the highest percentage of people who walk to work is Alaska. The percentage of Africa that is wilderness: 28% The percentage of North America that is wilderness: 38%   The cost of raising a medium-size dog to the age of eleven: $6,400   The average number of people airborne over the US any given hour is 61,000.   Intelligent people have more zinc and copper in their hair.   San Francisco Cable cars are the only mobile National Monuments.   Each king in a deck of playing cards represents a great king from history: Spades - King David; Clubs - Alexander the Great; Hearts -Charlemagne; Diamonds - Julius Caesar   111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321   If a statue in the park of a person on a horse has both front legs in the air, the person died in battle. If the horse has one front leg in the air, the person died as a result of wounds received in battle. If the horse has all four legs on the ground, the person died of natural causes.   Only two people signed the Declaration of Independence on July 4th, John Hancock and Charles Thomson. Most of the rest signed on August 2, but the last signature wasn't added until 5 years later.   "I am." is the shortest complete sentence in the English language.   The term "the whole 9 yards" came from WWII fighter pilots in the South Pacific. When arming their airplanes on the ground, the.50 caliber machine gun ammo belts measured exactly 27 feet, before being loaded into the fuselage. If the pilots fired all their ammo at a target, it got "The whole 9 yards."   Hershey's Kisses are called that because the machine that makes them looks like it's kissing the conveyor belt.   The phrase "rule of thumb" is derived from an old English law which stated that you couldn't beat your wife with anything wider than your thumb.   The name Jeep came from the abbreviation used in the army for the "General Purpose" vehicle, G.P.   The cruise liner, Queen Elizabeth II, moves only six inches for each gallon of diesel that it burns.   The only two days of the year in which there are no professional sports games (MLB, NBA, NHL, or NFL) are the day before and the day after the Major League All-Stars Game.   The nursery rhyme "Ring Around the Rosey" is a rhyme about the plague. Infected people with the plague would get red circular sores ("Ring around the rosey"). The sores would smell very badly so common folks would put flowers on their bodies somewhere (inconspicuously), so that it would cover the smell of the sores ("a pocket full of posies"). Furthermore, people who died from the plague would be burned so as to reduce the possible spread ofthe disease ("ashes, ashes, we all fall down").     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday funny picture of the day. I actually have this on my office door. We got it out of The Onion Newspaper. It's a real ad for a real place  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday's hot guy picture.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow. I've been busy. (translation: I haven't done jack shit) actually I have been busy. Nate was in town yesterday. Brandy went to the National Team(soccer)game with him and then I met them at O'Dowds and Eddie was there. We'll get back to Eddie in a minute. Monday, I can't remember what I did. Tuesday, I had a station party then met Brandy out for drinks, dinner and fun at Harpo's then Tammy and Amanda met us. Brandy met a boy there and they are happily emailing each other last time I checked. He was a step up from a car salesman in my book but when has my high powered judgmental attitude ever stopped Brandy. (never, okay maybe once but I was really right about it.) Yesterday was O'dowds and tonight was the Queen's party. How fun. We went to Kabuki Japanese Steakhouse in Crown Center. I've never personally eaten Japanese but it wasn't too bad. Fried shrimp and crab with teriake steak. Not much to write home about but hey it wasn't god awful either. So Rustichick and NurseBuxom were there. I've talked to them from the urlLink  Sweet Potato Queens  board. Too fun. If you haven't read Her Royal Highness Jill Conner Browne's books, you haven't lived a very full life and if you are a woman you should drop whatever you happen to be doing at the moment and go get them immediately. Especially the Big Ass Cookbook, because you need to put some meat on your bones.  Back to Eddie. Eddie is Eddie Delahunt. I met Eddie about almost 7 years ago. Eddie is my first and only love if there ever was one when it comes to drinking beer, singing Irish tunes and basic all around happiness. You can find more about him at  urlLink www.eddiedelahunt.com If I were you, I'd book him immediately and pay him big buckaroos!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, there's  urlLink pictures!!!!  Cool! You can see my wierd ass. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink a mystery of my life solved  Now I know why I'm always so broke. I'm a Homer Simpson. The number of drinks I've consumed since I've been legal is 7534.8. The amount of money that I've spent is $48,222.72 and the amount I drink could fill 5.79 bathtubs. But I still can't buy a ferrari. Not that I would want one anyways. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink  Cabana boy  is drinking coffee......at 3 in the afternoon.  And boy does it smell good!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  So, I love the show Newlyweds: Nick And Jessica. And they are coming to town thanks to our station! HOORAY! I'm so excited. I can not wait. I've met a few people but I've got a huge crush on Nick and I can not wait to trap him in the station van......okay, maybe not.  But he's coming and she's coming and I've got lots of tuna lined up!!!!!! I'm Sooo excited. We're gonna be on Newlyweds!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Never hold your farts in. They travel up your spine, into your brain, and that's where you get shitty ideas from.  -Tammy 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      got these in the mail, since I have a cat I thought it was funny. :)  EXCERPTS FROM A DOG'S DAILY DIARY   8:00 am - OH BOY! DOG FOOD! MY FAVORITE! 9:30 am - OH BOY! A CAR RIDE! MY FAVORITE! 9:40 am - OH BOY! A WALK! MY FAVORITE!v 10:30 am - OH BOY! A CAR RIDE! MY FAVORITE! 11:30 am - OH BOY! DOG FOOD! MY FAVORITE! 12:00 pm - OH BOY! THE KIDS! MY FAVORITE! 1:00 pm - OH BOY! THE YARD! MY FAVORITE!v 4:00 pm - OH BOY! THE KIDS! MY FAVORITE! 5:00 pm - OH BOY! DOG FOOD! MY FAVORITE! 5:30 pm - OH BOY! MUM! MY FAVORITE! 6:00 pm - OH BOY! PLAYING BALL! MY FAVORITE! 6:30 pm - OH BOY! SLEEPING IN MASTER'S BED! MY FAVORITE!  EXCERPTS FROM A CAT'S DAILY DIARY   Day 183  My captors continue to taunt me with bizarre little dangling objects. They dine lavishly on fresh meat, while I am forced to eat dry cereal. The only thing that keeps me going is the hope of escape, and the mild satisfaction I get from ruining the occasional piece of furniture. Tomorrow I may eat another houseplant. Today my attempt to kill my captors by weaving around their feet while they were walking almost succeeded, must try this at the top of the stairs. In an attempt to disgust and repulse these vile oppressors, I once again induced myself to vomit on their favorite chair, must try this on their bed.   Decapitated a mouse and brought them the headless body, in attempt to make them aware of what I am capable of, and to try to strike fear into their hearts. They only cooed and condescended about what a good little cat I was. Hmmm, not working according to plan.   There was some sort! of gathering of their accomplices. I was placed in solitary throughout the event. However, I could hear the noise and smell the food. More importantly I overheard that my confinement was due to MY power of "allergies." Must learn what this is and how to use it to my advantage. I am convinced the other captives are flunkies and maybe snitches. The dog is routinely released and seems more than happy to return. He is obviously a half-wit. The bird on the other hand has got to be an informant, and speaks with them regularly. I am certain he reports my every move. Due to his current placement in the metal room, his safety is assured. But I can wait, It is only a matter of time. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Demi Moore and Ashton Kutcher are to be married next year, according to reports, and the bride will be given away by her ex-husband. Toyboy Kutcher reportedly asked the actress to be his old woman in time-honored tradition. 'It's official,' he told pals. 'I got down on one knee to propose to Demi and she said "yes." We were both so happy we had tears in our eyes.' And Bruce Willis may well be shedding a tear or two if he decides to accept his former wife's proposal that he give her away, since the wedding will take place at an altar in Las Vegas, the city where he and Moore tied the knot themselves in 1987. An estimated £600,000 will be spent on the wedding, and 120 guests will be invited to what is thought will be a Valentine's Day ceremony. 'He'll want his twin brother Michael to be best man, and don't be surprised to see Bruce giving the bride away,' said the friend. Reports recently that Kutcher had taken his woman friend to meet the folks fuelled speculation the couple were gearing up to get hitched. 'We sat and talked about her kids, and my kids, and we had a great time,' said Kutcher's mother, Diane Portwood. The happiness with the union may stem more from the fact that Ashton's mum isn't so much losing a son, as gaining a sister.  Does this bother anyone besides me? I don't care so much as he's younger, just I don't see Ashton and Demi having much in common, like Justin and Cameron don't have much in common. I don't know them personally but hey I'm just taking a random guess. Ben and Jen had a little more in common. He's a pretty boy, she's J.Lo. He likes to gamble, she likes spending money but her "love don't cost a thing".  Just 1.6 million in the form of a pank and white sparklie on her left ring finger. You could feed a small country in Africa for what her ring cost. Hell, if Hollywood would donate one million a piece to the Iraqi fix up fund, we'd have $87 billion in no time. But why would they do such a thing? How politically incorrect that would be. Funding other people's freedom. How horrible. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just to let you know, if you haven't read  urlLink madpony.com  lately, you need to. Kristin's ideas on Baseball are not only humorous, but informative too!!!!  Go Sox!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I slept till 8:15 this morning. It was a hat wearin, no shower day. I don't feel very good. I'm very very sleepy and I know it's due to the fact that I just took some Benadryl. That stuff always makes me feel very sleepy and ironically enough, it's non-drowsy. So I'll wrap this up rather quick. I'm gonna go and do my streetscenes and go home. Besides, if I sit her much longer I'm going to eat all the candy in my cup on my desk. I know I'm PMSing but that's rediculous.   Got a ton of e-mail today, including 1500 posts from the stupid Britney Spears fans. Geez, it's a shitty song. Get off it and quit with the e-mails. I'm not supprised the server crashed. I just got 12 more of them. I sent them all back with a reply that the Top 20 does not respond to spam from artist's websites. Thank you. When in all reality I wanted to put on the end of the message, "now fuck off and go annoy someone else!" I guess the world needs lemmings somewhere. Speaking of artist's, Trey from Magik gave me Outkast's new double CD Speakerboxxx/The Love Below. I jammed to it in my car and I have to say, it's really really good! I've always liked Outkast though, even when Ms. Jackson got old and played out and honestly, it's a pretty good CD from the little scan and sample I got. I need to sit down and actually listen to the whole thing. Right now in the office it's moody with the candles burning and Tori Amos on the stereo. It's kinda an avoid me day.   Perhaps because the Cubbies lost? Maybe, maybe not. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's official. I'm getting old. For some unknown reason I woke up from a nice and peaceful sleep at around 3:40ish and I couldn't for the life of me get back to sleep. So I said fuck it and got up, went to the grocery store at 4am and got sausage, hash browns, tortillas and some Pace Picante sauce.  I had to eat Egg Stuff this morning. So I'm slowly decaying into one of those little old biddies that only needs three hours of sleep and goes to the grocery store really early. It doesn't help at all that my allergies are acting up. I had a way early morning sneezing fit. How fun. Now it's 6:30 and I'm tired. Even after two cups of coffee. 20 ounces to be exact.   I could sleep for a few minutes till 7, then get up and take a shower. Or I could just keep writing......  need a nap. Gonna sleep.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink when office supplies attack  EXPERIENCE ZE FRANK: In times of dire crisis... when the unthinkable occurs... when office supplies attack you'd better make sure to... take a picture. There are a number of ways to experience Ze Frank. On this site you can be a part of a number of quirky projects -- all you need is a camera. If you ever encounter a disgruntled piece of office supplies, shed a few crocodile tears, create a wardrobe of toilet paper, or write a single word on a piece of paper, take a photograph and send it in. View his video series which includes the "how to dance properly training workshop" and the "how to impress your date" tutorial. Ze Frank also provides interesting games, interactive toys, and "stuff to read." Address:  urlLink zefrank.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tuesday is News Day. You'll be happy to know that the idiot who decided to sue the Columbus Metropolitan Library in Ohio for violating his civil rights because they wouldn't let him come in barefoot has lost his case! Robert Neinast said the joint infringed on his constitutional right to get information. He lost in the lower courts and then had the nerve to appeal. Fortunately we have American heroes on the 6th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Cincinnati who reaffirmed a lower court ruling. What a supreme jerk! Get some self respect dude so you can start learning to respect others as well. You moron! You communist moron! Too bad that Nazi party folded huh? You'd fit in well with them!   Here's a freak show! According to two maintenance workers on duty at Cleveland's Carver Park Estates, 49-year-old James Black, boldly dragged a dead, bloody body out of his apartment house in broad daylight and laid it on the ground in plain sight of the two workers. He then calmly went back inside and emerged with a mop, which he used to swab up the blood from the sidewalk. After they managed to pull their jaws back off the sidewalk, the workers immediately called police, who arrested Mr. Black and charged him with aggravated murder. (Plain Dealer)   Doing a story for the LA Weekly, a staff writer hung out with several adults (mostly in their 20's) who are all self-proclaimed Disney Enthusiasts -- that's DE's for short. Basically these little lost souls spend hours nearly every single day at Disneyland and have almost total recall of the park's history and culture. They rabidly collect memorabilia and preach with intensity on which aspects of today's park Walt Disney would not have approved. DE's usually wear Disney-themed clothes, use the pronoun "we" as if the park was theirs, and are dismissive of their "Star Trek" counterparts. As one DE put it, "Trekkies are devoted to some stupid pop-culture fad but Disney fans believe in the magic." When DE Benji Breitbart was asked why Disney was such a central force in his life he said, "I tried to figure that out. I just ended up with no answers." (LA Weekly)   16 percent of all Americans have a tattoo, according to Harris Interactive, which conducted a nationwide poll of 2,215 adults to find out how many of us have body art. In the 25 to 39 age group, the number is even higher at nearly 30 percent. How does a tattoo make you feel? Those with them said:   34 percent -- it makes them feel sexier  29 percent - it makes them more rebellious  20 percent - it makes them feel more spiritual  5 percent - it makes them more intelligent  3 percent - it makes them feel more athletic 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Excedrin migrane and a coke. If you have bad headaches or migraines and you don't know about this remedy, there you are. My gift of relief to you. I woke up with what I thought was just a bout of sinuses. I had stuffiness and pain and that quickly advanced to paralyzing pain in about two hours. Not even a hot shower could make it go away. Not to mention I'm having the long extended visit from "Aunt Flo" who has come with a vengeance along with killer cramps from hell. If I happen to die in the next few days, please tell the cops that I wasn't killed in the bathroom even though they will find huge amounts of blood residue there. I go to the bathroom and have to wash my hands twice because it looks like I murdered someone I'm bleeding so bad. So, I'm not going to take my birth control any more. Makes me feel like shit and causes me to bleed constantly. Vampires would love me. Anyway. Sorry. I know, totally gross. It's my blog and if you want to bitch about me talking about my period, get your own fucking blog and do it there. But the added element of the migrane made it worse. I was laying on my bed. Sicker than a dog and I had my daddy go and get me excedrin migrane and a coke. Took it, laid down for 30 minutes. Felt like a million bucks. I even went into work, when I could have taken the whole day off and no one would have probably noticed. So, if you suffer from migranes and they aren't so horrible or so frequent that you need medical attention. I have one in a blue moon. Get a coke, an excedrin migraine, lay down and feel better. Works like a charm every time.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay. I don't claim to be a genius or anything but what is it about people who can't type? Don't they realize that how you type is how you write and it's about as informative about how you speak. It shows your intelligence. Maybe it's just me. Long story short, I signed up for eharmony.com. No big thing. I'm really not looking nor am I truly interested in anyone, just curious on how much response I'd actually get. So I got some and you go through this structured way to talk to people. So I start talking to a couple of guys and we get to open communication and then wham. They spell horribly. Maybe I'm a snob. I'm a spelling snob. I understand the importance of not scribbling out things on a resume'. I know where the spell check thing is. I'm notorious about using it. I like perfection in my typing because the written word and the spoken word are two of the most powerful tools you can use. Why, why why....Do people not know that it's not okay to spell and type like a gorilla pounding on a keyboard. Netspeak, cre8tive spelling and typing like a moron are not cool in my world. It shows a lack of intelligence, improper social skills and basic disrespect of other people. People don't appreciate not being able to understand you and if you type or speak like an idiot then your point will never be heard and you will be discounted. Not a fun thing to happen so come on people, take a typing class for christ's sake. And use that little spell check thing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      eww. I don't feel very good today. I woke up with the worst leg cramp in the world and that wasn't a great way to start the day. Now I have a headache and my eyes feel funky. But, one good thing is that I just payed off my first credit card. Ahhh...that feels good to only have on card to pay off. Now I can up the payments on that sucker and get it done and over with very quickly. Suzi Ormand is a goddess, if you didn't know.  Now I have to wait a few days, call Citicards and get them to send me a paper saying I've paid it off to get it removed from my credit. Hooray. Financial freedom is always a good thing.   Well, here's your saturday quiz    Your magical style is Witch.    urlLink What type of Magic do you work? . Take the Magical Style Quiz by  urlLink Paradox  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So now the tower is up and running at 101%! Beware the super Z, now at full power. I talked to brandy today and she seemed really bummed or pissed or something. I don't know. I can see why. She's not at the Royals any more and that would bum me out. It's hard to get what you want. That I realize
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Remind me not to drink a huge mocha latte at 10:52 pm. Then again, you don't have to. It's not like I've got a ton of things to do tomorrow. I'm actually kind of excited I'm not on the air tomorrow. I can do a millon things I don't usually get to do, and I could probably get all my work finished early. Even better.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, today is my last official full day on the air, again. I've been full time for about three months almost doing Middays from 10am to 2pm. I was off the air for a while but before that I was on the air full time for at least 9 months...I think. I can't remember. Anyway, I'm off the air again. So now what.  There's always school. I need to figure out what I can do. Bascially, I left school for the summer. I didn't want to go and I wanted some free time. Well, I dropped out at the end of the spring semester and I got a loan sent back to the government. I paid on it but I'm still $800 short on the payment and they won't let me enroll for this semester till I pay that off. Problem is, I didn't know that was going to happen if I would have known that I would have never dropped the classes. So now I don't have the money to pay that off, I need another $3000 to pay for full time classes and I'm waiting for the government to send me my default info.  I'm half tempted to enroll at Maple Woods or something just to get back into school and get in the groove of things but I don't know what to do. I could call and find out what to do. I could just tell DeVry to fuck off and I'll try to come back next semester because there's no way that I'm going to work this out right now.  It's just irritating. Other people, I won't mention any names because it's really not worth it get all the help in the world but I can't even get a straight answer from anyone.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Britney's got a new song. With Madonna. If that's not a cry for help, I don't know what that is. And if you haven't seen her latest pictures in  urlLink Esquire magazine. ...Let me just say that she's wanting the world to be her gynecologist. Song's pretty good for a steaming pile of crap that the record companies love to force feed us lately.   You know what I hate more than anything. Rude people on the phone. Sorry sweetie, It's not all about you. I hate people who think that the world fucking revolves around them and other people are here to cater to their every whim. Long story short, someone calls up on the request line. I was giving away movie tickets, I already got a winner. I informed the person on the line that I had already given them to someone else but was about to inform them that I had more and to keep listening but before I got that out they said, and I quote, "Well, aren't you a steaming pile of shit."  So I said we did have more but I guess not for rude people who make stupid comments to a radio dj. Do you realize we record all of our calls so we can turn the ones who say stuff like you just did in for harassment. They said, "Well, get this on tape. Fuck you..blah blah blah" and hung up. Why? What was the point of that? What low level mullet wearing stupid fuck of a human being decides to call someone up and be rude for not getting what they wanted. Not even worth the nut stain in their mamma's drawers people who think that it is truly my job to be their servant, get them some water, maybe some more breadsticks. Do a little tap dance. Perhaps that's why I never worked in the service industry. I would have dumped a whole pitcher of scalding hot coffee on that ass and been happy to do it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       THIS MONTH IS    Cookie Month  -- There's more going on inside your cookie jar than meets your taste buds. In fact, psychologists have discovered that the way your cookie crumbles reveals the flavor of your personality, says family therapist Jim Franklin.      Chocolate Chip : You're as American as apple pie, and you're raising   your kids with the traditional values you treasure. Your low-key approach   to life makes you a favorite with family and friends because you bring a   steadying influence to the most chaotic situations.    Ginger Snaps or Snickerdoodles : You're bold, brave and in search of excitement. Life   is never dull when you're around, and both kids and adults are attracted   by your zest for life. You never shy away from new adventures, leading a   happy band of friends and family who'll gladly follow you anywhere.    Graham Crackers : You're softhearted and kind with a taste for   nostalgia. You have many fond memories of your childhood, and your closet   is probably stuffed with keepsakes from years gone by. But you don't dwell   on the past because you're too busy making memories today.    Vanilla Wafers : You have uncanny intuitive powers that give you the   unique ability to size up a situation or a person with breathtaking   accuracy. Loved ones caught up in complex problems often turn to you for   advice because they know you'll steer them in the right direction.    Sandwich Cookies like Oreos : Whether you eat the creme filling first or dunk   them in milk, your choice says you're a creative person with a vivid   imagination. A born storyteller, you're often the center of attention at   parties, regaling your pals with funny, sometimes outrageous, tales.    Fig Newtons, Fruit Cookies or Cookies with Nuts : Quiet, reserved and mature, your keen mind makes you a   force to be reckoned with. You always have your "ducks in a row," and your   organizational skills assure your home and job are both running smoothly.   Just don't forget, spontaneity is a good thing too.    Sugar Cookies : You're a nonconformist who believes that variety is   the spice of life. Your avid interest in a multitude of subjects, teamed   with your antiestablishment sensibility, makes you a challenging   companion. You may not always take the safe path, but there's no doubt   that life with you is never dull.    Oatmeal or Peanut Butter : As homespun and down-to-earth as a comfy pair of slippers,   you're a genius at making others feel loved. Your family and friends   blossom under the warmth of your generous spirit, while your practical   approach to problems helps you find the best route to a solution that   satisfies everyone involved.    Shortbread : You present a placid face to the world, but beneath   your calm facade beats the heart of a passionate romantic. In fact, those   closest to you would be amazed by your colorful fantasy life. Once you've   found the right partner, you're able to give this untapped side free rein  with totally satisfying results.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Weather lore warns that every fog in October will bring a snow come winter. Well...two so far. Fun. I like snow as long as I don't have to drive in it. Yes, and I changed the layout again. I know. I can't decide on what I want.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I chopped my hair. I lost two inches. How fun. Why this is relevant is because lately I've been in a serious fight with my hair. It's dry. It's damaged. It's straw if I don't condition it every time I wash it and about I'd say three months ago I decided to dye it since I have gray hair beyond belief. I used an at home dye and no one is really sure if I had a spot on my head that had broken out and we didn't know about it or I had a sun burn from the lake a few weeks before and it hadn't healed but I had the dye on my head for about 5 minutes and it burned my scalp so bad it made the spot worse. It hasn't healed up yet. Most recently, I used a 24 shampoo semi permanent dye and that made everything worse. My hair is already pretty dry and damages. Swimming in the pool at the Y isn't making it any better either but never the less, my wet hair has the consistency of wet mulch, just a mess. No moisture to be found. I have to slick it down with the most waxy conditioners on the planet to at least not get it to frizzy.  But the gray has made it curl or more of a wave I should say. I don't have perfect corkscrew curls but I have a gentle wave to my hair now. So I spend many a morning straitening or curling with a curling iron just so it looks normal. So much issues with hair.   I didn't go to church today. Bad me. And if that weren't enough turmoil? I have until the first of November to get into class at DeVry. I'm half tempted to go tomorrow and get info on Maple Woods. It's cheaper. I can pay off DeVry and try again next semester. It's really a pain in the ass to be completely honest. So much money and I am learning a lot but do I need to make such a fuss over this school just because I don't want to take my damn math and English classes? I could get them done at Maple woods and get that associates then transfer with less of a hassle. I think tomorrow I'm going to go and find out what I can do about this situation because to be quite honest, despite it being so far out, I don't want to be over $30,000 in debt when I get out of school, especially in the business I'm in because to even get a salary that large would be amazing. I'm already at least $20,000 with my car and my student loans and all. Ah...So much on my mind
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I broke a toe. Great. Now I'm wearing a clompy open toed shoe and my foot is killing me. Hurts sooo bad! I was walking around the edge of the pool at the Y this morning and ran smack into a bench and I heard a crack. I had to have broken it. I can move it but it hurts like a bitch. I need some drugs. I'm so wimpy when it comes to pain. Enough about my toe though.  Against the RIAA: Rapper LL Cool J testifying before Senators on Tuesday in defense of the music industry's lawsuits against hundreds of Internet users who illegally swap songs online. On the same day, Public Enemy's Chuck D. took the opposite stance, testifying that people should be allowed to distribute music via file sharing.   Healthy Diddy? Sean "P. Diddy" Combs announced that he will run in the New York Marathon on November 2 to raise $1 million for charity organizations. The rapper admitted that he's only been training for the race for three weeks. "It's gonna be a rough one. Probably around the 13th mile, I'll really need your support--water, Gatorade, whatever," Combs told reporters.   There is a god! Heath Ledger and Naomi Watts splitting up, confirmed the actor's rep. No official reason given but the twosome's busy schedules are reportedly to blame.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     urlLink Which Survivor of the Impending Nuclear Apocalypse Are  You ?    urlLink A Rum and Monkey joint.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday Five answers! 1. I love to shop. Why? I like having new things. It's like presents every day.  2. I bought groceries.  3. Actual store! I'm into trying on, touching, tasting...whatever.   4. I did and it was 10 dollars a week.  5. A pair of shoes that I promptly donated to charity. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you are just dying for some creative spelling on this site because you can understand the pure english.  urlLink Here you are  also the  urlLink urban dictionary  works great too, if you are having a hard time understanding your children.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      TWAS THE NIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS, HE LIVED ALL ALONE, IN A ONE BEDROOM HOUSE MADE OF PLASTER AND STONE.  I HAD COME DOWN THE CHIMNEY WITH PRESENTS TO GIVE, AND TO SEE JUST WHO IN THIS HOME DID LIVE.  I LOOKED ALL ABOUT, A STRANGE SIGHT I DID SEE, NO TINSEL, NO PRESENTS, NOT EVEN A TREE.  NO STOCKING BY MANTLE, JUST BOOTS FILLED WITH SAND, ON THE WALL HUNG PICTURES OF FAR DISTANT LANDS.  WITH MEDALS AND BADGES, AWARDS OF ALL KINDS, A SOBER THOUGHT CAME THROUGH MY MIND.  FOR THIS HOUSE WAS DIFFERENT, IT WAS DARK AND DREARY, I FOUND THE HOME OF A SOLDIER, ONCE I COULD SEE CLEARLY.  THE SOLDIER LAY SLEEPING, SILENT, ALONE, CURLED UP ON THE FLOOR IN THIS ONE BEDROOM HOME.  THE FACE WAS SO GENTLE,  THE ROOM IN SUCH DISORDER, NOT HOW I PICTURED A UNITED STATES SOLDIER.  WAS THIS THE HERO OF WHOM I'D JUST READ? CURLED UP ON A PONCHO, THE FLOOR FOR A BED?  I REALIZED THE FAMILIES THAT I SAW THIS NIGHT, OWED THEIR LIVES TO THESE SOLDIERS WHO WERE WILLING TO FIGHT.  SOON ROUND THE WORLD, THE CHILDREN WOULD PLAY, AND GROWNUPS WOULD CELEBRATE A BRIGHT CHRISTMAS DAY.  THEY ALL ENJOYED FREEDOM EACH MONTH OF THE YEAR, BECAUSE OF THE SOLDIERS, LIKE THE ONE LYING HERE.  I COULDN'T HELP WONDER HOW MANY LAY ALONE, ON A COLD CHRISTMAS EVE IN A LAND FAR FROM HOME.  THE VERY THOUGHT BROUGHT A TEAR TO MY EYE, I DROPPED TO MY KNEES AND STARTED TO CRY.  THE SOLDIER AWAKENED AND I HEARD A ROUGH VOICE, "SANTA DON'T CRY, THIS LIFE IS MY CHOICE;  I FIGHT FOR FREEDOM, I DON'T ASK FOR MORE, MY LIFE IS MY GOD, MY COUNTRY, MY CORPS."  THE SOLDIER ROLLED OVER AND DRIFTED TO SLEEP, I COULDN'T CONTROL IT, I CONTINUED TO WEEP.  I KEPT WATCH FOR HOURS, SO SILENT AND STILL AND WE BOTH SHIVERED FROM THE COLD NIGHT'S CHILL.  I DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE ON THAT COLD, DARK, NIGHT, THIS GUARDIAN OF HONOR SO WILLING TO FIGHT.  THEN THE SOLDIER ROLLED OVER, WITH A VOICE SOFT AND PURE, WHISPERED, "CARRY ON SANTA, IT'S CHRISTMAS DAY, ALL IS SECURE."  ONE LOOK AT MY WATCH, AND I KNEW HE WAS RIGHT. "MERRY CHRISTMAS MY FRIEND, AND TO ALL A GOOD NIGHT."   This poem was written by a Marine stationed in Okinawa Japan. The following is his request. I think it is reasonable.....  PLEASE. Would you do me the kind favor of sending this to as many people as you can? Christmas will be coming soon and some credit is due to our U.S. service men and women for our being able to celebrate these festivities. Let's try in this small way to pay a tiny bit of what we owe. Make people stop and think of our heroes, living and dead, who sacrificed themselves for us. Please, do your small part to plant this small seed. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well the evil is upon us. The s word came on Sunday and I saw the I word in the parking lot coming into work today. Yup. Snow and Ice. ewwww...  While I understand the changing of season and all that. I enjoy them from time to time but fall never lasts long enough and winter comes too soon. It's cold. It's icy. It's snowy. My car doesn't enjoy driving in that. I would like to be like the bears and the woodland animals and telecommute to work via my cozy room with my pajamas on and no have to shower. Hibernation is a good thing because bears understand that driving in the snow is crazy. Besides, MoDot doesn't really do much to plow the streets. We should have street heaters.   So, it's cold and nasty. I need some warm chili for dinner. Time to go to the store.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since January 2000, at least 190 Missouri children have died of abuse or neglect. In a six-month examination, The Kansas City Star has identified 116 of those children and researched their cases.  At least one-third of those 116 children might have lived if only the safety net we rely on to protect our children — family, friends, state workers, law enforcement officials — had come to their rescue when the first sign of danger emerged.  That percentage could be far higher if more details about all the cases were known.  The sad result: funerals for dozens of boys and girls — most younger than 3 years old.  The Star examined thousands of pages of court records, death certificates, coroner's records, media reports and state reports. The newspaper interviewed or contacted scores of county prosecutors, dozens of family members of victims, and several convicted child killers.  Under a relatively new Missouri law, The Star also obtained once-confidential case files for 37 of the dead children — the largest such media request ever honored by the state.  “Accountability is always good,” said Missouri's new social services director Steve Roling, who released the records. “It shows the extent of how the overall system works to protect children.”  Child fatality records remain closed in Kansas, though many lawmakers want to open them.  But child abuse and neglect death rates are higher in Missouri. Although it has twice as many children as Kansas, Missouri experiences at least five times the amount of fatal abuse and neglect, the newspaper found.  Kansas appears to have a low child abuse fatality rate, but the numbers may be flawed, the newspaper found. State social services officials had counted 16 child abuse deaths since 2000, but The Star found 36. After researching The Star's list, officials added eight deaths to their tally, disagreed with one case and are awaiting law enforcement reports on 13 other deaths.  In some years, Missouri's fatality rates are among the highest in the nation. But the state's high rates may be attributed, in part, to its aggressive tracking of child fatalities.  Whatever the statistics, child advocates maintain that society cannot rely on the police and state agencies to protect our children.  Schools need to teach young parents how infants develop and how to cope with crying. Churches and relatives need to help parents find safe day care. Prosecutors and judges must insist on stiffer penalties for perpetrators.  Everyone should report abuse when they see it.  Although the state plays a key role, Roling said, “so do loving parents, grandparents, churches and schools. We're all in this together.”  But unfortunately, not everyone is concerned enough about the welfare of children.  The 116 deaths examined by The Star revealed a sad litany of needless suffering at the hands of parents, boyfriends and baby sitters. Children were beaten, burned, poisoned, shaken, stabbed, shot, scalded or suffocated.  Other youngsters simply were left unsupervised near danger: full bathtubs, vicious dogs, dangling ropes, loaded guns or stifling-hot cars.  Had responsible adults done more, many of these children still would be alive.  Repeated abuse  Preston Vestal was a sparkling 11-month-old whose death Dec. 19, 2001, ended a long fall through Missouri's courts and child welfare system.  Virtually everyone involved missed opportunities to save him from a savage beating by his father, Christopher McDermit.  Preston came to the attention of the former Division of Family Services on Feb. 25, 2001, when he was hospitalized with a fractured skull.  McDermit eventually told police he had struck Preston at their Wellsville home when the then- month-old baby began to cry, police reports show. Prosecutors charged McDermit with felony child abuse.  Though seriously injured, Preston recovered quickly. But resolving the charges against McDermit took seven months and culminated with a plea agreement in October 2001.  Instead of the felony — which would have required a prison sentence of at least one year — Montgomery County Prosecutor Kelly Broniec negotiated a plea agreement of misdemeanor child endangerment and misdemeanor assault. Broniec did not respond to interview requests.  In a hearing so brief that the court transcript consumes just three double-spaced pages, Montgomery County Circuit Judge Keith M. Sutherland accepted the agreement. McDermit, who already had spent three months behind bars, received no further jail time.  At no time in the hearing was Preston's name mentioned nor his condition discussed, according to the transcript.  “I generally don't go into the facts as deeply on a misdemeanor as in a felony,” Sutherland explained recently.  But the judge ordered McDermit to take parenting and anger management classes.  After his plea, McDermit resumed living with Preston and his mother. State records show no follow-up contact between DFS case workers and the family. State officials told The Star they would not discuss individual cases, only state policies.  Missouri's Board of Probation and Parole also supervised McDermit. In the next two months, he missed one probation meeting and was late to another, said Tim Kniest, a spokesman for the Missouri Department of Corrections.  On Dec. 14, his probation officer cited McDermit for probation violations, though he did not deem them serious enough to have McDermit arrested.  His probation officer also had not conducted a home study of McDermit's residence. Kniest said such studies usually are conducted within four months of probationers coming under supervision.  Five days after being cited for probation violations, McDermit carried Preston's lifeless body into a Columbia emergency room.  Later, McDermit admitted striking Preston at least 12 times when he apparently began crying for his mother, who was not home, records show.  McDermit “stated it was hard for him to understand what Preston wanted, and he did not know what he wanted, and ‘Waa' could mean 15,000 things,” according to a police report.  McDermit pleaded guilty and is serving a 20-year prison sentence.  Members of a committee of Boone County child welfare workers, doctors and law enforcement officials were disturbed by the case when they reviewed it in January 2002.  They questioned whether a misdemeanor conviction for assaulting Preston the first time was appropriate. They criticized the judge for not restricting McDermit's contact with Preston.  They urged probation officers to conduct home visits within 30 days to make sure probationers are not living with child victims. They also recommended regular reviews of child victim cases to make sure agencies follow up.  Lana Vestal said recently that her grandson fell through the cracks.  “It seems like there should have been more things in place to make sure it wouldn't have happened,” she said.  In a recent letter to The Star, McDermit said that one week before he killed Preston, he had tried to enroll in an anger management program. But he said he was told he would have to “wait a substantial period of time for classes.”  Defense attorney Kathryn Benson said she and others should have made certain McDermit was receiving medication that could have tamed his volatile temper.  “Everybody involved failed Preston and Christopher,” Benson said.  Warnings ignored  When paramedics brought a nonbreathing 3-year-old girl into a Rolla emergency room in March 2000, a nurse thought the child was wearing “101 Dalmation” pajamas. Then the nurse realized paramedics had cut away the girl's clothes.  Those dark splotches were bruises.  Doctors were unable to save Sara Tibbetts that day. But other people could have if they had acted sooner.  Just three months earlier, Sara smiled innocently as a photographer took her Christmas portrait. Sara then lived with her younger sister and their mother in a trailer home on her grandparents' farm near Blackwater, in central Missouri.  About that time, Sara's mother, Tommie Tibbetts, began dating Daniel Lee Collis, a 20-year-old parolee with a drug problem, state records show.  Soon, Tibbetts and her daughters left the farm. Weeks later, she called and asked whether Grandma would take the girls for awhile.  Sara arrived with a black eye, a bruised face and bruised legs. She walked awkwardly and had trouble sitting.  “She would scream in pain,” recalled her grandmother, Debra Hall. “She couldn't bend over to pick up toys.”  Hall took Sara to a Columbia hospital and told nurses she feared Sara had been abused. The hospital called the child abuse hot line.  DFS labeled the call an “assessment” rather than an “investigation,” which is more serious and often spurs law enforcement involvement. Despite that, a DFS worker told Hall that if Tibbetts came back for the girls to “call the sheriff and then call me.”  However, that worker never contacted Tibbetts or Collis to assess whether Sara could go home safely, records show. Ten days later, in a phone call to Hall, Tibbetts demanded her girls back.  Hall called DFS and the sheriff's office. Both said she must return Sara to her mother.  DFS based its decision partly on a call from Hall's ex-husband, Tom Tibbetts. He said he would supervise Tommie Tibbetts at his home in Belle, Mo. That reassured the case worker, records show.  But Hall fretted. At the farm that afternoon, she begged the pair to leave the girls with her. Sara pressed tightly against Grandma.  “Me stay with you, Maw Maw,” Sara cried. “Let sissy go.”  That was the last time Hall saw Sara alive.  DFS transferred the case to Maries County, where Tommie Tibbetts lived with her father and her boyfriend, Collis, who had notched two parole violations in two months. He was not working, and he was using drugs.  His parole officer referred Collis to a substance abuse program. If parole officials had known that Collis was suspected of hitting Sara, they would have investigated, a corrections department spokesman said recently. But they were not told, he said.  It took two weeks for a new DFS worker to visit the Tibbetts household, and only then with an appointment, not through a surprise visit, which Hall had wanted. Collis was not there when the worker arrived.  The DFS worker asked a supervisor whether to upgrade the assessment to an investigation. The supervisor said no.  Tommie Tibbetts soon asked DFS for help with her own drug problem. But DFS could not pay for an evaluation, the case worker noted on March 14.  That day, a Belle laundry owner learned he had been burglarized. A security video camera recorded Tommie Tibbetts and Collis taking items from a storage room. It also showed Collis yanking Sara's hair.  The laundry owner reported the burglary but refused to give the videotape to city marshal Shawn McKinnon because the owner wanted to find the burglars himself and get them to pay him back.  The next day, McKinnon saw Tommie Tibbetts in town. After recognizing her from the videotape, McKinnon again asked the laundry owner for the videotape. A day later, on March 16, McKinnon received a usable copy.  That evening, Collis killed Sara.  “If I had had the tape a day or so before, I could have gotten charges and had them arrested,” McKinnon acknowledged recently.  Tom Tibbetts, who promised to protect the girls and had wanted to get Collis' probation revoked, spent the fatal day in Texas. He had been there a week.  “The person I blame the most is myself,” Tom Tibbets said, “for … my own inability to see the seriousness and the depth of the danger involved.”  Tommie Tibbetts, who had gotten a black eye trying to protect Sara from Collis in February, left the girls home with Collis part of the day Sara died.  That evening, a neighbor called 911. Paramedics saw Tommie Tibbetts kneeling over Sara on the lawn.  “Help my baby!” she screamed. “Don't let her die.”  Sara's intestines were torn from multiple blows. Her heart stopped on the way to the hospital. Half her blood had seeped into her abdomen, the autopsy showed.  Bleeding to death took an hour, maybe two.  “It was one of the worst (cases) I've ever seen,” said the pathologist, Mary Case, St. Louis County's chief medical examiner. “But how can you measure these things? They're all so horrible.”  Convicted by a jury, Collis received a life sentence. Tommie Tibbetts pleaded guilty and is serving 30 years.  Hall still tries to cope with losing Sara, who had potty-trained herself, adored Winnie the Pooh and loved helping feed the cows.  “I blame myself,” Hall said. “I should have taken off with the girls.  “I blame my ex-husband because he said he would protect them. I blame DFS because they never checked on those girls. I blame the parole board. I blame the Belle police.  “There were a lot of people that failed Sara.”  Family failures  Isaiah. Dayun. Ariel. Ozshana. Katelynn. Josh. Tyson. Wesley. Anthony. William.  When killed, they ranged in age from 1 month to 3 years.  In each case, adults knew that the children lived in danger. Friends, family or neighbors had noticed bruises, rough treatment or consistent neglect.  But they did not tell authorities.  One mother let her 3-year-old son play alone for long periods outdoors near a dangerous dog. Neighbors remained silent until the dog mauled the boy to death.  Another mother watched her boyfriend squeeze her 17-month-old daughter's foot until it bled. The mother did not seek medical treatment because she feared the girl would be taken away. The boyfriend later killed the child.  Today, some witnesses to abuse and neglect regret their inaction.  Dixie Foster, whose great-grandson was murdered in 2001, said people should note suspicious bruises or behavior changes. Her great-grandson, Josh Polson, lived only two years.  “All of the sudden he has bruises, big bruises,” Foster said. “If we just went with our instincts and said: ‘There's something wrong with this picture.' ”  But family members believed Josh's mother, who said she had fallen down some steps with Josh. They ignored her boyfriend when he said he needed help to stop being mean to Josh.  David Manwarren was convicted of killing Josh by shaking him, dropping him to the floor, then throwing him on a couch — all because Josh cried when his mother left.  Al Iantorno grieves the loss of two granddaughters: Katelynn and Megan Duvall. At least one life, if not both, could have been saved, Iantorno said.  The girls' father, Geoffrey P. Duvall, faces murder charges for allegedly suffocating 3-month-old Megan last year in Lee's Summit. He could not be reached for comment.  After Megan's death, Blue Springs police reopened an investigation into her 8-month-old sister's death in 2001. The medical examiner originally attributed Katelynn's death to Sudden Infant Death Syndrome, but later changed it to unknown.  Before Katelynn died, Iantorno said he had noticed a black eye and other bruises. He thinks she was murdered.  He also wishes he had done more.  “Katelynn could have been saved,” Iantorno said. “She should have been saved by me. I take full responsibility, and I will live with this the rest of my life.”  Dropped calls  When hot-line calls go uninvestigated, children can die.  Consider the cases of two Independence girls: 23-month-old Alexis Smothers and 21-month-old Breanna Leonard. They lived only miles apart and died only months apart in 2002, both allegedly killed by their mothers' boyfriends.  A neighbor repeatedly heard children screaming in Alexis' apartment and eventually enticed Alexis' mother to say what was happening. The mother's boyfriend had been hitting the children, she said.  The neighbor called the hot line. No report was taken, the neighbor later told police, because she had not witnessed the bruises.  If that happened, it was a mistake, state officials now say. Witnessing bruises is not necessary for a report to be taken.  In Breanna's case, a friend of her mother called the hot line and reported a black eye and bruises two months before Breanna died.  Although she asked to remain anonymous, she provided directions to Breanna's home, the family's phone number and names and ages of family members.  Despite those details, the state worker labeled the call “unable to investigate,” which usually means there is not enough information.  After Breanna died, the caller repeated her story to police. At first, DFS denied any record of her hot-line call. But after a police request, DFS checked its tape recordings. The call had been made.  “I think more should have been done, and that sweet little baby wouldn't have lost her life,” said Amy Bryant, the person who called the hot line. Bryant, who still carries a picture of Breanna in her wallet, said she would not rely on the hot line again.  “I'd call the police first,” she said.  Three years ago, Missouri Auditor Claire McCaskill raised concerns about hot-line lapses. Her audit showed that about a fourth of the calls were labeled “unable to investigate.”  Since then, the number of “unable to investigate” calls has dropped 26 percent, records show. Sandra Wilkie, the hot line's supervisor, said such calls should decrease further as the division makes improvements this year.  But the total number of unable to investigate calls last year exceeded 18,000.  State officials still encourage people to call the hot line.  “When in doubt,” Roling said, “err on the side of calling.”  Fatal errors  Of all the abuse suffered by Missouri children in this decade, few likely approached the cruelty that 3-year-old Anthony Buhr of Independence endured.  Anthony apparently was let down the hardest by the two people who should have cared the most: his father and mother. Both are awaiting trial on criminal charges in his death.  DFS could have intervened, too. But in an eerie similarity to the 1999 Bass case in Kansas City — where two brothers in a set of triplets died — DFS failed to locate Anthony at a critical time.  His father, Frank Buhr, first saw bruises on Anthony in January 2002 after Anthony spent two days with his mother and her boyfriend. In February, Anthony underwent surgery for a ruptured testicle. He had been kicked in the groin at his mother's home.  Frank Buhr won custody of Anthony and his brother, and the court restricted the mother to supervised visits.  About 10 weeks later, though, DFS took a call that Lena Buhr, the mother, again had the boys. A worker contacted Frank Buhr, who lied, court records allege. He said the boys were with him.  DFS policy is to locate children, in person, within 24 hours of such a call. That rule is well-known in Jackson County, because the mother of the Bass brothers also had lied about where her children lived.  Police records mention no other efforts by DFS to locate Anthony.  Three days later, while Lena Buhr was gone, her boyfriend tortured Anthony. Bryon Griffin — now imprisoned for life — beat Anthony with a table tennis paddle, knocked out a tooth and burned his genitals with a hair dryer. He held Anthony's head in a toilet and threw him against a wall. He shook Anthony until his neck muscles snapped and his brain swelled. As Lena Buhr arrived home, Griffin was strangling Anthony.  Ten minutes later, a police officer — answering a disturbance call — came to their door. Both adults insisted everything was fine, according to police reports. The officer left.  About an hour later, police went back. Lena Buhr had called an ambulance.  But first, according to police reports, she waited until she felt no pulse on Anthony.    ABOUT THE SERIES  The Star began researching “Protecting Our Children” about nine months ago. In several stories since April, the newspaper has examined child welfare issues ranging from inadequate after-hours hot-line staffing and privatization problems in Kansas, to a lack of accreditation for programs in Missouri 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ahh...quizzes   You come from the Ocean.  You've always been drawn to the sea, the sound of the waves, the crystal blue water, near the sea is where you belong.    urlLink   Where Did Your Soul Originate?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate my hair. I got a haircut and I hate it. I used to have long flowing reddish brown hair. I now have a brown football helmet on my head.  I went out on Friday night with Brandy knowing fully well that I had an appointment on Saturday morning but still we went out and had drinks at Harry's then went to the Falloon. So I got to bed really late. My mom comes over and wakes me up and asks me if I want to go get my haircut or sleep. I wanted to sleep but she already got me up so I was cranky. Didn't feel good and she guilted me to get my haircut because she wanted to get her hair cut.   So I made her go first while I looked at magazines. To be honest, I was looking at haircut magazines and I had talked about getting my hair cut short from my just past shoulder length to something snappy and cute. So I asked Cheryl about a certain cut. She said she didn't think so. So I said never mind. And before I really connected what was going on, she said, are you looking for something different and I said yeah, sort of. That should have been a clue that I wasn't sure about cutting my hair. I said, okay and snip snip there went my hair. Of course, my mom and Cheryl were talking politics while she was cutting my hair and maybe she got a little crazy but now I look like a hobbit. Apparently my hair was a tad bit curlier than expected. I'm just now finding out my hair has curl to it because I've had it long so long I only saw the curl around my temples.   My parents said it was cute. My friends said it was cute. I can't look at myself in a mirror. I think I look like a soccer mom who doesn't have time to do her hair so she gets a haircut that you don't have to do anything to your hair. I know this for a fact because I not only put root lifter on it but also curling gel and it didn't do diddly. Just turned into it's yucky brown helmetiness. I would talk to Cheryl about how much I hate it, but she'd just cut it and make it shorter. So, thankfully it's wintertime and I can get away with wearing hats for three or four months, which is my only option other than wigs or hair extensions.   Isn't there a wives tale about getting your hair cut after the full moon? Something about looking like a retard?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
           What Irrational Number Are You?     You are &radic;2
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm taking quizzes again!          Which Founding Father Are You?     
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I watched Britney on Primetime Thursday. I will humbly change my opinion of her. She's not a no talent ass clown. I don't know if it was the embarrassed tears or that she took Diane Sawyer's questions with a real honesty but I have to say I have a new respect for her. I know how it feels to totally be embarrassed by a question and just want to run away and cry alone but you can't help it and you cry. So that really touched me. Her year was tough. So was mine so even though I don't really respect her as an artist because I don't buy the whole not lip sync-ing thing but I do respect her as a person because she's honest. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've totally got into playing BlogShares. I'm addicted. I love Monopoly so this should be rather fun. If you have a blog, or like playing stock market games...then you'll love this!  urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Talk about flanagaling! Long story short, I am the line party leader for the Lord Of The Rings movie here in town. The theater is showing the Trilogy on Dec 16th and tickets are gone. They are selling them on Ebay from $200 to $600 a pop. Yup, it's that popular. I don't have a ticket. I want to go see the movie so I started selling the idea of getting the radio station to sponsor the event and get our names in it so that we could own the event.  Basically, the idea is, every movie theater has a corperate theater buyout program. They love that stuff. Get the theater to work with New Line Cinema and us to have us buy out the theater if I promised Eric, our promotions Director, that it wouldn't be a bust. We'd get people in those seats, no problem. Then our station would be the people at a very very exclusive event and we would own it. It will be great! I promise.   As long as it works. If I don't hear anything from him by the last week of November, I'm doing it on my own. I could do it. No problem but it would be a great promotional event for the radio station.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Spent most of the evening after work arguing with Jay about why the war in Iraqi was justified. First point, and it's an important one, when is war ever justified? War is unjustfiable. Second, like Bush said, is the world truly worse off because Iraq is free of Saddam Hussein's rule? Well, if that doesn't tempt you, then maybe this will. If only I had this at the bar but then I fell folly to the rule of Mark Twain. "Never argue with an idiot. They bring you down to their level and beat you with experience."  Why We Went to War  From the October 20, 2003 issue: The case for the war in Iraq, with testimony from Bill Clinton.  by Robert Kagan & William Kristol  10/20/2003, Volume 009, Issue 06  "When I left office, there was a substantial amount of biological and chemical material unaccounted for. That is, at the end of the first Gulf War, we knew what he had. We knew what was destroyed in all the inspection processes and that was a lot. And then we bombed with the British for four days in 1998. We might have gotten it all; we might have gotten half of it; we might have gotten none of it. But we didn't know. So I thought it was prudent for the president to go to the U.N. and for the U.N. to say you got to let these inspectors in, and this time if you don't cooperate the penalty could be regime change, not just continued sanctions."  --Bill Clinton, July 22, 2003   FORMER PRESIDENT CLINTON is right about what he and the whole world knew about Saddam Hussein's weapons of mass destruction programs. And most of what everyone knew about Saddam's weapons of mass destruction had nothing to do with this or any other government's intelligence collection and analysis. Had there never been a Central Intelligence Agency--an idea we admit sounds more attractive all the time--the case for war against Iraq would have been rock solid. Almost everything we knew about Saddam's weapons programs and stockpiles, we knew because the Iraqis themselves admitted it.   Here's a little history that seems to have been completely forgotten in the frenzy of the past few months. Shortly after the first Gulf War in 1991, U.N. inspectors discovered the existence of a surprisingly advanced Iraqi nuclear weapons program. In addition, by Iraq's own admission and U.N. inspection efforts, Saddam's regime possessed thousands of chemical weapons and tons of chemical weapon agents. Were it not for the 1995 defection of senior Iraqi officials, the U.N. would never have made the further discovery that Iraq had manufactured and equipped weapons with the deadly chemical nerve agent VX and had an extensive biological warfare program.   Here is what was known by 1998 based on Iraq's own admissions:   * That in the years immediately prior to the first Gulf War, Iraq produced at least 3.9 tons of VX, a deadly nerve gas, and acquired 805 tons of precursor ingredients for the production of more VX.   * That Iraq had produced or imported some 4,000 tons of ingredients to produce other types of poison gas.   * That Iraq had produced 8,500 liters of anthrax.   * That Iraq had produced 500 bombs fitted with parachutes for the purpose of delivering poison gas or germ payloads.   * That Iraq had produced 550 artillery shells filled with mustard gas.   * That Iraq had produced or imported 107,500 casings for chemical weapons.   * That Iraq had produced at least 157 aerial bombs filled with germ agents.   * That Iraq had produced 25 missile warheads containing germ agents (anthrax, aflatoxin, and botulinum).      urlLink Read the whole article 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whew! I'm really really tired. So this is a long post today. First off, Friday was my birthday! I am now offically 27 and very very old. I went to eat with the parents at Cafe Italia and let me tell you, that place has seriously gone downhill. It used to be fantastic. I loved eating there and would miss lunch because it was so good. This time, I barely ate anything. Then I went to party with the friends. We met at Tammy and Amanda's house then traveled to Cactus Cafe. A little cheesy but I wanted to dance. And dance we did. Then to Harpo's and sat in back being loud and obnoxious and played quarters.   I got Cucumber Melon lotion (small and large), body wash, spray and a candle, a new piece for my  urlLink Charlotte and Tipit ring , a makeup bag, and a matchbook emery boards. My parents gave me jewelry, a tv and a dvd player so I spent much of Saturday in my room watching Lord Of The Rings. Both movies. I know. I'm a nerd.  Sunday, today, I went to watch the Cheifs game! 9-0!!! Yeah! and I had to work.   But I found a cool website. There are a ton of old abandoned bulidings around the area and I've so wanted to go and hunt in them, including a few abandoned insane asylums. I love old buildings. So here's a cool website!  urlLink dark passage 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So it's time to beg the internet for money! How fun! I'm very poor. I'm a college student. I have debt up to my ears. I want a nice Christmas, so if you want to help out that would be nice!                          
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      We're Stunned! Most Fun U.S. City Is... It's not New York, New Orleans, or even Las Vegas. The city where you'll have the most fun is...Minneapolis.   That's the word from game maker Cranium, Inc., which commissioned Bert Sperling, who masterminded the "Best Places to Live" feature for Money magazine, to rank 50 cities for their fun factor. This was determined by the city's number of sports teams, restaurants, dance performances, toy stores, and the amount of the city's budget that is spent on recreation, among other factors.  And why did Minneapolis beat out cities known for the classic fun factors of sin and sun? According to Cranium, the goal was to find a city that is an "outrageously fun experience with something for everyone." Minneapolis won because it's the home of Mary Tyler Moore, four professional sports teams, and the best mall in America. Minneapolis has more theaters than Boston, more parks than Denver, more golfers per capita than any other city in America, and with 10,000 lakes in the state, Minnesota, has more coastline than California, Florida, and Hawaii combined. It even has 15 dog parks. Woof! Cranium CEO Richard Tait said, "It's almost a no-brainer" to crown Minneapolis the Most Fun City.  Perhaps even more startling than the fact that Minneapolis is No. 1 is that New Orleans is No. 50. Does that mean a trip to the Mall of America is more fun than Mardi Gras? You decide.  Here are the top 50 fun cities, ranked from top to bottom:  Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota Orange County, California San Jose, California Atlanta, Georgia Chicago, Illinois Raleigh-Durham-Chapel Hill, North Carolina Washington, DC Oakland, California Salt Lake City-Ogden, Utah Seattle-Bellevue-Everett, Washington Portland-Vancouver, Oregon-Washington San Francisco, California Baltimore, Maryland Milwaukee-Waukesha, Wisconsin Denver, Colorado Detroit, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri San Diego, California Indianapolis, Indiana Cincinnati, Ohio Columbus, Ohio Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Sacramento, California Nashville, Tennessee Las Vegas, Nevada Los Angeles-Long Beach, California Kansas City, Missouri-Kansas Nassau-Suffolk, New York Charlotte-Gastonia-Rock Hill, North Carolina Omaha, Nebraska Norfolk-Virginia Beach-Newport News, Virginia Houston, Texas Cleveland-Lorain-Elyria, Ohio Dallas, Texas Memphis, Tennessee Orlando, Florida Louisville, Kentucky Fort Worth-Arlington, Texas Riverside-San Bernardino, California Greensboro-Winston-Salem-High Point, North Carolina New York, New York Boston, Massachusetts Hartford, Connecticut Austin-San Marcos, Texas Newark, Newark Miami, Florida Bergen-Passaic, Newark Fort Lauderdale, Florida Phoenix-Mesa, Arizona New Orleans, Louisiana 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
           Who Will You Marry? by Sari      Name           Date    July 28, 2034      Spouse    Bill O&#39;Reilly       Price of Wedding    $134,579             Created with  urlLink   quill18  's  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, concert crisis abound in KC this Halloween weekend. First, our concert. Jessica simpson got drunk on Halloween or she caught a cold. That was the gossip. The actuallity of the gossip, she didn't sing because she had no voice. Supposedly she's supposed to be back. Sorry to those I invited but didn't get to come. I know that's bad but oh well. Life goes on. And of course, Freaker's Ball with the Rock. Here's the report from KMBC  Freakers Ball Turns Violent When Manson Ends Show  October 31, 2003  kmbc   Police were called out to control a crowd of concert-goers unhappy after shock rocker Marilyn Manson, featured attraction at a "Freakers Ball" event Thursday night sponsored by KQRC 98.9 The Rock, ended his show early when fans pushed down a barrier.  According to accounts from people attending the concert at the Kansas City International Raceway, a security fence between the fans and the stage was pushed down twice, and after the second time the Manson band left the stage.   Some of the fans began rushing toward the stage, upset that the concert had been cut short. Kansas City Police Capt. Robert Zimmerman said some threw bottles at off-duty police officers who were hired to provide security at the concert.   "The crowd became unruly," he said. "We ended up calling in what we call a field force. It involved approximately 100 officers."   The officers, some wearing protective helmets, came from nearby Independence and Lee's Summit as well as Kansas City. Some fans said irritant sprays were directed at them as police took action to control the crowd.   Concert-goer Rodney Borden said that crews began taking down the band's equipment after the fence went down a second time and the musicians walked off.   "Everybody started just getting all freaked out and rioting after that," he said. "Cop cars were getting smashed. Cops were trying to get everybody out of there, and people were just fighting back. They wouldn't do what they got to do, just leave."   "It was like total chaos," said another young man.   "People are nuts," said Darrick Knight. "That's why I don't go to rock concerts that much."   The concert had started in the afternoon, and Manson's group was the last of six acts to perform. Zimmerman said about 12,000 people attended the concert.   Ambulances were at the scene, but apparently there were only a few minor injuries.   According to the Marilyn Manson Website, the band is scheduled to perform in Dallas Friday night. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      As per the instructions from my friends crazy Venezuelan Sister in law!!!  On NEW YEAR'S EVE...Anytime from 12:01am until 11:59pm.........Bury some money. It doesn't matter what it is.  As you are burying it say "I am burying my poverty". (you might want to put the money in a zip lock bag so it doesn't get all muddy!)  Then on NEW YEAR'S DAY...Anytime after midnight but before the end of the day on 1/1.....Dig up your buried money......While saying "I'm digging up my wealth"!  This ritual is supposed to assure that you will get unexpected money sometime during the new year!  **now, remember, you cannot spend this money once it's dug up!  Here's hoping for prosperity and wealth for you in the new year!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        A great loss to the blogsphere has come.  urlLink Rightweare.com  is closing it's doors. Lori and Maripat have things to do and the loss of such intelligent and wonderful women doing what they do best will be great. I'll always miss their no holds barred look at things but Lori's doing a new blog and I think that's great. Hopefully someday, rightweare.com will come back. I hope so.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Ah 2004 is almost here and the political unrest in my urban family has come to a head. At "church" (I must say that church consists of all of my friends and I showing up at the  urlLink GranFaloon  to watch football and drink beer all afternoon long) Jay and I have political discussions about pretty much everything. Okay. Calling it a discussion is really stretching it. Basically, Jay is a liberal who browbeats you with moot points and illogical arguments (like we were friends with Saddam, but now we don't like him when you argue the point that History and time and politics changes things such as Hitler and Stalin were pals till Hitler decided to try to invade Russia or that we weren't friends with the British for a while back in the Revolutionary War but they are one of our closest allies now) and doesn't let you get a word in to make a point. Jay could argue that you are breathing wrong.  We've had a discussion, while drunk, so there was our first mistake about gun control. Jay, who believes guns should be controlled because they are getting way out of hand and very disrespectful to their parents tried to argue that the consequences are the same if you hit someone with your car drunk or shoot someone. I said not true because the most you would get with hitting someone with a car if your drunk is a DUI or DWI and vehicular homicide which might land you a few years in the pokey but there are people with 10-20 DUIs still driving where as someone who shoots another person could get Murder 2 or manslaughter which holds stiffer penalties. He said, no way. I said, I've studied criminal law buster. He didn't stop till we stopped listening.  I don't even try to talk to him because he gets his news from the newspaper and I try to be educated and look at several sources such as CSpan, CNN and Fox news, most local news, the paper, internet sites such as the cato institute and oxblog. I don't claim to know everything that there is to know about politics. I actually hate politics. I think there's nothing worse than politics because basically it's not true, it's who has the best story.  I think there's some real people in Washington but they are few and I wouldn't have a beer and a pizza with most of them.   But in Jay's case, I have to remind myself that you should never argue with an idiot. Bystanders can't tell the difference. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I was getting my hair cut this weekend and to describe my beauty parlor as being like the one in "Steel Magnolias" doesn't really do it justice. It's our gossip place, our quilting bee, our chit chat area. I love going there because it's girl talk. It's smell good, feel good, look good and talk about absolutly nothing of substance time whenever I go there. So we got to talking about men. I'm 27 just so you know. Average girl, still in college and I made the mention that I like hot guys and wouldn't kick them out of bed for eating crackers. Cheryl said she wasn't interested in sweaty men in loin cloths. That disgustingly attractive men (i.e. Brad Pitt, Nick Lachey, Justin Timberlake and the like) didn't get her all hot and bothered.  WHAT? I hope that I never get to the point in my female adult life that I think that sweaty men in loin cloths are not attractive. That's crazy.  I don't know. Perhaps it's a part of the patriarchy or whatever that at some point you don't really look at men as sexual objects any more. Or maybe it's years of women asserting themselves that now make men the objects of desire no less than women who peel their clothes off. We look and examin more than their faces and now look at the chest, the arms, the legs, the amount of hair on thier bodies, the amount of fat on their love handles. They are our eye candy and we drool all over the glass of the candy store. I know fully well that I will never be part of a Viggo\Orlando love sandwich. But a girl can dream, right?  I also hope that the man I marry will never just become a boy I share a house with. I hope that after 30 years of marriage, I can look at him and think, "Damn, I wouldn't kick him out of bed for eatin crackers."  If he happens to be Orlando Bloom, then that problem would be solved.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Whew! I'm tired but I did it! I went to the Lord Of The Rings Trilogy! I saw all three movies. I even got interviewed by Cabana Boy for the afternoon show because everyone at the station says I'm a dork! Yup, self proclaimed dork here.   The movies, fantastic. I was a little disappointed with the last one only because it kinda drops you on your ass and after a huge build up. I won't spoil it for you and hey, you may like it but that's my one problem with it but I would totally say you'd have to see it.  Would I do it again? Geez, I don't know. I'm so tired. Do I regret it? Not for a second.  Basically we showed up at the theater at 6 in the morning. It was so cold and I had several layers including a hoodie, a stocking cap and two pairs of socks on. I got the blanket out of my car out and it was still very very cold. My friends and I ran over to Target for coffee and those little heat gel pack things.   11am came and we got seats and the pass that you see right there. The First movie, the extended version of Lord Of The Rings: The Fellowship Of The Ring started at 1pm that after noon. We didn't leave the theater till 1am. There were intermissions in between the movies so we weren't sitting in the theater the whole time.   Me, Frodo, Aragorn, and all the boys...The whole day. Ahhh... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday Five Q and A  1. Do you enjoy the cold weather and snow for the holidays? I enjoy it if I don't have to go out in it.  2. What is your ideal holiday celebration? How, where, with whom would you celebrate to make things perfect? Sleeping late and maybe getting up for breakfast, possibly with a hot boy.  3. Do you do have any holiday traditions? I buy a new ornament for my tree every year.  4. Do you do anything to help the needy? I give to the salvation army and Harvester  5. What one gift would you like for yourself? a new computer 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Oh how I love the holidays.   I was being facetious.  My mother and I decided we would take a trip to Wal-Mart. Actually is wasn't much of a choice, we had to go there for some rock salt and I needed a shovel to clear the walk from the snow that was now covering it. Nothing like a little snow to prove that you should have moved to LA. So we thought, were there, let's get some presents and some groceries while were there. My mother is handicapped and she has to ride around in one of those motorized carts. Shopping with her isn't the problem. The problem is the carts are never charged up at Wal Mart. I've had to plug her cart in at the lamp section of the store just to get her enough juice to make it back to the front of the store to complain that the cart didn't have power. What do those door greeters do besides greet. The problem is the other people. Why on earth do you need to take up the whole damn aisle? My mother isn't huge. She is in a motorized cart that beeps when she backs up. It annoys the hell out of me but I'm the only one who can give her dirty looks. YOU! Yes YOU! Glaring at my mother for riding in her cart and shopping like a normal human being better wipe that ugly look of your face!   Another thing is, is there something they put in the air of Wal-Mart that says that's the appropriate place to beat the holy living hell out of your child?   I did get a cool cookbook for Christmas.   Too bad I hate holiday shopping. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What happens when you have:   1) nothing to do   2) a sharp knife    3) a large lime   4) a patient cat   5) too much tequila   6) and it's football season?              
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm not a morning person by any stretch of the imagination but nothing is more refreshing in the morning than a shower.  Even better if it's an icy cold shower.  If you like that sort of thing, which unfortunately I do not. Maybe it's just me but I recall a time I could take a 15 minute shower without the thought of losing heat. Maybe it's the hot water heater? Maybe it's just too many people taking showers in my house? Who knows but this morning was enough. I barely got one toe in the tub and the once scalding water turned ice cold. I saw cubes coming from the faucet and the day before, I had a full head of shampoo on my hair when I got a nice shot of ice cold water down the back. I proceeded to do the "avoid the cold water" dance while doing my best to not get shampoo in my eyes and brace myself so I wouldn't fall and brake my neck. I didn't break my neck, thankfully but I also didn't wear my contacts yesterday.   Something must be done. It's not enough that my tub could literally fill two buckets so no long bubbly baths can be taken but now I can't even enjoy my showers.   Me and the hot water heater are going to have a long talk today.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What is the deal with the station bathrooms? Long story short, we have a plastic surgeon moving in on the 9th floor. Our station is on the 8th floor and we pretty much take up the whole floor except a corner where there's a dentist's office. One side is the sales and office side. They are on the south side of the building and on the north is programming offices and the broadcasting studios, production studios and various important electrical equipment.   Our brilliant plastic surgeons have decided to build their patients a bathroom, with a shower. Above our studio. Where's there's really nothing between the floors except insulation, floor tiles and various building supports that I know nothing about. I do understand water. Lots of water.   Water coming in the broadcast studio. Next to the equipment tower where we have our computers, EAS machine, transmitters and all that.   This is not good. So we argued with the 9th floor for months about the rain coming into our radio station at rare moments. Trash cans all over the place.  The bathrooms though are a whole other enchiladas. I don't know who is doing it but it didn't start till they started the work on the 9th floor. A smell that would knock an adult to the floor and probably asphyxiate small children. It's coming from the women's bathroom. We've had plumbers and technicians come out all the time. We keep saying that the coroner is next but no dead bodies found. Either someone around 10 am is doing a major colon cleansing or something is clogged. It smells so bad. You hold your nose if you are dying to go or you hold it, period. Until around Noon and all is well in the girls bathroom at the radio station.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Dad tells me to day what I'm getting for Christmas. Apparently Friday of this week is the only week that Dish Network can come out to the house to install my new receiver in my room and in my mom's room. That's very very nice. I kinda feel bad because I know how expensive it is but hey, it's Christmas.   I actually need like 50 bucks. I've got fines to pay and hey, I don't have the money. Go figure. What else is new. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Some people, namely my parents were complaining that they couldn't see most of the links...well I've solved some of the problems with buttons. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Russian man freezes penis to bus shelter   A Russian man had to be rescued after his penis stuck to a frozen bus shelter while he was urinating.  The young man was on his way home from a bar in temperatures of -22F  He stopped to urinate, leaning against the bus shelter for support, but swayed at a crucial moment and got stuck to the frozen metal.  The BBC reports the man was apparently taken by surprise by the cold temperatures.  A large crowd gathered, shouting advice. Finally a passerby was able to free the man using a kettle of warm water borrowed from a chemist.  The man reportedly refused further medical help before running off. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink         
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        As you can probably see, the site has changed. My brain hurts. Staring at lines of code is just hard on my eyes.  Bad bad bad. So there might be some problems as we get everything transferred over to this template.  Big Major linky love to  urlLink Groove Lizard Web Designs!  The talent that is on that site it amazing! Groovy Lizard is where this template comes from and a payment is on the way. (As soon as I get back from Dallas, Texas) Whether you get a freeware or buy the license, I'm keepin the link on this page, and you should too. Talent like this shouldn't go unnoticed. Great job!  As for everything else. I'm so tired. I'm fighting off a major cold and I've got about a week or more till I'm in Dallas Texas with the Queens. Personally, I'd like to not infect anyone so hopefully I'll get over it. I'd also like to get some more sleep but I've got a vengeance with the Spider solitaire game.   A little history. Today is Martin Luther King Jr. Day. I have a great deal of respect for that man. Stanford university is holding a Martin Luther King Jr. Paper's Project. It's an interesting read. You can check it out  urlLink here.   Also  urlLink The King Center  is an educational website that teaches about Martin Luther King Jr.   I think you should check them out.  Another Historical thing is that it's also Janis Joplin's birthday too. If you don't know who Janis Joplin is, you need to learn. She was inducted into the Rock And Roll Hall Of Fame in 1995. She only lived to be 27. As it says on my urlLink  Bad Girl calendar by Cameron Tuttle author of the Bad Girls Guides , "Rock And Roll's first bad girl superstar is born on this day in 1943 in Port Arthur, Texas. She hitched her way to San Francisco where she went on to change the face of Rock & Roll forever.  Her career was explosive and short, marked by passionate, Southern Comfort-fueled performances, an ass kicking voice that could never be replicated and a tragic heroin overdose in a lonely hotel room in LA at the age of 27."  You can find out more about this great rock icon, one of the great ones in my opinion at  urlLink www.officaljanis.com.  Then do what it says in my calendar. Order a round of Wild Turkey shots and lead the crowd in a passionate rendition of "Me And Bobby McGee."
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This is Doug. He's been my friend for a while and I met him through my friends, Tammy and Amanda. He lives in their apartment complex. I bring him up because he also happens to be deaf and we are taking sign language classes with him! We went to our first class yesterday. A few of my friends know the alphabet and I used to know it but they sign to me now and I'm like, Huh?  So we all went to class with Doug. We all signed up and he really liked having us all there with him. He teaches us the dirty words so we can cuss each other out too. Why bring this up?   I don't know. I just thought it was a rather unique thing to happen. Here are my friends, all of us, taking time out of our busy schedules to make it easier for us and for Doug to be able to communicate, not because we can't understand him or he can't understand us. He speaks and he reads lips but to have 12 people you hang out with on an almost daily basis do something together that doesn't involve beer but still having fun, learning something and everyone pitching in to help a friend makes me very happy that these people are my friends.   I take that back. It did involve beer. We went to a bar after class. :) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            urlLink What Classic Movie Are You? 
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I have a cat. This is my cat. She likes to sleep on the kitchen table. Actually she likes to sleep anywhere.  But that's not the point.   I get up this morning, get ready, and my cat is acting strange. She kept running to the garage door and I thought maybe she needed to use her box so I open the door as I'm getting ready to leave and what do I see?  Another cat.  Another cat that isn't my cat.  In my garage.  It meowed at me and wanted to come in my house. I quickly shut the door so the cat couldn't come in the house and my cat came outside with me and a little spat ensued. I opened the garage door and the cat ran under my car. My cat chased and more growling was heard. Then I moved over towards the driver's side door and the cat ran outside and to my neighbor's house.   I don't know how long the cat was in there but it was long enough to get dirty little kitty paw prints all over my car. So now I have to go clean my car, and when I come home, I'm sure I'm gonna hear it from my cat about allowing another cat in the house. She's very particular about who her humans are. She only likes me and follows me around like I'm her mother.   But that got me thinking about the funniest cat site on the web   urlLink my cat hates you.   Entertain yourself with the cat pictures and enjoy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         I refer to  urlLink Lauren at MadPony  who knows my pain.   I'm 27 years old. I fee like I'm 13 because I'm back to using clearsil. I'm also drinking water like it's going out of style and washing my face with the only thing that I've found that clears it up, antibacterial soap, which amazingly enough was recommended by my dermatologist.   The only problem with me getting a zit is I'm obsessed with it. My mind can not focus on anything else. It continuously reminds me that I have this monstrous red thing on my face, and it's not going away. Get it off. Get it off, my mind says.   So, I remind myself that it's not good to touch it. Leave it alone. Put some more clearasil on it and ignore it.    Any beauty advice to get rid of this sucker would be great. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Britney got married. For about two minutes. According to MSN.com, Britney Spears and a childhood friend apparently "took a joke too far" by tying the knot at a wedding chapel after a long night of partying Â and then quickly planned an annulment.  That's a pretty good joke. I wish I could joke with my friends like that. I can see it now. "Hey, you know what would be totally funny? If we got married! Wouldn't that be a hoot?"   Because Nevada law allows for community property between married couples, any income that Spears made while she and Alexander were married could be contested, Sommermeyer said.  Bwahh..That'ss funny. I wonder what it cost to be Britney Spears' husband for 12 hours. That might be the most lucrative job out there.   Spears and Alexander journeyed by limousine to the Little White Wedding Chapel on the Strip after a stop at the Ghostbar, a club in the Palms Casino Hotel. The chapel staff told the couple they couldn't get married without a license, so they were taken to get a license and driven back to the chapel, where they were married.  The bride wore a baseball cap and torn jeans down the aisle and was escorted by a Palms limousine driver, the source told the AP.   Well, at least she wore something comfortable. My favorite part of this report is the fact that they keep repeating that she wasn't drunk at the time. Well, that narrows down my options of why she did do it to she's on drugs or she's just plain stupid. Too bad it didn't last. Most people now a days have a starter marriage. Perhaps she could blame it on the fact that her album sucks. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Friday five  What one thing are you most looking forward to . . .  1. ...today? Being off work  2. ...over the next week? Filling out paperwork for full time  3. ...this year? Going on a roadtrip  4. ...over the next five years? finding my mr darcy  5. ...for the rest of your life? having fun 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Your Candy Heart Is "WHAT EVA"  Valentine's Day makes you a little sick  And not just from eating too much candy  You're opposed to the commercial celebration of couple-dom  It's not all about love - and love is not all about overpriced flowers!      urlLink  What Candy Conversation Heart Are You? Take This Quiz :-)        urlLink Find the Love of Your Life  (and More Love Quizzes) at Your New Romance.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Texas Queenly convention in Dallas was last weekend. I was there. It was fabulous is all I can say. Basically, you need to go to  urlLink www.sweetpotatoqueens.com   to understand. After that, all will become clear  The convention was in Dallas, Texas. I found out that I could live there. Only problem is, I live here and I'd have to buy bottled water because the water in Dallas is disgusting. No offence to people in Dallas or anything. You are used to your water. My water, I'm used to it. It's not as minerally I guess. We filter the hell out of it so it's just different. I thought it sucked and tasted like water you boiled corn in, but that's just me.   I drove down, by myself, on Thursday and stayed with Calistar that night. We drank way too many margaritas! Then we headed over to the Raddison and met Laura Ann and Waynesqueen. God, how do I love those women. They make my dick hard.  The whole weekend was a blast. My roommates, The Queen City Queens showed me the wonder of sparklies and travel hair.  I'll post the pictures soon. We won't go into the drive back through the snow storm
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know it's been a while since I've posted, including pictures and all that from Dallas. Promise I will get those up and Brandy's going away party and St.Pats are coming too. I swear...plus a full update on the goings on. I swear, when it rains it pours and I've been very very busy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why is it that some people think that as being a fat person, I don't own a mirror in my home and know this? Long story short, got into a fight with some idiot who decided that their real crushing comment to me would be to call me a "fat bitch." I of course retorted with, "That's all you've got? Fat bitch? You think I don't know that I'm a bitch already? You don't have a fucking clue and couldn't catch one even if you smeared yourself with clue musk and did the clue mating dance in a field full of horny clues."  So, needless to say, unless it comes a some great shock to you, I'm fat.  Not fat in quotation marks or parentheses, fat in actuality. Not that girly, "I am so FAT, I had to buy a medium and not a small T-Shirt!" Not movie fat of like twenty extra pounds that two weeks of diet and exercise can erase just in time for the "big makeover reveal" scene-that isn't fat. That's bloat. Not even beach novel fat, where some strange miracle or tragedy occurs that suddenly makes the pounds melt off without having to diet, attend meetings or eat tiny portions of shitty food, after which the fabulous man that loved her in spite of her size is able to watch her float down the wedding aisle in a size 6 Vera Wang. I'm not large. I'm not voluptuous. I'm fat. I'm a size 26-28 at Lane Bryant. That's the highest size they have. I wear a 3x at Target. I have since joined Weight Watchers because it's the best way to control my diabetes until the doctor decides whether I can control it with diet and exercise or diet, exercise and pills. I am medically categorized as morbidly obese. Nice. Let that roll off the tongue for a moment. Of course my whole family is overweight, but I can narrow my obesity down to two things. I like to eat and I hate to exercise. I shouldn't say hate because I do like some forms of exercise. I'm a self taught gourmet chef, and the creation and eating of fabulous meals is a joy of mine. I like to see people enjoying what I make and I like to feed people. It's the southerner in me. With a different metabolism, or with a strong interest in major physical activity, I might be okay. I am a woman of significant physical amplitude. I am not hourglass. I'm a dayglass. Possibly a day glass and a half. I wear a 44C bra and you could park a Honda in the shadow of my ass. When I sit crossleg, I look like Buddha in drag and way more hair and I am one sexy beast. I'm totally not kidding. I'm totally cute when I pull out all the stops. I may be big but I am genuinely beautiful. I have a beautiful face, thanks to my mom. I have big blue gray eyes and nice full lashes. Great shoulder length reddish brown hair with golden highlights, alabaster skin that is mostly flawless with the exception of a few freckles here and there. I am, for a fat chick, a real hottie.  Luscious, luxurious and abundant. I'm the fat girl the guys who aren't usually chubby chasers go for. Sure, there have been guys who didn't want me for my size and kids have been cruel, and there have been a few moments of genuine depression and despair but overall, I've had a great life. I've accomplished many of my goals and continue to set them and push myself to my very limit. I've also had more than my fair share of high quality men. I am done making apologies for being fat as if I had some sort of social disease. Do you want to see me naked under halogen lights? Of course not but I look great under candlelight and moonlight. Are my tits going to be in my armpits when I lay on my back? Of course, but who's aren't when you have breasts over a b cup? How about weird sexual postitions? Um, probably not. Am I great in bed? You bet your ass I am.   If any of this bothers you, well that's your problem, not mine. There is more to humans than one characteristic, be it skin color, religious belief, sexual preference, or size. I find the whole fat discussion very boring. I am who and what I am in more complexity than any single label. Success, failure, happiness, misery, the will all be mine in some measure, and none is avoidable or achievable based on what numbers the scale may flash.   Don't get me wrong. I understand fully what lays before me. I realize that my being overweight has only helped me get a disease that was perfectly avoidable until I ended up pregnant or later on in life. It doesn't shock me at all that I'm diabetic. I knew it was coming. I ate the food, I didn't exercise and I have to live with the consequences of my choices. There are a lot of things I can not do and places I cannot go because of my size. People who dismiss me simple because of my weight and probably say awful things behind my back. For ever man who has loved me, there are probably a dozen who said "Not in a million years." I have a lot of very lovely and good friends but I'm sure there are people in the world who dislike me and refer to me as "fat bitch" like the girl tonight instead of just "bitch".   I guess the point of the matter, besides venting a little, is that calling me fat isn't a shock to me. It doesn't hurt. It probably did when I was in the 4th grade but not any more. I've had years to live with it. I wake up ever morning and look at myself in the mirror, just like you. Right now I laugh at your stupidity, and give you a big "thanks, Captain Obvious."
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      bombshell of the month: I'm diabetic.   Yup, all those years of hard living. The whole whopping 6 of them have made me diabetic.   Okay, that's a little more dramatic than what is the truth. The truth is everyone (and I do mean everyone) in my family has it. We're roly poly fat Irish people. We like the meat and potatoes. Yum yum. So that's the first knock. Second, I'm overweight. I know, I had no clue either. Maybe I should get those mirrors in my house like everyone says. (totally joking) and three, I forget the third check mark the doctor said but I have a pattern. Like the psychological idea that anyone abused has a predisposition to become an abuser or anyone the child of an alcoholic is destined to be one too, I am falling right into the family curse....at 27.   Not good.   So, to say I was surprised is inaccurate. I naturally assumed and went ahead and had the doctor do the blood work. Ding! We have a winner on the High glucose price is right!  I went on Friday and had my Diabetic class and my nutrition class and thankfully there is some hope. I'm still young enough and my number fluctuate so much that IF I get my weight down and IF I eat a balanced, low fat, low carb diet, I could live several years if not the rest of my life practically medicine free. Nice. I'd already started weight watchers three weeks ago. I restarted working out and I actually just got back from a rendevous with my new love, the elliptical machine. We spent 30 fun filled sweaty minutes together in perpetual motion. I multitasked by reading an Allure magazine and saw some studies that would make for interesting topics, it counted my calories and strides. So the relationship is going well.   But then after it turned sour as when I got home it was time to stab myself with a needle, again. See, being a diabetic means you have basically blood let yourself in the name of your health. I thought we got away from this sadisticness since the middle ages but no. To be a diabetic means you like to ritually prick yourself and let a machine tell you how high or low your blood sugar is. I have yet mastered the art of getting blood from my arm and after several tries, give up and prick my very sensitive fingers. Again, I'm being melodramatic. It doesn't really hurt that much. Not as much as an insulin needle, which I swear that I will never use since the thought of sticking myself with a needle makes me woosy.  So, in light of that thought here are my goals.  1. Lose weight (already in motion) 2. Exercise (again in motion) 3. Prick myself twice a day at various times 4. Eat a well balance low fat and low carb diet according to my nutritionist 5. Feel better 6. Get into that blue dress in a few months 7. Take care of my feet 8. Never get to a point that I will have to contemplate sticking myself with a needle 9. Don't get discouraged. I may have a disease, but I haven't given up control to it yet and it doesn't have me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      THINGS THAT ARE DIFFICULT TO SAY WHEN DRUNK:   1. Innovative  2. Preliminary  3. Proliferation  4. Cinnamon   THINGS THAT ARE VERY DIFFICULT TO SAY WHEN YOU'RE DRUNK:   1. Specificity  2. British Constitution  3. Passive-aggressive disorder   THINGS THAT ARE DOWNRIGHT IMPOSSIBLE TO SAY WHEN YOU'RE  DRUNK:   1. Thanks, but I don't want to have sex.  2. Nope, no more beer for me.  3. Sorry, but you're not really my type.  4. Good evening, officer. Isn't it lovely out tonight?  5. Oh, I couldn't. No one wants to hear me sing.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      With the weekend upon us, I figured it would be good to write a little letter.  Dear Alcohol,   First & foremost, let me tell you that I'm a huge fan of yours. My friend, you always seem to be there when needed. The perfect post-work cocktail, a beer with the game, and you're even around in the holidays hidden inside chocolates as you warm us when we're stuck in the midst  of endless family gatherings. However, lately I've been wondering about your intentions.  While I  want to believe that you have my best interests at heart, I feel that your influence has led to some unwise consequences, briefed below for your review.  1. Phone calls: While I agree with you that communication is important,  I question the suggestion that any conversation of substance or necessity takes place after 2 a.m. Why would you make me  call those ex-boyfriends/girlfriends when I know for a fact they do  not what to hear from me during the day, let alone all hours of the night?  2. Eating: Now, you know I love a good meal, but why do you suggest  that eat a kabob with chili sauce, along with a big Italian hoagie &  some stale chips (washed down with chocolate Nesquik & topped off with a Kit Kat all after a few cheese curls & chili cheese fries)? I'm an  eclectic eater, but I think you went too far this time.  3. Clumsiness: Unless you're subtly trying to tell me that I need to do more yoga to improve my balance, I see NO need to hammer the issue  home by causing me to fall down. It's completely unnecessary, and the  black & blue marks that appear on my body mysteriously the next day is  beyond me.  Similarly, it should never take me more than 45 seconds to  get the front door key into the lock.  4. Pictures: This can be a blessing in disguise, as it can often  clarify the last point below, but the following costumes are banned from ever being placed on my head in public again: Indian wigs,  sombreros, bows, ties, boxes, upside-down cups, inflatable balloon  animals, traffic cones, or bras. Also, what is with you making me take  pictures with people I clearly don't like when I'm sober? Yet they  suddenly become my best friends when a flash is presented?  5. Beer Goggles: If I think I may know him/her from somewhere, I most likely do not. Please do not request that I go over & see if in fact, I do actually know that person. The phrase "Let's F***" is illegal  from now on. While I may be thinking this, please reinstate the  brain-to-mouth-block that would stop this thought from becoming a  statement, especially in public. Please stop me from talking to the guy/girl with the crooked teeth; acned-up face; bad breath, beer belly, etc. Why are they so appealing to me while I'm with you & why are they so disgusting to me the next morning after you have worn off??  6. Furthermore: The hangovers have GOT to stop. This is getting ridiculous. I know a little penance for our previous evening's debauchery may be in order, but the 3pm hangover immobility is  completely unacceptable. My entire day is shot. I ask that, if the  proper precautions are taken (water, vitamin B, bread products, aspirin) prior to going to bed/passing out facedown on the kitchen floor with a bag of popcorn, the hangover should be minimal & in no  way interfere with my daily activities.  Alcohol, I have enjoyed our friendship for some years now & would like  to ensure that we remain on good terms. You've been the invoker of great stories, the provocation for much laughter, and the needed  companion when I just don't know what to do with the extra money in my  pockets. In order to continue this friendship, I ask that you carefully review my grievances above & address them immediately. I  will look for an answer no later than Thursday 3pm (pre-happy hour) on your possible solutions & hopefully we can continue this  fruitful partnership.  Thank you, from your biggest fan.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whew! Finally the new template is up and running...Sort of. I've got some bugs to fix but it's here. Very summery. I'm ready for the warmer weather.   Spent much of the day watering the lawn because nice hot sweaty guys came and sprinkled weed killer on my yard. How nice of them. I will kill those evil thisles if it's the last thing I do.  I'll have a real post soon about the goings on.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ah, much nicer, don't you think? I loved the daisies but hunny they had to go. So here I sit, at work, doing nothing but working on my website.   I ate my tuna and crackers. I want something a little more substantial. I think I'll go home and eat some soup.  More to come.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, honestly I've always been cynical. Just to let you know, this isn't a political thing, it just started with a political comment. I was chatting with a friend who happens to be a liberal and he said, "I know why you are a republican."   Amused and waiting with bated breath as to how he came to this realization I asked, "Why am I a republican?"  He says to me, "Well, you love the George Romero Living Dead movies. You have all of them. You love societal disaster movies like The Matrix, Terminator, The Day After and all that. You are a cynic. You believe that society shouldn't help itself and others, it should fend for itself and do what it can to survive."  So I thought about this and I guess he's right. I am growing cynical. I hate society as a whole. I think society is evil. I see stories like the people who killed the puppies and a teacher having sex with a 14 year old boy and think, is this it? Is this life as we know it in the modern world? Is this how life was envisioned to be in the 21st century?  I love watching and reading old English Literature. My mom tells me I'm old fashioned because I understand English society during the Empire days like Jane Austen and Pride And Prejudice when everyone was civil and quaint. Do I want to go back to that time? Heavens no. I like my internet, my coffee from starbucks and my car. I like the fact that I can do pretty much anything I want and I can inherit all that my family owns and I don't have to worry about finding a man to marry me based on my dowry. It's the idea of civil society I miss. Bowing to each other. Showing respect. Ill behavior isn't tolerated and looked down on. Now a days, anyone can get away with almost anything.   So I'm cynical. I don't like the world. I think it's evil. I see what we do to each other every day and think, this may be our last because whoever came up with this idea surely has gotten fed up by now. It seems there are so few little slices of heaven now.  So I said to my friend, that yes, it's true that I'm going cynical but I see society today like Romero's Living Dead. Most of us are Zombies, decaying bags of flesh just wandering along with the rest of the pack. No heart, no mind, just instinct and hunger, willing to do almost anything to satisfy that insatiable urge that they can't seem to control. And there are just a few survivors, struggling to stay alive, struggling to do good in the world. Struggling to hold on to that last shred of humanity that makes us so unique. I occasionally say that animals have better manners than people do. My cat loves me with better respect than my neighbor's kids do and all I do for it is give it food, water, medical attention and pet it a few times a day. My cat may get mad at me sometimes, but it would never throw a rock through my window just because I said for them to not come over and ring my doorbell and run. They aren't even smart enough to know that I can see them do it through the window in the door and I sit there, watch them giggle on the damn doorstep, ring it a few times, then out of courtesy get up and open the door so they can run across the street and laugh as I open the door and play dumb. They really get mad if you walk to their house and tell their mom that they are doing it and they should stop. So if I may be cynical, it's because I'm tired of finding zombies. I want to find humans. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm just having a bummy day. I can't break it. First I'm mad at Dave, then he makes me upset. I can't really go into that. I'm just not feeling good.   I want to eat to comfort myself, knowing fully well that's what I don't need to do right now.   I now realize why I feel so bad. I didn't take my medicine this morning.   Always an important thing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just sitting around doing Jack chit. I love doing that. Every person who saw me today asked me what I was doing for July 4th and that was my response. I actually didn't do Jack Chit. I went out and bought a gas grill but that was pretty much about it. I didn't have the energy to even buy the propane for the tank so I could actually use the grill, I just bought it in the thought that I would get around to using the grill eventually this week. Just not today.  Yup, today is July 4th, Independence Day to you and me here in America. I love Independence day. I really do. It's one of my favorites. Anything that can combine, family, friends, drinks, food and the proper (or improper) use of explosives is a great holiday. Hell, let's have a day like that once a month. I think it would seriously improve things.   Besides the fact that we celebrate today that 228 years ago today old Tom Jefferson stayed up all night and wrote the Declaration Of Independence, everyone signed it (especially John Hancock) and we shipped it over to King George of England with a proper American Eeff You, it's a day to celebrate our nation. I like that but besides that I like July 4th for so many other reasons that have nothing to do with history.   I love July 4th because it's hot. I don't know about the rest of the country but it's almost the dog days of summer here in Missouri. I've live here all my life and I used to be a little girl growing up on an acre of land just outside of St.Joe. Not really a farm but I just recall my life being much like the Country Time Lemonade commercials. Running around barefoot. Enjoying yourself. Making a day of just having fun. July 4th reminds me of that so much. We barbecue, talk to our neighbors. Dad puts the flag out in the lawn. I pull out the tanning lotion and sit on the deck all morning in the sun, drink a diet coke and enjoy myself. Doing jack chit. I think that should be a requirement that everyone, at least once on July 4th should be allowed one to two hours of doing nothing but Jack chit but sitting on your azz, drinkin something with your sunglasses on and maybe talking to someone you like enough to talk to. How American is that?  the main reason I love July 4th is fireworks. I love fireworks. I even love the smell of fireworks powder. You know when they've fired them off and the streets get all hazy. My mom gave me a little plaque that I keep on my desk with a quote from Sarah Williams' "The Old Astronomer To His Pupil." It's one of my favorite quotes. It says, 'Though my soul may set in darkness, it will rise in perfect light, I have loved the stars too fondly To be fearful of the night....' I've never been afraid of the dark.  What does this have to do with fireworks? They remind me of shooting stars. Homemade shooting stars. Mixtures of chemicals that when lit light up the night sky in a rainbow of colors. I could sit and watch them all night long.   Back in high school, I dated a guy who's family ran a business that put on fireworks displays around the Midwest. He got my phone number because we were talking about stars and I told him about my love of stars and he said to me, I swear to Gawd,  "I could light up your night sky any time you want."  I didn't know what he meant until the family fireworks connection was revealed. I was hooked, what can I say? That's where I learned my love of the smell of fireworks. I just love that smoky sweet smell. I learned what some of the powders make. I also learned that he'd lost a cousin in a fireworks accident so the danger is there. So beautiful, yet so deadly.  I went to almost every display he had in town. And he did light up my night sky. He hated talking about fireworks but I never got tired of it.   Fireworks and my love of them started early. I would be like a kid at Christmas. I couldn't wait to get outside and shoot off my fireworks on July 4th. My parents would buy them a few days before. A whole huge brown paper sack of them. My brothers got the bottle rockets. I got the snakes and smokebombs.   I would be outside, 9 in the morning, begging my dad to light my punk so I could go outside and play. After about 20 minutes, the drive way that was once concrete grey turned into a mosaic of smoky colored stains and black ashy starry spots. Then I went and ate, went to a barbecue all in excited anticipation of the main event. I would ask all day, is it dark enough yet? I couldn't look outside and see the sun was still up apparently. My brothers would sate me for a while with the screaming bottle rockets till finally, the sun went down.   Then red, blue, yellow, purple sparks light up the night sky. The sparklers, the roman candles, the jumping jack fire crackers that you'd light and stand far enough back or so you thought but then'd you'd have to run in another direction as they chased you all over the yard.  Fountains in every color, white streakes shooting into the sky then exploding with a loud pop. And even my families favorite, the egg laying chicken firework. Nothing says July 4th like a paper chicken shooting white hot colored eggs out it's rear end then bursting into flame.  I loved it all. My parents would sit back, drinking and watch us having a good time. You could see. They loved it. We'd always run out of the big stuff but never bottle rockets and those would be saved till New Years when at the stroke of midnight we'd set the last of them off too, standing in our pajamas in the freezing cold.   So here it is July 4th, 2004. I smell horrid from the Off Skintastic and being sweaty all day. I just got back from a bar with my friends. I have to work in the morning so I should be in bed. But instead I grabbed the citronella candle, a diet coke and sat for 30 minutes enjoying my neighbors shoot off their fireworks. My next door neighbors leaned on their deck and we chatted for a few minutes. All smiles and light. They complimented my new grill. I thanked them and invited them over next weekend for a barbecue. Then we quieted down and watched the sky turn colors and the wind blew my way and I got that smell. Fireworks powder.   I sat back in my chair and just did jack chit for a few minutes, thanked ole Tom Jefferson and the bunch for deciding they didn't like England and drank my diet coke. Said a small prayer to the fireworks boy and thanked him kindly for lighting my night up for so many years. Smiled for a bit and just watched the sky as new stars were added for a few seconds. Red ones, blue ones, purple, white, and green ones. Then they went away.   I grabbed my diet coke, took one last look as my neighbors set off a huge chrysthansimum looking firework. It streaked upward above my house with a golden tail, then popped and burst into the sky lighting the whole neighborhood up in a shower of purple then white. Then it rained down in little gold sparkles.  It reminded me so much of a saying. Life is not measured by how many breaths we take, but by the moments that take our breath away. Today was a breathtaker.  Happy Independence Day.
       
    
    
</post>



</Blog>