<Blog>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is this?:  urlLink     It is Sarah from Joe Millionaire, AKA Cindy Schubert, professional fetishist!  She has starred in bondage and fetish films (though fully clothed only). I was at dinner last night with some other reality show savants who, had I been able to reveal this knowledge, would have undoubtedly been impressed.  In this particular picture she is tickling a woman's feet. But it's all over the internet and now everybody knows so they won't be so impressed; i bet chris will be shocked however.  I had a really yummy dinner last night, trout salad, it was really quite good. I have a wireless internet card, i discovered but then i discovered it doesn't work when it almost exploded my computer. Yes, I said exploded, so what? And now my left shift key doesn't work so I have difficulty making question marks. This sucks. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did super great on my Fantasy Challenge!  For those who do not know, Real World and Road Reals have battles, where a variety of former cast members, some who are well into their 30's, come back to reality television and compete in games for money. This year the gimmick is all the girls are on one team, all the boys on another, hence, "Battle of the Sexes."  MTV also has added a feature that is similar to fantasy baseball, where you choose teams and gain points when your members do things like get into hissy fits, give hugs, cry, get bleeped, or actually earn points on the "challenges" this show is based on.  So I have a team, and currently my members are Ellen (go Korean American exposure on television! from the Road Rules no one watched and where she hooked up with totally hot Adam who kind of looks like Evan from Joe Millionaire but better looking), Ruth (the drunk from Real World Hawaii who is kicking ASS during the games), and Emily (more on her). The guys on my team are Antoine (my favorite! but sort of weak, from Road Rules Europe, known for threatening to kill Belou with a fork.), Yes (again, a cutie, yes yes yes!--from road rules semester at sea), and James (a random road rules, but not the same one emily is from).They met on another of these challenges, and now they are dating, and they are sooo cute together. But they are going to earn me points for making out (i hope!).    My team is named Puck Sucks, because PUCK is on the show, infamous from Real world season 3, where he made fun of Pedro, who later died of AIDS and was a good decent person while Puck was everything bad that exists in the world. He is the biggest point earner because he is bleeped numerous times, trash talks, fights, cries and whatever else you get points for in the game.  So if i wanted to play competitively, he would have to be on my team, but since i am playing with heart, he can kiss my ass till he dies.  In knitting news, things are not going well. Does anyone know how to knit? Does anyone want to help me?  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have switched to a new comment host; it's at  urlLink blogExtra.com . Unfortunately it's not as coool as enetation, but it is far more reliable. It still has some smilies though.  Enough of this madness, I'm going to bed!!  Just a side note, for anyone watching Joe Millionaire--Isn't he the densest guy alive? He's trying to be so sincere but he is literally a lunkhead! And those two girls (you know who i'm talking about, meow!watch out for those claws), would dump him in a minute if they found out he wasn't rich.  Poor Zora, she deserves so much more. At least Mojo is gone.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what have I been working on? The comments function, powered by  urlLink enetation , which is a wonderful wonderful service, it is just driving me super batty. So I will keep working on it. Basically, sometimes it works and sometimes it does not.  I like the smiley feature and I may be updating the template soon which the enetation site allows you to do, so I like that. It's just that sometimes it doesn't work (the link to comment won't show up at all). It helps to hit reload a lot, I have discovered. It does not help to bang your hands against your head in frustration.  Update on Ms. SAT (Stinky Awful Teacher)--this afternoon while I was working on this commenting dilemma, Ms. SAT came into my room and asked if Mr. BYT (Brash Young Teacher) next door was still there, saying, "his door is locked." My assumption was to tell her, no he is not there. Unfortunately she took this as an invitation to use the door in my room that is connected to his room to take a pen. I was like, "um, I said I don't think he's there," and she, distractedly, answered, "oh yes, i just want to borrow I pen I use sometimes." A PEN? that she USES sometimes? She's going to sneak into his room for a PEN? doesn't she have ONE pen???  I was about to offer her a pen, when she went into his room, then popped out saying, oh I couldn't find one, then rushing out again.  So so sketchy.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      one more time
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ugh, more and more. what is this syntax error they speak of?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woohoo, it worked it worked it finally worked. now i wash my hands of it. I wasted my whole afternoon, so i tip my hat to you, glen, for being my inspiration.  I am happy to have this, hopefully it will stay around and I won't have to waste any more time on it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Goddamn i hate this!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got so many things done today: I went to my first Unitarian Universalist Church Service. It was pretty interesting but in the end, it was pretty much like..church. You sing songs and you pray and you listen to a long sermon. Some interesting things: They don't have crosses, they have "chalices," they call the prayer time "meditation," the prayers include poems by Walt Whitman, the sermon today was a long history of how Unitarians and Universalists are crazy liberal and how their whole thing is religious freedom. Basically they're saying, hey, man, believe whatever the hell you want, peace, you know?  They're very new-agey. Chris was like, let's get the hell out of here, it is super white. I enjoyed myself however, I thought it was interesting, but at the same time I'm always looking out for the big C--not christians, cults!  I will be back next week however to check out the 11:30 service, maybe it will be a more diverse crowd.  I got stood up at brunch. The person who was supposed to meet me was fifteen minutes late. The Fabulous Girl's Guide to Decorum states that you should never stand tardiness. You should wait until your designated time and then leave, explaining later, "Oh, I just assumed you forgot." The person who was supposed to meet me ate brunch by herself, while I ate brunch with my fabulous boyfriend--french press coffee, crisp bacon and sweet orange rolls.  I bought playing cards. Chris and I, rather _I_, enjoy board games but many require too many people. I decided to get a pack of cards, teach chris gin rummy and hopefully this will expand our friday night repertoire, which is to watch movies, eat food, and that's about it.    I got my hair cut. My stylist is from Alaska, who knew? She made my ugly hair look pretty again. But she always blows it out until it looks like a big mushroom cloud. I want to scream don't you see how puffy my hair is??  Apparently she thinks I like it this way. But she flipped the ends out and everything became ok again.  I bought yarn. I was reading martha stewart living--a mistake already--and it had an article about knitting. Long story short, now I can do both a knit stitch and a purl stitch, and I need to special order angora wool from some crazy yarn company in New Jersey to complete the project. Frustration complete.    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are so many things you can do to a blog, even if you know nothing or next to nothing.  You can even get  urlLink cool skins , so non-designers like myself can have attractive blogs. If I keep this up I think I get an honorary "bloggin" membership card or something. Of course some of us have had this blog less than a month, hardly respectable.  If you see many blog changes then WATCH OUT, i've been fussing.  I tried to watch Y Tu Mama Tambien, but the gratuitous sex just made it unwatchable, particularly late at night when I was sleepy. It was ew, get that teenage boy's ass OUT of my face!  We ate Malaysian, which I was surprised Atlanta had. Chris and I have constant arguments about this all the time, is Atlanta the south or is it an urban oasis?  You see signs everywhere that it's the south--confederate flags, people in hunting gear at the mall, but most of these sightings have been OTP (outside the perimeter).  What I see is the gay hub of the south, ethnic restaurants and the real desire to eat there, and learn more about the culture that created this food, and some cold cold weather for what is supposed to be a hot and humid area.  However the more I live here the more I like it, so maybe I'm just making excuses!  Truly there is very little racial mixing though there is a large non-black/white presence here.  But the city is growing and changing and diversifying which is a good sign for the future.   Tonight we eat Moroccan--belly dancing, woohoo! And the Hours--woohoo again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      School was cancelled today in Atlanta because of the "abnormally cold" weather. It was 9 degrees this morning! I think the reasoning was the many kids who ride the bus or walk should not be exposed to this abnormal weather, which they are not at all used to.  I agree, most of the kids in my class wear huge parkas when it's forty or fifty degrees.  I spent my day making:          It took a few hours--it's one of those  urlLink quilt a month projects  from Jo-Ann fabrics. Each month you make a quilt square (this was month one), and at the end you get the setting set and complete the quilt. I only got the one square, but maybe i'll stick with it to the bitter (batting) end.  I think I might take a class. That or knitting, which is infinitely cheaper. You have to buy all kinds of tools for quilting.    Wednesday was the 100th day of school, so we celebrated by doing all things one hundred. We played 100 hide and seek, made 100 froot loops necklaces, made 100 crowns, and had 100 snacks.  Here is the 100 poster we made:          To that end I spent all day on the one 12" square piece of fabric and now i'm spent.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw an IMAX about whales yesterday and fell asleep several times. It was sooo soothing with the music and the waves and the quiet and the lulling and the warm seats. Anyway, I felt bad. I was at the  urlLink Fernbank Museum of Natural History  researching a field trip my class is taking next week.  There's dinosaurs and dead stuffed animals and shells and jewelry too! Very cool museum.   Ate at  urlLink Taqueria Del Sol  which is one of my all time favorite restaurants now. They have these soft tacos that are sooo yummy--this isn't the refried bean and fatty chicken taco my friends, we're talking jalopeno mayonaise and fried tilapia tacos, pulled pork with red chile sauce, the best damned shrimp corn chowder on the planet!!  And it's very cheap. I would consider it one of the best reasons to live in Atlanta.  And I don't even like mexican food. It's kind of neuvo mexican take-out I gess. On my list of things I don't like: 1. Pasta 2. Indian food, particularly anything okra related 3. milk, except whole milk, sometimes 4. turkey  That's all for now. Right now I'm reading The Founding Brothers--pretty good read, very informative and well written.  Joyce Carol Oates' Middle Aged: A romance, which is good but her use of the second person narrative is a bit jarring at times.  (i.e. You are dead, you are being cremated, you were so ALIVE, now you're dead...yeah, we get it, stop beating us over the head with it!), and finally Choke by Chuck Palahniuk.  Apparently Bret Easton Ellis called him the new Delillo. When you write like bret Easton ellis, I guess that can seem realistic. The book is ... juvenile, but still interesting. He definitely comes up with some interesting stuff-but it's like, can you write a whole novel based around urban myths? I guess so!  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday Dr. King. I know people are supposed to go to church or volunteer or whatnot but as this is a day off I have plans to get a manicure. If i ever get out of these pajamas. Yesterday we went to  urlLink Discover Mills , a suckier version of Potomac Mills and Arundel Mills...most prerequisite shops such as Gap or Banana republic were missing. Not even a movie theater. However I did end up getting these cool shoes:      and Chris bought me this awesome stuffed animal at the Sanrio store--I don't usually go for this stuff, but you must admit, this is damned cool:     It's a dog...wearing a bee costume. YEAH!  We saw  urlLink Catch Me If You Can , which i have to say I enjoyed thoroughly. Now I have to read the book, because his story really was affecting. Some people say they didn't like the end, but frankly I thought the end was really what made you understand that his journey was not the superficial whim of a teenage hoodlum, but a vulnerable "man-child," if you will, looking for guidance and security.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Vintage coffee mugs at the thumbs up diner.     Under the table.     The remains of the breakfast.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we ate at  urlLink Thumbs Up Diner , my favorite breakfast place ever. You have to wait a long time because it's small and people like to eat there.  Chris had the buckwheat hotcakes and I had a very cheesy omelet. I was watching the new MTV show,  urlLink Made , where the girl wanted to be a cheerleader and she was a little chubby so she had to go on a diet. It included no cheese and that was so sad.  I'm updating my journal in one week so i must be doing a better job keeping it up to date.  My favorite little kid stories this week include showing my kids the " urlLink Really Rosie " video, which is a cartoon made in the 70's with a soundtrack by carole king. It's so funny to hear the kids singing along to carole king.  I think carole might be a good baby name. I'm always on the lookout for those. Anyway, their favorite song is called "I don't care": it's about this little boy who says I don't care all the time and one day he meets a lion and the lion asks, aren't you worried? I'm going to eat you! and the boy sings, "I don't care!" so the lion eats him (or as one of the kids says, swallowed him, because he didn't chew, and in the end he gets shaken out of the lion by worried parents). We were playing alphabet bingo and another little girl sang, I don't care! every time her letters didn't get called. Isn't that hilarious??    In other news I just completed this application to be a  urlLink CMA at the Teach for America Institute , which means I will either be in Houston or New York this summer if I get it.  It basically means you guide new corps members to be great teachers, but we'll see! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The EYE is watching you    Wow!   Exciting things happened this holiday season. After a looong but fun vacation at home where I received long awaited Marc Jacobs perfume and a cool minidisc player, I got home and decided I needed MORE STUFF and i bought a digital camera. Now I can upload lots and lots of cool and exciting pictures to this blog. And yes by cool and exciting I mean pictures of henry the cat.  Here's a long story about my school : So I'm a teacher and on Friday we had a teacher in-service day where we would be evaluated on our teaching/assessing, etc.  As a teacher it is not all fun and games, we have to keep all sorts of records on our students, fill out a lot of paperwork, etc. The teacher across the hall from me (, let's call her Ms. Stinky Awful Teacher (SAT), is, despite her fifteen years experience, incredibly disorganized, a terrible teacher (1-she has no behavior management, 2-she can't teach AT ALL--unless your idea of teaching is sitting your fat ass at a desk and giving out handouts to five year olds who don't know what they're doing), and she has terrible BO. I wouldn't not mention this if it were not truly heinous.    She has been stressed out because the new administration is trying to get rid of Ms. SAT for being stinky.  It's her first year of kindergarten (she was in fourth grade, but they had to move her for being stinky).  and they're watching her performance all the time, and it's like she doesn't even care. But the worst is, she waits until the last minute and then asks myself, and our extremely efficient lead teacher Ms. EEL to pick up her slack.  Thursday, while ms. eel was picking up her daughter from school, ms.SAT snuck into her room and stole (YEAH, i said it!), a portfolio and a math test because she did not have ANY and did not even have a clue as to what should be in them--keeping in mind that a portfolio is a folder of each student's work that should have been accumulated over the semester.  So she TOOOK it, as well as taking Ms. Eel's self evaluation which asked a bunch of gibberish questions about how we rated our own teaching abilities and then COPIED it.  The funny thing about ms sat is that we both really dislike the way she does things, yet she seems to have no clue that we hold any animosity towards her. And also, I tried to like her. I really did--i tried to look over the bad BO, I tried to answer her endless and often repeated jackass questions about things she was just trained in, but i got really tired of her lazy butt attitude.  So the next day after her meeting with our principal, Dr. X, she came out crying and complaining.  I feel bad for her because her job is seriously on the line, and the new administration does want to keep inept pple at their jobs.  At the same time it's hard to feel sorry for someone who lies and steals and doesn't actually do any work.   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       blahghghg   So I'm thinking of getting a new computer, and it's making my head hurt. Current money situation=not good. Loads of money dropped on recent New York disaster trip.  Still have to go to dentist RE: ground down tooth that requires root canal due to bruxhism.  Have to go to eye doctor.  Have to go to "ladies" doctor.  Have zero insurance (i know i'm a walking accident waiting to happen).  And now I need a new computer because the one we have is a piece of shit and the school's computer is, apparently, on its last legs.  Plus we have to find a new apartment because the place we have now is falling down around us. In addition to the constant ant problem, for whatever reason our bathroom tiles are falling off and the shower curtain rod just randomly fell off. Though these problems are currently resolved, I think it warrants mention that I'm apprehensive about renewing a lease.  In a Ms. SAT (stinky awful teacher) update: one of her students was transfered to my class after one of the students in her class BIT her.  I requested her portfolio which should have included 1) student work and 2) an updated GKAP assessment. Which of course it did not.  How can a portfolio, which is an accumulation of student work over the school year, contain ZERO student work?  And how can the GKAP, which we have just finished the second round of, be almost completely empty?   Students who enter kindergarten in GA are tested individually during three windows, beginning middle and end of the year. We just tested for the middle, which included items like sorting shapes, blending sounds etc.  When I confronted Ms. SAT she said, I didn't know. Even though she had come into my class in the middle of the day last month (as usual!) and asked me what those numbers on the assessment guideline meant. And even though I told her that meant those were the items to test.  So now NONE of her kids have been tested. I think the sad thing is, those tests are meant to help you understand what you need to re-teach or emphasize in terms of skills. And even if she had tested, she wouldn't use those tests for that information. In a way I don't want to go to the principal because she's probably already fired, due to her poor overall performance. But in another way I feel like I need to bust her ass for being so stinky (both literally and figuratively.)  I can understand why people feel sorry for her, and why she feels sorry for herself. She's fighting an uphill battle in an already difficult field. But damn it, there are children's futures at stake!   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I bid you, shut up!   ...if you're talking about the war that is.  This reference is "borrowed" from another blog who recommends this  urlLink article :   Do Keller, or any of the members of his "club," really believe that anything they write registers with the Bush administration? Is Donald Rumsfeld feeling more secure now that Slate is on board? Was Dick Cheney sitting around waiting for Lance Morrow's reluctant approval? In what world are these writers living? This is not a second-year honors seminar at the Kennedy School of Government. This is war, motherfucker!   Great Bylined Thinkers of America, I bid you: Shut up!    What's refreshing is that it's not pro- or anti-war, but rather, anti bad writing.  It's good to have high standards.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       books   As i'm not doing much, I thought i would write a bit on what i am am filling up my time with!  No more reality tv for me, thanks, just some good old fashioned reading.  Glen reminded me of what a great writer Thomas Friedman was, so I picked up  urlLink  The Lexus and the Olive Tree   from the library.  I'm working on E. Annie Proulx's  urlLink   The Shipping News   which was a wonderful movie and now is turning out to be an excellent novel; as well as  urlLink  Family Matters   by Rohinton Mistry. The same author wrote  urlLink  A Fine Balance  , one of my favorites of all time, and though his writing is often sad it's always compelling.  I always want to re-read certain books, but I think my next choice will be  urlLink  Interpreter of Maladies   by Jhumpa Lahiri. I don't know what all this writing about India is about, something about the language of these two writers, maybe the more formal yet still sensual or rhythmic stylings appeal to me more than most American authors--example the whole  choke  incident. I can't take a book that features an enema in its climax seriously. Maybe I just like stories that make me feel sad, because i'm usually so cheery?  I was on the hold list for the hours, but was mysteriously booted off.   My favorite children's book recently:  urlLink  David Goes to School  .  Just look at the pictures and you'll see why.  Weather has been beautiful here, took a long walk on Sunday that included lunch at Harry's. They had the best Tom Kha soup, I was pleasantly surprised. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       awesome!   ooh i had such an awesome day today. i did awesome on my observation, the bane of all teachers; and i finished my portfolio and my principal said, I love it!  that made me feel so good, considering how crap i felt the same time last year. i'm excited that teaching is going well for me, and all my hard work is finally paying off.  Teach for America conference this weekend, including happy hour tonight. i don't know any of the people coming in but i might as well go and see what that's like.    So i ended up getting an interview for Houston, not new york, which makes me kind of sad because after my visit, strange and troublesome as it was, i fell in love with the city all over again. i was definitely looking forward to being able to spend a few (paid) weeks there. but alas, it was not to be, and i may be stuck in the mires of houston again. how i hate that place!!  so why do i go, you ask? because i want to help our corps be the best teachers they can be!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       whhhaaat   a jerk Aaron is. He is a complete liar!!!  I also stayed tuned for about twenty seconds of Are you HOT? and that ended when I was actually judging whether people were hot or not. I said to myself, this is too disgusting, even for you jane. So i just walked away. You can do it America! just walk away!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New York as told by ME   Here's the  urlLink photojournal . Enjoy! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Trista is a ho   I'm sorry but is anyone else disappointed with Trista's total cop-out? She didn't choose Charlie who was totally the right person for her, and instead chose Ryan, the puss in firefighting boots.Chris got really mad when I said that Ryan was a loser, because he relates to Ryan, and says that I would have chosen Charlie and that made me a bad person. Charlie is hot. Case closed.  Also, what is UP with the whole Helene/Aaron thing? They didn't just split up, that is major drama!!  I feel sad that I'm so addicted to their pathetic little story. I bet Brooke's patting herself on the back now.  On the New york visit front, I am putting a link to the photo-documentary of our trip. I put the camera to good use, taking over a hundred pictures of the various things we did around town. Oh and also, while I have no pictures of this, H & M, greatest store ever. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       zora zora zora   I'm still stuck in new york and i just watched the finale to joe millionaire with a lot of damned dirty hippies who are also staying at this hostel.  I was totally surprised when he chose zora--and i was even more surprised when zora was like, I really like you.  She really likes him?  He's not that likable. Weren't you surprised that she didn't have heat?  I was.    More when I finally return to atlanta.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       new york new york   It's a hell of a town, the bronx is up and the snow is down. and down. and down.  eta: tomorrow evening... probably delay: 1-2 days???  I hope not!  I have many many pictures to share when I return...whenever that is!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i'm so super duper     -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Traffic and Breakfast   This weekend told me a lot about Atlanta, namely that if an event is happening in Atlanta, get toilet paper, bread, and bottles of water because you're going to want to stay in during that time.  After our attempted drive to buckhead friday evening, and the closing of the big lennox mall in buckhead (several malls around town actuallY), for some reason I thought Sunday would be a GREAT day to go to the mall.  The drive up was annoying because people in huuge Cadillac Escalades and Hummer limos kept stopping to either buy/sell things out of their cars or from the side of the street.  Or to yell at women for their numbers.  After sitting in traffic for an hour, cursing myself, chris said, we'll get there and when we do we won't leave until it closes.  Two stores later, and the doors are closing; I ask, 'are you closing already?' The nice salesperson tells me, 'yes, we're closing early. i would leave the mall if i were you.'  Explanation: Two fights, a couple strippers and some fireworks have caused a mad dash for the doors, and the ensuing mayhem has required the mall to close approximately thirty minutes after our arrival. I didn't even have a chance to buy anything. I did see the SWAT team in the mall though.  Also, strangely, while the mall WAS packed with people, the stores were virtually empty.  People were just leaning against walls staring at other people staring at them. I wish I had my digital camera!    8 1/2 x 11 was an excellent festival, some notable plays were actually dance numbers, one was completely set to the music of the clash, one was a strange rip off of Waiting for Godot, one was a story about a pedophile.    Best part of my weekend: cheesy omelet at Thumb's Up Worst part of my weekend: I think you know.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Roccocco?? I hate roccocco.     urlLink         urlLink which art movement are you?   this quiz was made by  urlLink Caitlin     this test is bullshit. I never should have said i associated myself with a poodle--but i do!  The girl who made the quiz has this hilarious website--she's only 18 years old. What was I doing when i was 18? too embarassing to consider!  Fill out her survey, she asks you to write haikus and a poem about a historical figure.  My haiku:  largely functioning  i watch unmoved by events  gripping a large stick    My poem:  henry v i wish he was my boyfriend i always wanted to date an action star    I like surveys.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ANGRY jane   Damned NBA All-star game bringing in traffic from all over the goddamned place making a fifteen minute drive to Buckhead an hour and fifteen minute commute from hell!!  We were over an hour early to get to How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days, and we were stuck in traffic the whole time, forcing us to turn around. We ate good  urlLink Thai food  instead and rented The Good Girl, which I must watch so as not to accrue further late charges on my Blockbuster card. Both Sweet Home Alabama AND Igby Goes Down were out, which makes you wonder why there are a hundred copies of freaking Master of Disguise (Dana carvey movie where he's dressed as a turtle? Yes, that is so clever. ha ha ha, that's why all of two copies were rented), and only ten copies of movies people actually want to see.  So i hate you Blockbuster and NB Allstar traffic.   Only in Atlanta would you see a Hummer driving out of a strip club with three TV's inside and 19 inch rims.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Working hard for the money   I'm so excited for this weekend, i'm going to see 8 1/2 x 11, a short play festival at  urlLink Dad's Garage , a comedy theater.  I'm also torn between wanting to see How To Lose a Guy in 10 Days or that new Shanghai Noon movie. Chris realllly (in a guy way) wants to watch it, whereas all I can think about is when we had to sit through The Tuxedo.  i stayed hoping it would get better, but I now wish I had walked out after the first thirty minutes. I still haven't seen The Hours, it's a travesty, I know!    in Ms. SAT (stinky ass teacher) news, it turns out a library book I had been missing for over two months has been in her possession all along. AND another book that is considered LOST by the library, resulting in a $17 fine, is probably also in her possession. If I don't get that book back, I am going to scream bloody murder. Apparently she has been sneaking into our rooms to use valuable and rare supplies, such as rubber cement and construction paper.  It is impossible to work with a person who sinks so low as to steal office supplies on the fly.    In CRAZY chaperone parent news, she confronted me on Wednesday morning, asking me why her oh-so-not-perfect daughter who was recently chastized for hitting other kids was given a "needs improvement" rating on her progress report. The oh-so-not-perfect Parent went on to tell me I was a control freak and that my kids could not have fun on the field trip because of that.  But I, I would not sink to such a level,  NO , I am proud to say, I spoke to her calmly and rationally, cutting her down to size with good sense.  But she is still a crazy awful person that I have to deal with all the time.  And the  Biggest News  is Feb. 15-17 I will be off to new york city after what seems like forever of not having a trip (and drives to maryland do not count!). Now I can explore somewhere (almost) new, and have fun with my friends while doing it. As I told Kathryn the only word I can say is "yay!"
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, it is so sad when the glory of your life would be to just see your blog's name on  urlLink recently published blogs .  Like i said, today was a full day--I'm going to have to get up earlier on the weekend. We got to Thumb's up at 11 am, which is just about the time everyone else in atlanta arrived, so we waited an hour there. Luckily we got seats inside. Total time for breakfast: 30 minutes--it was worth it, I got the Greek Scramble and Chris got Eggs of Paradise, which was eggs with some tomato saucey stuff under it. Then we went to the High, where Chris did not realize we would need tickets; ahh, the heady days of free museum admission are over, at least outside DC they are.  Here is one interesting piece of art Chris enjoyed very much.     It was 70 degrees in Atlanta today, it was just totally beautiful!!  We actually went outside!  Piedmont Park is where everyone goes on the weekend, especially on good weather. We live right next door to Piedmont Park, and the parking is terrible anywhere near the park, and people even park inside our apartment complex. Today was the first day we took advantage of living so close to the park and took a very nice walk. There are lots of dogs in the park, big dogs, little dogs. I want a little tiny dog, but Chris wants a huge ass man dog.  We'll see who wins this battle!  Either way it's hard enough to take care of our crazy cat.   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Friday we went to see the dinosaurs at the Fernbank Museum of Natural History. It was a great trip except for one thing: the chaperone from hell!! Among her many faults: Blaming her daughter's partner for not being able to walk with her, and grabbing her hand away. Ignoring the rest of the group and walking with her daughter only. Disappearance at lunch time while other chaperones were helping students eat.  Arguing with me about whether it is appropriate to allow eating on the bus, then giving her daughter left over chips anyway (and where did these chips come from? i told all the kids to throw their left overs away!!). I walked out with 14 over excited, but tired and happy kids, and one huge migraine.  One thing is for sure, my tolerance level for bullshit has risen to a new level.  I have totally loved Sam Rockwell since I saw him in Charlie's Angels and Heist; I was kind of in awe because I couldn't believe this was the same geeky guy from that movie with Tim Allen, Galaxy Quest. Speaking of Heist, if you haven't seen it, please do, it's one cool caper movie.  Sam Rockwell is a chameleon, sometimes looking like Tom Cruise, sometimes like Christian Bale, sometimes just like himself, but I saw him yesterday in Confessions of a Dangerous Mind, and I think we all have to agree that he did an amazing job. So add him to my list of favorite actors: Philip Seymour Hoffman, Tobey Maguire, and I don't know who else. My mind is not awake right now.   Plans for today: Breakfast at thumbs up and the  urlLink high museum.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Wind Done Gone...   I enjoyed reading Gone with the Wind. Though I love the movie, I never read the novel until after I moved to Atlanta. "Tara" is fictionally located only fifteen miles away from Atlanta, and much of the novel is based on how Atlanta went from a tiny little train depot town to the booming industrial center of the south; so beyond the mere entertainment factor (and it was just entertainment, no real insight into humanity here) it was quite informational as well.    However, as anyone who has read the novel can attest, the novel is very racially skewed, caricaturing all African Americans into neat little boxes. It troubled me when I read the novel because I felt like, um, should I like this? It's quite racist. When I heard about The Wind Done Gone, which has this big sticket on it saying Unauthorized Parody on it, I though oh, this person is trying to capitalize on Gone with the Wind and make even MORE fun of the characterizations of African Americans in the slave and Reconstruction Era. I found quite the opposite as I read it this week.   It's a very insightful little novel (only a hundred or so pages compared to 400+ of the original), and rather than being a "parody," I thought it more to be a voice for many children of the time who had inherited a very confusing heritage (mother a slave/father a plantation owner).  Though the author uses clever little nicknames (Other for Scarlett, R. for Rhett, Beauty for Belle Watling the prostitute), the texture of the story interweaves and builds upon themes that were present but never addressed in GWTW.  Anyway I enjoyed it and anyone who's a fan of feminist/African American lit will definitely find it worth reading.  Whenever I think of Gone With the Wind I think of Stephanie, the crazy red haired woman who was a supervisor at the library when I worked there my freshman summer.  She was literally obsessed with the novel having read it, she claimed, hundreds of times and also collected miniature porcelain dolls of Scarlett in different dresses (yes, like the ones you see featured in Parade Magazine).    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       excellent dining   Two great evenings of dining out...  Friday:  urlLink Iris  is a restaurant that has been missing in Atlanta for a long time. The emphasis was on fresh ingredients, simply prepared, artistically served and moderately priced. I loved this place, and it's only ten minutes away !  I started with the delicous lobster bisque; Chris had the lamb shank with roasted root vegetables (he literally left his plate clean--only the bone remained!) and I had a delicious pork tenderloin with mustard sauce.  We even managed dessert, but it was disappointing: my creme brulee was room temperature. But all in all, a wonderful experience!  Saturday:  urlLink Mu Lan , upscale Chinese restaurant. I had no idea how upscale until I saw the menu, where the entrees were around 15-20 dollars each. Obviously not your regular Buford Highway restaurant. It was in Midtown, a posher section of town, and it really presented itself well. Unlike Iris, this place was extremely done up. But like Iris every detail was attended to, from the lighting, seating, linens, and silverware to the excellent service. And the food was out of this world! We started with pork dumpling in a delicious and just right soy sesame sauce.  Then Chris had the jumbo shrimp in black peppercorn sauce and I had the seafood combination in red curry. Both were out of this world fantastic. I also had the smoothest vodka martini i've ever had.   Currently I'm playing Word Mojo and Cubis on  urlLink Yahoo games .  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A triumphant return!   Things I learned on this trip:  1. Chris really hates the Counting Crows 2. There is only one good ride at Universal Studios 3. Jimmy Buffet's Margaritaville has great coconut shrimp 4. Florida is the trashy capitol of the world 5. Universal Studios has the cleanest public bathrooms hands DOWN  Universal Vacation was an astounding success despite bumpiness at the start--getting lost on the Florida turnpike and an inability to get the park tickets because the ATM machine had eaten my debit card which I had used to purchase the tickets. Everything worked out and we had a realllly good time.  And I even felt happy going to teach again so that's what I call a pleasant vacation.  We did not eat at Emeril's, but the highlight for me was definitely Jimmy Buffet's Margaritaville restaurant. I had to drag Chris there (he hates Jimmy Buffet with a vengeance), but I thought the coconut shrimp was delicious.    Warning--Nerd Alert   In terms of rides we went on the Dueling Dragons roller coaster (which is two seperate roller coasters that intertwine) a million times, and Men in Black, which is the best ride ever, because you get to shoot at things and even I did well, so of course I enjoyed it :).  My favorite ride is ET because it feels like you're flying on the bikes.    We heard about Iraq when we got in the car and the hip-hop station we were listening to was broadcasting Bush's speech, so of course we knew something sketchy was going on, which it was.  I don't feel nervous, more a gut reaction of this is not going to end up well for anybody. Hopefully it will be over soon, but we all know that the war is just the beginning; the US's relation with the rest of world is jeopardized, but who cares? At least Bush is happy.  Again, I would like to say that Howard Dean is the only presidential candidate who not only admits to being against the war, but actively states he believes it is wrong.    In less serious stuff, ahem, people who are "playing" the Battle of the Sexes game should note that having 2/6 people voted off will result in not getting many points! And why don't I have enough faith in Antoine who is the coolest player and gets the most points. It must be because he's Belgian.  Dinner at Hae Woon Dae, the best Korean restaurant in Atlanta, and the best I've ever eaten at in general and finally I get to see The Hours!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       florida here i come   Today was a teacher planning day so no little kiddies were running around. Which is good because I had to get my sub folder ready, as I will not be in school for two whole days, woe is them. They have no clue that I won't be there. I was going to tell them, but then I was like, nah.    Nothing exciting to post except listen to my launchcast station. it's ever so much fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       futurama   Currently we are addicted to futurama, which is in syndication on cartoon network sun-thurs at 11.  It's such a fun way to end the evening before falling asleep. yesterday i fell asleep at 7:30 ... i was pretty tired i guess!    School is almost over, only two more months! It passed by so soon. Little children go crazy when the weather turns warm, and mine are no exception. They have all become hell beasts, difficult to handle and with a wild look in their eyes.    In other news, I have been damn good about cooking at home recently: Sunday: steak, oven fries and asparagus, Monday: Soy-ginger chicken, spicy broccoli and rice, Tuesday: curry, Wednesday: Meatballs, roasted corn and risotto.  Good right??    This is good news because we have been eating out non-stop it seems for the past few months. Stopping only for left overs and the random porkchop. But I read somewhere that you only have to be able to do something for 11 days and then it becomes a habit. I like that idea.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Oh what a beautiful day!   Gorgeous weather resulted in jane actually heading outdoors not in a car!  Took a walk to the nearby park, where we had a picnic lunch and read for a bit. The weather is mid 70's today, so obviously we had to take advantage of it.  In other news, Universal Studios trip is shaping up, but the big question is whether we should spend a wad of cash to eat at Emeril's restaurant?  We're going to try anyway, reservations there are impossible to get apparently.    And in regards to yesterday's post, I forgot to mention my first romantic comedy was The Cutting Edge, does anyone remember this movie?  I loved Moira Kelly and DB Sweeny in a take on Kiss Me Kate, on ice.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Watching Kate Hudson still makes me a little queasy   Why does she have to be so cute and blonde? And her boobs look really small, but she's so tall she can carry it off.  I still really enjoyed this movie. My top five romantic comedies of all time have to be:  1. Pretty Woman 2. Sixteen Candles 3. Amelie 4. 10 Things I Hate About You 5. Grosse Point Blank  Some say these movies lack a certain romance, movies about prostitutes and hit men, teenage angst yes, they can be depressing topics. But isn't love grand?? We're all saved by love! I like movies that make me cry, and these do, but they also give you the warm fuzzies.  I also have a special place for An Officer and A Gentleman, but it hardly counts as a comedy.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OTP blues   So we tried to go see How to Lose a Guy in 10 Day again, at the same theater, same weekday, etc. If you remember, dear readers, last time I was unable to go because of the nightmarish traffic caused by the NBA all star game.  This time the damned movie was sold out even though it's been in theaters for weeks.  ARGH.  We were super hungry too because this is a theater where you can watch and eat a full meal at the same time, so we had been expecting dinner.  So we decided to go OTP to Mandarin Gardens, a buffet chinese restaurant that also offers snow crab legs for an extra five dollars. It's a tasty deal.  But when we were driving back, there was a HUGE accident only three miles before our exit. It took us an hour to go that three miles.    The accident was really scary--two people were exchanging insurance information on the emergency lane when another car came up and hit them, killing them.  Of course we didn't know that until this morning. What annoyed me last night was that there were a million emergency vehicles but people were starting to drive in the emergency lanes just to go a leeetle bit faster. So disturbing!   In other news we're going to be at Universal Studios Florida next week for Chris' spring break. We'll be there for three days and seeing Universal Studios Florida and Islands of Adventure of course. We had hoped to go to Key West this spring break but the drive is just far too long for such a short period of time. Did you know USF was named Frommers #1 Best Bargain Vacation?  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      test again
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If my template ever worked I could only be too happy.  Unfortunate mishap with meatloaf last night. I wrote down 2 1/2 TBLS salt as opposed to 2 1/2 TSP salt.  3 tsp= 1 tbls.  I got to 1 1/2 tbl before i started thinking...this is a lot of salt.  so I basically added 5 tsp, not 2.5  Realizing my mistake, I made a test meatball. It was super salty, of course. So we went to McDonald's. the end.  I woke up super late today. I think all I want to do this weekend is sleeeep. I had a perfectly good post written last night when my computer froze so you're all getting drivel today.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is not working!  I'm referring to my attempts to modify my template.    I just attended the Dean meetup which was very exciting. I hope more people start to get behind Dean, who I see as a great no-bullshit, grounded, yet hopeful candidate.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dean in 2004   Ok party people, I've finally chosen a candidate; after the loss of Gore and no clear road to take, and then just puttering about pondering the state of the democratic party and any good chance we have of winning this election, considering Kerry and then rejecting him, I'm agreeing with Dean. Supported by Rick, and then later Alex, Martin Sheen too, I see now that he is the only logical choice the true lefty, or at least the Democratic lefty has! And a damn good one too.  So the only way of getting this guy elected is letting people hear who he is. On that, I've signed up to volunteer and to meet up with other Dean supporters. It helps that the meet up place is two seconds from my house.    If you are interested in  urlLink Howard Dean , and would like to find a meet up in your area, just go to  urlLink meetup.com .    In other news, I was awake at 7:30 today for no particular reason.  I watched My Big Fat Greek Wedding and did not like it. I saw half of Igby Goes Down and while I did like it, I only watched half of it, woe is me.  I finished the Shipping News and while I enjoyed it greatly, I would have liked to have read it before watching the movie.  Dinner at New Indigo, which used to be Indigo Coastal Grill. The french seafood restaurant was very whimsical but there seemed be a strange smell lurking in the air, even when we asked to have our seats changed.  And NO the smell was not me, I smelled like perfume.  I should have had the salad rather than the french onion soup which was as Chris said, "only OK."  Edible but not delicious.  The entrees were great though, ribeye for chris (though it came underdone) with garlic potato rounds, and Grilled mahi-mahi with red pepper sauce on yukon gold puree (or mashed potatoes).  The other choice was agnes and muriels and I might have preferred it, but change is good. I was feeling under the weather so we didn't make it across the street to What's the Scoop, supposedly the best ice cream next to Jake's in Atlanta.  I don't crave ice cream, but I enjoy it. I'm not a very dessert person. What is YOUR favorite dessert dear reader? Inspire me.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       looking into other people's windows    urlLink buddyzoo.com  . which brings us to note if i do not have your AOL screen name, please pass it on, i'll definitely talk to you more than if i do not have it--maybe.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       listening   Badly Drawn Boy-hour of the bewilderbeast Colday-rush of blood to the head...over and over and over again Rufus Wainwright-cigarettes and chocolate Pete Yorn-Day I Forgot--i'm going to see him May16.  Inman Park Parade yesterday-my first "parade" perse, it was quite entertaining. highlights include the "Anna Nicole Smith" homage, complete with large brassy blonde with exposed bra waving to crowd and the "Nile Style" float, a cardboard Sphinx attended by strange and glittery Egyptian stereotypes. Everyone was pelting candy.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       boring life   oh this boring life Here at the dying end of the day I wasn't made for this scene baby !  because my life is so boring, here's a recipe for  urlLink spicy fish soup  that will spice things up! I replace canned jelapenos for the canned chilies and it really has a kick!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sooo sleepy   For the past two days when I got home I fell asleep.  It was the groggy afternoon nap kind of sleep and I only felt groggier after it. Damn you time change i blame you.  I bought two mice for my classroom--a little brown one that is friendly and a little white one with black spots that bit me.  The little white one keeps getting out of the cage so I haven't brought them to school yet until I can figure out what the situation is.  I watched the final episode of Married By America. I haven't watched any previous episodes, which must have been tedious, will they or won't they, who cares until the last episode???  It was sad, both couples ended up not going through with it--tres humiliating for the other person involved. Both of the contestants were girls, the former a princess type who had posed in playboy and whose father was a complete whack job and who of course ended up changing her mind at the last minute; and the latter a blonde bartender who was actually quite sweet. Her name was Billie Jean. She was like i love love love you Tony. And tony was like, yeah, that's great...i don't love you! But let me get up to the altar and wait for you to declare that you will in fact go through with this and then reject and humiliate you in front of all of your friends and family.  She left crying hysterically while her friends yelled about what a loser and asshole he was. Chris thought: I don't think he should have gone through with it, this show is crazy! Jane thinks: He's a jerk for doing that to her, the least he could have done was do it before they got up there; the most was take a chance and do it, what the hell was he on the show to do anyway??? I am of the mind however that if you want to make it work, it will, but if you don't then it won't no matter how you feel about the person.  Part of the reason I felt this way was because though he did not love her at the time, he noted he was well on his way to being in love with her.  He's a chickenshit jerk head who, like most cultural Americans, can't commit to diddly squat.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dogwood Festival   Now that I feel all better, we spent this weekend eating eating eating. We ate at Cowtippers, which is a very gay friendly steak and potato place up the street from our house. Damn good steak.  Then yesterday we ate at Hae Woon Dae, which i've mentioned before. It's chris' favorite restaurant in atlanta, and one of mine too. I felt very homesick for DC so I had to get me some good Korean food. I love that they serve lots of  banchan , the many little side dishes Koreans eat to round out the meal. I never went to a lot of Korean restaurants in DC but it's hard to imagine one that serves better food than Hae Woon Dae.  And this morning Thumbs Up Diner, yummy yummy.    Thanks to the gooorgeous weather we went to the Dogwood Festival at Piedmont Park. There were lots of artists booths, music stages and food being sold out of trucks of course, but they also had a Frisbee catching contest for dogs which we stopped to watch. It was very fun and very crowded. And now back to school.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why have you failed me, Atlanta weather???   So rather than relaxing this spring break, this one week of rest before six non-stop weeks of teaching, I  1) am sick with a nasty cough 2) ripped my last toric contact lens so I had to go to the eye doctor rather than the dentist 3) am wearing layers of sweaters it is so fricking cold here.  However I can not complain, some things that have made my spring break good include reading Life of Pi by Yann Martel, which if you haven't heard of this book then you must not be a reader! It's all the buzz, for good reason, it was very good, very entertaining. I think I should have read it twice, but oh well. If you've read it please let me know what you think.  And last night we went to team trivia at Mellow Mushroom. It was a lot of fun, BUT, I just want to publicly apologize for Alex for not believing when he said, Bagdhad is further east than Moscow. He's been to Moscow, so...he would probably know. Anyway, we were in first place the whole game until the fateful question: Put these cities in order from east to west..and the answer was Bagdhad, Moscow, Istanbul and Belgrade.  Geography is el stinko.    Rick got a miniature dachshund..I am obsessed with miniature dogs..I want one !!!! His is named Beatrice and her back was broken, is that not the saddest thing in the world? They told her she would never walk again but she proved them wrong!  And that's that.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       mulholland drive   is so fucked up.  My head is reeling a little bit from watching it. Then I cheated and read this  urlLink article  on salon.com that helped clear a few questions up. i do have to say i now know what all the fuss about naomi watts is about. she was pretty fucking amazing.  it is spring break for me and on the roster:  1-a root canal (yay! yippee!)  2-relaxing! 3-planning for school!  these are all very relaxing i know. i think the one thing i'm definitely going to do is see all those movies chris does not want to see, the hours, the pianist, talk to her, and spider. no one will see these movies with me. oh well. no one said artsy fartsiness would make you popular.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Teach For America  Yesterday was the Teach for American Alumni Induction, which marks the end of our two year teaching commitment. It was quite an emotional night, with slide shows and award presentations. Direct quote from one of my students about me:  Ms. Yang is nice because she reads books. She gives us candy from the grab bag.  She is mean and funny.  And a new chapter opens, when I go to Houston this summer and also I will be the kindergarten Learning Team Leader as well. So it's more of a leadership role.  Anyway, the end of the school year is here, the planning/cleaning is almost done and then I will be off to Maryland for a few days then off to Houston for a few weeks, then back in Atlanta for just one more year.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Graduation Day   Tomorrow is the kindergarten graduation. When I think of all the work we've done this year, all the wonderful things our class has accomplished, I get quite weepy. These kids were so wonderful and fun and awesome to work with, they're really the teacher's dream.  It makes me thing, wow, I'm so glad I did this or else I would never have met these kids and changed their lives and changed my life!  This whole experience was pretty awesome, even the first year which was god-awful.  Soon to post--pictures of graduation, and maybe even a short (soundless) movie of the kids performing!  sniffle sniffle, I get sad just thinking about it!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       News, Exciting News Here!   So many exciting things to share, dear readers. I have received a copy of The Crimson Petal and The White, a quite interesting book you should check out if you're interested in late 19th century prostitutes or if you were a fan of Manor House, this is a relevant read.    In more exciting news I bought a game cube, so I can play the new Legends of Zelda game on it. Yes I am a big fat loser, OK, I understand this now lemme alone so I can work the buttons right... Well it hasn't actually gotten here yet. I bought it on Amazon and you'll know when I've received it by another long absence.  And if you are a faithful reader you may know that long long ago I applied for a job to work as a corps member advisor at the Houston Institute for Teach for America.  I did not, sadly, receive the position and so I put it out of my mind and decided to work on planning for the summer. Lo and behold, someone dropped out and who will it be to come to the rescue, none but your stupendous heroine herself, namely, me. So I will be in Houston all summer hopefully not too busy to continue to entertain with stories such as the one I am about to tell:  Kindergarten is at an end and we are busily preparing for our graduation this Thursday.  Each teacher shall prepare her or his class with a poem and a song to be recited before the diplomas and awards are handed out.  Our class' poem is quite cute, it goes like this:  Now I know my ABC's, colors shapes and days. I sang some songs, learned some poems, rhymes and fingerplays. I played outside on sunny days and inside when it rained. My little hands and feet were busy every day. My teacher was Ms. Yang, I kept her on her toes. She tied my shoes, combed my hair and even wiped my nose. But now it's time to say goodbye to all my kindergarten friends. School is over, summer's here, but learning never ends!  Ah, but cruel and cunning Ms. SAT is back in the picture folks. It has been confirmed she is not returning next year, so we all assumed she is out of the picture. But her merciless ways never cease to amaze me. Her class has not really practiced at all for the long and complicated graduation ceremony as attested when we practice together in the afternoons.  Up until last week her class had barely memorized their poem or song, much less the ones we recited as a group.  One day I went to use the phone in the office next to her class to call a parent; wasn't I surprised to hear her class reciting their poem, just as usual, but with a new addition that goes: Ms. Williams was my teacher, she tried her very best, and so on and so on.  The nerve! The sheer audacity!!  Isn't it bad enough she created all of the "student" work displayed in her room? Isn't it bad enough that her children cannot recognize numbers past ten?  Isn't it awful enough that she steals supplies, portfolios, even observations from fellow teachers from which to plagiarize?  Oh the humanity!  I fear that too many stories like this one seep out however, while the good ones remain quietly, uninterestingly abandoned in the corner.  Which is why I'm proud to announce that my OTHER fellow kindergarten teacher Ms. EEL (extremely efficient lead teacher with the acronymicly-unfortunate pseudonym) has just won the Master Teacher Award for our school and our School won the Trailblazer Award out of half the schools in Atlanta. So go us!  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What have I been doing?   I adopted another cat, who came up to the door and said, can I be your cat please?  and we said, Yes! And we named her Esme and she is a cutie.    School is almost over, only two more weeks to go, and while I'm very very sad because I love my babies this year, I'm also very very happy to have a break!   Speaking of which, I slept in when someone (we won't name names) did not set the alarm and was very late for school Thursday.  The same unnamed someone left the television blaring so I did not hear the numerous phone calls from the school to reach me and in fact I only woke up thanks to sunlight streaming in. That same school day we went to the Atlanta Botanical Gardens, which was nice, however, it was quite HOT and quite TIRING for the poor babies, not to mention me :P  The next week will be INSANE with meetings and concerts and dinners and brunches.    I read The Dive From Clausen's Pier which I will speak more on later.  I need something else to read now...hmm, what could it be? Any suggestions?  Also to those of you who are being transplanted to DC, check out  urlLink Cakelove  on U Street; it's bound to make your transition sweet, or at least provide a treat to reward for the hell that is moving!  Banana Legs Crunchy Feet sound too good to be true. I'm going to have to head over there myself.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       shows chris is obsessed with and which i enjoy also   pete and pete--we get digital cable and reruns of pete and pete every day at least twice a day come on noggin, which also airs daria and clarissa explains it all  family guy/futurama--yay to animation that pushes the boundaries of all decency and pulls me back from the cloying normality shield that is kindergarten.   king of the hill--i never thought a show by the guy who created beavis and butthead could be remotely entertaining--especially a show about four conservative dumbass "rednecks." it's super funny.  on a side note, i like to take tea breaks in the afternoon and have been eating tuna chipotle dip from whole foods on crackers. i highly recommend it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Houston is hard.   I knew that it would be hard, but I can definitely see, despite my experience, never coming back here again!!  I'm getting about five hours of sleep a night, waking at 5:30 to get to the school by 7, and almost all of my time so far has been working. At the same time, my wonderful CMA group is the thing that keeps me going. They're all so dedicated and excited, and sooo far ahead of where i was, that I can't wait to see the work they do this year!  the only thing that worries me, obviously, and them, is the management.  Good classroom  management is hard to come by, and harder to implement, so we'll see!  until then i'm so homesick for both DC and Atlanta it's making me quite nauseous.  The food here may actually be doing that to me though...  Went to see the Hulk last night, it was after a "difficult" conversation that I had, so definitely, I had some other things on my brain. however, the experience was unexpectedly pleasant, with lots of in your face, thinking man's action that Ang Lee is known for.  Loved it (the ending was a bit iffy...call me if you wish to discuss). 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Houston, I'm back!   I just want to say I'm in Houston now, again, and it feels so eerie to be back when everything feels exactly the same as when I left it!  This time I feel much more prepared, however, and am happy to be productive and energized and organized.    The caravan was good, we stopped in New Orleans, the first time I have ever been there. Basically it smelled really bad .  It was beautiful (architecturally) and there was a lot of music around.  There were also a LOT of tourists.    I will have more to write later I'm sure and now that I have my computer thanks to the lovely angela I'm all set!  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm on my way out  So starting tomorrow, Thursday, at 10:00 am I will be in the DC area. From Saturday morning I will be in Cumberland, wretched wretched me. From Sunday morning I will be in Takoma Park. From Monday I will be in Atlanta. From Tuesday I will be in New Orleans with crazy Alice. I shouldn't speak badly about her, she really is a awesome gal...unless she's just a genetically engineered cyborg designed to seem like an awesome gal...bad bad green eyed monsters. From Wednesday on for the whole whole summer until late July I will be in Houston.  My what a crazy life I lead!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ugh, I am a bad blogger   Well if anyone still reads this site, go you. I stopped posting due to the hectic and data sensitive nature of institute.  It was a blast however!!! I love love loved working there, even though it was hard and sometimes made me think too hard. I feel like I'm used to breaking things down so much for kinders it's really difficult to get back into that critical thinking phase. I'm reading more feminist women's theory, but then again, school starts in two weeks and I feel this may be a momentary lapse in intellectualism.  met some amazing people though. Being my usual self I'll probably have trouble keeping in touch though.  ah well. lucky come, lucky go.  Again school is starting soon so get ready for some zany school stories!  Like.... half our school left and now we have many new teachers...ZaNy!  I'm going to be a learning team leader this year which means I guide all the new kindergarten teachers, so so exciting for me :)  and i'm taking classes to get certified (my five year renewable instead of my three year provisional which runs out this year). however these classes are twice a week, three hours a class. eep, if i stop posting you can only imagine what happened.  also i'm considering travelling abroad to japan to teach with jet, if i get in.  oh me oh my when will the world stop spinning for jane?? 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i watched the vma's yesterday and my surprise that coldplay actually won the best group video was the highpoint, the bizarro world britney/madonna/christina/missy performance was the most boggling point and beyonce's performance was the most fun point (i wish "funner" or "funnest" would just enter the lexicon once and for all so lazy people can just relax).  i hate when the same five frickin videos are nominated for everything--annoying.  i was excited by the prospect of the new sorority life though-yippee! yikes, i am losing it.  my right shift key is broken; the previous exclaimation point was only entered by a wonky stretch performed by my left hand. expect to see far fewer exclaimation points. i am also neglecting to capitalize letters on the right side of the keyboard to maintain consistency.  i am eagerly awaiting the arrival of jhumpa lahiri's new novel which i preordered on amazon.com.  apparently _ urlLink the namesake _ lives up to the hype. I read the  urlLink newsweek article  on it and I am dying to get it.  i also bought plane tickets successfully on priceline. no one was more surprised than me. 130 bucks to chicago, baby. why am i going to chicago--for my cousin john's wedding of course. i'll only be in town for a two days however, then sunday morning i rush back to atlanta. still a day off and free food and a family reunion ain't half bad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Camp (i'm going to see this tonight) Bend it like beckham-waiting for video, just saw bhaji on the beach again and would recommend it highly for a rental. whale rider-about the maori tribal leader born into the body of a girl OT: our town, about the production of the play in a compton high school American Splendor-weird quasi documentary about comic book creator harvey pekar  In other news went to a Dean fundraiser last night at Gordon Biersch Brewery which was not half bad. They had these amazing garlic fries and good beer. Dean is coming to Atlanta Sept. 15 but unfortunately I have class that night.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink IKEA | Catalog online  Oh Joy! the new ikea catalogue is finally here.  Unfortunately the nearest ikea is 600 miles away. Oh sadness.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Power Rangers Movie!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink RollingStone.com: Recordings: Damien Rice, O, 3 Stars -I have to remember this. I also have to remember that I want to check out the new Fountains of Wayne, whose first album I really enjoyed.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, we all knew it was true, but now it's even more true. Even though Real World Paris blows the big one and Road rules is even WORSE, I'm hooked on The Restaurant and The Family.  Is it strange that The Family is like some Comedy of the Grotesque to me?  I enjoy Rocco on the Restaurant though...yes he's kind of smarmy but still so charming. Some of those whiny waiters have to go though.  I'm going to try to go mini golfing with some of my students. I have mostly angels (or at least kids who try to be angelic) and one demonic spawn child. yuck - o
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today was the first day....It was interesting. Let's start with the fact that the listening skills on these kids are nil.  Story?  no. Poem? maybe.  simple sentences are difficult right now.  Then the crying. Lots more crying this year than usual, including one who wouldn't stop for about an hour. Finally i pulled him on my lap and gave him a big hug and told him that his mom was not coming back until the end of school and wouldn't it be better to play than cry?  He actually stopped--it was a minor miracle. Because if he hadn't I would have called his mom and told her to come get him. But the crying doesn't stop there, oh no, many other children cried; one of the fifth grade teachers has a child in my class, and he was MR. WHINY. I can't do it, I can't eat it, I don't want to. Ugh, I just wanted to be like, chill out already!  I think the only saving grace is realizing the struggle is the journey--a popular phrase from this summer.  I vaguely remember feeling this way last year, and that class was wonderful...Is it too much to wish for two wonderful classes? I'll tell you one thing, there are no geniuses in this bunch :P  oh, and what kind of a name is "essence". In the litany of "invented" names, that one takes the cake. I also have a "ZyDerryo." Which actually quite pleasantly rolls off the tongue.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally used a gallery program to catalogue the pictures from institute this summer. More pictures of other things will follow. You can find the pictures  urlLink here !
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess the site is due for an overhaul, but time is not my friend. I have loads and loads of pictures from the summer but no time to upload them.  School starts Monday and I am pretty nervous though still excited.   Chris' parents are in for a visit this week, so I anticipate a lot of eating out.  Must go shopping, must get manicure. These are girl prep strategies for survival.  In terms of moving to japan, try  urlLink Why Japan Sucks , a raving rant from someone who appears to be an ultra left wing feminist who is teaching english in japan. i think i should email this person for more information before going to japan! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy Birthday to ME   Yay! I'm now 24--on the cusp of twenty-fiveness...yikes!  Chris made me breakfast, and presented me with two dozen beautiful red roses. Quite a nice surprise! I also got Seabiscuit, which we just saw Friday and which I loved; and a yoga mat and dvd so now i have no excuses not to work out :)  I'm very excited because tonight we get to go out to my favorite restaurant- urlLink Iris . yum yum!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                    ESTJ  - "Administrator". Much in touch with the external environment. Very responsible. Pillar of strength. 13% of the total population.  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got clothes?:  urlLink Everythingchic.com - Shop for Women's Designer Clothing  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink NPR : Atlanta Public Schools Shrink as City Grows  :   Here's an interesting article on the state of our school system. It kind of makes you think all the bullshit hoops you run through are a way of weeding out teachers or something.  Sadly we lost a staff member today; someone who actually contributed a lot to the school. I think he got tired of all the bullshit and just decided to leave.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up this morning with a familiar stingy feeling in my eyes--i have pinkeye. Another day missed from work, another desperate search for a doctor. Just terrible. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yet another look for jane's blog, still girly enough though I suppose.  Hmm in the recent past I have come down with a mysterious women's illness that has forced me to go to the doctor for the first time in who knows how long. I even had to miss work. It may have something to do with running myself ragged, but there's no choice to slow down unfortunately. I'm working, I'm doing something for TFA that involves a massive project once a month, and i'm now taking classes twice a week. Unfortunately the classes so far are terribly not helpful.  THankfully wonderful chris has come to my rescue and really made life easier by being just generally wonderful. So thank you chris :*  School is better and worse--the kids are better; the administration is worse.  They told us that we could no longer post work on the bulletin boards (in the hallways at least) that is "below par"--i.e. if the kindergarteners write their names, their letters must be perfectly formed. If they are drawing pictures of dogs, then they must be absolutely beautiful well proportioned dogs.  This is "quality work" they said, and it must be posted now.  Hmm, they realize this is kindergarten, do they not? They realize this is why children come to school, do they not?? anyway, this and a lack of caffeine led to massive headache yesterday from which I had to go to bed at 9:30 to recover.  Atlanta is quickly losing its vapid charm for me. I have exhausted the "diversity" of restaurants it has to offer, there is no DECENT shopping for hundreds of miles, I hate nature, and that's the only damned thing this city has in excess.  No culture, no interesting people, just dismal cloying small minded small thinking small caring people. Yuck-o is all i can say.  and thank goodness it's only a few more months until we can leeave!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jo Ann's Fabrics has closed down on Cobb Parkway--so so so so sad. where am I supposed to go for quilt patterns now??  All the way out to lawrenceville??? That's too far!!    I got my wallet back and I was able to write a thank you card to the lady. how nice, is all I can say.  After all the wedding hustle and bustle and housecleaning and homeworking, things are getting relatively calm. I went to Agnes and Muriels with some friends Saturday and ate til I was a bloated hog. I watched 40 days and 40 nights, and in that movie Josh Hartnett (HUGE SPOILER HERE) is RAPED by his ex-girlfriend. And they act like it's no big thing.  I was aghast.  Applications for JET moving slooowly but surely. There is a LOT of paperwork involved.  I never got my diploma. That's all i can say. I never received it. And now it will take 4-6 weeks to get here? I hope it gets here soon! I ordered it a while ago.   And also did they cancel Boomtown? I loved that show. :(
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Contents: Three credit cards one social security card tax related receipts dental appointment reminder staples and borders teacher discount cards.  Last known location Wedged under seat 18F on flight 967 US Airways, Philadelphia to Atlanta  Current mood: forlorn
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a little bit of deliberation I realized, I really hate this new template. I only like the cat template.  So it's back, and I'm not going to waste another saturday trying to tweak the other ones. I'd rather be knitting.  I've been reading too much, so much so that I'm getting headaches. And I have an assload of assignments; I was glad when I finished college, why must it pull me back??  Now I must waste time by watching RW/RR: the Gauntlet. If you don't know what it is, don't ask--you'll just laugh at me.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I had no idea Chicago was so cool.  I got there at 1, took the cta (finally I ride the El after watching it for years on ER), to  urlLink the Art Institute of Chicago , then a harried trip to the north shore via bus, commuter transit, and taxi resulting in a frantic search for correct change and a cta card worth 9.40 that still resides in my back pocket today.  I saw sooo many wonderful pieces including a small and delightful collection of Klees, and Seurat's infamous sunday on La Grande Jatte.  ooh and warhol's mao which is 15 feet tall-did you know that? because i certainly didn't. and hopper's nighthawks which was prominently featured on last week's dead like me ironically.    the wedding, the real reason for this trip, was a brilliant success!  and i got to spend a lot of quality time with my parents, which was great. i get to see them again this week when i head home for the real wedding of the year: gnr! I'M SO EXCITED!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hallelujah I have to say, I needed that.  My local atlanta fulton county library gave me amnesty on the $11+ fines I had accumulated.  I love them. Thank you!  So what am I reading?   urlLink Voyager , book 3 of the Outlander series (it's historical fiction)  urlLink The Devil's Larder , Jim Crace --he wrote Being Dead--(short stories about "food, sex, desire and death") 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy birthday Chris, my lovely lovely love! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ate at  urlLink Iris  last night for  urlLink dining out for life , where 10% of your tab goes to project open hand. The organization provides healthy meals to people living with HIV/AIDS.  But my duck was absolutely nightmarish! It tasted...not like i expected?  but our waiter was sooo nice and he took it off the tab.  That was redeeming.  New  urlLink Sarah  album is finally out! I'm still getting used to it.    I will be home briefly for Thanksgiving and I'm looking forward to that; I think I'm just looking for a break in general. This semester is rough going what with the schoolwork and all. It's not all that hard, it's just annoying. I think the worst is the classes, which I feel are very little value. VERY LITTLE.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Planning my life is a lot more difficult than I thought it would be. I now I have a timeline that says where Jane will be and what Jane will be doing for the next ten years. It's not depressing though I bet for some people it would be, but not for Jane-haha-but rather, I wonder how accurate it is.  I joined  urlLink upromise , which takes little bits of money from things you buy and puts it into a mini savings account which you can then roll over into a 529 plan (which is a tax free investment plan from which you can pay for college). This is for all my little unborn children.  I like to plan things I like to be organized I want to take all the furniture out of my apartment and put it all back in in a more organized way.  I wish my boyfriend could throw more things away. I wish container store would re-do my apartment. I wish my apartment was bigger than 700 sq.feet and less expensive too, while we're at the wishing stage of this rant.  I wish there was such a thing as a transporter so I could see my friends whenever I wanted to.  In more interesting news (really, i swear), I watched  urlLink 28 days later , which is a fucking awesome movie, and I loved it.  I watched it again (some parts anyway) with the commentary on.   Anyway, someone told me that friendster was going to start charging--is this true? I only just started using it. ALSO if you will please, email me your address and vitals if I don't have it. Card giving season is coming up soon. I am bound and determined to be on top of it this year. I already bought  urlLink Holiday Stamps . And if you think THAT's crazy, then, take a look at  urlLink this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, it has been a long time since the last post. This has been a very exciting few weeks.  urlLink This link should provide some clarity.     We just turned in our JET application this week.  Wish us luck!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The catchiest song in the world has invaded my brain. I downloaded it from napster. it's just lodged there like a piece of cheese.  So is boomtown not on anymore? I find that very depressing. How can they have THREE successful law and orders and boomtown which was riveting and had carefully drawn characters and storylines, be cancelled? it had donny wahlberg for christ's sakes! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think all my blog titles should be song lyrics from now on. It's been over two months since I posted. I think no one reads this, which tempts a person to you know, post a naked picture on here or something.   Rather, I post what I have been reading:      urlLink Empire Falls  by Richard Russo   urlLink Three Junes  by Julia Glass   urlLink The First American: The Life and Times of Benjamin Franklin    The last is actually the most interesting. I'm trying to get into the other two but they're both cut from the same cloth and just not that engaging yet.  I've just finished  urlLink The Dogs of Babel  by Caroline Parkhurt, and it was very good, finish in one sitting good, though rather emotionally traumatic.  I'm trying to think of who would be good in the movie. Perhaps Winona Ryder.  It's strange I've enjoyed the last two books I've read with dogs in the title, the other one was  urlLink The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time . They're both Today Show Book Club books too.. but they WOULD be good book club books.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just finished Three Junes by Julia Glass, which I ended up enjoying immensely, well drawn characters and I like it when people are changing still mid course in their lives without it being this huge groundbreaking thing.  People are so obsessed with Janet Jackson's breast, but after having seen the image I have to say: she didn't even show a nipple!  What's the big deal?  I have to posit: culturally relevant teaching.  Does it, can it exist?  I mean, i know, theoretically, it does, but doesn't it preach to a one size fits all idea that this racial group or that racial group must be acknowledged in such and such a way. Or vice versa doesn't it just follow the good advice of all teachers that each child must be seen as an individual? Then there is the argument that certain groups (speaking African American here) should be taught from an ethno-centric point of view, such as afro-centric teaching which would focus on black history in america, and African culture in general.  Sometimes I think these are great ideas, where students could gain ownership of their past and feel invested in their future. Other times I think these ideas are bollocks, that students must be founded in a well rounded, if western culture biased, background.    In other thoughts, why don't more people I know  urlLink use launch cast radio ? aren't they interested in controlling every song they hear through a ratings scale which determines what songs will play or not?  I can hear Afghan Whigs and Wilco and Alanah Davis in the same half hour people!  The reason I find this so fascinating is that I can listen to other people's stations; I would be curious about what YOU were listening to, for example.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Keeping true to my pledge that I use only song lyrics as titles now, i feel this is appropriate, because i now have a job:    urlLink Two Rivers Public Charter School.    I will be a Founding Kindergarten Teacher at this  urlLink expeditionary learning  school. I am really really excited!!  For those of you who are interested (the two people who may still occasionally check this site), I will be moving back at the beginning of June.  I am obsessed with the  urlLink L word , the best new series on television today. I can't believe I have to keep showtime so i can keep watching this show.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Wilson Phillips is back!   They said it couldn't be done...But it's happpened!!  In other news, I finished Audrey Niffenegger's  urlLink The Time Traveler's Wife , and I thought it was quite interesting and very entertaining.  If you are thinking about reading it, it's out in paperback now! The ending is very very sad and it's all put together nicely.  Apartment search DC is not going quite as well as I had hoped.  I'll just keep trying. If you know a place in capitol hill or columbia heights that has enough space for two people, and that isn't over a gazillion dollars, please let me know :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a little boy in my class that has rickets. He is really bowlegged and really short.  Get your vitamin D people! Also another reason that people should get out in the sun more and that kids should have recess! and well lit classrooms!  There is a link on the title, but it's really hard to discern. If you want to read the article :  http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A43711-2004May20.html
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lenny on Law and Order (best show ever) is leaving! and being replaced by -- whaaa? Dennis Farina?  Best known for playing mob bosses and other smart alecky but wise criminals, he is a poor poor choice indeed.  http://www.cnn.com/2004/SHOWBIZ/TV/05/17/new.season.ap/index.html  Also, have you ever seen that Futurama where Fry eats the gas station egg salad sandwich and little worms take over his body and make it smarter? I wish I could have that kind of luck when I eat gas station egg salad sandwich.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They taste so good...like the yummy burnt sugar bits of creme brulee. Also, annoying--Pepperidge Farm cookies do not have their own website. WTF.  They deserve their own website.  This  urlLink one website  I found describes these cookies as containing genetically engineered ingredients.  Ew.  Looking at the list I see that basically everything I eat has been genetically engineered or modified. YUUUUUUMMMMY.  I have started watching the Gilmore Girls....I actually like it.  I don't know how to feel about that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back north!  I am seriously in need of an apartment !  Now i know where my school is located (southeast dc), i can start looking in earnest. but as angela says all of the good stuff will be taken by the time i'm seriously committing. and of course i need to SEE where i will be living before i can consider committing.  i just saw mean girls. it was awesome, it was great. i loved it. i can tell mira i'm a lindsay lohan fan now.  only three more weeks of school, thank god, i'm getting so sick of the place i can't breathe!  i only hope my new school will allow me to wear skirts without pantyhose.  that may seem a very trite concern, but i love skirts and i hate pantyhose. HATE. after years of imprisonment, i hate pantyhose and i will never wear it again. i will wear patterned tights--in the wintertime ONLY mwah ha ha haa
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the last blog for a while, as I am shutting off cable and internet. I won't be reviving it until after I get back from my trip to EUROPE which will be in a few weeks.  So in the meantime, I will be:  Moving 634.3 miles away from Atlanta to DC  Going to London, Edinburgh and Paris  Painting my bedroom "Peacock Blue"  Getting a new cell phone!   Planning my wedding    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it strange that I love cleaning out my yahoo mailbox. Can you believe that I am only using 37% of the ten megs allotted?  Down from 73???  Am I the only one that's excited about this?  Well, here are some other things that I am excited about:  1. Starting at my new school! 2. Actually going to happy hour at a bar I can walk to from my brand new apartment! 3. Hardwood floors! 4. Paying off credit card debt! 5. Going to Europe!   Things I am not excited about: 1. Increasing credit card debt while in Europe! 2. Twelve hour drive in a moving van! 3. Packing up all my stuff! 4. Being cut off from cable and high speed internet for over three weeks! (GAH)  Also incredibly excited about my friend Kara's wedding, which I attended yesterday. It was soo beautiful and she was a lovely lovely bride.  We couldn't stay long enough!! That I was not excited about :(  We are in the middle of a packign crisis.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After days of driving all over DC, we did it, we did it! We found an apartment that we loved. We're going to be right by Eastern Market, only half a mile from my new school! I'm so excited, you have no idea.  The apartment is comparable to what we have now, but it has these great hardwood floors, and beautiful big windows and the all important washer and dryer.  Hopefully the cats will adjust. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So renewed love for Canasta suddenly turns into remembered disgust when I lose utterly and completely to Angela last night while watching the convention. Love canasta, which is a version of rummy that can create major point stress.&nbsp; Lots of melds and draws and bonuses for red 3's that aren't usually included in solitaire, for example.  I'm also missing the Lion King on broadway, which is what Chris is doing right now. He and his brother and some friends went up to New York to do some sightseeing this weekend. I was too pooped from a recent&nbsp; urlLink workshop  I attended to tag along.  Tonight Angela came over and we made coconut shrimp and  urlLink Annie Chun's  noodles; then off to the mall!&nbsp; We scoured the  urlLink Nordstrom Anniversary Sale , where a pair of  urlLink hip new shoes  and the  urlLink best natural skincare products  were purchased;  urlLink Benetton  having a fabulous 50% off sale; and  urlLink Sephora !&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Don't you like how I added all those great links? It's like follow jane around the mall!  We went to DC Coast this past week. Let me tell you something. If you ever go to DC Coast, have the lobster bisque. Just have it. No no, don't question the lobster bisque. Just trust me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My best snack ever has to be  urlLink Natural Cheetos . I've been seeing them in the snack food aisle for a while, but always thought, "eh, it couldn't be that good." But I was dead wrong, they are the best snack I have ever eaten.&nbsp;  &nbsp; In wedding news, yes, there actually is some, just because I've been sitting here watching episode after episode of the Gilmore Girls, doesn't mean that I haven't been doing SOMEthing productive this summer, we have decided to get married in Hawaii. This conversation snippet should shed some light: &nbsp; J: "So I made the appointment to view possible reception sites; I'm also going to go dress&nbsp;shopping next week. I've&nbsp;been looking around for somewhere to have a ceremony too if we&nbsp;are going to&nbsp;try to find a separate place for that; &nbsp;are you sure you want to have the wedding in Frederick?&nbsp;" C: "um." J: "We can do it in a restaurant in DC, if we do that we can cut out the DJ, the dance floor, the reception site rental." C: "um." J: "OK. Why don't you just tell me flat out what kind of wedding you want, where you want it, how many people you want to come." C: "I want to get married in Hawaii." J: "um." 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One passport.  Two trips to Europe.  One sanity.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>