<Blog>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I decided I want to start blogging again since i remember how amusing it was way back when, when i did it regularly.  Yeah, today was cool cuz i went to stefans and AJ stole some chick's bikini top and threw it in a tree.  and we caught a glimpse of her topless and yeah, it was kickass.  oh, and austin + peanuts + binder paper = teh LOL.  yeah, i cant do shit tomorrow cause my moms making me do chores and hw all day, which is really fuckin gay.  Anyway, anyone wanna do somethin on monday?  I got nothin to do so yeah.  SPORK!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jaclyn's party was cool because of 4 people:  Stefan and Dre for the guitar skillz Rosie for just being, well rosie and paige for thinkin I'm good at singing.  Yeah, right now, i'm sad cause Ronald Regan died, and he was one of the best damn presidents this country has seen.  but, back on the topic of the party  dre and i were in the back and he played guitar and i sang, and we were awesome,  yeah that was the best part the end.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yeah, just messing around with my C4D demo.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ya, went to rowena's graduation last night.  it was cool cause i havent seen her in a long time.  yeah, after the graduation, we (dre, stefan, me) went to rowena's house in pittsburg and that was cool, cause we got to hang out and there was some really good food.  then we went home and I got to see dre's house kinda, which i had never seen before and that was cool.  yeah, it like about 11:45 when i got home and i was too tired to blog, so yeah.  up for today, jaclyn's party
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, so Kelly's party was the awesomesauce, yeah it was kickass, until the last 3 minutes which i will recount later.  Anywho, stefan and i show up and then like i didnt plan on swimming, but i wanted to so i jump in with my jeans on and it's kickass.  so yeah, pool with jeans, like the're were like slushies and food yay.  yeah, there was a trampoline it was cool.  i cant do a flip, and i got accidentally elbowed in the pills and it still kinda hurts. right before we left too.  oh well, the party was awesome  and tomorrow - rowena's graduation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Graduation is coming soon.  I was listening to a song called graduation, and it really made me think you know what?  I actually gonna miss you guys.  like, it's all gonna end, i'll barely see you all anymore.  here;'s the song that inspired the thinking.  Graduation - BeForU (NOTE: Requries a japanese language pack for viewing)  キズついた時あの涙もそっと薄れていった 振り返ったらいつでも自分の居場所があったからかな  歩いて行こう手を握ってそう いつもそうだった何があっても信じてた まっすぐに見つめてた遠い場所を  どんなときでも 必死になって 分からなくて 悩んで どれも 大切なきおきだから  掛替えのないそんな日々を きっと忘れないそれぞれの道ある無としても  歩いて行こう明日見つけよう 今から新しいスタートきって信じよう まっすぐにいつかの遠い場所まで
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, today was bleh, im in a bad mood, spanish sucks, i cant stop swearing, i think i have ADD, im a loser, no one likes me, i dont even like me right now, school's a bitch, i hate my teachers, i wanna cry or something but i dont know how..., i think in the end i will die alone and greedy, with nothing but money or somethign.  i should stop feeling sorry for myself huh, i guess i dont have it that bad.  am i depressed, i cant think.  i wish i could play guitar so i could write an angry song right now... fuck,
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I remember one night at a party a long time ago; the way it worked was the party was in one room, and it hasd a sceen door to go outside, where we hung out as well as inside.  It was raining but nobody gave a shit.  Well after no one was outside anymore, i decided to step out, cause it was hot, and I felt like standing in the rain to cool off and get away from the loud pop/rap/hip-hop for a moment.  I was standing by the screen door as I had intended to go back inside after just a short minute or so.  Then, some girl, whom I didn't even know, opens the screen and asks me if this is where all the people make out.  I said, I didn;t think so, me being the only one out there.  Then she asks "well you u like someone to make out with?"  I quickly replied with a polite "no thank you"  I still wonder about that though.  I mean, I still havent even made out with anyone, but should I have?  I dont know.  I want my first kiss to be special.. Thinking back, should I have taken the oppurtunity?  Are my ideas on romance outdated?  Well I'm only 14, but prolly 13 at the time, but yeah.  What do you think?  Comments?
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, im pretty pissed off right now cause i was supposed to go to my grandma's today, and then right before we leave, she calls and says one of her friends is sick, which means i'm stuck at home again all day.  this is so fucking retarded.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I didn't do anything today cause my mom wouldn't let me.  It sucked.  I was bored so I made a pop up, thats it.  AIM me if you wanna see it, sn is MagicalGiftCard
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yeah, working on a goblin like creature in Cinema 4D.  Here's what he looks like so far.  Comments anyone&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yeah, graduated, go me.  went bowling afterwards, i was bored cause i was too tired to do anything really.  my mom stole my energy drink.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, last night was memories night, it was cool i guess.  Kinda boring.  Yeah, afterwards, i went to corrine's then to stefans and we just chilled out and played ddr and stuff.  it was cool, yea.  and tonights graduation and bowling.  cool
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Made this with my C4D demo.  Got the idea from a tutorial but ended up doing my own thing in the end.  The only thing I got from the tutorial was the idea for the circular body and teh shape of the windows.  the rest was my idea.  I know there's not a lot of detail, but i wanted to get a real cartoon look to it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, i started listening to the ramones again, cause they're CD was sitting around and yeah.  i dont know why, and this will sound kinda stupid, but i listened to a song, and it actually made me think, like about my whole life, and about people.  i dont know.  maybe it'll make u think too.  Bonzo Goes to Bitburg  You've got to pick up the pieces C'mon, sort your trash You better pull yourself back together Maybe you've got too much cash Better call, call the law When you gonna turn yourself in? Yeah You're a politician Don't become one of Hitler's children  Bonzo goes to bitburg then goes out for a cup of tea As I watched it on TV somehow it really bothered me Drank in all the bars in town for an extended foreign policy Pick up the pieces My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down  Shouldn't wish you happiness, wish her the very best Fifty thousand dollar dress Shaking hands with your highness See through you like cellophane You watch the world complain, but you do it anyway Who am I, am I to say  Bonzo goes to bitburg then goes out for a cup of tea As I watched it on TV somehow it really bothered me Drank in all the bars in town for an extended foreign policy Pick up the pieces  My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down  If there's one thing that makes me sick It's when someone tries to hide behind politics I wish that time could go by fast Somehow they manage to make it last  My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down My brain is hanging upside down I need something to slow me down 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so yeah, we went to 6 flags today, it was cool.  i would talk about it, but i mean, you can kinda guess what i would say: rides, friends, etc. so im not gonna babble on what would be just the typical bullshit.  so yeah, right now, im am sooooooooo pissed at my mom.  i wanted to do something after school today, just something, and she wouldn;t let me do anything.  like i could have gone to the movies and prolly got a fucking ride too but she didnt let me, just cause she felt like bein a fuckin bitch and then she yells at me for a whole bunch of shit/  me = the fuckin pissed, and confuses, and insecure, and maybe a little depressions in there, and maybe i just wanna punch through the nearest window right now, but im not cause i dont wanna get my ass up to go to the hospital to get my fist fixed afterwards.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, you guys graduated so ya, good job.    so stefan and i went to teh grad and it was cool.  afterward, we went to paiges house and hung out and i think her dog is stronger than me...  then we went and saw saved and it was kickass and I;m ashamed to be chirstian now.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The final version of my character.  I think he came out nicely, especially for such a low polygon model.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, it was suki's bday yesterday i think, but today we all went to see dodgeball, and it was kickass.  Maybe i oughta get me some of those pants...lol  anyway, yeah it was cool, and now im kinda tired and i think i'm gonna chill out for a while cause im too tired to do shit right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know those AIM convos where someone just keeps setting themselves up for an insult?  Have an enjoy.  chickie5490: uuhhmmm...ur gay 2 bitch MagicalGiftCard: hahaha MagicalGiftCard: well u know MagicalGiftCard: some guys think lesbians are hot MagicalGiftCard: so maybe u actually have something goin for ya chickie5490: fuk u bitch MagicalGiftCard: when? MagicalGiftCard: im busy tonite, but tomorrow im free chickie5490: uugghhh chickie5490: bitznatch MagicalGiftCard: thats sounds german chickie5490: so do u MagicalGiftCard: yeah, I'm germany, and ur a jew, so fear me chickie5490: im white n ur asian...so fear me chickie5490: hehehe MagicalGiftCard: actually the phillippines was an ally of America MagicalGiftCard: philippines hated the japs just as much as america did chickie5490: actually all the asians shud fear us cus ur so small we cud EAT u cus ALL fat ass white americans luv 2 eat brown meat chickie5490: heheheheheh chickie5490: ooohhh!!!! tht was good MagicalGiftCard: you wanna eat some asian MagicalGiftCard: i've got somethin for ya then, but like i said, im busy tonite chickie5490: sicko chickie5490: no seriously...r we gonna do nething 2nite? chickie5490: sleep over chickie5490: yay MagicalGiftCard: eh? chickie5490: hehehe chickie5490: jkjk chickie5490: ur 2 damn ugly MagicalGiftCard: whatever chickie5490: g2g bitch! MagicalGiftCard: alright MagicalGiftCard: have fun with your lesbian lover angie chickie5490: fuk u! MagicalGiftCard: im sure the video will be great stuff chickie5490: muah:-* chickie5490: o u no it chickie5490: call me lata babe! chickie5490: bye MagicalGiftCard: later
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yeah, today was cool.  Did nothing all day then went to the movies so it was cool to relax for a while.  Yeah, saw riddick with stefan, dirk, and jeff.  it was okay, the plot sucked but whatever.  we were standing in front of the theatre at like 11:30 waiting for dirks mom and it was pretty much closed down and we were hyper cause of energy drinks and yeah, good stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    'Nuff said.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yeah, the next work in progress shot of my monster.  I've done some work on the body, fixed some stuff on the face, created a suitable texture for the sky, and modeled a sword which he will eventually carry.  What do guys think about it so far?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink solid07 - #1 stop for kpop   Yeah, found this site today, it;s awesome.  reminds me of when i first started listenin to asian music.  check it out, and listen to Number One by BoA (the korean one)  yeah, it;s the bestest
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you'd like to make a call please hang up and try agian...  Yeah, the fuckin hilarousness
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, we hit two parties yesterday.  First off is steph's and her back yard is like CRAZY. it was better than a hotel resort cause they had like friggin sand and shit and it was like whoa.  Hottub, sand, pool, food, ping pong, ya, u know it kicks ass.  and uhm, I pulled kate into the hottub, but i never got to push jaclyn into the pool.  but least everyone swam and didnt sit around all self concious and being stupid and stuff.  so after that, we go to jamies party, but it's just stefan, dirk, dre, and I from our school cause everyone else went to watch a movie.  ATTENTION: PARTIES ARE BETTER THAN FUCKING MOVIES. M'KAY!  so yeah, it was fun.  Paige taught me how to freak lol, i suck at, but it still made me feel so much .... less asian.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HOLY SHIT, NOW MY LAST POST IS FUCKED TO HELL, IT'S SATURDAY, NO CONAN, FUCK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! YEA ITS THIS SERIOUS THAT I HAVE TO TYPE IN CAPS. ENJOY THE REST OF THE POST:    FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!      FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!      FUCK I'M PISSED!!!    FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!     FUCK I'M PISSED!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      alright i get up, ,my mom offers to take me to breakfast and im hungry so i go.  then i go home for a while then its of to erinn's house.  so it's stefan, paige, erinn and i and we chill out in erinns room and i get orange hair spray and that didnt turn out to well and ended up with my head in her kitchen sink... yea... we went to longs, saw fricker for a few min, and just chilled out for a while.  then we went to mc donalds where this crazy guy threatens to kill us and shit. afterwards we hit the movies, saw white chicks it kicked ass.  but somethin happened tonite that well made a great day... well i dont know.  i hate all this shit.  drama etc.  it didnt even directly involve me and im still pissed.  wow.  i wanna talk to dani rite now, that would make me feel better about stuff i think, it always does.  i think im gonna sit around bored until conan o'brien comes on, since i prolly wont talk to dani tonite, listenin to conan tell jokes is the next best thing rite?
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay today, i get up and my grandpa comes over for a while and that;s cool.  after, my mom takes me to get some good old flip food and then she takes me to the mall and i buy a visor.  now that i'm all asian'd out, i go to waterworld where i meet up with paige and erinn.  paige and i got season passes and then when i get my pic taken for mine i look away from the camera.  then we go do some shit and we go the big kahuna (burger king lol) and the asian guy whose the life guard at the top refuses to be our friend, so he sucks.  but the life guard at the bottom was named zach and he said he'd be our friend and it was cool.  so erinn and i r gonna ride the halfpipe thing and then we dont but we do think of some amusing ways to embarrass paige.  well afterwards, we go on the tsunami thing, the double tube thing, and i have to ride alone and the tubs fuckin flips over.  it sucked but it was funny.  and yeah, paige and erinn got temporary tats.  yeah, i think i was supposed to do something with jacob tonite, but i cant find him online so i dunno.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       yeah, im on the phone right now, but i thought i would blog, just for the hell of it.  that said, i have no actual thiing to blog about... hmmmm.  im kinda hungry.  i would say what most people say when there hungry "im gonna make a sandwhich."  but... i fuckin hate sandwhichs so ima just gonna wait til morning and bug my mom to feed me.  by the way, TOGO's the SUCK...  never ever eat there, and if u see a dude named justin who works at togo's, be like "u is the gay."  and as a final statement "O-mizu nondara umee!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, jacob and i went to qzar and we played some lazer tag and we ate tacos and shit.  Oh, and u know that game Bust A Move, where you have to like shoot bubbles and match colors and shit, well ya that monitor fuckin sucked and u couldnt tell the colors from each other and watchin jacob, it was funny shit.  oh yeah, DRUGS ARE NOT THE WIN!!!! lol.  yea, that was funny.  So jacob and i are gonna get Übber-ricer'd out.  it's gonna kickass.  spikey blue hair for me, and he get B-day money, we're goin shoppin.  anywho, i need a visor.  oh and jacob is gonna program a trillian plug in to type like this "OmGz!!11!!! DiS bE sOme 1337-AzN tyPaGE biOtcH!!!11!~"  it's gonna kick ass.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, the color is gonna be blue
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday, saw kill bill 2, it was awesome, even tho i didnt see the first.  and yeah, stayed the night at bens house.  today, i dont know what I'll do, prolly head over to see my grandpa and then chill out the rest of the day.  Anyone wanna do something tomorrow?  Call/IM me...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yeah today, stefan and i go to Sun Valley and meet up with paige and i think dirk was gonna go but didnt.  so we go shopping and i end up with some bracelets and jeans, stefan gets some bracelets and i dont remember if paige bought anything.  so after that we go to paiges house and walk to the park and feed the ducks and stuff. then we go back to her house and watch house of the dead.  fucking funniest movie lol.  so yeah, i think paige and stefan hooked up, which is cool.    so, i did a lot of thinking today.  i see everyone is hooking up these days and i think about the girl i like.  okay, im crazy maybe, i mean, i havent met the chick, but i talk to her a lot, but i cant stop thinking about her.  is that strange?  i mean, i want to meet her.  she lives kinda far tho, (newark) also, beside the fact that i really like her, i heard she likes me... well i wanted to go out with her but she doesnt want to cause im moving in a month.  maybe its just an excuse to turn me down.  is it?  i dont want to believe it is, but im not sure.  i dunno, i just want to be with her, thats all.  spend sometime with her.  whatever.  comments anyone?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OOOOkay, so i went downtown again yesterday.  Pretty much the same thing as the day before except this time erinn got to go yay!  oh and we saw the stepford wives which imo was more comedy than anything else.  I didnt get to buy anything tho cause the store i wanted patches and stuff from was already closed when we got there.  uhm, wat else... oh, stefans dad beat me at air hockey.  and yeah, thats it/
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So yesterday was cool.  Stefan, Paige, and I went downtown and it was pretty cool.  We found this store that sold all these awesome patches and bracelets and shit and we bought some kickass stuff at Ross.  o, and stefan and I bought these energy drink and after watching him taste his, i didnt even open mine. SOBE ADRENALINE RUSH ONLY FROM NOW ON. lol.  uhh we ate some asian food and saw the terminal.  it was pretty interesting, but i think i was the only one who actually watched the movie.  (inst that what ur supposed to do lol)  ANd yeah, on the DDR ex in teh theatre, i AAA Mobo Moga heavy if any of u ddr players are reading this.  yeah, i think thats pretty much it for yesterday.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, went to waterworld today with some friends.  Phan man couldnt go and that sucked and we didnt even hit on any chicks... but it was still cool.    Today's stoner moments: "That rock looks like a thumb."  " She got murdered." "Did she die?"  Yeah, my mom isnt letting me do anything tonite for some reason.  it sucks.  the end.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright so yesterday was pretty cool, went to my grandparents house and hung out there and my grandma took me to the mall which was pretty nice.  so later, i go over to ben's house and you know whats he's doing the whole time (playing FFXI) so yeah, i just decide to hang out with his little sister who i swear looks kinda like uma thurman.  yeah, we just walk down to the drug store and i get to hear all the good 6th grade gossip... =P  oh, and somewhere in there was watching poker on ESPN and then learning how to play Texas...  as for today, my mom says i have to stay home and help pack for the move to maple land.  yeah it sucks.  tomorrow is gonna be waterworld tho.  any of u folks wanna come along give me a ring. (or IM.)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so today, the mom takes me down to get sushi (no, not to get myself, to actually eat some sushi) and tonite i went downtown with stefan and paige.  hit up that cool store, bought some pins, but i think they fell out of my pocket. =(  Then we ate some sushi (twice in one day, im hooked after jacob, jenna, and danielle got me to try the stuff) then saw king arthur which didnt suck nearly as bad as jacob said.  yeah, thats it for today
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Albino Blacksheep / Flash / Group X - Cereal Bawks   L M A O  Click it bitches
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      w00t, partay at danielle's house leik wut!!11! okay, so i show up at danielle's house at 2:45 thinking I'm late cause Jenna told me to be there at 2:30.  turns out im the only one there, danielle's in the shower so i sit down to some good ol' Judge Joe Brown waiting for danielle to get out of the shower.  so yeah, she gets out and then jenna comes by.  we help danielle take some clothes out of her mom's car and she gives me this awesome pink scarf, its kickass.  so then cathy takes us to pick up casey but she doesnt feel good so we buy some shrek ice cream and go back to danielle's while cathy and jenna go pick up the jacob.  yeah, he comes in, we yell surprise and all that.  so after presents and stuff, we decide the movies will be our plan of action.  but first, sushi, so we go to i love terriyaki and hand out some cupcakes jenna made to movie theatre employees.  yeah, the movie was decent, and now im kinda tired,  but once again.  happy birthday jay man, now that you're 18, u can order me girls gone wild off the TV!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      okay, so it was dirk, stefan, austin, ben, austin's cousin, and I sitting at stefans pool.  we decide to have a little fun and maybe put the pool furniture in the pool.  well this happens to be a community pool, and our actions happen to upset a certian pussy ass fagget.  well, the fucker calls the fucking cops on us and I think 2 cops show up just to tell us to take the furniture out of the fucking pool.  seriously, what is up with the citizens of moraga?  Is it necessary to call the cops on kids with furniture.  I think whats funniest tho is how two cops showed up, one in a car and one on a motorcycle.  Like what would we do?  Try to attack them which chairs?  At this time, i would like you all to give a round of applause to the citizens of moraga and their outstanding police department
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      k thursday.&nbsp; stefan rides his bike to my house, yes, i said he rode his bike.&nbsp; tool him an hour and 10 min i think, so he gets here at like 1015 and then we go downtown at like 11ish, where we meet up with erinn at ross.&nbsp; (I saw the AWESOMEST outfit, but it was too big =*(&nbsp;&nbsp; okay, so we walk around downtown, go to target, buy adrenaline rushes and erinn didnt try one even tho i bought one for her.&nbsp; (i ended up drinking)&nbsp; stefan got a south park trucker hat at target and they we're out of the starsky and hutch shirts, which was a bummer.&nbsp; so then we went to get food, i get asian take out and stefan and erinn eat johnny rockets, and erinn finds herself a new job opening doors for people, and its kinda awkward having her open the door for me and stefan so everywhere we went that day was a fight for who could open teh door but she always won.&nbsp; so we went shopping around more, then went back to jonny rockets where we sat for like ever just playing the juke box since the employees gave us free nickles.&nbsp; then erinn had to go home so we walked her home and stayed in her drive way for a while until she decided to go in and leave stefan and i alone.&nbsp; so after that, we went down to the picture show and we ran into meg L. and emily, but they went somewhere and stefan and i just went inside and waited for a long time, tried to call some ppl but none of them were around.&nbsp; fortunately, then unfortunately, megan meo, megan F., corrine, and steph come by, so then it wasnt gonna be just me and stefan but then they all saw something different than we did.&nbsp; so we went into the threatre and then stefans made a bet with me, that i didnt take but i will next time i go to the movies i promise.&nbsp; hes gonna give me his pocket nife and a chain if i just sit next to&nbsp;some random chick and ask her to make out with me.&nbsp; well, i dont get the nife and chain if it works cause supposedly im a lucky bastard and he hates me if it does work.&nbsp; well, anchorman was great even teh 2nd time, and tomrrow, (sunday) i plan to make off with either a pocket nife, or the taste of someone elses popcorn in my mouth, im assuming its gonna be the pocketnife. &nbsp; yeah, friday and sat, nothing happened cause my moms pissed at me for not doing enuff chores so i have to say home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so0o0o0o today was awesome.  went downtown with erinn and went to ross and that cool store that i dont know the name and target and stuff.  she bought some awesome pajamas that are a little bit big but still awesome and i got me a starsky and hutch shirt.  oh and we got pins and posters. =D yeah, so we ate dinner (more liek i ate dinner and she had a jamba juice) and then we saw teh notebook.  everyone was crying but we were laughing the whole time and that was kickass.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yeah, work in progress, definitely needs more detail,  Its gonna be the gate for a spooky themed scene im making.  Comments?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink My newest wallpaper, check it   Made this with Cinema 4D while messing around with a free plug-in I found.  w00t for cheesy effects!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      k so last nite erinn got home from her trip down to palm springs with leah and i tried my best to fill her in on wat she missed.  o and we both changed our sns.  NOw mine is so0o0o0oIMalex and hers is so0o0o0oIMerinn and our fonts match too, its the awesomeness.  so i basically sat around online all day and then erinn and I went to see anchorman but stefan didnt want to come =(.  BUT... anchorman has to be the fuckin funniest flick i have seen in a while.  im not even gonna describe it, just go see it now.  it was worth the nine overpriced movie ticket bucks it cost to see it.  seriously its the best...crap, its sunday isnt it?  shit, no conan tonite..
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    w00t, i got a new hair cut!!! wat do you all think.  leave a comment.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      okay, yesterday, my grandma picks me up and she takes me to goldilocks so i can get my flip food on, i go see my grandpa for a little while and then she takes me home.&nbsp; so later i go with suki (I'm gonna miss ya soooo much =*( )to see that Cinderella Story flick which wasnt as bad as i thought it would be except it was kinda cheesy.&nbsp; and u know what... how come all the ppl in that movie are so pretty and perfect eh... how about some one makes a movie about the rest of us.&nbsp; k, my rant is done... o, and i saw kill bill agian yesterday at bens house cause his family is gone...so0o0o0o0o0o... anyone wanna do something today or sometime before i leave?&nbsp; send me an IM foo! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Facts:  I saw Kill Bill. Tarantino is a genius. It's the best movie ever. Yes, it is better than Chicago or Anchorman. Uma Thurman is fucking gorgeous. You need to see movie... Now you need to see it again... And bring me with you cause it's just that fucking&nbsp;awesome&nbsp;I need to see it as many times as&nbsp;possible and&nbsp;I don't happen to own a copy.  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>