<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes i survived not eating for 24 hours, I am glad I don't live in a 3rd world country. It was fun, got to chill with folks don't get to hang out with since the start of the school year. It was fun. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm gonna work on my around the world today and hopefully get half of the paper done. Then i am going to the 20 hour famine at my church. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i promise that we won't have school tomorrow, which gives me time to work on around the world.   Everyone needs to watch the oc and chappelle's show. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got out of school, hopefully there will be no school tomorrow so i can work on my paper and go to the famine. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hopefully it will snow. Thanks to everyone who signed up for the message board. Well i have to go to school, who knows maybe we'll get out early.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      got the board up, now i got to see if people will sign up. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got cut, oh well guess I'm just gonna go get a job. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am done with my chem project, first to turn in the project also, now i have to work on around the world, planning on starting it on teusday, not gonna take a while compaired the chem one.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ralph, if you really wanted to de-throne Bush you'de stay out and let my boy Kerry do the work, but now you've made it just that much harder. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tomorrow I'm playing Wolla, holla. i should be a rapper. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can't play any tennis, can't get up with Chris Wolla. Guess i'll just chill and watch a movie, might even go see one, but i doubt it. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No practice, off to work on the chem project.    From College Humor   Tennagers guide to picking a AIM screen name  Whether you're sending e-mails or chatting with friends, an essential to using the internet is having a screen name that tells people who you are. Here are some suggestions to help you pick out an awesome name!   AE or AF - Use these acronyms for American Eagle and Abercrombie and Fitch. This will show people that you have rich parents and therefore, you are rich as well. And everyone knows that if you are rich and wear Abercrombie and Fitch, then you are very attractive.   Examples: AE_girl04, AF_snowboard19   420 - Putting 420 after a screen name will show people that you are rebellious and are cool because you do drugs. They won't ever mess with you, and girls will flock to you because you are bad.   Examples: Sublimegirl420, sk8er420   69 - This shows that you obviously have sex, A LOT. Others that see this will want to have sex with you because you know all about it.   Examples: Sexystud69, badazz6969   666 - Use this to scare away people. They will see how mighty and evil you are, and they will fallback in fear.   Examples: Death666, NeoMatrix666  "chic" - Guys are very attracted to girls who but "chic" somewhere in their screen name. This shows you are hot and want to have a boyfriend who likes to play computer games all day and collect Star Wars toys.   Example: tightchic13f, cute_chic02   "sexy" - Guys go crazy when you put on this screen name. It says "I'm a really attractive girl that wants to have sex with a guy I meet online." You can be uglier than Chelsea Clinton, but with this on your SN, you'll come across as Brittany Spears.   Examples: Sexy18f, Sexyskatergirl   "gurl" - Using "gurl" in your screen name shows that you are the cute girl that lives next door type. It makes you sound very nice, but also a target of weird 40-year old sexual predators.   Examples: fun_gurl_2003, pony_gurl82   "horny" - This shows that you are a 40-year old sexual predator that wants to find a young boy or girl to lure in and abduct at the local mall.   Examples: Horny_babe_696969, Horny4u   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well it didn't rain like Clingerman said it did, so i'm gonna go see if people are playing out at Tabor, hopefully so, but i doubt it.   I am DEFINATELY finishing my chem project today then i'm set to start my around the world paper. Wow I hate school.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah that new Pic Squad CD is very good, listen to number 6, 9, and 15. 6 Is easily the best. Got the teacher recomendations, got pretty much everything i want but 2 ap's and physics is gonna be tough if i'm working (which i most definately will) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tennis tryouts started, i doubt I'll make it, I got pounded today by some freshman
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well looks like 10 people are getting cut from the tennis team this year, hope i'm not one of them, but if i am I'll just go get a job. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1 Hour delays are cool, unless you still have to do like 15 chemistry practice problems. Oh well looks like i'll be in the library again during newspaper. Very close to finishing my chemistry project though, so that is good, but then i got to get started on Around the World. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, listem to Laney Pope today she might have something accurate to say, on account of the snow falling from the sky.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Still working on the chemistry project, not that hard but still takes a long time (8 pages)   I got $20 and a pocket knife for valentines. Funny i didn't know that violent weapons were a customary gift on valentines day, but I'm not complaining. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Like I said, don't count on snow.......stupid Laney Pope.   Well back to writing a research paper on Enology.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hopefully there will be no school tomorrow but i wouldn't count on it, last time WXII said 100% chance of snow we got nothing.   Well i got to go work on this Chemistry paper so i can have time to watch the OC. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Writing tests are retarded.......  Along with chemistry projects and most importantly projects that force you to travel around the world in 80 days.   Other Things that are retarded include....  People that steal candy bars Dramatic People languages other than English The Perfect Score  Things that are not retarded include.....  The OC Splinter Cell Mt. Tabor gangs War Movies Fight Clubs The Boondock Saints Coldplay 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok nothing happened that was crazy, except I chipped a back tooth, oh and I actually figured out what we are doing in math.   So you know who is the man, Chen, the president of Taiwan. That guy faked an assassination so he could win an election. Now I don't know about you but that shows dedication. I mean if Bush or Kerry took a bullet for their job, I would support them. Holla.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Daniel who do you want to win the election? I get that question alot, ok maybe not but stay with me here.  Basically I when I was a young and ignorant youth I liked Bush, yeah ok he had a pretty good start, he handled September 11th pretty well, but the economy is pretty bad now a days and this whole WMD thing really is starting to make me question our reason for war (not saying that going into Iraq was bad.) I don't think that he will win the election but I wouldn't be surprised if Bush "happens" to find Bin Laden around about September or October, to seal the deal election, but right now it looks like he is in an uphill battle.   Kerry on the other hand seems to have alot more expierience and I like that his is not so much of a cowboy when it comes to foreign policy (not that I really care/know about foreign policy)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally got around to seeing The Passion of the Christ. It is a well done movie and i think is gonna go on my list of movies you need to see before you die. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My chemistry teacher must think it is funny to make me stress this much, I mean she gives me all this crap to do today, I mean it was due today and everything but still....the nerve.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I'm finally back from camping and all I can say is "don't ever let Will Bullins handel a gun" he is quite the shot. Now I got to go do my project for spanish.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm gonna be gone for the weekend, that I why I'm going on a posting rampage, and because I've had nothing to do all day. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am finally done with my costume for my around the world in 80 days project. I'm gonna go celebrate by working on another project. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Many of you may have seen that my brother hacked my blog and changed my pictre to one of richard dean anderson, or McGuyver. Please disreguard any of this stuff.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well my Blog has had a face life. Now there is a retarded picture of me, i could make a better one but I'm just way too lazy. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been totally bogged down in H/W this week and thanks to Mr. Mecham I have to do a project this weekend also. Ugh oh how I loath large armed spanish teachers.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah i'm going camping this weekend. Its gonna be not fun/fun. Not fun because the stuff we're doing is gonna be boring until we go shooting wich with be fun. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found out I got an A in Chemistry, how cool is that. Another cool thing is that I am about to be done with my Around the World in Eighty Days project, speaking of that I got to go work on it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Way to go Sean May, you alone drew 3 fouls in 30 seconds. General Failure.   Back to my life:  Me and Will both agree that if your invited to the Prom by someone you should be greatful and nice about it. Because if your not we're gonna break your knee cap(s) and slap you. Oh and don't worry if your not greatful you'll be spending most of your night at home anyway, that is if you can keep your date. I'm not going to Prom so this really doesn't pertain to me, but I still find it comial the way some people act. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Christine got in a car wreck, she is ok though but it was crazy. Will and I went to her house, it was fun we just chilled really.  Go Heels
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      my dad got a new car (Camry XLE) so i get the 98 Accord, holla. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made a 104 on my math test, now i just can't screw up on my test friday and I am FREE AT LAST!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well i realized I'm not cool like other bloggers becuase I don't post about "meaningful" stuff. Well too bad, they can deal with it. Anyway, looks like the message board it dying, but oh well.   My b-day is coming up but i don't get my liscense till april (hopefully, depending on my grades and such)  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well basketball seasons over, our team lost to first pres in the simi finals, but we put up a valiant effort and i had a pretty good game. I'm tired now, i'm going to bed. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm sorry but the person who wrote the article they are talking about in this article (sorry if that sounds confusing) is a general failure at everything. They say that Pat Tillman was not a hero, just an idiot. I don't care if your a democrat or a republican you should support your country and those who die for you to live in it. Pat Tillman gave up a job which made him millions so that he could fight for the freedom of you and me. So to the author of that article i have just this to say to you.... Get a life you waste of space.    urlLink SI.com - NFL - UMass president criticizes student's column on felled soldier - Thursday April 29, 2004 2:13PM 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Schoolzone not metaphors   my favorite is "He was as tall as a six-foot-three-inch tree."
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha. Don't you love it when people try to attack you using a blog. It's a joke, you need to get over it. People have jokes about other people all the time. Matt Sedlack makes fun of me, he even has a pretty good impersonation. But do i go and cry about it. No, you know why? Cause i take it like a man. Now if you wanna cry and be a little nancy boy go ahead, but don't whine to me. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Of course i am the kid in the green sirt, but and well i'll have a set charecter for alex and adam but the rest of them you just have to decide for yourselves who they are. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This guy is a street hokey god. Seriously if you can do this show me, i'll give you 20 bucks just to see it.    urlLink CollegeHumor.com : New Funny Pictures, Funny Movies, and Funny Hotlinks Daily! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yea this is one of the cooler things i've seen in a while   urlLink HumanDescent -> Gallery    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Are my pictues awesome or what?   urlLink Mr. Picassohead 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      who ever came up with the idea of a highway in the South Pole is a complete idiot. No seriously we could be spending money to cure cancer but no, some people think it would be more beneficial to spend money building a road through a continent with a population of about 6.   urlLink CNN.com - 'Ice highway' opens Earth's last frontier - Apr 12, 2004 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally Phil has one a major, and everyone is happy......everyone, but John Daly. Yes the PGA's good ol' boy who claimed that he was gonna give everyone a run for their money at the Masters didn't even make the cut. But we can't blame John for this i mean, his wife was just convicted of money laundering and he was probably smashed by the 9th hole anyway.     urlLink SI.com - Mickelson's major pursuit ends with Masters - Sunday April 11, 2004 6:47PM 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes I got my license. That is all. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The apprentice is the greatest show ever. I mean who would have thought that desk jobs could be so cool. Essentially the show is water cooler drama at its finest. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I being the 16 year old that i am have already had my 15 minutes of fame. It all started when I was on a family trip to NYC, 1 month after 9/11. My family and I decided to take a trip to NBC and tour the studios. The tour was great but once we got out we saw on the news ticker "NBC Employee has anthrax."  Mom: "Oh that's just lovely"   Well we get out and are about to walk away from the scene when my dad who was alread tired began to pass out (we later found out it was also from the blood pressure medicine that he takes) Ok so i'm flipping out and the media think that I am a complete retard that thinks he has anthrax (not to say that there wern't people like that in the crowd)  3 days later i arrive back in NC, and one of my best friend's sister (who was my bro's friend) calls and asks if we were in NYC that week, he says yes and she told us that her mom was in Canada and I had made the front page of the Globe and Mail, one of the largest newspapers in Canada, (The picture was huge too)   Don't believe me, check out this search of gettyimages.com   http://editorial.gettyimages.com/source/CFW/imageResults.aspx?s=ImagesAdvancedSearchState|2|15||0||1|||||0|0|0|| 0|Justin+Sullivan|7|anthrax|513023||0  I am the last row, middle picture. Oh and just incase your wondering, i have that newspaper still. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have to go take my liscense test soon, but I'm not sure when. You wouldn't believe how nervous I am, probably because I hit a car in "in-car" so I kind of want to redeem myself. But if I do well I'll hopefully have my liscense soon.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah looks like I'm gonna be the master of ceremonies for the fashion show on day eighty. I guess that is cool, but there are gonna be a ton of people there.  So who is this cool cat that is telling all the Shiites (sp?) to kill Americans in Iraq. Regardless of the backlash I think that the US needs to take that cool guy down. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Isn't my blog in spanish awesome    urlLink Translated version of http://catchyname.blogspot.com/ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got splinter cell: Pandora Tomorrow, and I must say it is stunning, and the online is awesome also. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Summer is finally here. This means that I start work next wednesday and that I am actaully gonna be raking in some dough. Word Up. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So i have 3 more exams to go. So far I'm doing pretty well, and I even made 2 bucks playing poker at Brad's this afternoon. It was quite fun I must say. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Gotta give props to Hank Wirth for finding this gem.    urlLink Apple - Trailers - Lost Boys of Sudan 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So as another year passes I feel like I have learned a plethora of new information about life and about myself, so I thought I would share some of it:  I can become excruciatingly annoying jobs are hard to come by xbox's are not meant to be dropped onto the pavement do not sit near Alex pento when he has a full bottle of gatorade  The OC rocks true playas rock the Daniel herring look (collard shirt, pot head haircut, cargo shorts) poker is a great way to lose money la caretta is rater good drivers tests are way to easy to stress over the holocaust was bad, but you get tired of it REALLY fast gandalf will not help you get out of the boat (I'm not a LOTR freak, I just hallucinate) delux 247 is real  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I walk into third lunch and Alex is in his normal "hey there is a group of people, lets make fun of Daniel" mood. I sit down, don't really say anything and Alex decideds it would be funny if we got a black guy that could literally annihilate me, but I thought he really wasn't gonna act on it, that was until John Kincaid opened his mouth.   John: Hey Jeremy come over here"  Jeremy (black guy):what up  Neal: This kid (pointing at me) was talking trash about you  Jeremy: WHAT?  Daniel: Oh S#!T  Jeremy: What did he say?  Daniel: I didn't say anything, I don't even know you.    We go back and fourth trying to decide if i said anyting, until Adam Kincaid opens his mouth   Adam: He called you a N@#$%R!  Jeremy: You called me what?  Daniel: I swear I didn't  Jeremy: Hey Corey come over here   This is where I actually get a break, I have known Corey since I was in 9th and I wrote and article about him this year   Corey: Nah I know Daniel he wouldn't say that.   Daniel: Thank you Jesus  So after that I go into the lunch line and look over and see this Jeremy guy make a cut throat sign to me, which yet again made me think I was going to die. But I was pretty sure he was kidding with me.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's So true   urlLink Hahahahaha 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Probably a hoax but it would be cool to see if the creators of the matrix could actually come up with something as good as the first one.    urlLink Geiri3d: The Matrix Reentered 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the coolest flash movie ever.    urlLink Banana Phone 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Xbox.com :: EA + Xbox Live = Gaming Powerhouse   So it looks like EA and Xbox live are partners, very cool. But unfortunately i now must go to school. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Blogger FINALLY Added some new templates.   In other news, I think I finally got a job at Arbor Acres, washing dishes for $7.50/hour.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I just got to thinking if Dave Chappelle had a show about Mount Tabor it would probably look something like this:  1st Skit: World Series of Pat (For the black people, and Nick Jennings) 2nd Skit: World Series of Texas Hold'em Poker (for the white people) Skits 3-7:Mrs. Baily, an in depth look 8th Skit: Tyrone Biggums visits Tabor, gives up crack, starts smoking weed 9th Skit: Mr. Baily replaces Lil' John in his signature skits 10th Skit: Tyrone Biggums visits Reynolds and becomes an alcoholic 11th skit: Wayne Brady comes and is overwhelmed by all the whiteness. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, i really haven't been that vocal on my feelings about the election, i have stated that I support Kerry but I have realized that politics are best left for the class room not a friendly setting such as poker or eating out. So basically I don't really like bush but i really don't like Michael Moore. This guy made Farenheit 9/11 and he is a totaly jerk, essentailly he made it to get out the anti-bush vote, not to really look at the facts. Head on over to www.moorewatch.com and check out what they have to say.    Please note I am planning on going to go see this movie and will report back about what I saw.   Ok so thats it, oh i go the court date on tuesday, gonna be crazy down at city hall when D nasty gets in the defendents chair. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Unlike 90% of my friends, I am not in Daytona so i will be here all week not doing much until thursday. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So while all most of my friends are in Daytona Beach I am here, not doing anything because the people at work gave me 3 consecutive days off starting Monday which sucks cause i really wanted some hours.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I started work last week, its ok, I mean I'm getting payed 7.50/hr to serve people food, and usually I can leave an hour early if I want. 21 days till my court date, that means I have 3 weeks to acquire 150 bucks. That shouldn't be too hard. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I got a speeding ticket saturday, 18 over on shatalon (that is a 63 in a 45) but it looks like i'm not gonna need to get a lawyer. Apparently in Forsyth county they are leanient on first time speeding offenders, so all i'm gonnna have to do is take Alive at 25 class and then pay a fine, but it won't go on my insurance and is whiped from my record. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well i'm bout to go down to the beach for a week, definately won't be posting anything, not that I have lately anyway.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink MilkandCookies - Barney 2Pac   This is great, the best part is when the asian kid yells something, it looks almost voiced over exactly.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I got my head shaved on my chruch mission trip, thought i'de show everyone, please note i am terrible at taking pics of myself       Old Me       New me 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink He's back....  Chappelle is back, and he's gonna be better than ever
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I'm back from the beach, it was fun but I'm glad to be home. Now all i got to do is survive the next week before school starts.
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>