<Blog>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      THE CITY OF JOY – DOMINIQUE LAPIERRE “All that is not given is lost”  “Adversities are great, but man is greater than adversities”  Largely based on these two dictums, Dominique Lapierre’s The City of Joy tries to be an eye opener of sorts, for both Indians and non-Indians. Lapierre spent a substantial time in Calcutta doing research and interviewing people, who finally became characters in his book The City of Joy. Set in the poorest quarter of Calcutta, ironically named Anand Nagar, the book is an account of the undaunted spirits of the poor, the diseased and the helpless. Ranging from lepers to peasants, from mafia dons to beggars, from doctors to rickshaw pullers, from eunuchs to priests, the book tries to be an amalgamated tale of how in poverty - religion, caste, colour, lose importance and differences boil down to their minimal most.  Stephan Kovalski, the Polish priest, Hasari Pal, the peasant turned rickshaw puller, Max Loeb the American doctor, form the main protagonists of the book. Kovalski comes to India, a land where “the sublime often stood side by side with the very worst this world can offer” and decides that it’s Calcutta, overpopulated, poverty and disease stricken, that needs his presence. Kovalski soon makes Anand Nagar his home, overjoyed to see that his room would make him the poorest of the poor in this slum. Soon begins Kovalski’s life in Anand Nagar, his adjustment to the place, his winning over the people and his slow Indianization. Kovalski finds true friends and helpers in people like Margaretta, Bandona and Saladdin, who complete the picture of the social workers of Anand Nagar.   Kovalski’s experience is a complete one, with all the natural calamities striking, the tryst with the babus of the infamous Indian Government, his initial feeling of repulsiveness at the Leper Colony etc. etc. Lapierre does his best at making Kovalski’s character, closer to life and believable. On the contrary, that of Max Loeb is less believable. Brought up in a family of millionaires in Miami, the young doctor decides to come to India when he reads about Kovalski in a magazine. A touch of naturalism is added when Max Loeb runs from all the dirt and poverty of Anand Nagar and pampers himself in a hotel for some days, before his guilt takes over him and he returns to the slum. Why even Max Loeb has to live in the rat and insect infested slum is a question unanswered. After all, he is not a priest like Kovalski.   Hasari Pal’s story remains the most touching and one we’ve come across several times. The poverty stricken peasant decides to try his luck in the city and faces nothing but more poverty. Luckily for him, he obtains a rickshaw to be pulled, which leads him unknowingly to further disaster.  The City of Joy is a book well written. It’s basis in true life makes it impact strongly and does result in a dim and depressing feeling. The minutest details of life in India and typical Indian mannerisms show the depth of Lapierre’s research. The author’s style is at once heart rendering and matter of fact.   Although Lapierre clarifies in his note that “The book…. does not pretend to speak for the whole of India”, the story of Anand Nagar would befit any metropolitan slum of the country. The book is about one man’s initiation to make a difference, and his indomitable spirit that affects hundreds others. Encouraging as well as saddening, The City of Joy soundly conveys the message of humanity and unity; two factors that could help man stand through the worst of disasters.   For those who have not read the book, nor seen the movie, I’d opine that one should first read the book. The story has been ripped apart and (according to me) killed. Although with an impressive star cast, the true star of the book, Stephan Kovalski finds no place in the movie, which for me is a huge disappointment. To get a better impact of Lapierre’s writing, reading the book first would be justified.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      this is a drastic test!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I feel like a lost wave. Here's an old poem.   THE LOST WAVE   Does a wave ever lose its way? The one, that never reaches The shore?  Maybe it gets snatched in a storm Bangs against a vessel And dissipates into nothingness   Maybe it ebbs to the sun Goes up and comes down To a dry, patchy meadow  Or maybe it gets shy And never kisses the shore Staying behind the loud, big waves Losing its self to others forever… ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I can get as mindlessly talkative as they come. I can talk with anyone, of any age, and of any background. I am good at making people feel comfortable. Most people don't know the other side of me. I love silences. I love being alone. I love being alone with just some one person.  Most of the times, the ones who know me well (but not well enough) would think that I would be the one who'd like flowery language, romantic, sweet nothings, extravagant gifts, meeting everyday and talking for hours and hours together. That is ok, I don't mind it unless it's not a waste and beyond limits. But for me, that is not ultimate romance.  I cherish silences when I am with someone who's company I enjoy. I love to listen to the sounds in the silence - the sound of breathing, the sound of smiles, of eyes batting, of limbs moving, of clothes crumpling. I love the sound of thoughts moving rapidly through my head. I love the fact that I am sure the person with me loves all of this too. As important as words get -- true compatibility is only evident if the silences are as lovely as the 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The memories of a beautiful day folded neatly into 14 lines. Here’s my current state of mind.   Eleven shooting stars One single wish Happiness But that me, was a little girl So little did I know That Happiness Has a shape That it has a face That happiness can you touched That it’s heartbeat can be heard It’s warmth can sooth Your chilling fears  Little did I know That happiness is a he. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Monday morning joke prior to the damn exam..   She : So what all do we have to take? Me : Hall ticket, pens, pencil.... water?? She : Haan, water... and my medicines. (She is sick with hypertension) Me : Hahaha, yes medicines!! She : Fir, pen bhi nahi liya to chalega, khoon se lihkhegi, lekin I want my medicines. Me : *Too busy giggling to comment further*  Laccho, you're a monkey.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I am a classic case of an oxymoron...! I can't wait for those damn exams to get over, so that I can be free and live my life like I want to. But I am  sure  that once they get over, I'll be all like -- "Oh dear... Now what? What now? What do I do.....???"
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Pretty please, make me happy. Are sickness and exams good enough reasons for me to pamper myself???  Sampada is _____________ When I think of Sampada, I think of ______________  I want Sampada to _________________ I think Sampada should ________________ Sampada needs ________________ If I were to hang out with Sampada, I would _______________ If I could describe Sampada in one word, it would be: _______________ Sampada will never ______________ Sampada can _______________ I hope Sampada never _________________ I _________ Sampada because ____________________
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
        A Great Poem (Part 2)    How they beat me How they beat me How they beat me  Nobody understands poems these days!  -- by Sampada, just for Yasmine!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
            -->  urlLink     This is the list of the chosen bloggers for this weeks  Bharatiya Blog Mela .       urlLink Suhani   writes about the  strange reaction of the French crowd during the Henin-Williams semi-final match  on her blog “Between the Lines”. (Date of post – 7th June 2003)     urlLink Vikas Kamat   tells about how much he learnt from the magazine "Before and After". A little picture of the  FedEx and Amazon books logo , makes the post interesting.(   urlLink Permalink   )     urlLink N S Ramnath   dissects the  tradition of companies to hire people from the same caste and the drawbacks of this system.  (Date – 5th June 2003)     urlLink Balaji Singh   has the nicest  two short posts  I’ve ever seen. (Date of post – 4th June 2003)     urlLink Anvita Singh   of  “When I paint my Masterpiece”  reviews the book “The Nanny Diaries”  (   urlLink Permalink   )     urlLink Sandeep   writes an insightful article on the  Purushasukta hymn from the Yajurveda  and how interpreting this hymn is an integral part of understanding the Hindu Caste System (   urlLink Permalink   )     urlLink Shanti    criticizes the ersatz-intellectual article of Pritish Nandy  and explains why exactly she thinks his article is “nothing but unedible fuzz served on an elegant silver plate.” (   urlLink Permalink   )   And this is for the girls :   urlLink Anita'a blog   has the list of the  10 most romantic men  researched from a poll. (Date – 4th June 2003)  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ok...time for some etymology. Read this in my literature notes last month. Ever wondered where the word "tantalizing" came from? Of course not! :-) Well, word comes from the Greek myth of Tantalus. Now this guy Tantalus offended the gods tad too much, and they condemned him to an afterlife of an eternity of hunger and thirst. He was made to stand in a pool of water, but everytime he reached to the water that beckoned to his parched mouth, it drained away. Above him was tree laden with delicious fruits. But everytime Tantalus reached out to pluck one for himself, the boughs receded from his grasp.   That's where the word "tantalizing" comes from.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My refresher page does not work...  Refresher...LOL
     
    
</post>



</Blog>