<Blog>

<date>31,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       The engagement party last night was amazing. Everyone put so much work into making everything run smoothly and well. Especially Dane and Greg and Lisa's parents who really helped to put everything together and make sure that everything ran so smoothly. Even with the groom to be and his family managing to get completely lost and arrive 2 hours late... (though if anyone needs a good shortcut to New Millford, I can provide) Thank you to everyone for coming and for all your congratulations and thoughtful gifts. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Something weird going on with the archive. Going to try and fix it soon. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone who needs directions to my engagement party, give me a call on my cell phone. The party's Saturday Dec. 28th @ 6PM. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Merry Christmas to everyone! BBQ grilled turkey and stuffing are definitely the way to go for dinner. Korean food isn't bad as an appetizer, but it's nice to have a sitdown family meal followed by a boardgame. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Finally done with Finals for the semester. What a great feeling. Now I'm just looking forward to some Christmas and getting into the engagement party on the 28th. Happy holidays for everyone. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Last night was pretty crazy. The basic timeline: Miss the first train. Rush through dinner. Arrive at STOMP only to find out that apparently there's a time restriction on our tickets where you have to show up 1/2 hour early (not what I was told over the phone when I made the reservation) Decide to see Lord of the Rings:Two Towers instead. They're sold out for an hour. Wait in a bar until just before the movie only to find out OUR tickets are for the OTHER Loews theatre 2 blocks away (despite saying we didn't want that show) Rushing to that theatre. The movie was great, but by the time we get out, we rush to the Port Authority only to find out that their subway stop is closed late at night, causing us to miss the last train back to Jersey and wait in Penn Station for 3 hours... All in all, quite an odd night. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       Only 1 exam left to go next week, then nothing more for a while. It's such a liberating feeling to be free from that time immediate pressure feeling. I'm going to see STOMP tomorrow night, with some tickets I got through work. Should be interesting, and I'm excited since I've heard a lot of good things about the show. Ben Stein wrote an editorial about  urlLink How to Ruin American Enterprise  where he rants on about the decline of the American work ethic and willingness to take responsibility for our actions. I quite agree. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       This whole blogging thing is rather addictive, I must admit. I've had all these great ideas for things that I could do to my site now, to make it more interesting, and also things that wouldn't (hopefully) need more work from me. :) It should be interesting seing in a few weeks or so, how things end up progressing, and what we end up with. I was just thinking that I'll probably end up setting up a similar site for ROTC or something along those lines. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I just inserted sections on films and books that I've read or viewed recently. I will most likely be updating those sections rather infrequently, but there are so many good books and other works out there, that I just had to plug a few that have caught my eye. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I'm starting to add some other interesting items, in addition to the newslinks I have a photo album, guestbook, and some other items in the offering. Hopefully over the next few days I'll manage to put things together. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I'm engaged to the most wonderful person in the world. Lisa Ann Colon. :) 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I'm just about getting ready to go to my CS323 exam. I'll post later with how everything went. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I've added headlines from the  urlLink Daily Targum  where I work to give you an idea of some of the events that are occuring in the Rutgers area. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       I'm in the middle of final exams at  urlLink Rutgers  right now. I have 1 tonite from 8PM until 11PM, and another tomorrow at noon, so I don't expect to really be able to get into working on this site until later on, maybe after the holidays. I'm hopping that using a weblog style backend will mean that I update it more than once a month or so. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       This is the new recently revised version of my personal site. While things are being worked around, if you're intersted in my resume, it's still available at:  urlLink http://www.shao.org/jay/resume.html . More content will be following shortly. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Made it by the skin of my teeth on my run today. And damn, it was cold!!!  urlLink weather.com  said it was warmer than it was on Friday morning, but it really didn't feel like it. Rounding the bend in Buccleauch Park, right after the apartments I could feel the wind blasting into my face and it felt like my whole body was frozen through. I think I'll do really well in Push-ups and situps tomorrow on the diagnostic, however, as I almost floated through those events (admittedly I was only doing the 60 percent minimum) All in all I'm feeling pretty good about the performance, though I have to admit that it was one of the hardest things that I've ever done/managed to accomplish. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       APFT Monday that I have to pass. I'm about 24 seconds away on the run, so hopefully I'll be able to post here on Monday that I had an outstanding run time. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Been doing PT again now that the winter break is wrapping to a close, and it's really been wiping me out. Also, I've gotten a couple copies of the email form letter about Jane Fonda and Vietnam vets on the web recently. If you see it take it with a grain of salt. Many of the examples are fictionalized. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Snow this week has been unbelievable. My car was streetside parked, and it took me and Lisa almost 40 minutes to dig it out. (The first 5 minutes were actually pretty fun, just like playing in the snow as a little kid. 15 minutes later, when the snow plow came by and plowed me back in... was less fun.) Classes are still out, though they should be starting again soon.  Snow also postponed the other big task I've been working on, which is interviewing candidates for the Targum Marketing Director for next year. Oh well. I guess there's not much you can do when your carefully laid plans are upset by the textbook definition of an "act of God." 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Still working on fixing the archives. Hopefully they'll be up soon. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       RUSH is next week. Anyone who is interested in Fraternities at Rutgers should come check out  urlLink SigEp . 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Something that amazes me is the emphasis the media gives Anti-war rallies due to their numbers. 100,000 people is a significant amount, mind you, however I note that organizations like Louis Farakhan, or Promisekeepers, or NOW can rally larger numbers in peacetime without gathering equivalent attention. Although 100,000 individuals is a non-insignificant number, in this modern age of suberbia and mass-transit into urban centers, is it really as impressive a number as it would have been even 20 years ago? NYC draws not just on the population of the city itself, but that of surrounding areas in NJ, Long Island, etc.  I think part of the reason for the percieved liberal slant of the media is media's emphasis on covering "what's happening now" which has been translated into changes. Despite the fact that the status quo is an equally important part of the total picture, there's a wide bias that if it's not new, it's not news. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Lets hear it for nice weather. Such a relief compared to the last few weeks of snow, storms, and everything else. It seems like a good way to end Spring Break. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've posted the slides from the ROTC class on financial management online here:  urlLink financialmanagement.PPT  for anyone who missed the class and who wanted to read up on the material. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not going to be able to make it to the  urlLink CNBAM  conference in Miami next week. :( Unfortunately, I had some Army training which I won't be able to miss. I trust our 2003-2004 Business Manager and Marketing Director will hold us in good stead as far as representing the Targum goes, though.  Good luck on all the awards, and make sure you bring back somethign for us stuck in NJ types. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Event:	Raw:	Score: PU	67	96 SU	76	97 RU	15:42	63  Total Score:	256  That's pretty much my personal all time high, so I'm pretty psyched about it. I'm a little disappointed that all the time spent running over the past couple of weeks hasn't translated into a greater improvement in my run time, though. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just wanted to let everyone know that I had a good time seeing everyone at Andy's... even the strange veggie food place. Especially seeing Tejal & Ankur's engagement pics and video... though I must say that you have far more patience with all that garb and the picture taking than I ever could. :) 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Happy Birthday  urlLink Andy . Even if your room is a Star Trek shrine, you're still a pretty nice guy ;) 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Congratulations to Jennifer Vandertoorn and Christopher Sisti, the new Business Manager and Marketing Director for the  urlLink Targum Publishing Company . Congratulations to both of you as well as the many other excellent candidates who came out to interview, and best of luck for next year and at the  urlLink CNBAM  conference next week. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It should be interesting to meet everyone's parents. CNBAM in Miami is coming up real soon as well.  Also, invitations for the wedding went out recently, so if you got one... mail back the response card before I have to track you down... ;) 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Things are going well with interviews, and hopefully I'll be done soon. Meanwhile, I have a DBMS exam on Monday, but so far studying is going well. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It always amazes me how the weather can be so cold and frigid one day, and yet so warm and inviting (like today) the next. Oh well, I guess that it's just something we have to enjoy. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       2 exams down, and 2 more to go. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just playing with the new blogger. 

        
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Like any red-blooded, masculine man of the male gender, I love PVC weaponry. You should too. If the concept of heading on down to the local Home Depot and transforming $100 worth of random pipe bits into a killing machine doesn't appeal to you, you're a goddamn pansy. Also, you're probably sane and will live significantly longer than I will. Nonetheless you disgust me, and I take comfort in the knowledge that your obituary will be nowhere near as humorous as mine. For those of you who laugh in the face of hypersonic shards of plastic puncturing your spleen, here's an intimate look at how I've kept myself busy for the past week: building a PVC flamethrower.   This is just ridiculous.    

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        RELEASE: Mozilla Foundation Announces More Open, Scriptable Plugins Adobe, Apple, Macromedia, Opera and Sun Microsystems join in push to modernize plugins and create a richer web experience   This sounds like it would be a great step forward in terms of building rich clients in the browser.  Looking at the raft of companies involved, I wonder how much of this is motivated by the industry's fear of XAML based rich webapps taking over? 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        'Through 2004, outsourcing will continue to drive the growth in the worldwide IT services market, with IT management and process management growing faster than consulting services and development and integration services,' Hale said in a statement.   Interesting to see something so many IT workers have been afraid of described as driving growth in the sector.  I wonder if we're just starting to see a new round of consolidation as IT becomes more of a commodity.  It seems like a lot of companies have decided that it's more cost-effective to hire a specialist.  Wonder if that'll create new opportunities for specialists... 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        assuming that the unconfirmed reports are accurate, we have here a media company infecting users' machines silently with a file that affects a computer's functionality, without first obtaining informed consent: a likely violation of pretty much every jurisdiction's anti-hacking laws. It's possible to foresee criminal charges being brought at some point: after all, having a good reason for spreading malware has never been much of a defence in court. And a file that alters a computer's functioning without the owner's informed consent is the very definition of malware. Because this malware can be transferred from machine to machine on a removable disk, and requires user interaction to spread, it is, quite simply, a computer virus. (A worm, on the other hand, is distinguished by its ability to spread without user interaction.)   It does seem deceptive for companies to limit the functionality of something they're selling you without making it clear to the consumer before purchase.  I wonder if the actions taken by this CD are close enough to the legal definition of a virus to enable some kind of lawsuit. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The remains of a 27-year-old woman from Phoenix have been transformed into six precious stones and are set to be delivered to her family and friends on Friday. LifeGem's first order could be the start of a new age in the funeral industry.     Fantastically creepy, and yet at the same time kind of practical seeming.  At least it's much less loony than Anna Nicole Smith carting around her dead husband's ashes in an urn.  And, if you're looking for a small, durable keepsake, it is hard to beat a diamond.  Other crazy burial options listed in the same story include:    Being turned into a frisbee, like frisbee creator Ed Headrick   Having Eternal Reefs turn mix your ashes with concrete to make an artificial reef   Getting sent into orbit like Star Trek creator Gene Roddenbury   Painted into art, lending new creepiness to those family portraits hanging in the hall   Turned into comic ink, like Mark Gruenwald from Marvel Comics    

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In a research note published this morning, the analyst mentions that the company is poised to witness customer base expansion in the forthcoming quarters. The analyst expresses his concern, however, regarding Apple Computer's limited presence in the low-end markets. The company's fundamentals remain healthy, Banc of America Securities adds.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This article introduces the first working Xgrid agent for Linux and other Unix systems that can be integrated in any XGrid cluster (managed by OS X). The agent will compile and work on Linux (at least Debian and RedHat), Solaris (minimal testing) and Darwin (tested). You still need an OS X machine for the controller and for using the actual XGrid (with XGrid.app). Also, the user currently needs to 'be aware' that the cluster is multi-architecture (since the XGrid controller actually does not know). Examples are provided to show you how to deal with this.   This sounds like a fantastic tool that could make XGrid the standard for scientific clustering applications.  Ease of use for the consumers, and utilizing existing resources.  Sounds like Apple might not be happy (they're trying to use XGrid to sell more Macs) but that it could be good for them in the long run.  After all, you still need a Mac to run the thing, and it's a lot easier to get funding for one new computer than 50.  And once one's in the shop... 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The United States bowed to broad opposition on the Security Council today and announced that it was dropping its effort to gain immunity for its troops from prosecution by the International Criminal Court.  The United States has decided not to proceed further with consideration and action on the draft at this time in order to avoid a prolonged and divisive debate,' the deputy American ambassador, James B. Cunningham, said on emerging from the council.   This is good from the point of view of cooperating with the rest of the world and ensuring accountability outside of functioning nation states. I still have strong issues with the potential for abuse of the ICC, however. I'm curious to see if it does become an issue with countries using ICC summonses as yet another tool for attacking each other in the diplomatic realm. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Jason Smathers, a West Virginia man who worked in AOL's Dulles, Virginia, data warehouse, is accused of stealing a list containing 92 million subscriber screen names. Interim U.S. Attorney David Kelley said Smathers, 24, sold the list to another man, Sean Dunaway, who then sold it to two spammers for $52,000. Dunaway was also charged by federal prosecutors in Manhattan.   Considering the number of people who much have access to these kinds of lists, I wonder (long term) how you can stop people from taking a gamble and trying to make a quick 50k.  That's a lot of money for just about anyone. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Last summer, in response to the success that Linux was having in the Thai marketplace, Microsoft began offering Thai citizens a Thai-localized bundle of Microsoft Windows XP Home and Office XP Standard. As part of the deal, Microsoft also stripped out some unspecified features from both products and slashed the price for the pair to 1,500 Thai Baht, or about $38 U.S. Microsoft Windows XP Home sells at retail for $225; Office XP Standard retails for $499.   It seems odd that Microsoft can offer a product like this in one location, and yet fight so hard in other locations (like the US & EU) that Windows is inseperable, and that the components cannot be stripped out. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        distcc is a little application that hooks onto the gcc compiler and allows the compilation to occur on other machines where distcc is installed. The first step is to get distcc onto your workstation, so download the latest version from the Web site (see Resources for a link).   Fantastic 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Organizer cancels Comdex 2004 - News - ZDNet : "Computer trade show Comdex, once the biggest event on the tech calendar, has been canceled this year, a victim of the growing interest in shows emphasizing consumer electronics and specialist IT gear. " 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink US chastity crusade gets cool response in secular Britain | csmonitor.com : "The government prefers the message offered by a domestic program called APAUSE (Added Power and Understanding in Sex Education) that counsels an ABC of good practice (Abstinence, Be faithful, use a Condom). One of its architects, John Tripp of Exeter University, says that while Britain is unlikely to embrace US chastity evangelists, it can learn from US efforts to change cultural norms."  It's interesting that the abstinance group is the one pushing to be included as "another option" whereas the education lobby in the UK seems to be trying to be the "only way".  It's an interesting flip from what seems to be the attitude in the U.S. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink DVD Rewinder : "Some might say that the makers of the DVD Rewinder are scam artists, even despite their claims that the DVD Rewinder is for entertainment purposes only, but really, if people are buying them, can you blame them? I bought two to go with my centrifugal LP re-flattener and my cotton-tipped radial laserdisc demux pre-cleaner."    

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Mark Bernstein: Commentary : "Weblog comments incite duels. Duels are bad for society. We should all forego comments and return to carefully blogging responses -- including responses we disagree with, but excluding responses we cannot tolerate."  It's an interesting viewpoint, that is hard to disagree with on the face.  Comments appear out of context with a commentor's other posts, thus are almost always read without an ability to make a judgement on the posters credibility.  I could see this causing a greater instance of flame-like posts.  It seems it would be a shame to lose the directed dialogue traits that have become so much of the blog format.  Perhaps what's really needed is an author feedback system, perhaps tied in with a system like  urlLink typekey  that would let you see how many other comments an author has made, and how people ranked him.  Maybe some kind of averaging between how people ranked the author's weblog & his comments.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Techdirt has an interesting article going back and looking at some statements Jack Valenti had made about VCRs and compared them to his current statements about piracy and filesharing. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       via email   FINE This is the word women use to end an argument when they are right and you need to shut up.   FIVE MINUTES If she is getting dressed, this is half an hour. Five minutes is only five minutes if you have just been given 5 more minutes to watch the game before helping around the house.   NOTHING This is the calm before the storm. This means "something," and you should be on your toes. Arguments that begin with 'Nothing' usually end in "Fine"   GO AHEAD This is a dare, not permission.. Don't do it.   LOUD SIGH This is not actually a word, but is a non-verbal statement often misunderstood by men. A "Loud Sigh" means she thinks you are an idiot and wonders why she is wasting her time standing here and arguing with you over "Nothing"   THAT'S OKAY This is one of the most dangerous statements that a woman can make to a man. "That's Okay" means that she wants to think long and hard before deciding how and when you will pay for your mistake.   THANKS A woman is thanking you. Do not question it or faint. Just say you're welcome.  

        
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Nigerian mobile phone users have been anxiously checking who is calling them before answering them in recent days.  A rumour has spread rapidly in the commercial capital, Lagos, that if one answers calls from certain 'killer numbers' then one will die immediately.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        And there was another one where a bunch of us decided to take the second floor of one building and we put like sheetrock over all the doorways and re-plastered them and painted them. We re-did the numbers on the stairwells going up. We rewired the elevator system so that it looked like when you pressed two you went to what used to be No. 3. And we put in fake baseboarding so you couldn't tell where the friggin' doors used to be. And for that one I was 18.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       VeriSign is to rapidly update Domain Name System (DNS) records every few minutes instead of only twice a day. From 8 September changes in the .com and .net zones will take an estimated five minutes to propagate across all 13 .com/.net authoritative name servers. The old systems will remain there for those who don't want to make the leap forward. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The BSA seems to be confused on where to pin the blame on software piracy, but it may be due to the audience they are trying to influence. Piracy is a global problem and it is hard to pin it down to a single cause. Currently P2P networks are a problem, but according to this year's study, the addition of consumer program piracy statistics (which would favor P2P as a distribution method) only contributed to 2-3 percent increase in piracy rates compared to 2002. Blaming P2P applications masks what is likely the largest factors in piracy rates and losses: unlicensed installed software and counterfeit software sold on street corners. Unfortunately, the BSA and their representative companies feel that lobbying for restrictive laws are more effective in thwarting piracy in countries with the lowest piracy rates, than mustering up additional forces to crack down on counterfeiting in countries with emerging markets and the highest piracy rates.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You know, you can find the damndest things when you clean out your email, like perhaps an air conditioned jacket from Japanese firm PC2B. It keeps you cool and makes you look like a bloated marshmallow man all at once. Perhaps you could just, you know, take off the jacket.     

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Pop Goes the GMail  is a small Gmail -> POP3 converter that someone wrote for Windows.  It seems interesting, but most of the neat  urlLink GMail  features are actually more to do with the web interface, so it seems like you'd be giving up most of the benefits of the service. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Moviemistakes has posted a list of Spiderman 2 movie gaffs, factual inaccuracies, etc.  I remember back when these kind of mistakes would be the neat tricks your friends tried to get you to see (like the rumored shoe in Star Wars: Return of the Jedi).  Ahh, the progress of the Internet... 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In recent months, doctors have traced the problems to what has apparently become a phenomenon among New York City's Latinas: haphazard cosmetic surgery conducted in the Dominican Republic after being arranged through beauty salons in Washington Heights and other city neighborhoods. The salons act as conduits for the procedure, with recruiters, some from the Dominican Republic, visiting hairdressing parlors, where they casually mention to customers that they know of cheap places to get liposuction, tummy tucks and breast augmentation.  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Sun licensed the software from a small company in Alameda, Calif., called Karelia, which worked for years on a version of Watson for Apple computers. Sun has created a new version of the software--code-named Alameda--that runs on any Java-enabled computer, said Peder Ulander, senior director of marketing for Sun's Desktop Solutions Group.   Interesting.  I was wondering who Karelia's "big company" was.  It seems like kind of an odd way to make an attack on the desktop, though I guess this is yet another XAML fighting move.  Still, rich client UI's could be a strong future, and Macromedia isn't the only game in town.  Personally, I prefer  urlLink Apple's take with dashboard  more myself. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        A survey of around 350 undergraduates found nearly 25% had copied text from another source at least once. A new service that can scan 4.5 billion web pages is now online so that lecturers can check the originality of the work submitted by students.   I wonder how much of this plagiarism would be avoided if there were a simple, easy way to automatically cite sources retrieved from the Internet and encyclopedias.  I mean, there's BibTEX for scholars, and  urlLink Encyclopedia Britannica  has started providing MLA style citations for articles, but after 15 something years of the Internet, why isn't this automatic?  I think what we need is:  a combination of a bibliographic tool, like the one  urlLink proposed for inclusion with the OpenOffice.org office suite   some kind of browser plugin or feature designed to automatically capture site meta-data like URI, author, date created, date updated/accessed, etc.    There's been some interesting work in the blogging space with bookmarklets that automatically fill in the cite field in blockquotes and stuff like that, but if there was an easily available set of student tools, I think you'd see plagiarism drop.  Not in the "I grabbed a paper of the Internet" sense, but in the "I got this somewhere, but don't know where and I'm to lazy to find it again" context. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        A 16-year-old was arrested early Wednesday in a theater showing 'Spider-man 2' after a projectionist using night vision goggles saw him using a camcorder to make an illegal copy of the superhero sequel.   Pretty amazing to think that NVGs are so inexpensive that even movie theatres can give them out now.  I wonder how long until the military faces guerilla enemies with a stock of NVGs, GPS, and all our other cool toys. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Unsurprisingly, the book received massive press attention in the States when it was launched in April 2000. It has since been through several reprints, been printed across the world, and Katie has managed to make a career out of retelling her tale. Most recently an entire TV show called 'Katie.com' aired in the US. She now plans to launch a school curriculum to teach kids about online safety, called, inevitably, Katie.com.  There is only one snag however - the actual Internet domain 'Katie.com' is owned by a completely different Katie - Katie Jones, and she lives in the UK. Katie is furious over what she sees as the hijacking of her domain name - bought for her in 1996 by her husband. Ever since the book was published - four years after she had first been bought it - Katie Jones has received masses of email and heavy traffic to her site but wants none of it. She has had to pull her own content off visible pages on the site, and has posted instead a protest blog about how the book's publishers - Penguin - have effectively made it impossible for her to use her own property.   The most interesting thing in this situation seems to be the lawyers argument that they've invested resources and money into building a brand around the name, so the original owner cannot resell the name to make a profit. It seems to me more a case of squatting than anything else. If you build a house on somebody else's land, do you really have a recourse if they sell the land to someone else?  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        An audit conducted by Open Source Risk Management (OSRM) found 283 potential patent infringements in the Linux 2.4 and 2.6 code base. The OSRM, a group that offers indemnification against Linux copyright infringement claims, conducted a study in advance of the expansion of its indemnification offerings to cover patent infringement. According the OSRM, 27 of the patents are held by Microsoft, which has signaled its intention to make patent licensing a major source of future revenues. Another 98 are owned by companies with heavy Linux investments, including 60 from IBM and 20 from HP. HP acknowledged the possibility of patent infringement risks two years ago in an internal memo, which was subsequently made public."  

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The trauma of dirty loos could be a thing of the past for users of pPod, a guide to the best and worst of public toilets for iPod owners.    It's interesting to see more stuff like this happening as iPod's become a prevalent small digital device. It reminds me a lot of all the city guides and other items that came out for Palm Pilots when they were trendy. 

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The real difference between the two parties comes with the decision of at one point, exactly, the government should start restricting our lives. Does Big Brother have a place in markets, or in minds, or in both?  Up until this point in our recent political memory, the Leave Us Alone crowd has traditionally found a home in the GOP. The Take Care of Us crew, naturally, has found its home in the Democratic Party. But these are strange political times, and both Americas are feeling the growing pains of a two party system that doesn’t seem to quite fit anymore. Conservatives who remember the promise of the Republican Revolution in the mid-nineties scarcely recognize the new brand of conservatism foisted on them, having somewhere lost the hope of balancing budgets and shrinking government. Liberals have been stuck with a much more hawkish slant from their leaders, and an economic direction that is less left-friendly than some would hope for.  The Two Americas are having growing pains as both parties struggle for fewer and fewer undecided voters. In the process, the big tents are starting to sway uncomfortably, while trying to stretch over too many people with too many viewpoints. Some political analysts are predicting an upcoming realignment, a fundamental change in how the two parties define themselves. It remains to be seen if the Two Americas will stay put, or if voters will start to jump ship in search of alternatives.   

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Judging from the entries made on one police blotter after another, cars around the nation are having their gas tanks sugared by those whom their owners have displeased. Why is this happening? Because, according to widespread belief, sugar poured into a gas tank will Sugar, Sugar turn into a poor man's version of liquid cement and quickly render the vehicle's engine unfit for anything but a junkyard. In theory, the sugar dissolves into the gasoline, then travels along the fuel lines into the engine, where the heat of the vehicle's operations melts the sweetener into a dense sludge that gets into every nook and cranny of the engine. The sucrosed engine seizes and halts the vehicle in its tracks, but the real damage comes when the engine cools and the sludge hardens to rock-like consistency. Only the replacement of the entire engine will render the car fit for use again, says popular wisdom; otherwise, it's kiss your jalopy goodbye.  It is for such reason that this theory is so fervently cherished — it appears to grant, for the price of a 5 lb. bag of sugar, the ability to effect great and irreparable harm to an adversary's most prized possession. The touted mode of vengeance is both inexpensive and easy to carry out, a combination that seems to put the power of getting even into the hands of anyone, no matter how disadvantaged.  However, revenge fantasies aside, this snippet of popular lore turns out not to be the sure and deadly car killer the retribution-minded would want to believe it is. As with many grand schemes, it lives more vividly in its imagining than in reality.   

        urlLink link  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>