<Blog>


<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow..this daily thing is kind of getting to me...I'm surprising myself, by the fact that I might be going on this thing more often..=). Slow uneventful things in life...but all gets posted. Also on IRC a.t.m...but going soon...the huge-ass printer is printing...no wait, I'm lost..it just finished. Anyhow..yeah...it's okay..n/m..I'm out.  Got to hand in stuff.. RO server! http://www.enigmaro.com  OR!!  Join #EnigmaRO @ irc.irchighway.net!~  Muahahaha...  Yeah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       http://www.motellmaffian.com/bakgrunder/  Whoa. All I can say is..this place has some nice backgrounds. I don't use 'em myself...but it's pretty good eye-candy. Once again...I'm sittin' down in Comm..well, Comm 29, to be precise. Stewart's bein' a bitch, walkin' around, telling people what to do. For all who know and hate her, say "aye!". I can see plenty of hands already...  For all who don't? Let's just say..the injustice of being a student, sucks. Totally. I'm definitely failing three courses...probably failing another...and thanks to some bogus messed up test, I probably can't get to summer school for physics, too. Life just bites.  Maybe, on the other hand..there are some relieving things...summer's coming up..summer school is coming up..so I can stay away from home for a bit longer...see h.e.r for a bit more...but then back down to the messed up life of hell in the summer...  ..damn, it's the end of 4th, i got to get to patel, talk to her about my poster...and see what'll happen to me in English, if I can make it to summer.  Take care.  (Insert: Oh, by the way, did I tell you I failed my Unit 8 Physics test? I got to talk to Skillicorn tommorrow ...and ..uhh..yeah.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ..oh damn. I'm sitting here in Media Arts...bored..and working on Flash. God damn it..shut up, Ken. He just said, "If you're so-called working on Flash, why are you doing this?" By 'this', he meant doing this blog. Heck, the only reason I've made a return to this was cux Jose told me if I went back to blog, I'd get an invite for g-mail.  For all who are out of the loop, it's e-mail that's...uhh..it's got 1 gig of space, and the motto? "The Keyword: Search, don't sort." I WANT THAT ONE GIG!...=( Hey, it's useful for all the "junk" that I get.  Ken's taunting me about my sucky laptop again. Why do I feel so sad? =P...oh heck..well, back to whatever I'm doing..so yeah...I'm out. Probably update again, later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...so..i've started once again. After more than a year's hiatus on this thing, and thanks to Keane's unprevailing effort on recovering my blog, I've reverted to a cheap template. Which by me, looks fine. I don't care anymore. As long as I've got the content..yeah..I'll be fine. So heck.  Guess what? It's June 1st. The last few days of school are in progress...and I'm pretty much dead. Life. Work. Parents. Wtf. Eh. Other than resting, fighting, playing around..and spending time with...well.yeah... I'm out of the loop. Don't know if I can actually keep this blog thing up for long, either. See if people actually come. And do stuff...yeah.  Smile. =).  Cool. 
    
    
</post>



<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        *looks at previous post again*  Maybe I was imagining it... maybe I should sleep... "Maybe you should shut up."  *blinks*  Oh gee, sooorry. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        *looks at previous post*  I wonder why the first Paragraph was a different font face... Probably because of the line breaks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm going to change what this blogger looks like...  I don't like the colour, and I was thinking of adding a picture of Hikaru from Hikaru no Go... but I might change it to a Go Board.  Does Kifu sound suitable for this? It's like a record (play by play) of a Go game. So it basically tells how a game went, similar to a journal, ne?   Meh , I'll work on writing more when I finish the template. -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So...  This is a sort of Journal thing?    Rei told me about it, and she got it from Kas... I wonder how long I can keep up with this one...  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I was right...    I'm currently downloading the X series.... Unfortunately it kept saying  Failed . I couldn't understand why...   Then  I noticed my Hard Drive was full... had to do transfering and deletions... *sigh* BUT! Episodes started downloading again! ^-^  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       aww.......*thinks to past* i dun member last time i had civies....but ne one who forgets is considred a big.......L-O-S-E-R!!!!!!1 LOL!!!!!! *pokes* u 2 r sooo cute.......*giggles* course itz easier not to kno about a civies day @ ur school...so i wont hold it againt yas......^-~ HoS|-|i* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I know eh?     Don't feel too badly about the civies and all, I missed the only day I was supposed to get civies because no one told me there was... ^^;;   The anchors looks really good, glad you fixed it all up! Things are definitely looking up *looks up*   Anyhows, busy and interesting month coming... soon there will be International night and the art show to work on. Actually, as a matter of fact, we're working on it right now... let's see: for International Night, we *pointz at self, keane and von* are in charge of the japanese pavilion and we have a bunch of stuff planned. Hopefully they all will work ^^;; As for the art show, the same group of people are going to work on a comic... hopefully that works too!   As for just myself, I'm joining up for badminton... I know for a fact I'm not going to make it, cause I only play for fun... some people there take lessons and go to tournaments!! Ah well, it's the fun that all matters.    ~ Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ah that sucks...    But what's worse was that I remembered to wear civies clothes today, but... it  wasn't  a civies day!!! Good thing I had my uniform in my bag... -.-* Paranoia can come in handy some times...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I'm only on to say this...    Today... as well as yesterday were Civies days for me.  Good thing I forgot to wear civies! @.@  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          ooo do i haveta put a "title" tooooooo??      *coughs* well, well, i c dat this site is going fairly well....*looks around* ten times better than  mine  *clears throat* demo...ne wayz..i hope u guys r doing ait, and dat u Boo-chan r getting ur work done =-= oooo Em! maybe *light bulb* maybe me or Boo-chan can put up a link to ur site! ^-^ sugoi???   *heehee....ja ne....HoS|-|i* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Nobody can say I don't listen...    I added the linkage at the bottem of all posts yesterday. In doing so, I spent all my time without updating my blog. >.  I might not be updating here as often... That doesn't mean other's cannot post!  *sigh* I got 80 on Rei-chan's test   while Joe got 90???   HOW???  *cough*Cheater*cough*  Well, that's all for today...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I will not put a title for this one...     ...cause i can't think of a good one.   Anyways, today i went to mandarin class ... and guess what I found?? Keane wasn't there!! My first thought was like: "Has he started skipping sat classes to go to hoshi-chan's house?", then later I asked hoshi-chan and she's like: "no... haven't seen him...", and I was thinking: "ohh... he must be sick... I should phone him", but then hoshi-chan phones him first and then tells me: "Keane didn't go to sat class cause he slept in."  *Face-fault*  ... and there i was hoping he was ok...  grrr ...    On to sadder news... I got 94% on mid-term exam and 91% in midterm overall for my sat class... and I hafta say that really sucks. No really... it does... cause this stuff is like extremely easy...   Started playing a bit of Warcraft... haven't gotten addicted to it... and I hope I don't...*mutterz*  3vil 3ric...     On a misc. note... i think we should end off all the blog entries with something that can snap you back to the top of the page... think anchors. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Testing...    I'm testing the "Blog This" link found at the bottom of the settings page... if you're reading this, I guess it works!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         He was studying...    A lot of Grade Tens were up late last night finishing History Day projects that were due today. -.-*  *sigh* I was angry too!!! But he had to finish it... *sigh*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       o.O Chronos!!!!!!! Wat were u doing up @ such a late hour! u deserve a slapping! since ur parents dunno and  I do   I'm just going to havtea teach u a lesson! 3 AM!!!!!!!!! O.O   Boo-chan! dun u have ne thing to say bout this??? *SIGHS*  ne wayz, i hope u 2 dun over-do it, rit now ur at school....O.O just realized...man my inner clock is so messed up, it's not even 1pm yet *eh heh heh yet i feel like u guys should b @ home...oh well...just....bored..  ne wayz, good luck on ur test! b^-^ and i doubt he wants u to b late  *glares at chronos* ill scold u later...  HoSHi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Coool...    I'm playing around with the settings at "mail2world" my new e-mail account!  r  2v  q  @mai  l2d  ream.com   They have anime skins! Make my inbox have an anime picture!!! ^-^  Ah yes, finally my dad said 'let's go!'  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Gawd...    My dad is taking so long to get ready... All he has to do is drop me off, then he can come back... I think he wants me to be late... @.@  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Wha...? Today is soon tomorrow..?     Chronos here, wasting ArV's blogger space again.   Pshiness! Tired because of a simple less-than-an-hour class? Yeesh... I'm weaker than you and I'm not tired from it. Hehe, as for that test... I think I'm going to fail it...didn't practice the reversal and couldn't perfect the scarf-hold...   Ah... history project... need... to...finish... tired...want...sleep...but...CAN'T!...    ~Chronos...till the end of Time   *later in the night... or early in the morning*   ok...it's like 2:45am... but at least I'm done! Yay! *collapse*   ~Chronos...till the end of Time   *5-10 min later*   Woot! Staying up this early was all worth it! I'm one of the first people to read the new Megatokyo comic for this Friday! Ahh... finished listening to Invoke for like the 20th time... found that it was one of the few songs that can keep me energetic in such a desperate time... hehehehe... too tired to get high though... *flops*   Don't get me wrong though... I like "Invoke"... but I still like "Northern Lights" the most! "Do You Be-Li-Eve In Des-Ti-Ny?!"   Now off to bed I go before my parents wake up and kill me... ^-^;;;   ~Chronos...till the end of Time  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I'm Catholic...    But you correct me when I say "god" by making it "God" so often that it's become a habit to capitalize that word.     Rei-chan and Jade-san visted our school yesterday. Jamie-san visited today. Fun. m-i-c-k-e-y-m-o-u-s-e. Mickey Mouse... Mickey Mouse, m-i-c-k-e-y-m-o-u-s-e.  I'm so tired... Today was the fourth Self Defence class. Tomorrow will be the last day, they'll be testing us then. I've been tired all week, and it may be because of the class...  I'm downloading X TV. I want to see the series...  so tired... gotta wash the dishes still... *sigh*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was just thinking........  Boo-chan, r u Catholic? hm.......  "By the Gods, I...."  should  b, "by the gods!"  plural , gods? yes, "Gods" iieeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee  sorry, im just  really  boreD!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! speaking of God...im supposed to b studying religion...*whines*  nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo    *sniffles*  ja ne......  HoSHi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Kawaii!     oooo... that emoticon = kawaii-ness, I can just see the glow around you two ^-^b   Anyhows, if I knew you were supposed to work on Geo... I would've dragged you out of the com lab... ah... you can get the Guidance thingy some other time.. it's not often that people teach you how to fall ^^;;; IMO, that self-defense thingy they teach us is turning out better than I thought...   Now that I've confused people with my brief dose of non-sensical-ness and weirdness, I will go poof now... *poof*   ~Chronos...till the end of Time 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         New, but... is it improved?      Ha, anyway... ya...  TODAY was tiring...  I wasted the first two periods when I  should  have worked on Geo... The third period I used to walk around the school in search of people before sitting in english and doodling. Fourth Period I was  supposed  to go to a Guidence Appointment, but I realised I messed up my schedual and it was actually supposed to be fifth, but I missed it because at fifth I was a Gym Conflict Resolution Seminar with these guys who were teaching us  Budo  The way of the Warrior... They taught us how to fall and how to flip someone who grabbed our wrist.  As I mentioned in my last post... Last night I got a haircut... and yes... it is short... really... really short... Am I bald? No, not that short... but  much  shorter than it was, or should be!!!  meh  at least I can gel it.  WTF??? My dad just told me he wants me to vacuum. By the Gods, I vacuumed 2 days ago! What, he wants me to vacuum everyday??? *sigh* Tomllow. I refuse to vacuum till tomollow at least.  *sigh*  meh   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       oooo haircut eh?? cant wait to see it! i bet they made u bald!  *HEEHEE HE ehe eh ehe eh eheehrefhkef  ahh sorry im going crazy...itz prob the cold..and the fact that i stayedup reallly late last nit   *looks around* these dang gloves.. l8z! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I got a haircut...    It's short...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Argh!!!    My computer crashes whenever it leaves or refreshes when on a page with embedded audio!!! >.  Anyone know how to solve? Would be greatful for  any  help.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         PH34R!!     MUHAHAHAHA!! I have hacked into Keane's blogger and am now writing in it!!   Anyways... let's see what I should put...:     ok, keane gave me permission to work in his blogger  i have a blogger too, except that it's in shambles and it has nothing in it (seriously)  um... the above-mentioned page is like my aa page which does not work either...  ha! while you (keane) were having trouble with you're japanese exam, i breezed through my mandarin one!  ah... i will not waste more of your precious space...    Till next time! *disappears in the form of many bats*   P.S. yo keane... i think i just completely villified your blogger... ^^;;;   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I was really tired when I posted my last message...    But now that I've had 10 hours sleep, I'm even  more  tired for some reason. >.  Well how do people like the new colours? Rei-chan chosed them ^^; I think I'll have the change the orange font to something else though... hmm...  *yawns* Well, ja!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         So we took the Japanese mid-term exam today...    I guess it was hard... but if you actually listened to the teacher and studied what she asked you to, it should be a piece of cake.  Unfortunately, although I listen to the teacher, I am not to adept at studying.  Thus, I am quite good at grammer, but am horrible at vocabulary. -.-* *sigh*  Afterwards, I went to Rei-chan's house! ^-^ Yaay! Watched movies with Rei-chan and Mishi... um...   Austin Powers in Goldmember  Half of Monsters Inc.  Half of Ice Age  Three Quarters of Scooby Doo  And the first half of Rush Hour 2    I fell asleep during Scooby Doo... saw it many,  many  times (on account of my sisters' obsession to overwatch movies), and I was  soooo  tired.  -.-   My sister bought a bunch of 3D Puzzles ( P uzz 3 D is the brand name...) and she's currently working on an Aircraft Carrier. The  USS Nimitz . I was helping earlier... but I think a lot of the pieces are missing - She got the puzzles used...  What else happened today... it was kind of busy... Oh yes... Now I'll talk about school!   Yes, I know, I'm not writing chronologically...  *blinks* And I'm using a lot of italics.  Woke up at 8.30 am. Which isn't good since school starts at 8.30 and it takes an hour and a half to bus there. After a quick, and I mean  quick  shower my dad dropped me off 45 minutes late. Good thing Mine-sensei didn't start the exam until 9.30. -.-   We had the test during first period... fun. During the break I played speed Go with Von. She says I won, so does Chronos. I disagree. While we were playing I could hear people around me murmuring "Chinese Checkers." Geez people! It's Chinese  Chess !!!! Wei-chi Chess to be exact... but we play by Japanese rules. ^-^  Second period the teacher taught us out of the text book. It's actually quite good for grammer. When school finished, I had to  shamefully  ask Rei-chan to pick me up so I could go to her house. -.-* But it was worth it, even just to see Rei-chan but 3 days early!  Oh yes! Rei-chan's coming to Mary Ward on Wednesday with Jade! That'll be interesting...  Well, until next time! Oyasumi Nasai!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Alright    I'll be waiting... and I always believed that you shouldn't study the night before a test.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ohh myyyy baddd i just dun listen to the radio very often...and i never said "twiddle" was grammatically coorectt....:P i was just saying ive never heard of it..ne wayz instead of going on dis blogger shouldnt ub studying?? tsk tsk tsk..hey im gonna phone @ 6:30 or 7, is dat okie? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ohhhh....    That's not Spider-Man, it's the radio commercial for McDonalds! lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Of course...    It's like a message board!  This computer doesn't have Messenger so I can't go on it, but Spider-Man quote? *blinks*  I'm pretty sure "twiddle" is a grammatically correct word. And don't worry about stealing code... that's how I started learning HTML.  *evil grin*  Actually I think that's how most people start into HTML... unless they read a book about it.  Study early? *blinks* too late now...  -ArV  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       heys~ No worries Boo-chan im sure ull do fine ^-^ heys how come ur posting but u..u..dont go online? *sniff* and oh aout that comments thing, i think itz gonna b awhile till they let ne new members join...soooo im gonna phone kaz and ask him if he can help out ^-^ once i had it u can have one too, btw i hope u dun mind if i continue to take a few of ur stuff so i can get the same things ^^ but then again i dun feel very original...ur site IS cool! and watz wid quoting from spider man? lol...wat happened to austin powers? u should study early THEN sleep early...baka...btw i never knew there was such a word as "twidles" and r u alrit wid this being a way 4 us to communcate? hmm maybe is hould jsut use the phone....lol.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Japanese mid-term exam is tomorrow...    *sigh* and I'm nowhere near ready for it... -.-*   Parker you've got style, you've got Moxy!   Gee thanks Mr. Johnson!   And you've got one of those McDonald's Chicken Flatbreads! Let's have a look at that!   I believe, what we're all thinking is...  What's  Moxy ?   I'm so tired... I dont know why... I was like this all day... -.-* Maybe I should sleep early... But I have to study... this'll be a canundrum...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ah don't worry...    I  did  make a new template but only the old one showed up at the computer at school... Strangest thing...  I like this template... I'm wondering how much I can do to make it my own...  *sigh* That site with the comments thing is still not allowing people to sign up... *twiddles thumbs* I guess I'll have to wait. *sniff*  *blinks* Wow... I actually  did  sniff... must be the weather.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       u did change ur template...not unless ur template is no longer the latest one ive seen ^-^'' *eh heh and sorry if u dun like me posting here! btw! i stole ur sum stuff from ur template *snickers* and made my own "recomended links" sugoi! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Strangest thing...    I could have  sworn  that I changed my template... why is it the old one again?  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        ^-^ Sugoi!  Team thing-e worked!  Sugoi!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Watch! Seee "Ar Vs" g/f *snickers* i know all his secrets!! *laguhs evily* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I've noticed...    That the most common thing said on internet journals is   "It's been a long time since I updated."     It seems to fit this occassion... so... It's been a long time since I updated!  I added quiz results on left side... same results as Rei. *blinks*  Rei'chan-s coming on Wednesday! Sugoi!!!  On a lower note... I couldn't go snow tubing today... -.-*  On an even  lower  note, I have midterm exam on Saturday! Japonaise... *sigh*   meh  Wish me luck!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Foods and Shows     Ah, last night was International Night. Unfortunately, I was too busy running around the place the enjoy ^^;; ah well. Our pavilion (japanese) seemed to be quite ok, thought we cleared out of food very quickly, many times.    As for the show... besides the little timing problem we had, I think it was ok ^^;; need to get Trisha to send me the video clip *grins*   Don't feel like writing that much... did everyone else just give up on their blogs? And why is nobody online? (Actually there are many people, but still!)   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ugh.. Horrible day...    Had a TA interview... ugh...  Took a WHOLE HOUR... UGH...  He's making me drop my favourite subject!!!! UGGHHH -.-...  Backblog error? ugh...  Fellytone no work... UGH...  o.o... wait a minute... no...  Fellytone no work.... UGGGGGGGGGHHHHHHH...  *sigh*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Happy two-month...    Too bad my phone no work so I can't call you... :'(  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whoa, not many people posting ne thing up here........  *pretends she is Boo-chan*  Happy 2 month anniversary Rei-chan!!!!  *herself*  *flutters eye lashes* OH! ^-^ y thk u! same to u!  *coughs and get bak on track*   yes....yes.......i kno im weird.....  Hoshi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Books and more Snow     Ahh... either you guys are spending more time offline or I am. Or both.    Yesterday was interesting, went to Keane's house to practise some kendo.. it was a cheap imitation of the actual bamboo sword they use, plus we were just practising... but somehow I got slightly hurt ...*glares at von* ah well... pretty fun, even though we didn't get that much done.   Finish The Song of the Lionness quartet... I think I fell asleep while reading till very late... parents must've been wondering why the lights was still on in the morning... and why I was wearing my glasses... ^^;;    Course selection soon... I can't escape it, my dad is forcing me to take all 3 sciences even though the smart people at my school advise against it... --;; watch me fail and my parents blame it on my slackness.    Eheh, church was so empty today... must've been the snowstorm...   That's about all.. seems like I'm forgetting something.. ah, homework! Haven't done that in awhile.. must start soon... ja!   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Snowscapes and Starlight     I hope I did well in the Waterloo contest... I know my parents would really be disappointed if I didn't...*looks around* I'm quite sure I won't do as well as last year... *groans* last year I placed first and got 128....    On to more cheerful news, International Night is coming... origami and kendo practises are needed! Hopefully, we can try to not make a fools of ourselves on stage.   Yesterday I went from 8pm to 4am reading "Alanna: the First Adventure" and "Wind in the Door". Ehheh... ^^;; gomen hoshi-chan.. it was just that it was... so... interesting.   Ah... just went outside to get something (mailperson put an envelope for my sister in my neighbour's mailbox instead)... noticed how clear the stars are from where I am, even though there's still quite a bit of light pollution. The snow and the stars look really nice at night... heck, what other time are you supposed to see stars? ^^;; welll, let's all decide to try to catch up, if I ever get there... I'll try to pull you ahead with me keane... until then... I must prevent myself from drowning... gomen.. no position to help anyone...yet.   Ah... tomorrow is my  urlLink site's  first official anniversary. I used a different background just to celebrate it!    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Out of bandwidth...    I wont be able to go online much... or download much in the next week, as the title might imply what happened, I've exceeded my bandwidth limit...  Please, let me explain a little something about Sympatico (my ISP), the service I was given allows me to upload and download 10 GB roughly everymonth. Now, since it's  unlimited  Internet, they're not going to cut your internet off if you keep downloading, but they instead charge you  a lot  every Gigabyte you download/upload over the limit.  Ah, well, fine... I've downloaded too much CSI this month... heh... and I've been online a lot... but I can resist the computer for the next week or so! The next month starts on February 26th so it's not that long... just... seven... days away... -.-* ugh... I just hope my sister wont be Instant Messaging too much on MSN...     I know that for every character I type, I'll be uploading another byte, and downloading it at least twice... but I feel obliged to type what happened on Monday! Too bad I don't remember... -.-  But today... Ugh.. I decided that I should start working... TRYING TO CATCH UP. *tired, yet happy face*  *shrugs* I guess I should leave it at that! All you guys know my number if something important comes up.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Choices and Decisions     Let'see... main things that happened today... got TWO units done... (count 'em... TWO - cause for celebration *wastes rest of week* crap.. there goes all my hard work...)   Ehheh... hopefully that won't happen... but  anyways ... the second thing that was quite interesting that happened today was that the number of people helping out for the japanese pavilion just tripled...where did all these people come from? ^^;; More people... more PAWA....so oh well.   Well.. last thing was course selection... and do i have a lot to go through or what... ah well, the top 5 right now are: the 3 sciences, Computers, and Media Arts. Media Arts being the funnest.   Ah.. hafta go to library... Song of the Lionness awaits..^^;; and so does "The Swiftly Tilting Planet".     *Later that day*     I must be really messed up these days... when I got my shoes to go to the library... I picked up  dress  shoes... then i was like "what the heck am I doing?".. and just yesterday.. after taking a shower, it was cold and I wanted to wear a sweater... I wore a sweater and it wasn't till I went to bed that I found out I was wearing my school uniform sweater... I was like "wha...?" and no one seemed to notice either.. maybe we're all tired and messed.   Ah... did I say Swiftly Tilting Planet? I meant Wind in the Door...^^;; The second book in the series in any case...spent most of the night reading the first book of Song of the Lionness... really interesting so far. Seems like a hybrid of Mulan and Sword in the Stone.    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ugh...    I wrote a blog twice... They were good blogs too...   My blogs were deleted... twice... so... Tooo tired to write anodder... -.- ugh...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Concentration and Consequences     Ike.... I just found out today I lost the piano-flute music sheet I was supposed to practise... I'm going to ask for another one, and hope I don't get in too much trouble... -.-;;   Ah, and then I found out that "hey, I have to get all of History Day research done by this Friday and I barely started" and "ooo... I have 43 out of 80 units done... soon to be out of 88 if it isn't already..." and "my site is supposed to launch March 3rd and we're not close to being ready!!" and "omg... just noticed that my sister's and mom's bdays are coming soon, what the heck am I supposed to do?" and "I am so behind~! WAH!!" and "why am I talking to myself?" and "I tired and flooded..." and "mustn't procrastinate any longer..."   And so on.   Well, anyways, despite all that, let's continue: to keane - day's event eh? Are you going to put in the time where you cruelly got everyone worried about you? =.= ... to renae - ah... i see you got those comment thingies now, coolz... to vics - sounds like quite an eventful day... and how the heck can you concentrate on work?? I need that kind of concentration!   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I fixed it! ^-^      I fixed your site :P  Last time I asked if you wanted me to add the comment thingy you said you wanted to do it yourself  Why would you give up? I found a template that would be cool, it has fire!!! ^-^    Ah... g2g... will post day's events later...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *cries* me site dissapeared!!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *clears throat* Boo-chan...what happened to my site...you said ud fix it long time ago...*cries* *sniffles* guess u kno care....*cries* *heehee jkz jkz, dun hafta do ne thing...when the cable's bac ill just hafta try again...>.   Hoshi*  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Sugoi!    After yeeears of searching, (actually one boring Friday) I have suceeded in finding a site that'll let me store pictures for my blogger! For free (actually it's part of my ISP so technically my parents were already paying for it). Eh heh... ^-^  That means I have more room to customize my site and I can use images now!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ice and Quartets (but not necessarily in that order)     Ah... yesterday I finally got the first book of the Immortals (lucky for me it came in order... Wild Magic - I just finished reading...). Unfortunately, the quartets are all related to each other...  therefore ... i just spoiled the first quartet for myself... fun. Why didn't anyone tell me?? Ah well... *cancels all Immortal holds and places ones on Song of Lionness* excellent..done. Hopefully, they come in the right order..^^;;   Ah... skating was good today, the usual skating around in circles, and talking.   Sat school was pretty interesting too.. we had to split the class into two, and i went with the group that stuck with the assistant teacher. The assistant teacher was nice and let us do whatever. I practised self-defence with some people from my home school...^^;; got thrown to the ground a few times...eh...heh...ah, well, it was fun. Breaktime was fun too, ne?   ah, that's bout all...happy whatever-that's-coming-up-let's-just-say-international-night.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         confused and puzzled (confuzzled)     Yikes... did i really make those mistakes? Never again! At least not for this post.. ^^;;   Ah... Happy Valentines Day to everyone that celebrates! Ah... and my sister just arrived... that means.. no computer for me for awhile...^^;; I'm guessing she'll be wanting the computer a lot... ah well, need to cut back on net anyways.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Yunno...    Watching  Solitaire  throw cards with the R.O.D. theme playing in the background is strangely satisfying...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Keane... no know HTML?     hits self on head   I just put &#60;i&#62; instead of &#60;/i&#62; >.  hopes em wont hit me  eh heh...  -ArV  (After post...) Ugh... I just did it again... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Never stand...    ...infront of me when I cough...   looks at phlegm on floor I just coughed up...   ewwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Em... no know HTML?    Em... to close an italics tag you type  &#60;/i&#62;  not  &#60;i&#62; .  tsk tsk tsk... had to edit your post... *shakes head sadly*  Ugh... anyway... at home...  again . Got some rest... enough? Not sure...  Saw X episode 0. I liked that episode better than episode 24.  Playing with... sl&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;&#166;&#161;&#124;nky.  ^-^  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Reading and Writing     Today was an interesting day... for once, I actually did productive things for the entire day (kinda). First period, I went to play some piano... turns out I'm kinda rusty-ish...^^;; which is expected, but I guess I can improve with practise... plus never played duet before. Let'see... second period I spent studying for my science test... must've asked like 5 different people about the test, took the test in 3rd, and found out that people weren't lying when they said it was easy. Fourth and fifth I spent working on my Computer Engineering Course, FINALLY managed to get the stupid printer networked... that got us stumped for like an entire period yesterday.    Ah... I fear for my safety... TA interview tomorrow ... I'll try to get it postponed... ^^;;   After school, we had Anime Society, and as a Valentine special, we watched Karekano... I liked it, even though I usually hate storylines fully based on romance. It was definitely better than Boys Be, though one member of Anime Society disagrees...meh, hope we get back to Gundam Seed, Wolf's Rain, and Scryed. Now, I'm back home and ready to work some more... che sera sera... I won't worry too much bout my TA interview right now...^^;;   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Third day in a row...    ...that I'm stuck at home... -.-  Well, I saw the last episode of X last night... actually kind of disappointing. A few reviews I read said that manga was better, and the movie had a bad storyline... Maybe I could ask Maureen for the manga...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Being sick sucks...    I was stuck at home again... but I'll be going to the doctor soon... -.-* I think the appointment is at 4.30...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Planning and Toiling     Woot! Actually got ONE unit done today!! *feels special* eh heh... anyhows, hope you get better soon K-kun. You missed the japanese pavilion meeting *glares* ... we decided to use home-made shinais for sparring and put up 2 of the swords as display. Mrs.Small offered some bamboo... which is perfect. You couldn't find origami paper at Pacific Mall???? wtfruit??? I was informed by 2 different people that there IS origami paper there... *suspicious* methinks you spent your time elsewhere...   Anyhows... I will not verbally bash you much more...since you're sick...^^;; ahh... what else what else... oh, it's been strange lately... unexpected things happen... ah well   As I said... I WILL be working harder this month... and I suggest we all work hard! MUHAHAHA!! WORKWORKWORK!! *grumbles* wasted first 3 periods doing not much... *sigh* at least using 4th and 5th I was able to finish one unit.   That bout all? umm... guess so. Later! (btw, I got cut from badminton... woohoo! eh...heh...)   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ugh... Sick    Stayed at home... sick... sleeping... -.-*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Explanations...    Okay... it was birthday beats. I  had  to punch you! It's the law! *evil smile*  Also... the reason you have to use HTML Tags in my blog and not in yours is because I made it like that :P gomen, I prefer it that way.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Working and...Laughing??     Lighten up Hoshi-chan... ^^;;... you could consider the situation funny...^^;; ooo... take a look at this:  urlLink "Boo's Blog"..LOL  and  urlLink some pretty funny articles    Anyhows, I won't be on messenger on that often... at least not until I finish everything I need to finish... which...might...take... awhile... but meh! I'll be with you guys in spirit! Hopefully... if I disappear for like a month or two... you guys won't forget me...^^;; then again... it might be hard to get rid of me... I'll still go on messenger sometimes (Keane... if I'm on often... punch me... *GLARES* you seemed to have fun doing that today)    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *glares at keane*.....=-= u did NOT say ud b studying...u DID say ud b sleeping...SO i assumed! that that meant u would b home......*looks left, then right* i forgot u had school...ok?demmoooo u didnt mention it! *folds arms* u didnt say ne thing about studying..*gasps* how dare u lie...=P lol ooo well..*looks at time* *looks at messanger* *pouts* no one's online, and y should i put p's to make lines????   datz insanity! i dun hafta do that for my blog >P BTW EPS @$ IS DONE! *waves banner in air* ooo today wasnt the best of dayz..check out my blog to find out...:) ja   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Thoughts and Reflections     Let'see, yesterday was an interesting day... had a bday party! My bday is actually today... most people comment on how I can drive now... but for me, more importantly is the fact that I can take NLS (lifeguarding course) now ^^;;    Ahh... basically, everyone split up and did their own thing yesterday... ^^;; something tells me that's not exactly very party-ish, ehheh... so... i need you people to tell me what I could've done better. Here are some things I thought of already:     The host could've paid more attention to the guests        The party could've been more interesting        There should've been more planning    I'm sure there is much more to that list... but can't think of any right now.   Present-wise... welll, the best present I guess... is just having everyone there ^^;; Thanx to everyone for being there (and of course your pressies ^-~)!   Ahh... itz aite with me if you stay late... but my parents are probably less enthusiastic about it... ^^;; I guess that's bout it...   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Well use BR tags =P    If you put  br  or  p  in front of each line (inside of the triangle brackets of course) it'll make a new line or two.  Meh, can't stay long... late... Emerson's birthday party. Happy Birthday to you *looks at watch* Yep. And I said Happy Birthday to Von as her birthday was um... Sunday (today? yesterday?)   *looks around*  Actually I  did  sleep in, but I got to school in time anyhow. ^-^... and gomen ne... I didn't  exactly  forget I had school...  I remembered I had school, and I tried planning it so it'd be after school... Demo... I thought school ended half an hour earlier than it actually does. And... you can note that when you talked to me, I said "You can call when I'm studying, or sleeping." Now... I know in Canada, studying means you're at home... er... studying... but I guess I picked up the filipino inuendo that when you're at school, you say you're studying... ah... gomen ne...  OOOOHHhhh... Almost forgot... how could I forget... *bows to em* sooooo sooorry for staying sooooo late... *bows*  Well, g'night.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Yestereve and Present     Gomen... ^^;; not my fault our school (and my old school) has Activity Day). Eh heh... I know what you mean... I thought Keane "slept in" again this week, since I didn't see him in the morning. As for paragraphs... surely you know some HTML ne? Use open-caret - p - close-caret, carets being those triangly brackets above the comma and period.   Anyhows, yesterday was pretty fun, after duelling a bit, I went skating then came back home to play Warcraft (with Eric laughing at my n00bism).    And today... should be interesting... unfortunately I forgot to reconfirm with 4 people... ^^;; they better come anyways *glares*. Ah... a new low: 2 people on messenger out of 50-something?? wtfruit..? Ah wellll...   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *clears throat* ait Chronos...ur hurting me...>  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Shots and... Shots       Welll... today was an interesting day. It was no ordinary day... it was activity day (yay...)     It actually went pretty well, first, we went to Laser Quest. Being my first time there, I was confused. Well...not really. It was pretty straight-forward: shoot people with laser. On the first game, I placed 17 out of 23, then the second, I placed 10 out of 24. Eh heh, I'm just happy that I'm not last. A surprising thing is... i had a 90% hit-miss ratio... oo;; which means that for every 10 shots I took, I got nine... weird, cause I thought I missed more than that. It was a pretty fun experience ^^;;     After that, we went to Putting Edge for lunch (which was 2 slices of pizza and unlimited drinks), and played mini-golf... Keane remembers mini-golf, ne? ^^;; Out of the 4 people I played with, I scored the best... like 3 under par or something like that.      Ah... when we got back, I waited for half an hour for the Playdium people (and Keane) to come back... waited for like half an hour, and watched as the rock-climbing people and the skating people return... then I was like  meh  and left. When I got off at Finch, I saw the schoolbus carrying Playdium people back to school... what irony...^^;;     Ah well, good day altogether, hope you had fun today snow-tubing! (*glares* you  better  have had fun...)   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       um........ah.........waa happened to ur blogspot? it looks pretty messed up...*blinks* oooo snowtubing...we dun get previlages like dat...... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ugh... Snowtubing...    Today is a break day for me... well, it's supposed to be an exam day where you only go to school if you have an exam or a test. I dont have any tests to do, and my exam... well, I'll take the late exam. -.-*  According to the VP those who don't have tests or exams should go home and make sure they're on track. HA! Like that'll ever happen. I was invited to the movies, but I doubt I'll be allowed to go out three times in one week...  Ah yes, Sunday is Emerson's birthday party! (#1) That'll be fun! *puts on glasses and smiles evilly* Or will it?  So, on Saturday I will be going with Von and Rei to mall to get gift! (#2) That still hasn't been planned properly yet... And there'll have to be some stuff bought for international night...  *goes back one step* Yes, so you see why if I went out with friends today, it'd be three times this week. Meh... at least I get to stay home and... *blinks* Vacuum??? *sigh* lol  I'll watch X! ^-^ I might be able to finish the series... and if Angelfire is friendly today I might be able to upload episode 23 for Maureen.  Well, off to finish vacuuming! Ja ne!  -ArV    Changed the links on the left side so that they'll open in a new window.  Thinking of playing with the colours... White seems very bright, either that or my eyes are extra sensitivte today...  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *blinks* 8 straight?!?! LUCKY U? were washroom break involved......? ^-~ ne wayz i think u should catch up on rest on ur day off, ashiteru Boo-chan, make SURE the next time im talking to u on the phone that ur not half dead for exhuastion......  um...i only..have..eps...24....to watch  the manga is like......so MUCH more detailed!!!!!!! er.....Arashi and Sorata have a so much better relationship! like the plot builds up SO much better...plz.....sum1 tell me WHY the confined the beauty of X/1999 into 24 eps.....?  argh....u.u things seems to b brining me down more....i must....get up....*climbs* ooooo u wont let me get down! noo school u wont! noo not time away from boo u wont!   *thinks* *rocks bac and forth* itz almost the weekened...itz almost the weekend...  *stomach grumbles* er.........  Hoshi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Four hours... Ugh    I just watched 8 straight episodes of X/1999.  It's fun to watch.. but I think that'll be all for tonight. I knows my limit!!! Well, kind of...  So tired...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Rain and War     oooo.... a Goban! I hope your sisters are good Go players... ^^;; Anyhows, I got beaten fairly badly at badminton today... lost 13-0 ^^;; (Joe!! You shall pay!!), didn't feel tired out until later...    I'm probably going to stay off messenger for this week... since my dad has been getting angrier and angrier each time he sees me on messenger... need...to...change...skin... of ... messenger... to...disguise... oh, and just found out that hoshi-chan would be off messenger for this week too... interesting coincidence... it's supposed to be some sort of test of self-discipline for her... ^^;;    I went to the library today... first time in a long time... had to, cause History Day Consultation #2 calls for internet AND book AND newspaper/magazine.... yeesh... these teacher nowadays want so much... *shakes head* ah well, borrowed some interesting books: like  The Art of War  and other war strategy books. On the way back, it was raining freezing rain... slippery for cars... hopefully there won't be any accidents.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         *Wipes Sweat off Brow*    I got them back... phew... Even though I'm not playing at my best today... Guess I'm still tired for some reason... >.  Oh, and my sister got me a Goban... well not really... it's 9x9... it's Green, Hard Plastic and it folds in half... I think it's used... there are no pieces though mine should fit. It would be difficult to place stones on the edges though because they are raised...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Aw this sucks...    I was playing Hikaru No Go GBA ROM and I actually won! And I got extra stuff! (A Hikaru plushie on the bed, and a poster on the door) but I accidentally pressed F1 and it loaded a previously saved game and deleted all my scores... *sigh*  meh   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Now all I need to do is watch them...    X has finished downloading!!! So has CSI 1x01!  ^-^ Sugoi!   Maybe I should watch them later though... damn dirty dishes...   Oh yah.. and I want to check how much I downloaded this month but I can't find my phone number and password sheet... -.-U *sigh*   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Floods and Fires     Let's start with the flood first, flood of events that is: chinese new year, bday, international night, art show, school units, volunteer (x2), website, book editing, badminton, and hopefully anime con. I know it's not much, but still!! (I'll explain some of them in depth later if I feel like it afterwards, MUHAHAHA!!! COMPLETE PAWA!!!)   Now the fire, some idiot tried to set my sister's building on fire... *mutters* these 3vil p3opl3...and unfortunately, there had been so many bluffs with the fire alarm, most people living in that residence thought it was another one. Luckily, my sister and some other girl found out there was a real fire, and warned everyone in time. *sigh* some people have too much time on their hands, either that... or..or... something...   ONLY 91%??!! Are you mocking me? That's what I got!! But then again, I was like "only 91%" too... ^^;; ... Ah yes, the space shuttle incident...I first heard of it - not on the news - but on  urlLink Megatokyo    Oh, and hope you and hoshi had fun today ^-~   Ok, I don't really feel like explaining those things in the first paragraph, ask me if you're interested... back to work I go...   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Report Card!!!    We got our report cards in Japanese class today!  I only got 91% -.-*  On a related note, I thought I came late today... turns out I was half an hour early...eh heh...  Unfortunately, today is a day of mourning in the USA. The space shuttle Columbia blew up over Texas. Seven astronauts died. My prayers go to them.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         IRAQ and QARI     Let'see, first Iraq...you guys MUST read Linwood Barclay's columns in Toronto Star... he's an amazing columnist, lol, I don't get Toronto Star anymore, but my sister came home for the weekend, and she brought Thursday and Friday's newspaper with her... Anyways, he was saying how since American businessmen were afraid of stocks going down of the war, and how this Iraqi was saying how that is a concern, and plans to become defeated as quickly as possible to protect their portfolios... then offhandedly mentions "oh look, there goes my living room". Then Linwood ends off saying "glad to know that there are people halfway around the world who care about us".   Oh... i also heard there's a bunch of civilian casualities so far, and that the war is going to go on for quite a while. Well, as long as it doesn't hurt the economy, ne?   As the war goes on, we have our own problem to deal with... QARI! Quite Acute Respiratory Illness is spreading around and killing and infecting and such... half our Saturday class decided to be absent either   a) their parents were afraid of QARI hurting them, and wanted to keep them home b) an excuse to skip   oh ... that reminds me... it's actually SARS for those that have been hibernating. I just thought that QARI would make a more fitting name   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ugh This Sucks...    I  knew  I should've just posted... I tried to make a comment for Renae's last post but it was too long and it didn't post. -.-*  Let me see if I can paraphrase it here...  Not all wars are stupid. There are just reasons to go to war. They were given to us by St. Augustin, a Christian philospher.  ~There has to be a just reason to go to war. (Defending oneself, or an ally. Preserving the peace)  ~The war has to be approved of by a lawfull authority. (The only lawful authority that has control in multiple nations is the UN)  ~The war must be for the betterment of mankind. (ie. Taking out Hitler so he doesn't cause more pain, suffering, useless deaths. Or the American Revolution which liberated the USA from England gave birth to democracy)  Although Mr. Bush would like us to believe otherwise, this war isn't a just war. The reasons for his war are oil. And no matter what he tells the U.N. or the rest of the world, that always was and always will be his reason.  As for us paying attention to the war. The reason we watch the war so closely is because  we  may be pulled into the war at any time. Someone may attack Continental USA, which we are so close to. Other countries may decide to join the war and soon may escalate to the third World War. The UN might decide to allow this war and Canada would go to war.  Either either, this war may affect us and change our lives at any time. That's why people pay so much attention to it!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *stomps foot on ground* All I hear about everywhere is this "WAR". Yes, I beliebe we are all aware of it....demo, wat can WE do? All these poloticians and leaders and coporations in charge of OUR lives, well well, then wat can we do? Sure Sure...let's make it our daily subject *mumbles* Ah, but i do see the seriousness in this...but let's just face the facts, we're not a part of this game. Meh, I dunno, im just going along like i normally do, i got one thing to say tho: STUPID! STUPID! STUPID! THIS WAR IS STUPID! SO IS  NE WAR  THAT TAKES PLACE *breaths* ja! ^-^ 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         2 Units a day? Anime!     I am very close to my goal of 2 units a day. If I keep to this pace, I can dig myself out of this hole, ^^   Anyways, today, we had Anime... saw Slayers. Kinda interesting, but the plot was so similar to many other plots.  Indeed... war on iraq has started... changes will appear, for better of for worse.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Stayed Home...    I was too tired to go to school today...  News says USA started attack on Iraq.  God save us all.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A Stitch In Death    Broke a cup... Cut my hand... Went to Hospital... Got stitches... Can't type properly... G'night...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Owwie...    *squishes face together* my tummy huyts...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         *Pout*    It didn't show up...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Cold, Wet, and Dirty...    Okay... so I'm not wet... but It's kinda cold...  I woke up and my grandmother wanted me to go with her to a Church downtown... I weasled out of it by promising to go to one on Saturday...  I'm sorry... but I don't like being asked to go somewhere the moment I wake up... especially if they tell me to be ready within the next 30 minutes...  Rei-chan was ova yesterday! ^-^ Almost beat Sonic the hedgehog together... stupid Metropolis crabs... grr...  Uhhhmmmm.... I'm really posting this because I want to see if my blog will show up as one of the ten most recently updated blogs on blogger.com! If it does I'll upload a screenshot.  Demo... what happened to my comment thing-e? Why it gone? *sigh* Meh...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Volunteering and Boredom     Firstly, I got the results for the rest of the people that went to the tournament: Clarence won the tournament, Philip got beaten second round by an Exodia-deck user (Clarence beat that guy 3rd round), and Daniel got knocked out in some round. Eric got what he came for... the only card he needed and wanted...finally found someone willing to sell.   Went to the daycare at 9:00am today, unexpectedly stayed till 2:00pm. Mostly just hung around watching how things are done. The kids had free time, went outside, played some games, sang some songs, and then half went tobogganning and half stayed for archery. I went with the tobogganning group since the park is near my house, and it was nearing 2:00pm. Pretty interesting, I actually talked more to the other counsellors than I did last year. Though still not much.    Came back home and wasted the rest of the day, need to finish unit before I sleep though. I finished one math unit yesterday... yay for me ^^;;    Ah... will volunteer 9 - 2 again tomorrow, then I'll have my 10 hours from the daycare. My total is 31 hours and counting ^^b   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Blood and Duels     The weekend was fairly eventful... some of the things that happened was the dentist got my mouth all bloody, went to some restaurant for my mom's birthday, some friends came over to duel and prepare for todays tournament. Also, I was practising "First Love" on the piano a bit. It's a simplified version... doesn't sound as good as the actual song. Oh well.   Anyways, today was interesting. I lost first round. So far, I know how two of my other friends did. Aaron got knocked second round by Eric. Eric got knocked 3rd round by the same guy that beat me. Clarence made it to the finals, but don't know if he won.   Umm... as for going on Thursday, I think that I'll probably be able to go. Probably as in not 100% sure yet... my parents can change their mind very easily... oh, that reminds me. I'll probably be off messenger for the rest of the month.    Ahh... just came back home from volunteering for Spelling Bee. Quite interesting. Not that bad.    If you're wondering why I'm typing in short sentences, it's cause I'm annoyed. I'm just annoyed cause there are annoying people in the house, who can't seem to quiet down. Since there hasn't been any visitors today, and my sister is at university, I'm sure you guys are smart enough to use the process of elimination. From now on, I'll have to rely on the phone as my main source of communication. Ja   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Three Units a Day???    I'll seriously try my best... and I'll even try to finish e-v-e-r-y unit I brought home for March Break, but frankly Joe... you're cwazeeeee....  Ugh... Joe's Blogger wont let him update his Template for some reason, and although I was originally going to change my template, I guess that can wait for another time...  Umm... I can't really think of much more to put... *thinks* *shrugs* If I think of anything I'll come back...  when I have time ... -.-*  Oh yah... You're not supposed to eat meat on Ash Wednesday... or on Friday's of lent... I had hotdogs on Wednesday... and Chicken today... does fowl count as meat?  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Ashes to Ashes     Our T.A. rep handled the ceremony for us. She didn't go to the training. She went giggly tracing ashes over people's forehead. oo;; ah wellll... let'see, this OAC was talking about the pointlessness of all this.. the ceremony.. the church.. personally i agreed that all the ceremonies and symbols were pointless... but it didn't seem right to voice it out in a catholic school ^^;;   Hotdogs are good... what have you against hotdogs? oo;; i got sandwich for lunch... and 2 boxes of juice... now there's a surprise... ^^;; eh..heh...   Finished reading the Immortals series... if only I have such dedication to my schoolwork as I do to the quartets...^^;;   There are other things, but oh well, don't feel like typing anymore   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         It's Ash Wednesday...    And my dad gave me hotdogs for lunch... o.oU  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Joe and I were playing    ...punch for punch again... and OW does my hand hurt...  And today's the official opening of NandaPanda Website! Though we don't really have anything up right now... and Emerson doesn't want me to do website work for the next three months... >.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ....y would u two need to share the same room? *glares* *coughs* ne wayz, welcome joe! demo, this is Boo-chan's blog, so i dunno if it's right for me to say "welcome" ne wayz...u guys' blog is ten times better than mine,  specially cause it's never updated u.u...oh well, wat can u do? i have a feeling this is going to be a slowwwww dayyy ahh! gomen nasai Boo-chan for keeping u up so late! >. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Stressful Day    I woke up late for Saturday school... I forgot a letter I was supposed to bring for Stanley to his teacher.  I called my parents, so they said that they'd bring it at 11.30... they were 15 minutes late...  Kyle came with us to Parkway Mall... I told him he couldn't come... he came anyway...  Emerson was there too... We left after class, but not before meeting Lynn and Renae at OCS.  ====notfinished====  Ugh... too tired to finish this tonight... maybe tomorrow...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Well well well...true, I must admit that...But wouldn't things be so much more enjoyable if Keane & I were to share the same room? (Not implying bed, Hoshi-chan.) I'm just posting this as I sit, munching, on Viet food, spring rolls, noodles, and fried rice @ a comp in my cousin/best girl-friend's house. (Note that this friend is a girl.) .......    *24 minutes later*    ....sorry just came back..left the post unfinished, strangest thing is, I was here tonight to mourn the 49 days after the passing of my best friend's grandmother's death.    We were praying, and I had my head down. When I raised my head to look at the picture of the deceased, I started to have a uncontrollable nosebleed. Strange enough, the bleeding subsided after the prayers were done, approximately 15 minutes later...I don't think I'll have good luck for another year or so....cia0....^_^ 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         OooOoo...    Now Joe can post onto my blog, and I onto his. ^-^  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         No More Comments!    Today's events.   Went on trip downtown.  Fun.  Tiring.    Today's blog events.   Removed comments.  Added a sort of message board.    Reason? The comments thingies seemed liked message boards in themselves.  Ja!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Jumbled Thoughts     The weekend didn't go too well, was feeling kinda mentally tired ( nothing  to do with sleep.. I had plenty of that). I could probably waste blog space by typing what went wrong with the weekends.. but I don't even remember anymore, so I'm not going to try.    Anyways, tomorrow is a civics trip.. missing one day to work, this better be good. The previous civics presentation we attended was surprisingly good. Some guy (i think his name was Mark Ford - can't remember too well) came in and sang/played guitar/played piano. The presentation was really good. He was funny and weird.. which is of course a good thing.    Right now, I'm listening to  "Shout it Loud"  from King of Bandits Jing.. I heard that KoBJ animation gets even better as it goes on.. (I won't believe it till I see it, as the animation I saw was already really nice).. but the plotline isn't too well cause the writer got fired in the middle of the series.    Lastly, I added a little special effect thingy to  urlLink my site . Have fun (but don't keep checking out the effect as it'd probably eats up bandwidth).   Yup, short blog entry, but oh well.   ~Chronos    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Invictus     Let'see ... 2 AM in morning still working on narrative poem for english *sees hoshi and keane angry* *ducks away* eh heh... i guess this isn't a good idea to tell you guys that i've been staying up late all week, ne? ^^;; keane might've guessed, since i was kinda tired at school  =P    Anyways, to the point. After doing this poetry unit.. i was reminded of the poetry project from last year (It's one of the very few assignments I kept from last year). We had to create some poems, draw a comic for a narrative poem, analyse some poems given, and choose any poem to analyse. It was an interesting project, especially that last part where you get to choose any poems. Stuck for a good poem, I borrowed my sister's little book of poems she copied down (a bunch of good poems to remember). There, I was wondering whether I should choose  "The Arrow and the Song"  or  "Invictus" .  "Invictus"  won... though the other is still a good poem.    For those of you that are too lazy to go and search for this really nice poem called  "Invictus" :    Out of the night that covers me,     Black as the pit from pole to pole,  I thank whatever gods may be     For my unconquerable soul.   In the fell clutch of circumstance     I have not winced nor cried aloud.  Under the bludgeonings of chance     My head is bloody, but unbowed.   Beyond this place of wrath and tears     Looms but the Horror of the shade,  And yet the menace of the years     Finds, and shall find, me unafraid.   It matters not how strait the gate,     How charged with punishments the scroll,  I am the master of my fate:     I am the captain of my soul.     Powerful, ne? The class liked it too ^^;;    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         No bunnies though...     urlLink Em wore this shirt at anime con!   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Looky Loo!    I made it to the most recent Updated Blogs list!  urlLink Here!   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         If I died right now, I wouldn't really care.    I know, that by writing this, I'll be setting up a little regret train for my near/near to near future self. I'll be like, yah... I guess I shouldn't have written that. But right now, I'm just miserable. And that's how I feel. And really, that's what this blogger was made for, expressing my emotions to the events that life throws at me, so ya, I just thought I'd write that down. Feel free not to comment, feel free to comment. Feel free to do whatever, just don't bring this up in future conversations trying to encourage me, because by then I'd probably be fine. It'll probably pass. Wow, even when I'm lugubrious I'm sickeningly optimistic. *sigh*  Meh .  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hoshi says: well well...today is Easter...(if im not mistaken) for some reason the word, Easter always makes me think of an egg? *scoffs* when it's supposed to make me think of Jesus....ehhhhhh.......well I'm sure many people r going to church today (unlike me) and now im just sulking over the fact that i didn't finish chap 9 of my story. *sigh* . Jade-chan's gonna b mad......(i wonder y im not posting this on  my  blog) oh well...i can try to finish it today when i go out..im sure im going to b bored ne wayz. (2 family meetings...yeesh!) well hafnt seen my cous in a while, wonder how she is now. *points to everyone who reads this* i wanna kno how UR weekend (Easter) was ^-^ soooooo people post when u get the chance (can u tell how bored i am yet?) ah......*notices this whole blog is a waste of Boo-chan's space* NeWaYz ashiteru Boo-chan, (if u read this) and happy easter to ya'll.....Astrid*signs off.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Chess and Go     Ahhh... it's been awhile since I have played either of those games ^^;; for like the past month or two... my lunchtimes were taken up by:     International Night - Japanese Pavilion         Organizing and Judging for some Duel Monsters Tournament         Playing Duel Monsters         Taking tests   So tonight, I decided to play one game of each to see if I still know how to play ^^;; wellll... i won both of the games ( *cough  faced lower-rank people  cough* ) but oh welllll... I just wanted to see if I could still play ^^ maybe i'll spend the lunchtimes of this week in the chess room... who knows...   Ahh... didn't get much done tonight, which sucks, but tomorrow my Focus group is meeting, so i'll  have  to work.    Yesterday was fun, even though we didn't get to watch the second part of Sen To Chihiro (Spirited Away - which btw won an Oscar... ph34r anime and itz l33t skillz!!), hoshi-chan came over to ward, so I spent that time talking to keane and her... though  of course  I let them have a little alone time ne? *3vil l4ff*    Next week, I'll have to be checking in with another TA... my TA's off to Europe for a week and a half, along with a heck of a lot of other music students... I hear they're going to Germany and Austria and... *sees Hoshi getting mad* eh heh heh heh...    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eiko-chan, no offense but i have like over 30 students cramed into one portable.....not to mention of drama room is pretty hot and the sun aim right there......so >P>P>P  ^-^ ne wayz, hope u guys had a nice day cause.....i heard that on thurs it's going to me freezing rain!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHH *weeps* well....u.u'' some reason im not surprised.....HosHi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Heat and Codes     Wow... today was  burning ... during 4th period - computer engineering class, in addition to the heat and humidity, it was a pretty small room with like 30 computers running. Heat + Humidity + Small Room + Mass Computers = Death thru Dehydration. Not to mention I had to run like 100m to reach the busstop in time (I didn't mind  that  that much, since I like running).    Yesterday wasn't that good... some guy in my computer engineering group said he lost 1 hour worth of assignments (luckily he found it again today). I got a bit angry and went to Social Science to cool off a bit ^^;; that worked... actually got some work done too.   Ah... now back to working on Computer Science... stupid Watcom Basic --;; ah well, almost done this unit ^^;;   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Sad thing is, it scared me more than most movies I've seen...    The comment thingies are bac, and when I looked at my page I saw the first three posts with 0 comments! I was like.  OMG WHERE'D THEY GO?   But then I realised that those were posts made during the time that  BackBlog  was down. *phew*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         No Comment    Comments aren't working for some reason. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *looks around* okies....i wasnt going to post again like this....(sorry Boo for taking up so much of ur blog space :P) demo.....the comment thingies are gone!! O.O ...ne wayz......for now ill just say this: is it just me......or does Boo sound like a news reporter.............LOL WAR What is it good for? seriously Boo, u can definitly get a career as a journalist......*sees her own job opportunity fly out the window* ohh well....ja! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *cloud of smoke appears* *fire-haired young woman steps out* That's me, btw. Ne wayz, *grins* I, being so manipulative as I am. Was able to make Boo-chan do at least  one  thing of his work. *claps* ill continue to do that. ^_^ NEWAYZ. for now.......KEANE!!!!!! I'm MAD at you!  >, last  one to post.. on the comments section?? *scrolls down* Hoshi Hoshi Hoshi Hoshi Hoshi Hoshi.............o.O Even on my own sitE! yeesh! lol! well ne wayz ^^ i hope today will b a good day, who knows wat's planned! :D sayooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo! *hugz ne one who reads this and gives and extra tight one to Boo*  Hoshi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Blast From the Past    This blog post should have appeared on April 9 2003.  I hate it when I type something and it just goes poof. >. edit your blog  screen,  none of them are mine!  Argh. Well, I'll try to rewrite what I wrote earlier (the keyboard fell and the whole entry dissintegrated into white pixels) and I hope I wont forget anything. Grr... First off, if you don't want to hear about the War on Iraq, skip the next paragraph. In this entry I'll also try to talk about my school work, the ice storm, last Thursday, and I'll let you guys in on what I plan to do with this blogger! But most chances are I wont be done until mid-summer. Then of course, by then I'll be editing NandaPanda for its second release.   WAR What is it good for? - Absolutely nothing! Well you'll have to tell that to the people of Baghdad. Today the people of Baghdad finally got a chance to breath! The bombs stopped flying but were instead replaced with pictures and statues of Sadam Heussain as Iraqi citizens tore them from their stands and frames as their chance to say " Good bye! We wont miss you! " to their apparently former dictator. Heussain himself is rumoured to be dead, but proof of this claim has yet to surface. Although, the lack of Imperial Guards defending Iraq's capital might be of some pursuasion in this topic. That's right, the Americans didn't have to fight the army to claim Iraq. Although there were some "amateur" attackers, there has been, in the words of an American Soldier, "No organisation, no organized army."   SCHOOOOL's out, for SummeR! - Actually, not yet. BUT sOOn!!! And I'm not ready!!! >.   It's Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas... - That's if, they celebrate Christmas in a frozen over Hell! An ice storm hit Lower Ontario and parts of the US of A. Freezing Rain, Snow, Hail, all through Thursday and Friday night. I didn't go to Saturday Class because the Ice froze my van to the drive way. Though, that didn't stop me from going to Anime Society... actually, it kinda started  while  I was at anime society... Speaking of Anime Society...   Ani-Me-Ay! It's a Hell of A Town! (sung to the tune of New York New York - kind of a stretch... but it's late at night and I'm out of ideas. -.-) - Rei-chan came to anime society! Argh... but we had to walk to my house in  h.a.i.l  though... ARGH.  Rei-chan came to visit and we all went to Anime! Shu-kun took some time out of his dueling to hang with us, but afterwards when it was time to go, we noticed the hail. o.oU About this time, Hanna, Janice, and Trisha came back from their trip to the movies so Emerson stayed behind with them so he could take the same bus while Renae and I left to take the McNicoll bus.   We waited for almost half an hour. In hail .  The Kennedy bus came, so I told Renae it'd probably be better to catch that bus. When we got on it, Emerson, Hanna, Janice and Trish were on it! Mostly everyone got off at Finch, but only Renae and I went East. From Finch we walked to my house.  In hail . -.- Argh.  Argh, I have to go. Just one more thing and then I'll leave. For this site, I plan to change it, to coincide with a song. What do you guys think? I'm thinking  Ask DNA  but other songs can do too, like the RahXephon song, or even Sakura Saku... though that'd be hard without pink. *sigh*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         What if...?     Today, I made some pretty good progress in work. Two units almost complete (just needs some group work parts), almost done my english essay outline, and will complete history essay notetaking. I might go and do some computer science, or religion later too. Manage to play half an hour of b-ball and half an hour of piano too =P    At times like this, you sometimes wonder: "What if I worked harder at the beginning? I was so stupid! *slaps head* Why did I waste so much time?" Luckily, those kinda thoughts don't come often, and I try to get them out of my head asap, before I waste more time wallowing in self-pity. ^^;; The only thing to do, really, is just look forward and do the damn work already.    Looks like I could probably make it... I have around 65 units left, not counting exams and "free" units. That's down from 75 units last week... I think it's cause I forgot to count some "free" units, but whatever. All I know is that summer school and carryover are not options... my dad was pretty clear that he did not think much of those. And taking that into account, he would probably kill me if i  did  take those options. yay.   S'all for now, ja!   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Missing: One Post    Actually, it's not missing... I know where it is... but that computer's not on right now, and it's not hooked up.  I wrote a loooong post and it's not even done yet... Since it's not done yet, I couldn't post it, so I just saved it on the hard drive two days ago. It might take a while for that to come back.  I have 50(?) units to do in 59(?) days. I'm not sure... Emerson counted for me, it could either be 50 and 59 or 40 and 49. Most likely the latter. I'm not feeling well today... I'll try to put up that post ASAP.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Bad luck? Oh well ^^;;     Let'see, so far this year, I lost a science textbook and a math textbook, fun. I only lost my math textbook only recently... who knows how much those textbooks cost altogether? Like 100? *sigh* Not only that, I lost my science unit 5... I spend like most of my working time during Christmas on that. (welll... that's not much, considering I didn't work much during Christmas, but still!) At this point, breaking down seems like a tempting thing to do... but nah. lol,  "Don't Be Discouraged" ... *plays song thru head*    Aaaanyways, it was really weird today. I went to the math area during second, just to take out some units, then the person there was asking "math contest?", and i was like "oO" and I somehow got dragged in and started doing the math contest thingy. Later, I found that it was on the announcements, which I don't pay attentiont to XP ah well... I guess that wasn't SO bad... since I didn't really have anything planned for that period.    Back to  "drowning for my life" , lol ^^;;   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         On my head the axe soon falls, closing 'round me are spiked walls     Umm... the title pretty much sums up how I'm feeling right now ^^;; basically, I have to finish at  least  2 units a day. Welll, I've reached about that much tonight, but I'm not satisfied yet. I plan on finishing 4 ^^;; And it's probably possible. Haven't shown my report card to my parents yet... all I know is that the all the yelling and lecturing will take up too much of my precious time, so I'll show it to them as late as possible, lol ^^;;   Anyways, felt like taking a break.. so now here I am... seems like it'll be a pretty rushed rush to the end. ah well, i look forward to it *grins* the only thing I'm worried about is that my parents might transfer me back ... that would really suck. Sooooo... back to work for me.    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Small Break and Protector of the Small     Yup, a small break for me today, as there is no school. I really  shouldn't  be taking a break *stares at mountain of units* but meh... I've decided to cut of MSN (for like the  n  th  time this year), and so far I'm succeeding. Really... need... to... chat.... *dumps cold water on head* much better ^^    I spent most of today finishing off the 3 rd  book for the Protector of the Small quartet. I've already burnt through 3 other quartets: Song of the Lionness, the Immortals, and Circle of Magic. I really liked the Circle of Magic quartet, though it starts off a different storyline. Song of the Lionness -> the Immortals -> Protector of the Small quartets all follow the same storyline. Yup, that's  12   books on Tortall, get reading Hoshi XP  As for the second set of books, Circle of Magic -> The Circle Opens quartets seem to be interesting so far, though i haven't even  touched  The Circle Opens quartet. Yes, and as the name suggests, quartet = 4 books.   Yesterday was really interesting, hoshi came to visit, and keane was actually allowed to stay. Ana-sama told us to work on the art show... but didn't really enforce that. So i was like "meh"... just was hung around with them. It was raining outside... like... hail... and i decided to leave around 5:30pm. Twish, Janice, Hanna and Kristina came back from somewhere... and since we were going the same way, i decided to wait a bit with Parry. Then keane and hoshi left. Then finally we left, and waited like forever. Luckily I had an umbrella... ph34r d4 umb3l4! Still though... when i got home my hands were like freezing... --;;   That's all for now, ja!   ~ Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i took the day off! *waves banner* ^-^ altho i didnt get to sleep in :( oh well..ja!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         *blink**blink blink*     It's been a weird day. Justin came over to work on science, we managed to get that done. but then I also have to get history and math units done. I still need to do a paragraph for history then work on math. I need to finish all this tonight for sure.    It's so weird.. lot'sa things are going wrong.. one of the worse things that could happen was someone losing all their units at this critical time of the year. I hope someone finds Joe's bag soon. At this point, I really couldn't care less if the person who took it got away free, even though Joe might take comfort in tearing that person apart. Justin's kinda mad too cause our (joe, me, him, brian) science lab was in there too.    Umm... everyone seems to be annoyed/mad at me today... maybe I'm doing something wrong..?    ~Chronos   ps despite all this, i hope everyone keeps a cheerful outlook ^^;; 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         9 Days    ...to hand in units and do tests.  16 units left.  Fun.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I had a dream     ok ok ... i typed out so much last time, and now i have to re-type --;; *sigh* no...fair... but since i haven't remembered any dreams in a longish time, i'll persevere and re-type this.. even tho i have many other stuff to do ^^;;   Some things might have happened before, but then i don't remember.. it was night, and my religion group for the religion retreat thingy, and a crush i had a few years ago (i forget who it was) were in a car. Then we were talking about stuff, and the subject went to dating. Some girl in my group - which i didn't really like - was asking me if i wanted to date her (wouldn't ever happen in real life, but meh), and i was saying that i wanted to have my first date special, or something like that. She seemed insulted, and i tried to apologize. And then i was saying that it wasn't really my first date, as i went on a "mock date" with that girl i used to like. And they were surprised - in a bad way for me ^^;;   Anyways, we eventually came to this really, really big school. We all went through a metal detector. I was in a classroom, and was talking to joe's crush. Then, I went through the school looking for joe, and eventually found him. I brought him to the room that she was in, and thought for a sec that he wouldn't want to go (was thinking real-life-ly). Anyways, i brought her to joe - since she was just standing/sitting (forget which) there. She seem apologetic (probably because of previously). Both of them seemed happy, so i was kinda happy for them ^^   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Afterwards, we were outside trying to get to the schoolbus at the exit. We were on a narrow mountain path - not steep - and some guy raced past me saying something like "I now beat you in everything!" (something similar to that). I found that it was someone from my first school - st.john fisher - named michael mele. Anyways, we kinda raced to the bus, and found that it was at the bottom - while we were still high on the mountain path. There was a mountainside on the opposite side, so it was like "\_/" where the bus was at the bottom, and we were at the top left hand side. He slid down, but when he go to the bottom, he tripped and fell. I think i was like grinning, and he said something similar to "why don't you try and come down?" I wanted to, but for some reason i didn't. A bunch of people were sliding down the hill, and one of them - perhaps sliding too fast (on the left side) - went up the opposite side (the right side), and then went thru the air back to the original side (left side) and slid back down. So it was like a loop-de-loop. Which is weird and impossible in real life. There may have been more, but that's all i remember. Exeunt Emerson.   So.. it was an interesting dream which i didn't really find any meaning to, but never-the-less an interesting dream.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Tour de Force     Last weekend, I managed to finish 8 units of work, and I'm hoping to do so again this weekend, even though there's only 2 days compared to 3 days last week --;;   Yesterday, Renae and Aiza came... yay ^^;;    Today, we had to finish off our Focus projects and do the Focus test. I don't think I did well on that test.   Anyways, that'll be all... cause i don't feel like writing too much.    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Final Dash to the End!     Ok, first off, some bad news: my mom just told me today that if I don't finish my courses I'll have to transfer back ^^;;   Now that that's over, let'see.. I hope you guys had fun at the con! Tell me what you guys did there! I am curious ^^;; ahh.. today, I managed to finish 2 math units.. good, but not good enough.. i need to arrange for myself to finish some english units before this night (or morning - watever) is done. Hopefully my parents don't suddenly wake out of nowhere - they have a habit of doing that - and yell at me to go to sleep.   Umm.. lot'sa people saw Matrix: Reloaded today... i want to see too :'( demo.. i guess i'll have to wait to summer ^^ I rewatched the original Matrix last night...I plan on using it for some assignment thingy.   Ah.. i think i really need to disappear off the face of the earth for 3 weeks to concentrate my full energy on the task at hand. The consequences for failing is too much to imagine... I rather not waste time thinking about it.   Umm.. on a cheery note, *thinks* um... well.. it's summer soon? ehhehhehehheh    kkkkkeeeeeeaaaaaannnnnneeeeeee... talk to me will ya?    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I'm getting sleepy... very sleepy...    When I ring this bell, you will have worked as hard as you can until you fall asleep at night...  When I snap my fingers, you will watch Hoshi's soccer game in the rain before visiting the art show.  Then when you hear the keywords, "today is Saturday," you will go to the anime convention and meet many people.  Now, when I clap my hands you will wake up and remember none of this.  *claps hands*  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Yesterday was a Mystery, Tomorrow is History...     Yesterday, the Focus/Tech students went to Wonderland to do stuff. Dunno what the tech students needed to do, but us Focus people had to test out the accelerometers we've built. I never been to Wonderland, nor have I been on a roller-coaster.. so yah, it was pretty good experience ^^;;   We went on  the Fly  to test out our accelerometers.. it was slow enough, so it was pretty easy to test out everything. I was with my Focus group for that amount of time. After we went on that ride for like 6 times, and got all the data we needed, we split up. I went with Philip for awhile, then went wandering off. Eventually, I found Joe and other people, and I stuck with that group for the rest of the day.    We went on some rides (even like 1 or 2 kiddy ones @-@), we ate lunch (joe bought me a slice of pizza, thx joe!), and went to the arcade. I didn't bring any money, but it was pretty fun watching people play DDR. Joe beat some stranger, but then Carson beat him afterwards ^^;; I played DDR once and i can easily get owned at that game XP   The bus ride was kinda uneventful... nearly fell asleep going there, and played some Big 2 coming back.    When we got home, it was around 5pm. Then we dispersed. Our family (and my sister's bf) ate dinner with justin's family (plus their aunt). So it was like 10 people. Played a bit of DM (actually come to think of it.. that's like all we did XP) and then went home.   Tomorrow... i really need to work on my History essay.. i think it was due this week, but not many I know of are done.. do yah, I'll try to get it done by monday.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you want to see the "blogboard" link is here ==>  urlLink This is a link...  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Bored   What is with the the... titles in bold? lol oh well.. I'll go with it...  Today sucked... not literally but yeah. I'm still at school... supposedly doing business crap, but a blogging break won't hurt. I'm about to go to orchestra rehearsal... I only have two left and we suck!! I'll be going to Richmond Hill for OFSAA.... I dun even know why I'm going, cuz I suck at shooting, and also, I'd rather go to dress rehearsal. So yeah... life is a lil busy, and I think it would blow even more but... I got a few things to be glad about:  Last Sunday! Wow that was quite a good day compared to my other Sundays (sundaes? yum hee hee). I also hope to go to Em's Von's maybe Keane's? lol art show next Monday! So I won't think about waking up at 6 for three days for now.... (I usually wake at 7:30 so it's a big step for me!!) That's all for now... back to my culminating project..... PSSST *hoarse whisper* anyone wanna help me?    Vickz   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Restlessness     Firstly, a welcome to vics ^^;; hope you can help with the slow updates, lol.. it's been awhile since someone has posted something here. Secondly, the comment-box-thingy isn't working.. but by the time you read this, it's probably already fixed.   I know I should be working, but my mind seems to be restless.. can't concentrate enough to do anything. I'll have to force myself to do something soon though.. because if I don't stick to the schedule, I'll be dead..^^;; fun.   ~Chronos (one of the shortest posts I have ever written) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sorry! I've joined now.. I tink... hee   Vick~  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Vick you still haven't joined my blog... Why??? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Unworkable Mood     I'm currently in a mind-block state, where my inner mind keeps telling me I should work, but my impulses over-ride it, and I do whatever. So here I am, posting on Blogger.    First of all, comment on comments: imo, the old way was better    Next, I will tell you about the civics trip... we were divided in 5 buses, I knew Justin and Annie, among some other people. yah.. we played cards on the bus, but then Justin and Annie complained of how hard it was to see the cards, so we switched to a normal deck of cards, lol. We split the group in half, and the first stop we made was the Mackenzie house, which was really cool, cause it was supposedly haunted.    Next stop was the police station.. saw someone there.. and yah.. there was a mannequin in the jail, and some girls were like screaming and running away. I was like "oO *nodznodz* what's with the overreaction?" I mean.. it  was  a convincing mannequin, but it wasn't  that  lifelike. Plus it was in broad daylight. Oh.. I didn't manage to get into the police car and get on the police motorcycle thingy.. someone was telling me about the car.. oh, and Orrin was saying how it was cramped in the car (he said he went to the police museum before.. more on that later).   At lunchtime, we went to a mall to eat. I had homemade lunch.. we walked around, and the first thing me and Annie did was to find the others. Surprisingly, we went in the right direction, and in no time, we found Keane and Orrin. Sam and Von joined us later. In the surrounding areas, I also found a bunch of other people who I talked to for awhile... and found someone while walking around.. and we eventually went back, though it was still quite early. Keane was like "I'm late!", but he was misinformed of the time, lol ^^;;   Afterwards, we walked around the old city hall place thingy, where we attended some court trial. The trial, as far as I could tell, was about this guy charged with drug possession, and during his arrest, he lost some money. Now, he's sueing the undercover police for the loss of money. It was interesting, attending a real court trial, though it was much smaller than I had originally expected, and besides the students on the trip, there was no other audience.   At the end, Annie decided to wait at the court house, while I went on to home. I am informed that she was later joined by Orrin, then Keane.    Today after school, I decided to walk home.. it was interesting.. got to talk to Orrin.   S'all for now!   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         New Layout!    Okay, in my defence, I know it's crappy...  I made this layout a few weeks ago to tide my boredom.  I dont remember when exactly...  A few things:  - The blue ad on the top is ugly... I may be able to cover it.  - The title on the top is ugly... I  will  change it.  - Having two people stand guard like that is ugly.  I will change it.  Possibly something Kakashi related?  Or back to X/1999 even?  - The buttons on the top are ugly... they too will change.  - The Archives are currently down...  Not due to the archives themselves, but due to that I have to design an archive page still.  - Grey is scary.  I know what you're thinking.  If everything is so ugly, why'd you change it?  I guess I was tired of the Blue Sai layout and just haaad to change it.  So welcome to ArV no Kifu v 4.01  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         New Blogger    Wow, I've been away from Blogger for so long that they changed the whole thing?  Hm... Interesting...  Now first...  Emerson that  was  long but not  that  long.  You had a cool year. ^-^ I hope next year will be as eventful... or not in some cases.  Now, I promised an update on my blog's layout... and it will come... soon... who knows when... maybe I should work on it... hmm...  Oh! Five days ago Hoshi and I had celebrated our six month anniversary.  ^-^ *huuugs Hoshi* Yesterday I was with her and a few others at Paramount Canada's Wonderland.  It was Jade who organized it, and she brought her younger cousin.  Lynn and Michelle came too.  One more thing... dirty book?       urlLink Which Naruto Character are You?  quiz by  urlLink orangeday.net     -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A.l.p.h.a ...     Ah... I finally have time to think about the past year. It was... an interesting year. I hope you have like 20 minutes to spare... lol, Part 1 of 5:   For the 4 th  time in my life, I was starting at a new school. It was what I've been fighting for for a long while... to go to Ward. I recall in grade 8, when I first had the school selection form. I debated with my parents to go to Ward, but they wouldn't let me, and eventually, when it got late, my dad just took the form from me and checked off Brebeuf... I shed a few tears ^^;; (*cough cough* yes, I realize that's very weak, but I done that since then)    The reason why my parents allowed me to transfer was because the school was relocating. This had promised - earlier - that they wouldn't relocate, and the new school wouldn't affect the old one that much. For awhile, this worked out ok - they provided schoolbuses to Bathurst Heights. However, they had annouced that they would be cancelling the schoolbus service for next year. This set the stage for my new arguments of why to go to Ward: it would take around 4 hours back and forth each day - this would drain energy for school. Not to mention in case of emergencies, I'll be nowhere near home. I found out near the beginning of the school year that they re-introduced the school bus service, and I stupidly told my parents that. They wanted me to transfer back.. and I was like.. "uhhh... no."   The only problem was... most of the original advantages of going to Ward had disappeared. I wouldn't be used to the place - don't know teachers, people, how things work, ... - and well, I don't know... just some advantages disappeared. New uniform for instance (actually i only bought the sweater thingy) Plus I felt like a niner.    I think that it was for the best that I went to Brebeuf for one year. It gave me a fresh slate to start off with. Also, it forced me out of the shell I was in for my elementary school years. This is because I knew like  no one  at Brebeuf, I was forced to make friends. This didn't turn out that bad, made me much less shy, and the result was a much enjoyable time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Anyway, back to the story: so yah, the experience left me less shy and more open. I met up with a lot of old friends, and found things are not what they used to be (stupid of me to think that it might - too much changes in one year). lol, I remember attaching myself to Keane for the first two months of school... and getting lost very often. Then there was confusion about tests and test centre, units and unit submission, day zeros (I spent my first Day 0 hallwalking because I had no idea what to do), and Focus (which I joined without taking the test - keane dragged me to see Mr.Church, the then-Focus teacher). I eventually met and got to know Joe and Hoshi throughout the year - among a bunch of other friends.   By the time I got adjusted to everything, I was quite behind in units. *sigh* I remember saying to myself that I won't fall behind to start with... but I did. And it got worse. On the bright side, I joined CSUNA for the 3 rd  year in a row, and actually got up and spoke some stuff. Best year ever... I plan to join next year. (CSUNA = model UN). Also, I joined the Anime Society, and was kinda... taken aback... at how late it ended ^^;; We watched Cowboy Bebop the movie - personally, I feel that Cowboy Bebop's plot and stuff goes too slowly... I heard that usually they start off with Akira. Glad they didn't, as I already saw that (and was left very, very confused).   Hope I haven't bore you all t'death yet ^^;;   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         t.o ...     Part 2 of 5:   There was this really, really long period of time where I did next to nothing. Mostly just chatted online, played DM5 (among other games), wasted time in general, and worked a bit.    It was either October or November that I didn't hand in a single unit... it's like, there wasn't any change from one TA interview to another. At first, my parents - not knowing how the system worked - did not pay attention to the number of units. Later though... when they finally managed to figure it out, it wasn't pretty ^^;;   Around this time, they had a Walkathon thingy, where you had to walk. I started out walking with a group, then I got tired of going so slowly. So I went ahead. Eventually I reached the school and got refreshments.    Then there was the Anime Karaoke thingy... I sang like two songs XP (terrible, i know) ah... that was when keane said he was grounded and couldn't come to anime anymore (it baffles me that he still manages to come when hoshi-chan visits), and it was the last day that jamie-chan would be at anime. Joe did a lot of the organizing: printing out the lyrics (I hope he still has that entire stack!) and playing the songs.    During the December break, I was so sure I'd be caught up by the end of that... however, I only finished like 2-3 units. Then during the March Break, where I told myself that this was serious... I did only like 3 units.    The Christmas Party at anime was pretty cool... I took a picture with the camera then jumped down and fell splat ^^;; They brought DDR and it was my first time playing. It was also Joe's first time playing (now he's amazing at it while I haven't touched a DDR thingy for awhile).    Besides units, I tried out - and failed miserably - for badminton, went for chess, started learning how to play Go, did some math contests (first for Cayley... yah!), and threw a bday party. Most people who visit this blog was at the bday party i believe...    Ah.. one thing I remember well, was in October, the Halloween party thingy.. i dyed my hair white ^^ that was fun ^^;; I should try more stuff like that sometime.   This was generally a period of non-work... ah, how I would've done much better if I had worked during this period. Anyway, the time of reckoning was near, for soon, April began...   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         o.m.e.g.a     Part 3 of 5:   Ah yes... April was when the rush to do homework first began. At first it wasn't really a rush... I did a bunch of tests in the morning (I think I did more tests in a single week, then the previous months combined). Also, started working on units a bit. However, there were still some stretches when I slacked off a bit...    One of the key events during this time was the Focus Wonderland Trip, this was a rather fun event, as I have never been - unlike the rest of the people here *looks around* My first time riding a roller-coaster was... um.. not as exciting as I thought it would be. It was definitely an experience I won't forget, and definitely something I've never experienced before... but I don't get why people would be afraid or go pukey just cause of roller-coasters! ^^;; (no offense to those that do). It was a really fun day...   For the last 2 weeks of school, for like 5 days, I slept at 4 am, and the rest I slept at 12am. I recall pulling off 5 tests in a single day, and 11 tests in the last week. On the final night, I pulled off 4 units ^^;;    It didn't help that I lost my agenda during that last week (as if losing my science and math textbooks over the year wasn't enough). Also the line-up at the test centre was interesting... I've heard of it, now I got to experience it ^^;; really, there wasn't any need for the line-up. Everyone rushed to take tests in the morning, while period 3 and onwards, it was like empty.    What did I learn from all this? One can finish 80 units and like 25 tests in two months. One can work if one is motivated to. Never take breaks - you  think  you need one... but you really don't. The best thing is to keep working while you can. Taking a break will cause you to lose your pace. Start working at the beginning of the school year... immediately.    Ah yes, it was around this time that Saturday School ended too.. it was fun this year, like every other year. Got to meet up with some people ^^;; Actually met Aaron at Sat School before normal school... and to think that this was a person that was at my old school for 4 years of my life... and that I never talked to him then, lol... same goes for Dickson. I guess there was this kinda barrier between immersion and non-immersion people...   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         e.p.i.l.o.g.u.e     Part 4 of 5:   So here I am, at the end of a weird parabolic journey, and currently, I should be studying for exams (since I have exams in all 8 subjects). Instead, I waste tonight chatting and posting on Blogger ^^;; Oh well. I guess it's for the best. I certainly hope that there's no unpleasant surprises awaiting me over the next days, and everything runs smoothly. I just want to pass everything already. I kinda care about my marks, but I rather pass now. ^^;;    Another thing is that my computer is starting to get screwy. I'm asking Joe to help me fix it on Friday... It's starts lagging out of nowhere, crashing sometimes, "fatal exceptions of 0E", among other problems. @-@ and it's a new computer too..   For the summer, I plan to take swimming (lifeguarding).. but I found out that my instructor didn't mail me my cert for Bronze Cross yet... I need to look into that. I can't take NLS (lifeguarding course) without having the Bronze Cross cert, I don't think. Summer school seems to be ruled out.. While I'm sure that parents' will still provide me with ample work @-@ There's always the ever-present paper route (I was carrier of the month last month! Yay!), and I want to get back to reading, Yugioh tourneys, and the website. I wouldn't mind just hanging around with my friends (*sigh* i hope that happens often... it happened a total of like twice last summer), and I know I have to help Vics with his violin exam by being piano accompaniment.    I guess those are my plans for the summer... It should go by really quickly... unfortunately   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Dawn of New Ages     Part 5 of 5:   So... what are my plans for next year?   First of all, there are a bunch of things I would like to join. Like this year, I hope to join Anime, badminton, math contests and CSUNA. I also hope to join martial arts, dragonboat, chess team (if they have one), and if Keane really insists... yearbook committee...   Like almost all the students at Ward, I hope to do better next year, start working quicker, do more work faster, and don't slack off ^^;; I also look forward to the arrival of hoshi-chan... and maybe DYT...    Hafta remember to take Career Studies next year, as I didn't take it this year.   I look forward to the next year, and hope that it would be more successful than this year.    Whew! That was a long post x 5, ne?   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Hello!!!    k, well, everyone uses that kind of opener so i will too >P...i havent posted here in a while b^_^ and everyone else has so it's Hoshi-chan's turn.yeesh! im so bored, these fool-cake classes are slow, no one else is @ school today cause dey all on da zooooo trip u.u; annoying. some people are already done their ISU..but noooo Hosh-chan is not done...nooo!! cause Hoshi-chan is lazy bum. (yes, i am trying to waste time, watz it to u? o.o;) k...sooo *whistles* *scratches arm* ya.....*looks around* it's almost the weekend!! i wonder wat im going to do this weekend...*homework flashes thro mind* omgosh! i did my history, right, and like, this morning i looked in ma bag and it was gone.......*head drops* i told u Em! sumtin unlucky would happen for breaking ma promise! *cries* argh..and i was rushing and everythnig...grr...and now when i tell sir it wont even b an excuse...@.@ lol *SIGH* well wat can u do, i guess i deserve it, it was crappy ne wayz LOL  really  crappy..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Che Sera Sera     Wow... first time experiencing June/May rush... it's a pretty interesting time. I feel slightly stressed out, and at points, flooded ^^;; demo, I feel ok now, even though I still have 2 units left to do. 1 math and 1 english... they should go fairly quickly.    Um... I hope that everyone isn't freaking out, considering suicide, deeply depressed, highly stressed out, or anything... that seems to be happening a lot around the school.    Anyway, people should try not to be discouraged... some people just give up working. They really shouldn't... fight to the end!! ^^ I hate giving up. Not only does it produce less results than I would if I succeed, it also damages my self-confidence: how come I wasn't able to succeed? Am I not strong enough? Do I lack the skillz? That's why... I stay up late to do work. I do  not  want to fail at this attempt to pass. I want to be able to succeed... to know that I can do this.   Whoa... I think I'm sounding really repetitive, but meh. Remember people... you are  invictus  unless you decide otherwise.    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         So Here's What Happened...    The lights in my house are  off .  I walk to my door and I'm thinking...  Wow, the hallway is dark...   Then I walk right into my door.   O.o   *cough* That's my little story. : # )  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Rising Tide     Things are finally starting to get interesting. More events are happening...   Anyhow, few days ago, we ate dinner with parents friends (they had two kids - gr.1 girl and gr.3 boy) at a japanese restaurant. That was expensive but delicious =P   We stopped by our house and I duelled with the kid. (duelling as in duel monsters for those that don't yet know). It reminded me of something.. about how the kid's parents was saying how I was a good influence. I know he must really look up to me, cause one time when we went to their house, he skipped a birthday party just cause I was coming... =\ do i really deserve that kinda respect? Also, another set of parents thought I was good influence...   So I start wondering... am I really good influence? I might be... I mean, I believe in good and everything like that, don't do drugs/alcohol/smoke, and get fairly good marks. Does the parents really think that hanging around me might do their children some good though? It makes me almost feel obliged to teach them something or other...   Well, I don't think I can do much more than what I already do, which is just act normal. I think that they'd start mistrusting me if I start becoming too much like a teacher or parent. So, in conclusion, I think I'll do nothing, and just continue on.   Next item, I started reading Hunter X Hunter... it happens to be quite an interesting series, and I definitely look forward to reading the rest of it. Kurapica is the coolest character I've ever met.. and at first I mistaken him as a girl... too bad he wasn't =P anyhow, he's the last living member of some clan, and is becoming a hunter to take revenge on the evil people. When he gets angry, his eyes turn red... kinda reminds me of how the badgers in Redwall have the "bloodlust" ability.    My opinion of H x H is that it's a story of 4 peoplewho became friends, trying to achieve their own goals and helping each other achieve theirs. Then finding that their goals are intertwined.    Next item: I'm starting to volunteer at a day camp thingy this week, so I'm definitely not going to be online as much. It's pretty fun, even though more work than during March Break or Christmas. I don't mind, because I actually feel like I'm doing something useful, instead of hanging around and playing with the kids like before.    Though a lot of the time, we just do that. I say "we" cause there's another volunteer, some guy that's one year older than me, and surprisingly, I found that he was from Brebeuf, my old school. Oh... I also met DYT there, she's a LIT, and I knew beforehand she'd be there. I'm be getting 20 hrs by the end of the week: 50 hours total.   Yah... I saw a rainbow today too... it was weird, I look at it closely for awhile, then went back to playing basketball, and from far, the rainbow seemed bigger oO;; Maybe cloud movements... who knows.   Enough with my inane chatter... that's all for now.   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Carpe Diem     For those wondering what the title means, find it out yourself =P   Anyway, today was pretty cool.. started out with me struggling to get out of bed (as usual), then the usual breakfast, newspaper, go on net (groups, favlinks, blogs, chat), and since it was friday, paper route. Then I managed to convince parents to let me go to STC with friends after leaving down their names and phone numbers. Josh must've asked me "can you go?" 5 times at least ^^;; and sorry to hoshi for putting up with all that silence while I scrambled to negotiate with my mom. Thanks to keane for providing the gift cert half a year ago, I finally put it to use...  too bad you weren't there though... =  Anyhow, right after lunch, normally I would be playing piano, then on the math, then watch TV (transformers and beyblade... yes I'm bored), but then I phoned keane and asked him about the bus route. Another thanks... I would've went the wrong way =\ Anyhow, the Finch bus was ok, but the Brimley bus was killer... waited for so long, and ended up 5 mins late! --;; Josh and Ken were there already.   First though, I made the same mistake as my sister, and went all the way to the roof where the GO trains were.. went back down, saw Carson's little group of people (Carson, Claire [Clarence], Tracy, Anne-Margareth, Lyris, Christopher, Shirley, and Brian Chen) and found out that Josh was already there.   After a good 35 mins of waiting, we finally met up with Orrin, Trisha and Hannah. Since we were so late, we had to wait another 2 and a half hours before we could see Tomb Raider.    That was spent by walking around, the music store was pretty cool, I got to play with the keyboard... ^^;; and trish was playing with the guitar. Oh, and I saw a bunch of people while walking around... a group of 11ers (one of which i knew from sat school), a niner from sat school, a group of niners (which stephan was part of, i asked him if he saw aiza..), some other 10ers (actually just Sam), Ana-sama, and some 9ers that helped with japanese pavilion for international night.    Pretty interesting, my theory is that since summer school just ended, everyone headed to STC.. either that or they spend a lot of time there =P    Now for the actual movie. It was ok.. better than the first one IMO, but still, lack of plot is not my type. I rate it 3 out of 5.    I was way over the time I said I'd be home... luckily enough, they didn't seem too mad, and Orrin was kind enough to drive me home... thanks Orrin ^^;;    Managed to learn a few things about people today, like how someone broke up with someone, and someone wanted to avoid some other person because of something, and how someone was not there because that person was with someone else somewhere else, and how someone was mad at someone because of something. I don't want to list any names or specific events, I'm sure you guys understand ^^   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Comments?     urlLink English Unit 16    -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was wondering....does ne one know how to put a mucis file in the background of the blog? including a "Stop" and "Play" button? hmm just curious is all... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Unexpect the expected!     Yesterday was unexpected.. I mean, I knew it was going to be different, because of the visit to ward, but besides that, it was still pretty interesting.   Met DYT while doing paper route, so I helped with hers too... then I won't mention how I left 10 mins early (me and hoshi decided to leave house at 2.. next time, decided when to  meet , not when to leave.. =\ ), then waited for 1/2 hour and watched 4 buses go by... lol.. i won't mention that at all ^^ anyhow, after walking/talking awhile, we saw Joe.. turns out he finished summer school. We talked with him a bit, then it was dismissal.. and then there was Keane. We talked for awhile too, before I went.. hope you guys had fun!   Anyhow, after spending some time watching Transformers Armada, Yugioh and Beyblade (yes i'm bored), I ate dinner then went out to play basketball. For like the first half hour, my mom wanted to play to *chokes with laughter* she actually got quite a few in at short distance =P anyhow, then like usual, I spend most of my time just shooting the ball by myself for like an hour, then this girl appeared out of nowhere and asked if she could play, so I said yes.   we spent like the first 10 mins shooting in silence.. i'm always awkward around strangers =\ but anyhow, after talking for a few mins, justin and ashley came along, and i introduced them and stuff. Turns out that that girl immigrated not too long ago.. only spoke mandarin, so she couldn't understand canto. Surprisingly, she was 16 too (i had thought 17 or 18), and goes to a school in downtown. and she's fasttracking high school oO;; taking it in 3 years rather than 4... scary... =P   no hoshi, i don't think she was trying to hit on me... and no, i wasn't "interested" in her =P   we played bball till 10, then i had to go home.. then after a short convo on the phone, then freaking out for awhile about the HP1 i lent *coughcough* (it was late!!) i went to bed. For some odd reason, I woke up at 5 am... I decided to stay awake. I mean... might as well, no? I think I woke up because a dream finished...    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Oh...    I tipped a whole styrofoam cup of hot Mr. Noodle Chicken Noodle Soup on Joe's head.  He seemed forgiving.  I did not get to finish my game with Veronica.  I barely ever finish games.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         From BackBlog    June 28, 2003: Google Ads now appear in backBlogBasic accounts for a trial period of a few weeks.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HIII!!! Well, i just read Jade-chan's dream. and since she has no "comment" thingies, i decided to type in here....ummm interesting dream Jade! im just wondering...hmmm y u didnt at least TRY to climb the rock. i mean, it sort of seemed like it was ur mission....to relate this to real-life, id have to say ..that maybe the rock represents a challage and the "ghost"/"demon" is ur pressure to complete the challange. in the dream, u choose wat u feel like is that way to b "free" from this "responsibility" (or the "rock"), so instead of climbing the rock, u face wat u feel is the inetivable, to die. (or to fail) but u think that ull b free from the ghost (the pressure) once a decision has already been made, and this decision seemed to b easier then tiring urself climbing the rock. once u die, though, things r not as they seem, and the ghost/demon (or the "pressure") follows u even after ur false freedom. so....possibly this could b a warning, or, it could even b something that has already happened. As for ur family, i think this decision also affects them, they and the priests and nuns, (the "good" people) expect this from u, (as the nun expected u to climb the rock) but they probably werent the ones causing the pressure....hmmm think on that, tell me wat u think, and ill tell u more.    Hosh1~*   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Yesterday     Ah.. haven't blogged in ages ^^    Anyhow, yesterday was fun.. it was keane and victor's party ^^ too bad victor had to leave early tho =\ To sum up, I went near brimley and finch to meet keane.. originally, I had thought that we would be leaving at 11:30.. I was proven wrong ^^ we left at like 2 =P not that it mattered that much, it was enjoyable at keanes ^^ thx for da hospitality!! ooo.. and thx to kevin and his mom for driving us there!! ooo... and thx to renae for  her  hospitality!!    *cough* getting kinda off-track here.. um.. oh yah. met jeffrey and jeffrey there... probably forget who they are until next time I see them ^^;; Afterwards, when we reached the place, they played smash bros for awhile then went on a scavenger hunt thingy where jeff won. Then we went and kinda had a water balloon fight which quickly turned into an all-out water war where everyone (except me *cough* =P.. oh, and jeff) got really wet.    Oh wait... in between that, there was lunch and a movie.. we watched like the beginning of ringgu and then switched to phone booth... they were enjoyable ^^ anyhow.. afterward, we had dinner and did a little truth dare then i left. so yah.. what happened afterwards is a mystery =P   Dunno why i'm writing this as most people who read this blog already know all this... i guess jus for keeping in da archives so i can use it later to store in my diary ^^   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Boithday    I should've posted this on my real birthday.  Contrary to what I may have told you, my birthday is on July 08th, not 10th. XP  Yes, I am now 16.  Oh, BTW.  Karen, the Karin that posted was another Karin.  A great newly published author if she doesn't mind me saying. >P  Her name is Karin Lowachee, go check out her first book.  Warchild .   *looks around*  I sound like a commercial.  -Arv 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Karin Lowachee wrote a sequel to  Warchild .  It's called  Burndive .  It's about  Ryan  Azarcon.   urlLink Cover Art    urlLink Burndive Home Page    urlLink Author's Home Page   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Linkin Park - One Step Closer    I cannot take this anymore   I'm saying everything I've said before   All these words they make no sense   I find bliss in ignorance   Less I hear the less you'll say   You'll find that out anyway   Just like before...   Everything you say to me   Takes me one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break   I need a little room to breathe   Cause I'm one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break   I find the answers aren't so clear   Wish I could find a way to disappear   All these thoughts they make no sense   I find bliss in ignorance   Nothing seems to go away   Over and over again   Just like before...   Everything you say to me   Takes me one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break   I need a little room to breathe   Cause I'm one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break   Shut up when I'm talking to you  Shut up Shut up Shut up  Shut up when I'm talking to you  Shut up Shut up Shut up Shut up  I'm about to break  Everything you say to me   Takes me one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break   I need a little room to breathe   Cause I'm one step closer to the edge   And I'm about to break  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         *flame splashes out of no where* *Hoshi-chan steps thro*    HIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Hoshi is here! *grinz* it HAS indeed been a while since ive posted here, *cough cough* ne wayz, i usually make my monthly appearance to write meaningless nothingness.....*grinz* itz F-U-N! ne who, this site has come a long way...yeesh, keep it one way i say, lolz, actually, i think i like it the way it was the first time better....*lookz off* *shrugz* ne whoz, im sure mine's going to b staying the same way for a while now..*eh heh heh..........but, being the >nice  ~HoSHi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Summer School = ?     ...Not that I  have  summer school... demo, it'd be nice to know how it works. I heard that if you don't finish at least a unit every other day, they'll kick you out. That's good I guess... keeps people from procrastinating ^^ demo... hope they can handle it. For people taking normal summer school (non-Ward summer school), well... have fun too ^^    Um... all my friends are taking summer school... that sucks. I'll be left with nothing to do *yawnz* um.. stupid math work dad gives me... *looks around*   Too bad I missed the fireworks yesterday... didn't have permission to go, because it was "illegal". @-@ ah well... the party on friday was cool, and so was helping sister move houses on sunday. Plus, I'm almost done the Circle Opens quartet... just need Shatterglass! Too bad I'm like 120 out of 135... something like that. Harry Potter and the O. of the P. is 4400 out of 4600 (estimation). Just reserved it for fun, as I've finished it already. Wonder how long my sister will take to finish...   Cool new layout btw... it's nice to have some change ^^;;    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Midnight Blue    I can't sleep...  It's 1:21 AM...   Unwelcome Intruder   I probably would've been asleep by now if my dad didn't open the door for 5-10 minutes with his questions about blah and blah useless crap about moving the computer to such an illogical location that all I could do there was lie there dumbfounded at why he would bother me at that time for that subject.   Home Aint Where My Heart Is...   He goes on to say, "You're not going out tomorrow."  A straight rejection of the proposal I had previously requested earlier on in the night.  An answer so blunt and late at night that all I could do was again lie there, dumbfounded at why he says this now.  My head hurts and my eyes hurt as I sit here wondering how I will be able to sleep and wake up on time during the school year and how soon the carpal tunnel sydrome I'm giving myself with bad posture will kick in.   Sleeping Potion #9   A few minutes ago I was in the kitchen due to the sound of water running through taps annoying me enough to stand and walk.  I warmed up half a mug of warm milk.  Apparently that's supposed to help people sleep and I thought "*shrugs* what the hell."  Note that I didn't actually shrug, I just thought the word.  I'd blame it on the time if I didn't do similar actions when I was fully awake.  *sigh* (yes, I sighed in Real Life)   Turn That Frown Upside Down!   Let's look at the good side: if I'm up in an hour and fourty-one minutes I'll be able to see Naruto.  I wont  want  to watch Naruto, heck I don't want to watch Naruto  now , but the fact that it's only 44% done and it only needs one hour and thirty one minutes (it changed) is a globally life-giving wonderful-amazing event, no?   Sigh...   *sigh*  I guess I'll be trying that "sleeping" thing again.  If it doesn't work, I'll see if I can come back.  *shrugs* (no, I didn't sigh in Real Life)  Or maybe Mr Radio can help me out.  I'd use the phone if not for three reasons,  1. Don't want to wake people and refuse them the privilages of sleeping.  2. Don't have energy to do more than sit and stare, or lie and stare.  3. Don't have access to a felly-tone without parents noticing and angering.  Well...  this is me stalling again.  I will no longer waste the time of your precious three day weekend.  Last weekend before school starts... *sigh*  -ArV   PS - I finally heard an actual "broken telephone" style rumour.  I heard from *** that they were informed by *** who was told by *** that *** would be coming to Mary Ward because *** wrote a two-page essay for that one person.  Hey...  We were going to do a powerpoint presentation for Vick's parents...  I don't remember why we didn't... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Success     I passed! ^^ After 1 week of training and pushing to the limits, I managed to scrape together a pass! ^^ I can lifeguard now! What a whirlwind of a week, it seems like just yesterday I was nervously attending my first class.   Let's backtrack a bit: First day, I didn't even expect to take the course at Don Mills... I phoned at 8:30 in the morning asking if I would be transfered to some other pool, or if it was cancelled altogether, then the lady said "the pool's open..." ...  oO;;    Luckily, my dad was there, so I got a ride to Don Mills Collegiate pool, around 1-2 mins before class started. My friend was not as lucky and came 10 mins late (we registered together, and when I told him that morning that it was open, he'd just awoken).   I've been to Don Mills Collegiate exactly once (varsity chess game), so I kinda knew the bus route. Well, I ended getting rides back and forth tho... my friend would drive me there in the morning, and my dad drive me (or us) back.   The pool itself was kinda small... and the lifeguards there were bored and cramped in that stuffy office. That's why they spent some time racing each other on wheely chairs... oO;;   The pool's depth reminds me of L'Amoreaux, where I usually go swimming (I went for rec swim a few times there this summer), but NLS wasn't offered at L'Am.    Now for the actual course... it was kinda straining: we learnt new stuff and was expected to do it right after, we had to memorize a bunch of sequences and stuff. We watched some vids and took notes... we had like 2-3 quizzes during the course (I don't think any of them were that serious). We had to treat spinals (land and water), do something called the Pia carry, save submerged victims, and practise lifeguarding.   The one item I was afraid of failing most was lifting the 20lb brick from the bottom of the pool, then surfacing and carrying it back to the side of the pool.    We also had some problem solving things that were kinda unrelated to the course... like how to carry someone from one point to another without that someone touching the water. The condition was that we can't move if we're holding that someone at the point... so it's basically teamwork and problem solving... pretty cool.   There were some interesting people there... (out of our class of 16, 15 passed - the one that failed couldn't do the brick) 3 people there takes air cadets, 2 goes to UTS, 1 person went to my old school (brebeuf) and now goes to the current school (don mills). Some people were already swimming instructors. Our instructor was pretty cool too.. he was pretty funny and I think we all had a good time despite the fact that the course was tiring (well, for most of us).    We have like 2-3 breaks everyday. A 5-10 min one in the morning, and in the afernoon, and then the 45-60 min lunch break. During the lunch break, I went to the Instructor's course classroom, and found Aaron and a person from my old Bronze Cross class. Which was pretty cool. The person from my old Bronze Cross class had a MT t-shirt and helped Piro during CNAnime... cool, eh? ^^   After my first class, I had to buy a Fox 40 whistle - which was like any other whistle, except without the ball inside, so its waterproof. I also knew I needed a bigger bag, so I took a bigger bag out from the closet. Your bag was put to good use, thanks Keane ^^    Also, after 1 day, my swimming trunks changed from green to brown... oO;; (it had stayed green for an entire year)... and then orange later in the week. Almost everyday when I came back, I would exercise a bit, then study. And have like a 15-min break sometime. During my exercises in the basement, I think I've developed a kinda fear for bees... I found a live one and a dead one down there. I disposed of both a bit aferwards... but took  me awhile.    Oh, and I went out to see Mars at 10pm one day. It was only a bright light... brighter than the stars around it, but not bigger... I'm going to try seeing it at midnight tonight to see if it makes any difference.   Today was a bit of a good luck/bad luck day. The bad luck being I forgot my goggles at home (on the last day too!!! @-@), the good luck being I passed my course anyways (I borrowed my friends goggles for awhile, and sometimes I went in the water with my glasses). Bad luck being going home after waiting 1 and half hour for my dad to pick my up. Bad luck being I shattered a glass today. Good luck being I only got a small, superficial cut.    But... I passed NLS, and that's all that matters! ^^ (... at least until I get over the fact that I passed NLS!)   ~Chronos   p.s. it's weird cause I thought I wouldn't pass. There was one thing called the "DNS swim", where you have to swim, then do a surface dive, Pia carry the DNS (drowning non-swimmer) to the side of the pool. I tried the DNS swim a few times with "ok" results, and my instructor told me to do it again. So I did, and I did fairly good that time. But my instructor said he wasn't watching (and sounded fairly serious).... then I didn't have time to do the DNS swim again. And yet I passed. Yay!   p.p.s. the chlorine smell, minor scrapes and bruises are going to take awhile to get rid of =P I think everyone in the class had minor scrapes and bruises by the end.    p.p.p.s. school's almost starting, yay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         It's ME! ...or IS it...?     It's been a while since I've blogged, but then I haven't had much to blog about...seems like I can't compare to the amount of blogging Rei and Shu have put into it...*looks around* o.o' Oh well, I hope to have a new design up soon and I am currently working on something for Jade  and  Rei-chan. ^-^ I doubt I'll get it done before the school year starts though...*pouts*...    As to my comments towards the blackout, I too found it an interesting experiance...well, if I had  flashlights  it may have been a bit more interesting...^-^; But oh well, otherwise I think it really woke people up to how dependant we are on it....hm...    Well, seems like I'm stumped out of words and I don't have much left to write...o.o' er...so..yeah...*looks around* *curses and dissapears*      
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Onward Bound     wow... is it just me, or Blogger has a nice new template... um...   Anyhow, first, the blackout. Blackout '03 as the newspaper called it, was a pretty interesting time. For me at least. It meant I spent almost an entire day duelling and playing chinese checkers with my neighbours. Fun. And the stars were pretty bright too! I didn't get much sleep during those days tho.. was on the phone. Anyhow, we were pretty well-off, because we had flashlights and cold rice. The next day we brought out some stove thingy and cooked congee.   Ah... some other people were not so lucky. Most businesses loss a lot, specially those that stocked frozen foods and whatnot. My condolences go out to them... =\ ..    My neighbour managed to bbq some stuff, so that was cool. Which reminds me, the sunday which followed, i went to a bbq at parent's friend's house. That was pretty cool.. they had like 2 kids, one my age, and another 6 years younger. The one my age was at some camp thingy, but the smaller one actually duels, so I did that. Fun. (i carry around my cards almost all the time)   Anyway, back to the blackout. Interesting to see the very wide range of reactions to it. Interesting also, to note how dependant we are on electricity. Umm... somehow makes me wish that we  didn't  have those generators, nuclear or fuel-powered. Then see how we can survive. And maybe develop better sources of energy, like natural!   Investigation is still underway on the electricity problem. They kinda think that it has to do with an Ohio power plant, which caused a sink because it was overloaded by a huge current. The sink cause other surrounding plants to overload. Only those that isolated themselves from the power grid was safe. Those that didn't spread the problem. Around 50 million people were without electricity.    Now, if you haven't fell asleep yet... I have good news: my computer is now re-formatted and ready to go. It has sound, windows XP, trillian pro... the whole nine yards! Complete with bells and whistles! (not really... it's the same old computer with an upgraded OS, that's all). The only problem is getting the ancient computer running again... I seem to be having problems with it. My sister and i are going to try to fix it... hopefully sometime soon.   S'all for now   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Out of the Darkness    (woo-hoo! im the first to post! *grins*)   I'm sure many of you know the events of the last 2 days. I am happy, but a bit disapointed to say...the electricity is BACK on!!!! (Course many of you prob. know that already) Let's see...on Thursday between 2 and the time the power went off, I had this reallly strange feeling...I think it was linked to the power outage. But I found out about the power outage as I was reading...and suddenly my laptop went, "ding ding" to show that it switched to battery. I also noticed it say, "Local Connection Terminated" ME: o.o'     So, I tried the TV and no success, I phoned Umi-sama and I figured out that hers was gone too....but, I'd soon know that many,  many  others were without also....*nodz nodz*But, I must say, the last 2 days have been exciting...it was...something different. And the stars were so clear, it was amazing....The power went back on at around 10....but imagine the suprise i had when I woke up to the harshest thunder storm i had seen in many years! The thunder was SO LOUD!  *sigh* Well, the electricity managed to stay. I bet many were like, "THANK GOD!" Hm. Does anyone know the cause of the blackout? Cause I've heard different stories.....    On a spiritual/supernatural/supicious level, I have come to a conclusion that was based off ideas that Jade-chan suggested...."A warning," she said, "this could just be a warning, it may not even be the "big thing"" (btw, this is not  exactly  what she said) I began to wonder...was that why our premotnitions came so sutle? My warning came only 2 hours before, Jade's was just a vision within a dream, about her frige having lots of food in it. (Turned out her mom bought los of food when the blackout came about) Then, just this morning, things started to piece together.    Q: Who would send the warning?       Well, last night I had a dream that I was drinking milk...well, trying to, cause suddenly this bee and two different types of flies started coming at it. I put the glass of milk down and decided I'd have to get the fly swater, dispite my wishes not to kill. So i held it in hand, but suddenly I noticed that even land insects started coming for it, all these aunts and such. *But amoung them, standing very still where they were all movinig....was a spider. My vision lingered there, I lifted a brow, there was something strange about a spider being with that bunch....* But I didn't have time to think and a bee came at me, I tried to swat at it, but my hits were weak and i fell to the ground as it started stinging me. I woke to the sound of this morning's thunder storm...a very loud one. So....we have here the clues: blackout; dream (spider); thunder storm.....It can only mean one thing: Thunder Emporer....(aka Thunder Ruler or Charles) I tried contacting him, and others, he told me that there was a danger to look out for....*looks around* we can only se....     ne wayz, nuff of my crazy ramblings, ^_^ i hope everyone found this experiance as exciting as i did...oooo the stars were bright....ne wayz, ja!    HoSHi*~  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Looking into the Past Today!     First, a little note before I get into the main point of the blog. I sneaked out of the house at 1 to try to see the Perseid Meteor Shower, but noticed it was too bright. Upon re-entering the house, I looked it up and found the best time to watch would be 5 am, so I hope to wake up then (I really want to watch, but the last time I planned to wake up for a celestial show did not work too well =P aka too tired).   Oh, btw, it was a miracle neither parents woke up (they're light sleepers), because I had to turn off the alarm and chime, and turn it back on. That makes some chirping noise. Also, the main door is kinda squeaky.    Ok... so anyway, the week started out with my mom adding 2 two-page chinese letters to my relatives onto my workload. Fun. So I was like... "must remember to search this blog's archive sometime to see what I've been up to for the past few months".    A few weeks before that, I had an idea of searching for my old trivia questions (we had 3-4 trivia questions to do for gifted, it was our "homework") to put on my site. Kinda like a database for random, fun facts. I remember copying the more interesting trivia questions onto a piece of paper before dumping the whole pile (yes, pile... I took the trivia homework very seriously and ended getting first place for points... but that's beside the point).    So... after some restlessness, I decided to start searching my room for the trivia questions. I ended up not finding them. I could bet almost anything it had to do with my mom's interference with my orderly mess (oxymoron there). It makes me really angry when she fools around and misplaces everything, and I end up not finding the items I want back. It's even worse when she blames  me  for losing those things. Um.. getting off-track here...   The point is... it made me feel like I lost some part of me. A memory of sorts. I worked really hard on the trivia questions, and they bring back memories... Agincourt library... the old man with white hair that always helped me (he's still there, and I'm wondering if I should go up to him and thanks him some day)... my prize for getting the highest marks in trivia (which got stolen then returned... another story)... and I guess that sheet of paper was kinda like a physical item to represent all that. It would help me remember when I had forgotten...   ... like some other items in my room that helped me remember other stuff... grad photos, math contest reviews (not a happy memory... my dad put so much pressure on me to do well, I remember crying before the contest), printed photos (thanks to my sister's improper use of her school's laserjet =P ), outline and pictures of a story which fell flat... etc   Oh, and back to that letter-writing and archive thingy I wrote about near the beginning, I found that the archive was down. Another part of the past which is temporarily or permanently lost.    To some people, the past doesn't matter. I have at least one friend of that opinion: never look backwards, waste of time. I find that that's not a good idea... your past makes up who you are, and one should always try to understand it. Some other people, like me, spends a little too much time looking into the past. Well, I guess it isn't that bad, as long as it doesn't hinder your progress in the present. I'd hate to think of what'll happen when I grow old... probably spend my days living in the past =P   Sorry for the long post, anyway, I should get some sleep. I want to see the Perseid Meteor Shower at 5am, it could be something to remember =P   ~ Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         There Were Errors in Publishing    Apparently, I have the same error as Belky does...  Does anybody else using blogger have this error?  Maybe it's accross the whole system...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Helping Hands     Hey! I'd like to help with Belky's blog! I could be of help.. I think... like here and there... I guess... *lack of confidence* lol  Check out my blog too! New layout! I'll try to post more often (cuz I know I don't haha...) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Early Morning Post!     Ah... not too long ago, I finished watching A.I. It was a pretty good movie, one that critics have high ratings to, but didn't do too well in the box office. I recall reading an article on it... supposedly it's a creation between Spielburg and the late Kubrick. It's about a boy-robot who's programmed to love, and searches to become human...there were kinda two endings... one that Kubrick would've used, which was pretty good - though kinda sad, the second is a Spielburg twist at the end... it made the final ending kinda bittersweet, and I thought it was ok... though it would've been fine if they left it at the first ending.   I recall my mom asking me if I would want to go to Hong Kong by myself for a week like next year. I was indecisive.... I mean, it'd be a nice adventure and all, but my chinese is horrible and I think I'd feel very out of place.    ~Chronos (hopefully i'll dream dreams that can point me somewhere)  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Grr! Now I know what you mean Renae!!  My post here didn't post! Arg!! I'm not re-writing it lol.   Vickz  is dying....   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Spiralling Times     In a response to jade's blog post, i'd say I'd haven't the slightest clue what they  might mean =P   In a somewhat more cheerful tone, I'dve been disconnected for a week due to internet restrictions and daycare volunteering (now I have 50 hours total, yay). Next week might be a bit better. In other cheerful news, I almost broke my nose ^^;; On the same note, I haven't been able to talk to people for a few days ^^;; so altogether, things are looking great, and I look forward to what the future brings.    ~Chronos   p.s. I'm not even sure if I'm being sarcastic or not... so don't ask =P 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG! OMG! I GIVE UPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPP!!!!!!! *ANGER* *ANGER* ALL I SEE ARE..........."ERROR ERROR ERROR!!!!!!!!!!" GRRRRRRRRR....IT'S ALL MESSED UP! *fangs to blogger*  *must do...something...*   ~HoSHi*  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       didnt work. *tries to stay calm* she's  still  not a member for me, but im a member for her. (back to the beginning) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Boo-chan,  there's a problem, Jade's team members include me, but when i go to my members there's only me and u. i tried sending her an invitation...and i went to her inbox to accept it, but...it went to the error page. it may b because it's all messed up because im on her members list but she's not on mine. oorr it could b something old, as she has said, this has happened already.  ill try to cancel my membership on her, then reinvite.   *crosses fingers* Jade's got bad luck wid these things man...  ~HoSHi* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm in the proccess of writing a post for today.  When you read it (most likely tomorrow) please pretend that it made the print for tonight.   -ArV   ps.  Please tell me what you think of my desktop colours.   urlLink  Desktop   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A Fair Fair     Ah. haven't updated in awhile (brace yourself for a long post)... managed to get quite a bit of work done this week, so that's good.   Anyhow, to the main subject, today, I got to go to the univ fair ^^ this meant that I got to leave school at 11am, after I got TTC photo taken. I was somewhat surprised I got permission to go... (my dad was like "you're going to miss school to go downtown?")... but I eventually got a permission to sign out ^^    I didn't actually use that note tho...I don't think my TA was here today, so it didn't really matter. I wanted to go early, but orrin, trisha, janice, joe, annie and hannah wanted to go later (they ended going after football), and clarence, carson, tracy, brian, and brian wanted to go at 11:30. (um... sorry if I missed any names). Anyhow, Karen wanted to go early to, so I went with her ^^    It was pretty cool, but I don't think I was much of a conversationalist during that trip ^^;; anyhow, we met up with the carson group at Tim Hortons. Surprising, they caught up, even tho we left half hour before they did. Umm... it might be that we took Kennedy and they took Finch. I knew we should've taken Finch =P    Anyhow, we all went to the Convention Centre where it was held, and we started getting stuff. I guess I should've really asked more questions about stuff... I only asked about architecture and what courses I needed ^^;; well, I managed to grab lotsa booklets to look at, so I guess I'll check those out and see what interests me.    Apart from the booklet, (keane, renae and victor should take note) several stalls were handing out pens. Nipissing was offering to take polaroid pics for people for free. Ryerson gives out these huge bags to store stuff in, and also pens. And if you ask them about stuff, you also get a cool keychain. You could also get a keychain from Western stall: that's the one I got. There were also magnets. I guess they ran out of mirrors, I heard there were mirrors yesterday. I want to go on the first day of the fair next year ^^;; get more stuff.   Also, next year, I hope to be better prepared with questions. This year I was somewhat bogged down by requests: I got stuff for aaron, dickson, derek and josh too... so it was kinda heavy. Oh, almost forgot, they were giving out free pogos near the entrance of the Convention Centre.   Now that I started to think seriously about university, I narrowed it down from "no idea" to these following choices: computer science/gfx, architecture, education (teaching), some writing job (journalism perhaps?), and maybe some sort of engineering. Still a wide range and pretty vague, I know, but maybe after I peruse through those pamphlets I can narrow even more ^^;;   Most of the time spent at the Convention Centre I guess was walking around, gathering pamphlets, and looking for people. I should spend more time asking next year. Some people spent lotsa time asking those people stuff. I should do that.    I went with the Carson group back to Union Station, and then after that, it was a smooth ride home. Got back a bit past the "4-5" I kinda said I'd be home by, but it wasn't much - like 10 mins, so noprobz. Had to do paper route afterwards ^^;;    ooo, after reading the movies section of the Star, I think I want to watch matchstick men sometime... the girl looks like Killua from hxh! (what with the casual pose with the skateboard). I know it's a fairly crappy reason to watch a movie, but the plot seems fairly interesting too ^^;;   Ah... extracurriculars are starting to pile up... yay ^^... so far chess and CSUNA. Newspaper will come soon, and I predict Dragonboat and Anime will follow soon. Need to prioritize these in case they clash.    I suppose chess would be my #1, since the team depends on everyone being there (I'm being presumptuous: dunno if I'll even make the team), then Dragonboat, then Anime. CSUNA is a 3 day thing, so I don't suppose it'll be too much of a problem, and I'm totally clueless about newspaper.    Um...I actually made a list of extracurriculars I want to join this year: chess, CSUNA, newspaper, anime, dragonboat.... International Night, Art show (not really extracurricular), and maybe swim team (if they have it) and yearbook (if I'm not exploding by then). Fun!   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dammit, y do i care to much? i always get mixed up in this shit, but i really end up loosing, dont i? keane, dun get mad at me, u kno how i haf that thing where i hafta try and try, well yea, if i do this, then at least ill kno ive tried my hardest. im so sorry. *hugz u really tightly* i kno id b pissed too...but just this one day, im sorry, and ill never do it again...arrgghhh but im so tired boo! *cries* i just wanna cuddle up in my blankies...yumm...yummy blankies...and i wanna get rid of this headahce and eye pain...ooo sleep...*drools* gawd..times like this i feel like kicking myself in the ass. "idiot! u shoulda left at ten! who gives a damn bout wat he's doing! it's HIS fault! soo just LEAVE for crying out loud yeesh." but NOOO i gotta frigin b up this late, even tho i kno by doing tis ill gain nothing, cause inetivablly he'll think wat im doing rit now is stupid and pointless. so i woulda ended up getting-who knows how many-hours of sleep for nothing. for someone who doesnt even appreciate it...u.u *sighs* keane i wish u were here. well, ne wayz, im not *weak* so ill frigin do this frigin shit. and i wont let u suffer too. even tho i got a feeling ull b mad about that too. im really sorry! i cant think straight rit now, and if i could maybe id think to go to sleep, or maybe id think to phone u............maybe i should just give up? people always falter...dont they..? *sigh* it's tru...watz the point...watz the point of doing this? i think this hasta do wid my dream...u.u no respect, unapreciation...ill stay up for nothing. and in the end ill b hurt and tired and sick and grumpy.  : (             ....yeah.......*a lil bit later* yays! yays! he's going to sleep! *jumps around* it was worth it! it was worth it! *heeheeheehee....!^_~ hoshi-chan wins the day!!! *flies away*  hey..i dun fly...*falls* ow... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       not to long ago i was crying but now...im here, in front of the computer, my pain yet a small familiar ache in my gut, but, im fine...not thinking about the pain and indifferent/satisfied. so, hidden beneth wat the computer can give me...is this greif. a worn out heart, that has felt this pain so often. now i treat it as a familiar setting...now i ignore it. *cracks fingers and looks off into the distance* wat can i do? i suppose live day but day, reminding myself as to why the pain's there..  y am i posting here...? cause i just recently posted something new, and i kno how u dude's dun like reading too many *new* things, so there >P  Boo-chan, aishiteru  ~HoShi*  ah, i suddenly start missing u a lot... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aoccdrnig to a rscheearch at an Elingsh uinervtisy, it deosn't mttaer in waht oredr the ltteers in a wrod are, the olny iprmoetnt tihng is taht frist and lsat ltteer is at the rghit pclae. The rset can be a toatl mses and you can sitll raed it wouthit porbelm. Tihs is bcuseae we do not raed ervey lteter by it slef but the wrod as a wlohe. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Summation     First, a little recapturing of past events. After NLS and before school, the only event worth mentioning was my visit to Woodside to participate in the final duel monsters tournament till who-knows-when. The admission was free (and no, we did not have to pay at the door). I won 2 out of 5, which wasn't that bad, considering my previous records at tournaments ^^;;   Anyhow, as school started, 3 new people arrived at Mary Ward... hoshi and dyt were expected, but aiza was a surprise ^^;; i must admit that that plot was hidden well.    There's a huge flood of 9ers and transfer students this year, over 300 9ers... it's crazy. Many resource areas were filled on the first day 0 because of this. Luckily, the Focus room is now opened, but that's besides the point. Oh, and we get to use the auxiliary cafe this year, so that's cool too.    Despite my resolutions to stay on track, I'm doing worse than last year... =\ 0 units handed in on time, and 1 unit done as far. *sigh* hopefully, I'll get back on track. Getting back on track is a must for me. This is also because intramural and varsity chess is starting soon ^^ yay! THis was something that was missing last year.   IF my typing seems bad, it's because I'm not too used to this keyboard... this cordless keyboard and mouse... it's something my sister's bf won for her over a online raffle thingy. THe downside is of course the use of batteries. Personally, I prefer the old kind of keyboard, I rather not invest in this sort of luxury, it's not something I need.   Ah.. Exit -> Running is playing ^^ besides last night, the last time I've heard it was a long time ago. It's one of my fav Slayers songs. 2 new songs I've never downloaded before and liked are Silent Weapon and Brave Heart, both from Shaman King (I'm starting to collect some shaman king songs).    Sorry if I worried people about my sleeping-late habits, but night is when I'm most productive, so I need to crunch out the hours.    ~ Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Doubt yourself and you doubt everything you see. Judge yourself and you see judges everywhere. But if you listen to the sound of your own voice, you can rise above doubt and judgment. And you can see forever.  Nancy Kerrigan 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Cold Rage (read previous post first)     I want to rant some more, cause I haven't been this angry in a long time.    If my dad wanted a child who was completely obedient to him, he should've gotten himself a friggin (I'm trying really hard to refrain from obscenities) robot. He'd fit right in a friggin dictatorship government. Award those that support you, kill those that don't. Not that he awards me for the things I've done right, but then again, he doesn't exactly kill me for the things I don't do right, so I guess it's kinda even.   At times like this, I remember an experience from childhood (Umm... I wonder if I wrote this in Blogger before... don't recall). A math contest was being held, and for like 2-3 weeks, my dad was making to a lot of math exercises. One night, I guess I kinda broke down and cried, and he hit me, saying something like "this is a math lesson, you can't cry during lessons!" The morning of the contest, I must've cried a bit, because I remember my eyes was all red and stuff, and my neighbour's parents (whose children was also participating in the math contest) was asking my parents what'd happen.    Well, anyway, I feel a bit better now, writing down stuff really helps ^^;; the only problem now is telling people that I'm switching to canto/mando... =\  some people were expecting me to be there and I told them that I would... I don't like breaking promises much... =\ *sigh* I wonder if I'll know anyone in my future classes...    oh, that kinda reminds me of another thing my dad said tonight: "are you just taking it for fun??" (note: though this seems like a question, he expects only one answer and I gave that to him) I said "no, I just want to try it out" (which was true, but this seemingly innocent sentence caused him to get angrier, don't ask) In my mind, I was like "Hell yea! What the hell's the point in life if I can't learn what I want to learn?"   ~Chronos (Cooled Down a Bit) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Failure     Ok, just one week before registration for saturday school, my dad suddenly tells me I can't take the japanese beginner's class. Normally, I let this sort of thing pass, wash over me, cause I know that arguing would make things worse. But after being constantly told by people to argue and stuff, I did, tonight.    So, I tell my dad that I want to take the beginner's japanese class instead of the canto/mando whatever-the-hell he wants me to take. He tells me I can't master the language in one year, and that he wants to "complete learning" the other languages, and that he had no objections to me learning beginners japanese if I had "perfected" chinese. I said something about how saturday school isn't going to help me perfect it anyway. Then he became really pissed and stuff. Which leads me back to my original philosophy, don't argue against parents in subjects like these, because they're just going to be jerks and be stubborn about it, and moreover, they're going to get even more pissed cause I'm "talking back" to them.   Anyway, after that, I closed the door to my room so I can seethe in silence, the he came back for no (insert profanity here) reason, even more pissed off than before and saying "are you throwing a tantrum??". I'm like "no, I want some quiet so I can work". Then he got even angrier, and practically shouting "Who's making it so it's not quiet?" (oh, and remember I'm translating too, so it may be imprecise)... and I was thinking in my head "ummmm... i WONDER". But I said nothing. Then he was pointing at the computer, and said "what about that music?? you said you want quiet??", so i was like "music doesn't bother my concentration", and my dad shouted (by now he was like bursting - which i don't get why, cause I'm the one who loses in the end) "So I'M an annoyance to you???". I said "no...", course, in my mind, I was like "YES!! SO GET THE HELL OUT!!". After a while he left saying "the older you get, the more disobedient you get!!"   It's only a short version of the entire conversation, but trying to recall it fully and type it all out makes it worse than it is now. So yah, so much for debating and communicating. I'll keep this in mind if I ever have the remotest desire to talk to parents about anything.   ~Chronos (severely pissed off) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey guys.  I just found a site with a lot of nice drawings!  ^-^  I thought some people here might want to take a look at it.   urlLink     -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         d.r.e.a.m.: distorted reality emitted - all messed-up     Actually remembered a dream last night. The reason why I remembered is probably because during the dream, I had explained my situation to 2 people, by creating a "memory" in my dream to explain from, it kinda reinforced my memory of the dream. Anyway, without further ado, my dream:   I don't remember much from the beginning of it... some stuff and conversations to various people inside the school. The part where I start to remember is when I was talking to Tom Volpe (some guy in my TA) in some classroom. They were cutting off student's hands so they could put bracelets around them, then reattaching the hands. (Don't ask me how this makes sense ^^;;)    I was hesitant to go and have that done to my hand, but Tom was like saying they make it so it doesn't hurt and stuff. I watch as they put some kinda cream around Mina's (some short 9er in my TA) wrist, then cut it off. Then they attached the bracelet, and put the hand back on and putting some cream around the wrist again. After seeing this, I was like "ok... it might not be so bad afterall.   At that point though, I thought of an excuse. I was like "my parents' are going to freak if they found out my hand was cut off", because the operation kinda leaves a scar around the wrist. Tom was like *shrugz* and went to get his hand cut off (I didn't actually see that happen, since I was leaving by then).   Afterwards, I was outside with a bunch of people. It was night time. I was talking to a friend... I think it was Donald. We were watching the sky, and I was like... "hey, it's a spaceship!" The spaceship kinda looked like this: "|__)", of course, like bigger, and with lotsa details.    After that, subway trains started arriving one after the other. There were monsters and stuff in each one, and they weren't particularly full. The crowd started choosing their subway trains to enter, and I had this gut feeling that those trains would carry them to adventures. Donald was entering one of them, and I was like "hey, don't go, wait for an empty one", but he left anyway. So, I kept waiting for an empty one, but there wasn't, and all the trains have left, and I was just standing there alone.     I thought all of them were going to die or something, but not much later, the trains started coming back, and they returned. Then some alien person came out and told us to board the train that we were previously on. You could tell which train was which by the monsters in them. (Ummm...i think i recall a skeleton and a jack-o-lantern thingy, but not much besides that). So, the trains started coming back again. However, there was a small crowd left, and I was obviously part of that crowd since I had never boarded one in the first place.    The alien person was like saying "congratulations, you all made first place". And I was like "oO;; o...k...". We boarded the spaceship, and then I saw Aiza amongst the crowd, so I was like "hey!". I went to her and started telling her how I got there, and she told me how she got there too (i forgot her story... for some reason, I think there was a horse somewhere in there). Anyhow, I started kissing her for some odd reason oO;; well, not on the lips, but yah...    After that, I was talking to the alien person, and he was like "congratulations!", and I was like "oh... but i didn't really do anything..." and explained again how I got there. He kinda turned from friendly to angry, since I got there so easily... but then, he kinda was grudgingly nice after that.    The scene then cut to Social Science resource area, where these group of 4 or so were like at a table, and I just knew that their job was to think of stuff. Then this girl stood up and was saying something to the extent of "I can't take this anymore!". In my mind, I was like thinking "oh... the only way you're going to get out of this job is if you commit suicide." And for some reason, I think all the "winners" was going to receive this job...    An odd dream... pretty interesting. Tell me what you think of it.    ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A Ward Award Night     Ahh... tonight was Award Night and I managed to get 1 st  in Cayley (waterloo math contest) and CNML (canadian national math league). Got a medallion and a piece of paper, respectively. Um... wanted the computer science award, but they didn't hand one out for the junior category for that subject, ah, oh well.    See, the thing is... i really shouldn't be getting awards. I didn't really try hard (I rarely do when it comes to school), so basically they're awarding me for something my parents hammered into my head when i was a kid. Umm... well, I guess you can kinda consider it compensation for that suffering... I dunno.    Award systems are really screwed up. Most likely, only 50% of the time, they'll go to the people that deserves it best. That's cause the only person who knows how much people have tried is God (or some other divine, all-knowing entity). Sure, there can be educated guesses when the candidates are people you know well. But when it comes to stuff like tonight, 50% is a fairly good estimate, IMO, considering they're just going by marks.    Of course, marks tell some of the story... you'd sometimes get higher marks if you try harder.   So, now back to real life facts: von won art award. justin chow, mike ip, tracy li, brian kwan got waterloo certs. donald got the cert and music award. karen ho got some award and the cert. nick cologna and kyle bibby got awards... mandy mcbean got top academic for gr10 amongst other awards. Last year 9ers - Josh liu and lily so - swept most of the awards in that grade.    It was interesting... my mom drove me, justin and his mom to ward... i feared for my life, cause my mom hasn't driven in like years. But all was well. For the first half, i was with them, then the second half, i went to sit with brian, tracy, donald and karen. So nice meeting friends there.    In other news, I'm behind like crazy, and chess, anime, newspaper and CSUNA will help me to do that more ^^   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       kie...kay! an update! there *will* be a new layout!! *hushes applaudes* and yes...it *has* been created and was created by *me!!* *bows* ^_^     Keane: "it's really good! i like it a lot!"  my first attempt failed...but, i think this one is a success....hopefully we can have it up and running in no time. (sorry about the lack of info...Eiko-chan is rushing me...*-* *lol*)    ~HoSHi*   p.s i want photoshop!! *tears*   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Tetsusaiga: "Iron-Pulverising Fang"!     Watched 12 episodes of Inuyasha this morning (woke up at 6:30am for some reason), and so far, I liked the 4 episodes where Inuyasha gets Tetsusaiga the most. I've seen most of the 12 episodes in english, and when compared, they seem to match fairly well. There could've been a lot that they could've edited, but they didn't, so kudos to them. Oh, not to mention they left the OP and ED fairly intact.   Speaking of anime, anime society was ok... lotsa problems on the first day. Lotsa people too. Ana-sama was late around an hour, cause she just came back from an art trip. Then there were "Technical difficulties" which prevented us from watching anime at all ^^ so bascially we just chatted and sketched, which was cool, but still.    Ahh... the sun dispersed all the clouds in the sky... must be a sign ^^ ... to get to work...    Addendum: happy thxgiving people! ^^ jus finish watching up to eps 32 of Inuyasha, that's all i have on me. Boy, did I ever underestimate the interesting-ness of that series... it's actually pretty good.    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Many people were at the University Fair.   As Belky, Lynn, Renae, Victor and I were driven downtown by Renae's brother, much worry was bestowed upon myself as well as others as Renae was visually ailing.  Arriving after an unenventful journey, the father of time itself could give no guess as how we would fare.   Although, that was not how the day was started.  For in the morning, the schooling with which we were to part take in was all worthy enough to have a post of its own in this humble book of lives and life.  When arriving at O'Conner, time was painstakingly consumed as those longing for lessons only arrived at a storage room.  Our information being more than a little distorted, Veronica and I failed to locate the room we were to train our Japanese language.  Though, after extensive search, we arrived at the proper area, just in time to start our hour-long wait for a teacher.  After recieving notice of our teacher's absence, the class in its entirity migrated accross the hall to the Eleventh/Twelfth grade class.  The teacher, a wonderfully funny Filipino man reverted to a review stage and many of us learned the uses of Particles and counting systems.  I created about half a page of notes that is currently in the possession of Veronica.  After missing the break, we were let out about 60 seconds before the anouncment that instructed teachers not to dismiss their pupils until the bell.  The very, very loud bell that met us while we greeted Renae.   After hasty goodbyes and a few phone calls, we (Renae and I) were on our way to her house to wait for the others.  Thus you find us where I left off, arriving downtown at the Convention Center Building North.  On our way to the South building, we bumped into Anne-Margareth and Donald's group.  (Please, excuse spelling).   Most of the people reading this should know what happened next.  There was an argument.  The details of which don't have to be displayed, but the 5 minute argument ended with me walking off and sitting at a bench for over an hour.     After returning, I was found by a teary Renae and an also worried Victor.  After meeting with an angry Belky and a stalling-Renae's-mom-on-the-phone Lynn, I took Renae to talk over alone.  Most likely another hour passed before Renae and I returned.  During which I learned of how sick tired Renae ran around the convention center looking for me.  I learned how she almost fainted from fatigue.  I learned how much pain, suffering and humiliation she went through.   All I can say about this experience is, I'm sorry to everybody that's involved for what I did.  And I'm sorry to Renae.  I love you, and I make a promise on this day, and on this page to prove it to you in all my actions, and do the opposite of what happened on that day.  I will always try my hardest to only give you what you deserve, the best, and always only the best.  I'm sorry to those involved, and thank you to everyone for taking your time reading this.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Angry beyond words     My mind is muddled right now... all i kno is that i'm angry... very angry... possibly the angriest i've been in my life... probably the most hatred my mind and heart had hosted for a long time, if not ever... over such a *small* thing too... he made a threat... to transfer me...  eh... should be used to it... plenty of threats... still... it is the moment... the feeling... seems or will seem like nothing in retrospect... but right.now. ... i swear... if he does... i cannot guarantee that his safety through the night...    sorry keane.. i didn't get ur msg... u msged at a rather inconvenient time... right in the middle of the argument... dun worry.. i dun blame you.. it's ok.. i closed it before he noticed anything...    crying... no.. not tears of sorry or defeat... but of anger... when i get really angry...i can cry... which is odd... but oh well... is it a sign of weakness..? ...    right now... want.to.hurt.him.so.badly.... so much hate... it does not suit me... yet there it is...    sorry hoshi... if u haf a bday party this year... dun even invite me... the odds of me going ... at this current time and point... are 0... dun even try to convince me... i dun want to ask anything from  that monster ... i hope u understand... it'll hurt me even more if u try to get me to try to go...    another mess on top of week.. month ... of messes... i'm going to reach the breaking point soon... if i haven't already... dun worry... give me a few days then i'll be bright and cheery again... rite now... i am ... angry... no other word to describe it... nor does that word even start to describe... how i feel...   tears of anger demand retribution... for someone who makes such a cowardly threat... for someone who knows nothing about my situation and thinks he knows everything... for someone who's - in all my 16 years of experience - bullied to get his way with his children... threats - carried out or not, physical or psychological. Understanding comes too hard for him.    heh... it's funny... one of the things he said "the older you are, the harder it is for you to learn!" ... same to you, buddy, same to you...   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Change in Pace     Question: where are the other people that are suppose to blog here?   C'mon, you guys shouldn't waste such a beautiful layout ^^ yes... it is indeed very good... good job!   Now, my random ramblings which I hope to cut short, as I know people find long posts tedious and boring and impossible to get through.    There's been quite a few failures recently for me... parents finally found out how far behind I am, which I shouldn't be in the first place. So yah, it means that I have to work harder. Basically it means less wasting time, and less MSN. Which isn't that bad I guess. Also, there was the entire thing about AM which was a total mess, but won't get into that. Then there was horrible goal-tending at 3-ball in our latest game... we manage to pull off a win because of Hanson's buzzer beater, which is good. I certainly hope I can do better next monday facing the winner of JR vs Kyle Bibby's team. Oh, and it was certainly a disappointment when BC lost today (13-9) *sigh* I was hoping that that team would win the championship. eh, and not to mention I left Lynn waiting on the phone for half-hour... =\    Despite this, I'm not really that depressed or anything, don't get that impression ^^;; for a change, I actually got some units done this week, and will start to wake up/sleep early starting today. Woke up at around 6:00, got out of bed at around 6:30 ^^;;   um... where were you guys today? (directed at keane and renae) I - nor a bunch of other people - saw you, so either a) you skipped, b) were both coincidentally sick, c) are dead, d) combination of the above. There might be some possibilities that I missed... but anyhow, I hope you guys are alrite ^^;; oh, and we saw Animatrix today.   ...which was unfortunate for Kwan and Jacky, as they both couldn't make it, and both wanted to see it. I thought that Animatrix was pretty good... they also did a little documentary thingy about Anime and its history at the beginning too... but eh... I saw the best parts of it already: Detective Story and Renaissance I and II. The other have "=\" animation, with the exception of "Program" and "Final Flight" which were runner-ups on my favourites list. The last one - "matricution" - left me with a "???" expression.    So much for keeping it short =P    ~ Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         CSUNA: Catholic Student's United Nations Assembly     Ah... I had mixed feelings going in and out of CSUNA. Going into it, I was fairly apprehensive (thanks to "The Giver" for the word =P ) ... I was hoping to make this year to be a success, something I had hoped last year, but the one day break I had to take because of Computer Symposium snapped my train of thought.    I was also a bit disappointed... the usual crew that goes is diminished to me and my partner kyle. Opening night was fairly disappointing too... there were some good introductions, but eh... and our Norwegian introductory speech got boo-ed =P it was about how we'd kick their asses in the 2006 Winter Olympics... well, Jason Lee was the one that actually siad the phrase, but still ^^;; could've been better... if Guinea Bassau hadn't stolen our line.    y'see... SJMP people have like... tons of school spirit... and everytime one of those delegates go up, the rest would cheer like crazy ^^;; so like... we thought of saying that we're from SJMP too... but the delegates from Guinea Bassau took those lines before we could say them ^^;; found out from the Libya delegation that they were 9ers from st.mike's... they did pretty good for 9ers.    Anyhow, I won't bored you guys with play-by-play for every one of those days... some highlights:   - the best delegate (Macedonia... a 10er from our school) in EcoSoc was kicked out because of his shoes, while some others were wearing jeans... he lost his steam and didn't participate as much afterwards... leaving the award to an undeserving Haiti delegate... i mean, good gods... i'd support Finland, or Belgium at the least.   - a quarter my saturday school class was there... 2 from SJMP, 1 from st.joseph college, 2 from st.mike's choir, and of course, me ^^;;   - other people i knew was a bunch from brebeuf, and an old gifted classmate ^^;;   - pizza on the first night... and donuts on the other two days   quotable quotes: (not 100% to-the-letter, memory not that good)  - U.S. : "we can get rid of weapons by dumping them in the desert!"  - Haiti : "if we don't reduce the prices for software, people in impoverished nations can't afford them!  - Norway: "Why would people in impoverished nations need to buy software...?"  - (almost lunchtime) Some country: "I motion that we do clause-by-clause voting because there are many points in here that contradict each other, and that voting for this resolution would go against many countries foreign policy."  - Guinea Bassau: "one word... lunch"  - U.S.: "Right of Reply! He just accused us of being terrorists!"  - Macedonia: "what? what was that? i can't hear you because of the bombs dropping"   (Closing ceremonies: odd, random activities)  U.S.: (when asked "if a cat was thrown out of the window, would it be considered kitty litter?")... so NO, it should NOT be considered "kitty litter", how can you call it that??... it's "road kill"   Back to points of interest:   - Jeff Bogues won "best delegate ever".... there were 10 contestants chosen by the audience beforehand through a ballot. There were like 4-5 rounds... one in which they had to answer a not-so-simple question (like the one above), another where they had to advertise a false movie (e.g. The Meatrix, Pirates of Lake Erie, Find Speedo), sing a song about whatever the guy in charge chose, then the final one was why they should be considered world leader   - The candidates were eliminated if they drew the least amount of votes and/or applause. Bogues drew the second-biggest votes/applause until the final round, where he scored an upset over the U.S. delegate from Brebeuf. Hafta hand it to the guy from 'beuf tho... he sure knew how to sing.    - got through a record of 8 resolutions this year. compare this to the two resolutions that we got through last year.    - New rooms were added... NATO and CSD alternated days. Old rooms remained: Security, HR (human rights), GA (general assembly), and EcoSoc (economic/social).   - CSUNA's 10th anniversary is next year   - Bogue's shocked a lot of us by delivering a serious speech about child poverty on opening night... we had expected humour.    - I did a lot better than last year. Compare 3-time Speakers' list, opening night speech, handful of amendments, dozen of "point of orders", a few "point of informations", and a bit of participation in the moderated caucus.... to opening night speech and one "point of order". I also manage to net at least 5 votes for one of the awards... not much, but hey ^^   - While i was gone... my 3-ball team won. So ... we're 2-2-0 now ^^;;    There ends my random ramblings.    Ah... CSUNA was draining... there's a lot of difference between participating a lot, and observing a lot... participation takes more energy, and you have like no time to send pages for fun - something which i did in abundance the years before. It's also a lot like acting... I swear... I have never did so much public speaking on a voluntary basis. I had to feign confidence and humour... it seemed to work well ^^;; except i wasn't consistant... i should've gone up more than i did if i wanted the award.    Ah... guess that'll be all, laterz   ~ Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Next Two: Read Previous Post First Please ^^     So, it ends up to be first is first... ohhh welll...   Buddhism day was rather... interesting..? well, i'd say it was something worth going to. The video at the beginning actually had my attention for 2 hours... without me falling asleep... which is saying something. Well, the Romero video last year caught my attention too... but yah. Pretty good feats for educational videos.    Oh, Keanu Reeves starred in that Buddhism Video... lol, i swear, the Matrix had lotsa ideas that were similar to "Little Buddha" (that's the name of the video). For instance, there was an awakening (aka awake from Matrix). There was a search for the reincarnation of the Buddha (aka "the One"). Instead of stopping bullets, Keanu Reeves stopped a bunch of flaming arrows.   His acting style is about the same too... the nearly emotionless, short-sentenced person. The only thing that was missing was some nice martial arts =P   Speaking of which, martial arts was my first workshop, out of 3. It was ok... none which can be used in real life, and the person that's  supposed  to be doing the workshop was absent. Next, it was Buddhism symbols... since it was "mandatory", i didn't have much hope for it, but it was actually quite interesting. Lastly, there was food... not really interesting... but... food! i mean, c'mon... free food.    After school, i went down to anime, but then, karen was like stressing over newspaper, and she was working on something that was supposed to be my workpile  anyway  (she took charge of it after it became clear we needed a better article). So i decided to do my share of the work, and spent around 2 arounds working on it.   Managed to get it done too... hopefully, newspaper would be ready for tomoro. Mike Sitayeb was saying how it was ok .. but karen was like "noooo... not good enough... change stuff"... so i stayed an extra hour till i got her i-give-a-damn-anymore approval ^^ *sigh* i'm easily satisifed... i'm not suited to become a layout artist. Anyhow, i really feel sorry for karen, who had to stay behind for god-knows-how-long to supervise the rest of the layouting. And for Mike, who i know also put in long hours for the paper.   Such hard-working people our editors our... they do the thankless, creditless yet necessary work...    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         The Post of Three: Afterschool events, Buddhism Day, and 3-ball     Ok, last thing first... 3-ball was really amusing, and here's the rundown:   B.C. wins 11-6 over Nunavut   historical note: (those who have access to Nanpan, skip the next part)     how i joined: some guy came up to me and asked me to be goalie, so i agreed   fun fact: did you kno that european handball is actually an Olympic sport?   what it is: basically, soccer with hands. up to 3 steps, and hold ball for up to 3 secs. throw ball in net.   teams that are playing: i believe i'm part of team "nunavut" and we're facing "b.c.", which is more or less the team with mostly Holy Spirit people (including justin, who is DYT's bro).   team records: nunavut - 1 win 1 loss. BC - 2 win 1 loss   my betting line: BC wins by 6   come down to the gym at lunch to see my team get slaughtered ^^     Nunavut team record: 1-2-0 B.C. team record: 3-1-0   Game notes: my betting line was pretty close... instead of winning by 6, BC won by 5. Star player today, IMO, would be Francross, who did some amazing goaltending. In 3-ball, 6 points is  very  little. To my credit, people said that i did a good job too. I guess i can be satisfied... BC had won 20-17 in a gruelling match against a gr.12 Phys.Ed team.   Chris and Derek team were against Jeff's team... Jeff (sue ping)'s team won 16-5...    joe, josh, sheryl, jacky, and i think, crystal and tracy came to watch... so that's cool...   overall, i hope that BC wins the intramural tournament... they've been "scouting" everyday, and it's the only team in which almost the entire team are friends. They're also pretty skilled, needless to say... their 3-1-0 record speaks for themselves. BC overcame odds in a stronger gr.12 team by playing more intelligently. All they need to do is overcome Conor's team and Emer's team. Right now, BC is 2nd overall.   Ahh... busted up my knees and ankles today ^^;; the gym floor is hard   will post the other two events later   ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Treats and... tricks?     Ah, since no one seems to want to report on our nice little halloween party, I will ^^ ph34r my biased post >P   Surprisingly, my parents gave me permission to go to the party... i spent most of my morning doing paper route and checking out groups and wasting time on various games.    Then my dad came home, and I decided almost last minute to throw together a costume that i used for my last trick-or-treat thingie... in like... gr7. Oh, and that costume was also used for my criminology project, i believe. A simple detective-looking hat and trench ^^;;    Surprisingly, I was the 3rd person to arrive. And I arrived later than the 3:00 that was stated. Von and Mishi were already there... we played a bit of vids, then watched various shows that were not scary (even tho they're supposed to be). Jade came by, but left... Lynn, Keane, Aiza, and Victor came later, in that order, more or less.    By then, we were playing hide-and-seek outside, in the dark ^^ that, imo, was the funnest part of the day. Definitely something new, lol... but the people who saw us must've thought we were crazy >P   Around the time they started telling stories, I left (I'm usually first to leave ^^;; )    Anyhow, got no work done the next day (sat school + dragged to mississauga), nor the next (church + runescape + chatting). Well, Sunday was my fault, the others were unavoidable.    My brain is really messed from yesterday ^^;; so confused, umm... hoshi said i was giddy... i don't think so tho, lol... giddy's a funny word ^^   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Me-ri-su Ku-ri-su-ma-su? ^^;;     hey people! Just wanted to say Merry Christmas ^^ it's around 1 and a half hours into Christmas right now in Eastern time.    Ahh... just came back from a party at Eric's house. And no, I didn't go there of my own free will... eric's family are family friends ^^ so the entire family was there. That's not to say I didn't enjoy the evening.. I did ^^;; There were a bunch of people there that I didn't know... in fact, the only kid i knew there was Eric =P   We played some Marvel vs Capcom (ahh... the old days of PS), some CS (counterstrike - in which i suck at), and duelled a bit (duel monsters!)   Well, hopefully everyone has phunn!! (Addicted to *phunn* ever since i saw 'fisiks is phunn' at OCS... that phrase made me laugh =P)   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         An end... and a beginning?     umm... i really should've spent my 1st period watching Finding Nemo... but eh... spent time hallwalking and picking up an eng unit. oh... that and 3 ppl gave me christmas cards... makes me feel bad =\ for not reciprocating   In any case, the assembly was cool as usual ^^ last year's was better... cause some jokes were drawn out too long... and when that happens, things get painful. Eh... but seeing Bellisario in Mario outfit was worth it =P   Trish's group, and keane/renae/lynn left before the assembly... and a bunch of other people left right afer, then more after lunch. There was like... around 50 students left in the school. Me, keane and fillazola were talking about how we beat the TCDSB: we got our half-day anyway. Teachers not only turn the other way, but a lot left too.    The 4th and 5th periods were spent in the science resource area. Was going to hang around with jacky since she seemed to be the only one left... but couldn't find her, so ended up going to comm. There i found some more 11ers... but they ended leaving.. so yah. That was how i ended up in science with DYT and the rest of her 9er friends =P     Keane came back, and around that time Ross ended up having a keyboard set up, along with some music sheets for people wanting to sing carols and stuff. There was actually some pretty singing ^^   After that nice and eventful day, went home aka prison where my dad gave me another lecture/threat... ehh... i think my patience is running low... he's starting to piss me off again, it's like, u'd think i *didn't* pass all my courses last year, with good marks no less. won't waste ur time on the same stuff again ^^    Looking forward to a friggin hellish christmas stuck at home. can't go out cause of aforementioned crap and hafta work like craxy. My two main problems ever since ...ever...: parents and school. When they mix - like how it's going now - it's ... well... y'kno.    christmas is really not good time for negativity ^^ so leave off with some positive thoughts... almost happy 1 yr for keane + renae ^^ yay! d/l some Initial D songs, and found that i actually liked them ^^ yay! Today was phunn, esp. 4th and 5th, the lightest and most relaxing day i've had in a lonngg while ^^ yay!    ~Chronos    ps must be... iinnnvviiiccttuuss!!!  pps to keane: i think we were all high or something, so disregard wat u saw today =P, if something happens then yay, if not, then eh ^^;;  ppps ooopss... sorry for pushing ur post down yet again =  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I moved...   We not in the same house anymore.  My parents haven't found a house yet, so we're at a family friend's house downtown for a while.  ^-^   We left the house on Tuesday and  maaaaan  we were late.  We were packing until laaaaaate into the night even though we were supposed to get out at 2 pm.  We finally got most of it out into trucks (and the rest in the garage) around 12 or 1 in the morning.  And a lot of our stuff was stored in a guys house in Ajax.  Completion...  2:15-2:30?  Arrival at the overnight stay at a friend's near Parkway (and Senator O'Conner) was probably around 3 to 3:30.  I might have slept for 30 to 60 minutes that night.   Last night we went to another place downtown.  That's where I am now.  Oooo... I so tired...    Rei just said to go to bed... >.   Oooooo... Eyes... I'll try to post more often!  ^-^   -ArV   ps.  Today at anime we saw Initial D.  Rei thought it was boring.  I liked it.  I sat on something and my shirt got itchy for the rest of the day.  I think someone swept sawdust into the corner of the video studio... :-s 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A less angry rant     I think I'm close to mastering self-control when it comes to my dad. I think I composed myself much better this time... and through that, I was able to think better and analyse the situation more.   Basically, my dad keeps to a single complaint (variating the presentation and peppering his speech with different threats and putdowns): i'm behind in my sciences. He can't even say I'm behind in my courses, because that would be not true. In fact, I'm actually ahead in three of my courses, which interestingly is something my dad seems blind to.   Keeping my mind clear during his lectures is most amusing, i see things that i would otherwise not see: he kept pointing at the chart "it's now december and you're suppose to be at this amount of units!! *points at sciences which are at 2s and 3*", then i stare below my sciences and see 3 other courses surpassing that line. Umm... looks like my dad might be partly blind... old age is really getting to him.   Later, he gives me another mini-lecture, which is basically the same message, except worded differently.    Now on to the purpose of lectures.    What I believe.. is that lectures are my dad's way of venting his frustrations (frustrations not only because of me, but elsewhere too). He has no other way of venting it, and uses me as a scapegoat. Does he believe that these lectures would help me? I doubt it... it's like... someone's incessantly yelling and insulting you... would you be more likely to listen to them? Or less likely? Ummm... tough choice.    Au contraire, these lectures are wasting my valuable working time - which ironically lowers my chances of accomplishing the goals of those lectures sooner. It also causes me to be angry. I do not like to be angry. But my dad insists on transfering all that anger and frustration to me. That is well and all, but he could do something more productive to vent his anger... like take up some hobby or something.    In conclusion, his lectures are simply powertrips for him. I must maintain my composure and not let my emotions get the best of me, 'else what happened 2 blogs ago would happen again. Umm.. but I could so tell that my dad gets even more angry when I appear calm... he prefers me broken down. He has that bully instinct =P oh well, what can you expect from a prison guard.    ~Chronos  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         European Handball Wrap-up     Well, it's been an amusing time... today, we lost the championship match for our conference. There were a few things that were not right about that game tho...: the team we were facing subbed in 3 good players from other teams; Dever does not know how to count; the winning shot was made on a travel. Other than that, it was like our other games, except with better passing than usual: Javiar gets the tip-offs, pass to hanson, score; or try to score.    I have no problem with hanson being a ball hog; he makes good shots. But when he's swarmed 3 to 1... it really couldn't kill to pass it to an open Kevin or Javiar... not to mention he went against our strategy of slowing things down when we're ahead... eh... oh well. All in all, i'd say we deserved that OT win... in fact... if it wasn't for those above points, we'd won it w/o going into OT, like we did last time (we played during regular season, and beat them by one)   Anyhow, there are two more games of 3-ball (Conor's team vs Fadi's team, and the All-star game), then onto other intramurals, presumbably 4 v 4 volleyball. Dunno if i should join... maybe if people want me to...    Eh... i will be dropping casual remarks about this in my article on 3-ball.. lol, it'll be something to toss my frustration against. I wouldn't be so frustrated if the team we were facing wasn't (a) unable to win without outside help, (b) trash-talking, cocky 10ers.    Besides that, life's been fairly good... thx to keane, renae and von for coming out to watch ^^ it's greatly appreciated... u really didn't need to sacrifice a practise for that... thx again   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Fast Forward to the Past     A quick rundown of what has happened since... 2 weeks ago..? Wow, that doesn't seem like too long, yet it seems like forever since this has been updated ^^;;   ok ok, let'see...  not much has happened, actually... been spending much time on English Unit 5 website (see  urlLink here  for the results of that).    Also, I've been spending time on Gunbound ^^ right now, my avatar is equipped with marine helmet, school uniform, rimless specs, and - costing my entire fortune - golden hammer. Just became a double stone axe, which means i'm barred from the newbie servers =\ ahh.. highest damage so far is 800+ w/ Grub's ss, then 750ish (Grub) and 700+ (Boomer). Been playing with Joe, kyle, phil, mike... um.. i think that's about it.    Besides that, chinese new year provided me with around 20-50 dollars so far ^^;; usually i net around 100-150 every year, and 100 goes to bank for savings, while the rest of it tides me over for an entire year =P (i spend very little as i don't get to go out often anyway). Better than money... chinese new year provided lotsa sugar!! SUGAR = GOOD!    Yesterday, went to parent's friend's house for more chinese new year celebrations. Forget the name of the person... but the house brings back memories... it's a pretty big house which I haven't seen for over a year or two, since it's usually adults and kids that go to such gatherings. Teens usually stay at home =P    I remember playing scavenger hunt with a bunch of people in the backyard... and the kid that fell into the tub of water with watermelons (only my sister would know what I'm talking about =P )... and other random moments. Interestingly, the two kids I was with yesterday, were about my age back then ^^;; the "second generation", lol. Not as fun for them tho =\ not as many people either.    Oh, and it's the year of the Monkey, for those that don't yet know.    In any case, the future promises to be busy: first dragonboat practise tomorrow, business day on wednesday, religion retreat and waterloo practise on thursday. Oh, and lotsa people have semi on friday.    Ah... and just found out Focus project was due tomorrow or the day after ^^ what fun   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Was kicked out of my house.  We're alright, staying at someone else's house, for a while anyway.  Don't have my computer (or my anime *WaaaAAAH*) but should get it back soon.  ^-^  Until then I have no access to internet unless through school.  Right now I hijacked Rei's laptop...  :)   Aa~~ kare wa kaerimasu!   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         A Lot of the Same: Normalcy     Ahh.. a whole year have passed and some things don't change: units, insecurities at times, some extracurriculars, talking to friends, sat school (jus had exam)... of course, under the microscope, nothing is really ever exactly similar. Extracurriculars may be different. I'm sure doing better in units than last year. Etc.    Some people would kill for such normalcy... those in countries with natural or man-made disasters... or even close to home, when income isn't always a sure thing. However, once you've conquered all those big problems, what next? Help others. There's always suffering and stuff in the world... and help is most appreciated.    Wouldn't it be funny... if people got what they hoped for, and everyone is well-fed, sheltered, stable job, and good health? Big problems ... all gone. I could just imagine... people looking around with a bewildered look..."what next?"    Then again, there's always room for civilization to grow... outer space to explore, new remedies to discover... however, civilizing the earth so far does not seem to benefit it much. Sure... we live longer now... but do we do more with our lives? Sure... we have all these conveniences and materials... but at what environmental cost? How long can we eat up the earth's materials, before it finally breaks down like a too-oft ridden horse?   I'm not saying progress is a bad thing... it's just that there's always balance.. no matter how much you advance, something else would deteriorate in its place. Which kinda contradicates my first point of how pointless it would be if the world was perfect, since if there's balance, it'll never be perfect.    Well, that closes off my random thoughts...    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I sit.  I type.  I read and watch.  All in waiting.  I work.  I play.  I hesitate and procrastinate.  Still I am waiting.  What do I wait for?  I do not know.  Maybe the school start.  The inevitable school end.  The school fail?  I wait quietly, though I feel like shouting.  No, I don't feel like shouting.  A voice shouts within me, screaming to be let out.  I am shouting.  How important is it?  No, really.  Why is it shouting?  It wants and end to this tired, old world.  This place of happiness and sadness and beauty and horror.  It wants a rest.  It wants to rest.  The voice feels ageless...  As if shouting for a time I cannot grasp or come close to if I try.  It makes me want to sleep...  Sleep.  School will come soon.  At once I dread the coming, yet long for it.  What does it mean?  Something about Pirates and Castles and Cave Drawings.  Why do these things seem closer to me right now than any school's halls do?  It feels as if...  They will return.  These signs of...  of something.  Until they do, I will be waiting.  No, the voice will wait, as I fulfill my own ventures and my own life and destiny.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HAPPY NEW YEAR EVERYBODY!!!  May this year bring us all we want but one thing, so we may always have a goal to strive for.  GOOD LUCK.  GOOD FORTUNES.  GOOD HAPPY!!!   HAPPY   NEW   YEAR!!!   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink irc.mircx.com   :'( that was my one and only anime irc network.  It had everything.  Those bastards...  Doesn't this mean that the place Em is a mod for ('s irc channel) went down too?  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Admin:  Hi.  It's me again, bringing you another exclusive interview with all the other parts of this giant machine we like to call society.  With me today is stud1413, a student full of dreams an aspirations to cha~   1413: Uh, not really.   Admin: Oh. Well, we have a resourceful, youn~   1413: *shakes head*   Admin: Um.  We have stud1413!  Tell the readers a little about yourself 1413.   1413: Well, I don't really know where to start.   Admin:  Your age, what you do, where you exist.   1413: I'm a student, hence my prefix and I am currently in my Eleventh Year.  Hopefully I can leave the educational facility that I am currently at to work as my father did, and his father before him (like most other fathers out there) in the unimaginative and resourceful workplace of the factories.  I hope to have no more than the 2 alloted children with whatever wife government gives me, hopefully I will be one of the lucky ones with a choice.  Maybe someday I'll move to Mars and work as a resource collector in the mines.   Admin: A very noble dream.  How, may I ask, is life treating you now?   1413: A pleasent life is always given by government and never anything less.  I enjoy my two square meals a day of  Soylent Green  and attend regular day school on my desk for the rest of my waking hours.  The teacher is very nice, I could not tell it was an artificial intelligence until you told me. And my classmates are very smart, much smarter than I am.  And much better students too.  At least, that's what my teacher  says .   Admin: And what do you do in your spare time 1413?   1413: Oh, the regulated excercises of course.  The automated treadmill, the holographic lifting appliance, and the electrical muscle motivator that stimulates my muscles with its electrical impulses.   Admin: Is that it?  Any secrets that you could share?  And hidden desires?   1413: Secrets...? Of course not!  I would enver keep a secret from government! Ever!   Admin: Oh of course not, and I would not ever assume as such.  What I meant was, any hidden desires (legal of course)?   1413: Oh... Maybe... Someday... I might get to see my birth parents, or even meet a classmate.  Just some form of communication with someone other than those Mr. Caretaker assigns... Not that they're bad or anything!! I really like Mr. Caretaker!! He is Very Nice!!   Admin: Well, thank you very much 1413 for the interview.  Maybe you can see it in the next issue of Always Dilligant, Machine Inscribed News. Always serving government with loyal devotion. These messages may be censored or changed without notice by goverment for he is all knowing and worthy of our devotion. :) Good-bye.   .The.End.   1413: ...but I'm not allowed to read that Newpaper...   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Of memories and present     Sorry to push your blog post down again >   wow, i've started my 5th archive file for this blog... blogark05.doc . i was just going through all of them when i saw the last post of blogark01... it was about how international night just finished. wow... tempus fugit, no? seems like yesterday... last year's international night. of course, many things have changed, and i'm not as excited... probably something that happens when an event loses its newness? who knows.    in any case, i think i might have bitten a bit more than i could chew =P let'see... 3rd issue of paper going to start soon, dragonboat, yearbook and reading book club joined recently, chess and anime are inactive... so lucky i didn't join intramural basketball and waterloo contests just ended ^^;;    speaking of newspaper, i'm pretty satisfied with the quality of this issue: it's bigger and better than last issue. and i actually got a bunch of feedback from people... my 3-ball article generated the most comments (ranging from "why aren't we placed higher on the list?" to "wow, cool article"). my v-ball - along with 3-ball - article generated comment only from artkin, who headed the intramurals. my saddam article generated favourable reviews from people...    ah, speaking of reviews, i was somewhat annoyed with a certain "alexiel" who burnt jax's article, but i figure she's not worth rant-space, so moving on. The newspaper special on the flood was pretty cool... i forgot that our school basement flooded until the newspaper reminded me =P    Along the lines of extra-curricular, dragonboat is exhausting... 15 mins running, 5 min formation running, push-ups, crunches, leg lifts, squats, "mission impossible"/"superman" (don't ask... they give weird names to exercises =P ), and if i stay for the after practise, more training ^^ all-in-all, i don't mind ... since the entire point for me to join was to get back into shape   Sorry for the long post... last thing i will mention is the focus debate. it really brought me back to the good ole ignatius days... i swear, everyone who's been in that gifted program knows that that place is *paradise*. And fittingly, any team who had ignatius people won at that debate... we swept the focus debates, go us! ^^ ah... i went all-out on my "worthy opponents" on that day... so fun ^^ during these formalized arguments thingies, i'm able to become more aggressive knowing there'll be no hurt feelings afterwards =P um... reminds me of CSUNA... but eh, the debate was cool ^^ good times... top debater for the two debates i've attended would be phil and carson.    kk, sorry again for the long post (then again, it wouldn't be me, if it wasn't a long post, huh? =P )   ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The place is a mess... Boxes, pots, pans, clothes.  Very messy, just moved.  Tired.  Waited on people for Valentine's thing-e at Rei's aunt's Church yesterday...  Just got computer less than week ago.  Just got Internet by stealing sister's line for the night.  :)  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Once Every Year, On the Tenth of the Second     Ah... it is nearly my birthday once again in approximately two days, and the celebration has just ended ^^   The day was really interesting... had it's ups and downs... let's take a quick look at them:   Pros:  - It was pretty long as my parties go... from 2 to around 10, even though i said 8 ^^;;   - I had fun... and i hope that people had fun too ^^  - People were there... especially vics who i don't get to see often   - The food was good, except for one thing (listed below as a con)  - I ownd at LF2 ^^  - pressies were cool: 40 dollar total, a weird maze game thingie, and a watch! i really like the watch ^^ (doesn't mean i don't like the others!)  - the cards were cool: especially vics! dude... u spent a lot of time on it! ^^ it is appreciated   Cons:  - renae and von couldn't come = - almost thought that we'd be stuck doing nothing  - as a conclusion: it should've been better planned =P  - the cheese-cake was horrble =P everyone agreed  - i was first eliminated at monopoly =P   - i get destroyed at duel monsters against eric and justin =P  - got creamed by justin at chess ^^;;  - the above 3 aren't really cons... i had tons of fun losing, seriously! it's fun just to play ^^;;   I gues that's about it... i mean... church, lunch, prepare, gunbound, victor arrive, a bit more gunbound, uncomfortable indecision on what to do, ashley/eric arrives, eric gets good idea to play monopoly, we play till keane comes, keane becomes banker somehow, justin arrives from cadets, we split into LF2 group and duelling group, dinner, back to two groups, cake, justin and i plays chess, everyone starts leaving starting with vics.    That's about it ^^   Addendum: that's odd... for some reason, my blog post keeps disappearing after awhile... =\ i have to re-publish it. In other news, thx sis for the card! ^^ wow... so much effort, it is much appreciated! ^^   Addendum: yay gift from keane is a rabbit inside glass ^^ cool! looks pretty =P   ~Chronos   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so here's a run down.   I want opinions...i don't rlly want corrections :P  So far I've been told that the story's "henchmen" are very western style, now, i don't rlly know how so, cause i dun watch american shows and such, but i kno from past experiance i dun LIKE that lol, ill see wat i can do also, hino-chan kinda annoying  otherwise imo there's lack of descrpition, seems rushed, bbut it's just for fun.  ~how come no1 is reading it!!! =_= POST! COMMENT! come on ppll!  :D  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Haruka peered through the window, carefully watching as Hinotama was directed towards the large inn. Looking away swiflty, she cracked her fingers and looked about the room, thinking. Finally deciding on a good plan of action, she picked up Hinotama's clothing, flooded them neatly and walked down the stairs in order to speak with the inn keepers. The man of the house gave her a stern look as she neared the kitchen. His wife and daughters huddled against a corner, the mother wrapping her amrs defensively around her children with a look of horror.  Haruka's cloudy eyes looked at them with indifference.  "Don't cause anymore trouble to our family!" the father suddenly yelled, his eyes filling with what seemed to be tears.  "What happened?" Haruka asked, her mind going over the images she saw of Hinotama being carried along. Who was that other young woman with them...?  "My eldest daughter! They took her dammit! Now leave my house!" he roared, throwing a pot at Haruka. Before it could hit her, she caught it with closed eyes.  "My apologies, I'll leave now," she said softly as she placed down the pot, "but I request one thing..."   Hinotama lowered her head as she entered the inn, knowing that in tradition she was not allowed to raise her head to the men. None the less, Hinotama had her ways to see around and marked every fine wooden corridor, classical paintings and every face of high class that held a weapon or too. The hallways weren't very crowded, so the men who handled her often took turns pinhcing her ass when Saro wasn't looking; Hinotama kept that in mind with a grin. Although all things were going as planned, she had hardly expected the inn keepers' daughter to be stolen. Hinotama glanced at the girl who whimpered with every step; the poor girl would be shared amoung many.   Hinotama suddenly fell to the ground in a great cry, startling everyone in her accompiment through the hallway.  Saro, startled more then any other, asked harshly as he hit Hinotama gently, "What the hell is your problem??"  "I am shamed! I do not know if I can face him!" she cried dramatically, tears pouring from her huge eyes.  "Get up bitch!" another man cried.  "I beg of you," she said with a sob, "allow me to take the girl with me! I do not want to go alone!"  There was a uproar with the men, all crying their protests. The girl, her skirts flustered and hair undone in a messy heap of black hair, widened her slender eyes in surprise and potential hope.  Saro, obviously stressed and wanting to get moving, pulled Hinotama to her feet roughly and pushed her forward.   "Not a chance, she's ours," he announced flatly, and the men gave out a gentle cry of excitement.   The girl sobbed once more, looked to Hinotama desperately and was then taken away.   Hinotama stared after her for the only moments she had left to before she was pushed in front of a screen door with a dim light burning behind it.   She lowered her head to the floor and pushed her kimono ends underneth her knees. Saro tapped lightly, being the only man left to escort Hinotama, and awaited to hear the voice of his lord.   A high pitched voice replied, that was none the less confident and relaxed. "Tell me what became of the strangers, Saro."  "They have vanished, my lord Seishuu, but left a gift for you and their deepest aplogies," Saro replied, sweat beeding down his forhead.  The candles flickered againt the paper door, causing odd releftions that appeared demon-like to dance along it's surface. Moments of silence seemed to take forever to pass, as Saro waited to see if his lord was upset, or pleased.  "Before I lecture you on letting them get away, tell me, Saro, what is this gift?"   Saro swallowed in relief, lowering his head and mumbling, "Just allow me to show you, my lord, and I'm sure you'll be pleased."  "Very well, come in," Seishuu commanded with a hint of agrivation.  Hinotama crawled on her knees into the room, and when told, looked up to the man Seishuu. He was old, very old, lines of age creasing even his bald forhead. Eyes like bottomless pits stared from where he sat on a sleeping mat and behind him, Hinotama could see three figures lying within the sheets. The room stunk of sweat and...other things, but she managed to compose herself easily enough as Seishuu's eyes searched over her longingly. It was Hinotama's time to shine. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Darkness has fallen," Haruka muttered as she slowly moved to the window, "but only last for about 10 minutes. Hardly enough time to accomplish anything.   The was a gentle rapping at the door, and Hinotama went to answer it, not before recieving a cold stare from Haruka.   One of the daughters of the house, who was about only 12 years of age, held in her hand a candle and a kimono in the other.    "Here you are...sir," she said with a mumble and bowed her head with a blush.  Hinotama smiled gently and pat the child head. "Thank you. Now off with you; to bed," she said with a wink.   As the door closed, Haruka asked, "What's all this about?" She could here the sound of Hinotama shuffling around, but making hardly any noise.  "No time Haru-chan," she responded lightly, "just stay there and be quiet."   Haruka looked away and edged into a corner.  "Ah," Hinotama said, "here are the necissities to hold my hair up. "Hashi!"  Haruka almost flinched,  eating utenils...?  she thought in puzzlement.   The men ignored the inn keepers and barged up the stairs of the small house. Being ordered by their master to dispose of any suspicious characters, they were more then happy to rid themselves of these annoying pests. The one who wore their hair short was a freak look alike, a walking disgrace, and not to mention the other who pranced around the village as if he were in charge.   Saro, a large man and the one in charge of the small gang consiting of five members, knocked loudly on the door. There was a cry from the room and the door swung open to reveal a beautiful woman kneeling on the floor. She was whimpering and sobbing and each man looked at one another with a wide grin.   Saro though, knew there was something he needed to know before he had any fun, so he held out a hand in front of his men before they let their ugly nature take over, and asked the woman, "Have you seen two men? They were supposidly loging in this room."  The woman whimpered and answered with a sweet voice, "They left me here, saying that I should be an offering to your lord for forgiveness! The wish to be forgiven, they say!"   The men all moaned, disapointed that their lord should get all the spoils. Each one knew that Saro wouldn't allow for misbehaivour and undamaged goods was  not  what their lord wanted.   Haruka watched as Hinotama was dragged from the room, Saro taking one last look at where she hide; Haruka did not move and was not seen. Light of the Moon shown through the window, reveiling a slight, almost unnoticable grin on Haruka's lips.  "So, this was your plan all along...Hino-chan..." she mummbled; Haruka prepared herself.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       that i will write a story here! cause i feel like it! (DONT SPELL CHECK IT!!!)   Haruka and Hinotama walked through the damp streets of the Night-filled village. Haruka's strange silver eyes searched the buildings for a inn. Her short-cutt, raven coloured hair strung damply in circlets, resembling serpents. Tugging her male kimono, that was black and navy blue, closer to herself, Haruka looked over to Hinotama who was hopping along close behind.  Hinotama refused to hide that fact that she was female, although she wore male clothing that flurished with autum colouring, making many believe she was in fact just a beautiful boy. Her bright brown eyes searched the streets with curiousity, a smile firmly etched on her pale skin, where as Haruka had a darker tone.  Hinotama held a red fan in her right hand, that she kept on using to point at certain things she found intruiging and her long dark brown hair moved freely in the Night wind.   "Calm down," Haruka said with her stiff, cold voice, "you'll attract the attention of the whole neighbourhood." Hinotama held the fan up to cover her face and wide wide, shiney eyes. "Oh, I'm sorry!" A hint of mishchieviousness sparkled in her eyes.   Haruka sighed as she glanced at all the watchful eyes which peeked through windows, alley ways, and passery byers. The streets were oddly lively for such late hours. A blue Moon glistened in the sky, which was unlucky for Haruka, as it would be much more difficult to complete her task. Her eyes caught onto a large inn that seemed suited for the wealthy, but instead of entering, she turned and spotted a little one near by and motioned Hinotama towards it.   Hinotama peeked out the window of their little room. It was rather small, but none the less the Night air was welcomed. As people stared up at her, she would smile and wave at them. Often they would turn quickly and leave, making her frown.  Haruka sat on the floor with her legs crossed and one hand supporting her chin.  Hintotama waggled her legs as she crouched near the window and whined, "I'm bored, Haru-chan."   Haruka replied, "I told you, do not call me that. And we cannot do anything right now as the Moon is full."  Hinotama snapped her fingers and stared wide eyed at her compainion. "You know, Haru-chan, I just thought something."  She sighed and switched arms, asking, "What is it?"   Hinotama pouted and looked up as if thinking. "What shall we use,"-she held out her arms to show she held nothing-"if we have nothing with us?"  Haruka couldn't help but slightly drop her mouth open, as a certain anxiety took over her. "You are unprepared??"   Blinking, Hinotama asked, "Was I supposed to bring something?"  Just then the hair on Haruka's neck went up and a feeling surged through her. "Dammit, you've practically invited them over."  Hinotama's eyes suddenly lost all light, and a smile that resmbled that of a crazzed man's marked her once light-hearted grin. Her voice was deep and confident. "We'll have to make sure they have a good time, now wont we," she said, as they faded into the darkness.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I feel so unmotivated right now.    I want to put up my new Blog but I haven't finished the damn menu.    -_-*    I've got this pain in my right wrist.    Carpal Tunnel Syndrome?  When the Median nerve is pressed?  Meh, probably...   Moo...  Unmotivated  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       O_O im liking it!  even tho the last layout was one i made....^_^ but o well!  this 1 is rlly styling, and keane's inviting ne1 to post here if they want, each person will have their individual pic. when they post....  :D ull hafta see it when itz done tho, i wont give u ne spoilers :P so there!  :D l8r all  ps ill try to post here more often...*looks off with a blush* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's the end of the (Insert Number Here)(st,nd,rd,th) Semester!   FRIIIIDAAAY! THE ULTIMATE LONG WEEKEND!   ...and it's cold...   The weather in Toronto is such a fluxuating turmoil of mass air currents, almost as diverse as the people in the city.  It's sickening to have such cold weather develop into beautiful skies before returning to the deathly cold.  Although this is true, few things can down the spirits of students as the (skip?) off the school grounds to their long awaited homes, friends, and beds!   March Break.  Ahh...   As the author of this post seems to be quite random today, it's only fitting to end off with the Title.   #aar - Anime Academy Radio (irc channel)  Took me so long to join the irc server.  I guess it just wouldn't connect?  MSN doesn't seem to be working either...  The DJ on AAR (live feed, Anime and JPop music) was singing.  -_- I would comment on said singing, but said DJ is said irc channel's moderator.   That being said, some credit must be giving.  She wasn't always singing...   Half the time you could hear typing...  Once she had to get the phone...  This is  NOT  how you run a radio station people.   -_-   Oyoy the wooden toy.  I'd like to be a Radio DJ.   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Interesting...     i was curious to know a bit more about the newspaper that won the online category last year, so i looked it up on google (never fails =P)... and presto!   http://www.libermann.tcdsb.org/Times/2003-2004/OctEd2003/index.htm   Admittedly, it's not bad... however, i'm sure there's some people in our school capable of doing better *cough joe cough jax cough*   They also seem to have lotsa stuff in it... and having stuff done is always a problem at ward *cue in "Procrastination"*    Anyway, another interesting thing that happened was the yearbook came out! *must get more people to sign* ^^;; I completely forgot that Galang said that it'd be out before march break... or rather i forgot that it was almost march break... or maybe it was both... i'm forgetting lotsa things lately >   So yah, this year's yearbook is much cooler than last years... and anyone that disagrees can die by the sword =P     Special Addendum   Why is this addendum special? Only because it won't appear on LJ =P Anyway, i was going over my post, and just wanted to add a few things. First off, happy belated bday to my mom (all i did was say "happy bday" and even that was near the end of the day --;; i almost forgot...). Secondly, keane would also make a good addition to an online newspaper crew ^^ Next, saw Chat and Eugenie on the libz site... oh, and i believe Eugenie helps out with that award-winning online newspaper.    S'all for now... *left wondering if anyone comes here anymore*    Double Addendum   http://www.earlhaig.com/carpanatomy/  http://schools.tdsb.on.ca/jarvisci/jargonline/main.html   I'd say  those  ones are much harder to beat... maybe when Toronto Star was evaluating, they took into account that public schools have like 4 times the human and technological resources that catholic schools do.    ~Chronos 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Addendum (read prev first!)     oops... for the dance performance, i forgot a noteworthy performance: the tango-ish performance by the Latin American pavilion. I'd give the dance performance award to them ^^;;   Also, happy bday to my sis who turns 22 today!! ^^   ~Chronos   ps ..oh, and i've reached 1001 damage on gunbound with Grub's ss + avatar on + thor lvl 1. after finally breaking the 1000 damage mark, i think i will now give up gunbound for lent ^^ 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Contently Tired: Int'l Night!     Ok, this will be long, so for those that don't like long posts feel free to press that "x" button on your top right hand corner.   It first started off when i found that i was the only one in the religion area to help set up. not exactly a nice start to things =P but that was ok, cause i went to the staff room and nabbed JR and Tim to help out ^^ the setting up and the displays were pretty much same as last year (with minor differences), except we had a TV showing a documentary thingie, and we had DDR on display. Hopefully, we'll get it to work next year =P   I took way more breaks this year than last year (when i carted sushi for like the entire night), so i got to go around the place many times. Saw lotsa people, and when the doors opened, saw more people. This year seemed to be less crowded (probably 'cause they didn't sell at door this time), and there were also ticket scalpers this year. Interesting idea.... too bad it's one that'll probably get them suspended =P   Now onto the actual pavilions. I'd hafta see ours (the japanese pavilion) was the best ^^ of course, i may be a bit biased, but still: we had the biggest pavilion, most displays, food that were much on demand (sushi, teriyaki chicken) and soup and tea to compliment. If DDR had been working, we'd win on interactivity too =P as it is, i'd hafta say the Chinese pavilion win in that category for their cool pick-up-marble-with-chopsticks-and-win game    Ok, now the performances. My memory is a bit off (damnit, i didn't get a programme =\), so i might alter some stuff later on if i change my mind.    Best music group performance:  Of these, there was the Germany pavilion, Italian pavilion and the group that did "O Canada". The award goes to "O Canada" for the best rendition of the anthem i have heard so for. Creative and sounds cool =P Germany would win the runner-up... theirs was pretty good. For those that didn't notice, it was the song they played this morning before the anthem... either that or it was yesterday morning.    Best singing performance:  There were a few... but France win hands-down. Danielle and Mark did so amazingly... it was really, really good. Oodles of talent =P   Best dance routine:  A lot were so similar i seriously considered sleeping through it... these were the "sluttish dancing" routines (quote by Tim =P). Seriously, after 1 minute... you'd be like "is it over yet??" I forgot which one i considered the best... oh well   Best skit:  There was really only Canada and our pavilion that did a skit thingie... and i'd have to say ours was better. iunno... to me the Canada one wasn't that funny except for the part where Francross roleplays as Don Cherry. For us, i have only two complaints: not rehearsed enough, and singing was mediocre. The play itself was very original idea, and really touching; von's acting skills are pretty good and the ending was really good too (even though DYT tells me that was the least-rehearsed part =P).    Best rehearsed:  Following up on the whole rehearsal thingie... i would like to see next year's japanese performance as well coordinated as the korean performance this year. The timing and coordination was almost flawless oo;; and fans are cool. I was like "wow"... the hiphop that followed it was pretty cool too   Most Amusing:  I'd have to say the Vietnamese one was the most amusing... the guys with the hoes (TOOLS USED FOR PLOWING) were funny... and it's not even a skit or anything like that =P i just found it... really amusing how they stepped and pretended to plow the field =P   Honourable Mentions:  The... Ireland?... pavilion did that Riverdance thingie again, and it's even better than last year (which was already pretty good). They swung people around and stuff this year! Imagined if one of the girls flew off ... also worth mentioning is one of the last ones... forget which... where they danced while those guys moved those poles beneath them and they have to avoid getting their legs hit by the poles ... and last but not least, the chinese pavilion with cool martial arts stuff and jen showing that she's better at it than all the other guys oo;;    Overall best pavilion:  I think the chinese pavilion would win that: even though they didn't have much (if anything) on display, they did really good on the stuff that counts: food and performance. Not to mention their cool marble game thingie.    I would really like to hear other people's feedback on int'l night ^^   ~Chro 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Everyone knows what I mean.  It's almost June and the pressure is on.  I'm failing 3 courses again this year...  -_-  That's a for sure. If I don't work hard enough I might fail more.  :'(  Math is the one that's most in danger...  It's all summer and night school for me next year ;_;  I haven't even had the chance to post about me being sick.  Or about Jade's really fun birthday. I didn't even get to read Jade's story yet.  :\ Gomen ne Jade-san.  -_- The network is acting up... So I can't burn or get things to or from my sister's computer and... And...  And Winamp5 is out.  That surprised me.  I learned something yesterday.  So l33t.  (tired) -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wondering if tomorrow is a dream Ceasing to exist in the heart of hope Confronting that which isn't what it should seem Deciding this world is too much to cope   This story is leading to destruction With a rose-colour'd view, life is lovely Should not this road go under construction? I swear, I shall bend this sad road for you   Yes, this sadness can be turned into joy Crack open your shell; I will bear your yoke This strength will prove that of a brave young boy A child isn't blindfolded to that which has broke   This life is leading to our destruction Let us see from a different colour It does not require too much instruction I promise, I will lift this smog from view   This story is leading into destruction With a rose-colour'd view, life is content Shouldn't this road go under construction? I vow to cross this arched bridge with you.  ~hoshi       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ooopss ^^;; sorry about the title thing... i was just too used to using italics-bold-close bold-close italics... didn't realise it would cause trouble =\   =\ sorry to hear about your car... hope it gets better soon!   haven't been here in awhile... been lj-ing when this was down; but now it's up looking spiffier than ever so i'll help decorate with this post ^^;; dunno if i'm going to give up lj tho =\ in any case, i shouldn't be  anywhere  that often now that it's nearing the end of the year; but i will not talk about the end of the year in case i freak some people out.   so i will talk about something else.   tomorrow is anime! hope kenae can come... (sorry guys, i'm going to start using that =P hope you guys don't mind) i put the 8 AMVs in my bag so i can help out a bit with that ^^ is tim bringing any? gahh... this reminds me of the chain reaction it set off. keane announces that it would be AMV week, i felt like bringing some, search "AMV" on kazaa, finds - among others - a really cool naruto one, gets hooked on naruto, downloads cool songs used in AMVs.   downloading the two songs i liked was easy enough... but still have several volumes of naruto to crunch through... i might do that tonight. if not tonight, then summer... can't afford to lose any more time.  oh btw, that title is taken from one of the songs... "bring me to life" from evanescence, mixed with naruto goodness.   ooo... speaking of chain reactions, how about last weeks? ana sama too busy, keane took charge, keane invited jax, jax brought pup, then that incident with kitai. coincidentally, i missed half of anime waiting for kitai ^^;; that was the first time that happened... and everything was set in motion... so cool. seriously, it takes something like that to wake me up, so i'm grateful for pup ^^;; even though he's like "sorry" when i talked to him about it later =P mehhh... i'm going to treat everything as normal, because it  was  normal for them.   kk, s'alll for now! i'm suddenly feeling twice as cheery and productive than i have for the last month... man, whatever happened to cheery being normal? *wants to get back to that state*  ~Chro 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spent the last two hours in my 'dead' car by Warden and Ellesmere.  First let me tell you about this morning. The car started with BOOM *smoke smoke smoke* chuga chuga *smoke smoke smoke* before continuing on its more than mildly dangerous trip to the schools of my sisters and I.  Half-way there, about McCowan and Shepherd, the car runs out of gas.   Us.  =.-   My dad force starts the engine and luckily enough there was a gas station 50 m away.  Thank the Lord.  My father then makes a left to get inside the gas station, but again the car dies... lying accross the oncoming traffic.  My sisters and I have to rush out of the car.  My sisters lightening the load, and I trying to push the car, unsuccesfully.  Thank God again for when the car started up and made its way into the station.  The car then choked and popped it's way to school.  More than once the thought that this car would blow up.  Now that I think of it, it reminds me of Archie's old Jallopy... the really crappy one that always choked and popped and smoked... like our car.  So anyway... This afternoon my dad picks me up.  Choke boom pop.  Instead of going home, we head towards a friend of the family's house for some business.  The car stalls.  As we're about the cross the bus intersection of Warden and Ellesmere the car overheats and stops.  My dad couldn't start it again because the engine was over heated.   The car behind us.  -.=    I  have to push the car accross the  inhospitable  intersection to the other side.  We just wait there for a bit for the engine to cool off.  But my dad realises that the police might arrive soon... so again, it's pushing time.  This time my sister and my father help in the pushing, since it was an uphill push, they were a great help.  Still, when I got into the car I was practically hyperventilating.  We had to push it down the street, about 100 meters, into a side street.  From there my dad walked my sisters to the house we were originally intending to go to while I slept.  I just found out my fly is open...  ON WITH THE STORY.  From this point, the engine has cooled off but the battery has died.  Like yesterday.  I'm there sleeping in the cold while my father tries anyone he can think of to come and help us.  Only when the battery of his cell phone starts to die does he listen to my suggestion of calling Renae, who lived just down the street.  This was just about an hour later.  =.=  Rei-chan comes with cookies.  ^^ slightly burnt, but still Rei-chan and her father were life savers.  My mom's timing was impeccable.  She arrived right after we lost a need for her.  Since Rei-chan's father's car was there we already had our 'boost source.'  We finally get out of there at six.  An hour and a half after we first died.  As we get home and pull into our street, our car starts dying again, but with the Lord's help it powered on and was able to go up the driveway.  Half-way up, the engine stopped.  -.-  But with the inertia we were able to make it  exactly , and let me stress exactly, where the car is supposed to be parked, at the top of the driveway.  Thank you Rei-chan for saving us, and for the slightly burnt cookies.  ^^ Thank you Lord for protecting us, even if it may seem like you were only putting us through pain, I know there were many examples of your helping hand.  Hopefully the rest of the night will go smoothly now... -_- Somehow I doubt it.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       BWAHAHAHAHA  I have completed dza ba ro gu.... (talks like guy form Wind ~ A Breath of Heart)  NOW PEOPLE SHALL VISIT~!  BWAHAHAHAHA 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was going to post last night... But it was pretty late.  Since Rei's not picking up the phone I guess I can post now.  It's a long weekend, but no matter how much I try not to think of school, there's little else to think of right now.  That and the computer...  It's been stressing me out lately.  My Windows XP User Account got busted up.  It wouldn't run Internet Explorer properly.  I had to create a new account and change all the settings to the way I had them again. =.=  I decided to just leave the desktop the way it is, and blah everything I haven't changed unless I need to.  I might just put up the blog today... This is one is getting on my nerves.  Yeah, I'll do that.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well, the reason i hafnt been continuing the story is cause ive been pretty sick lately...also, this whole paragraphing thing rlly annoys me...maybe ill just continue on my blog..cause u guys r probably like *o* when u try to read, thing is my blog doesnt use capz....x_x so it'd b even worse! so i guess u guts r gonna hafta live with reading like this, HOHOHOOHO poor u.   u kno wat! screw dis, i changed it :P HEEHEEE...Boo is gonna b mad...lol..OK let the story writing BEGIN...  English: Start! In Japanese: HAJIME!  Hinotama yawned and stretched lazily under a fine shady tree. The sounds of the river near by added peace to the serene afternoon as birds sang merrily. The tempurature was fairly humid, as it had just rained the day before, so she chose to laze around as Haruka slaved in the river, trying to catch fish. Hinotama stared at the flowing, long grass, then slowly broke one from the earth, placing it in her mouth to chew. She then lay her hands on her belly, holding her fan, too comfortable to even cool herself down. Haruka, sweating, wet, tired, hot, and rather uncomfortable, wiped her brow and peered about the surrounding forest. Ever since they had left the village of Seishuu, she had been wary that they would not be followed. About a week had passed, but she still felt the need to be sure. After a quick scan, she looked over to where Hinotama lay, making sure their belongings were near by. A set of samurai swords lay against the tree, and two special blades that were constructed especially for assassination. Much shorter then the usual katana, and with a much longer handle. Not far were sheaths that a common samurai would carry, and a two sacks that held extra clothes and food. Haruka kept all her daggers on under her clothes, Hinotama usually did the same, but with just one or two.   I'll use anything I can find , Hinotama had said long ago with a shrug.  Haruka frowned as she watched Hinotama. Such a careless creature, that she was unfortunately cursed with looking after. "You lazy ass," Haruka called from the river, very sure there was no one within hearing distance, "you're supposed to be cleaning the blades!" Hinotama opened one eye and peeked at Haruka. "What for?" she responded lazily, "We haven't used them since the  last  time you asked me to clean them."   Haruka rolled her eyes and breathed in calmly. She squished the mudd with her toes and immediatly felt the fish flutter around her legs. Aquiring a concentration only a few could ever master, Haruka's breathing slowed down rappidly, and her eyes followed the exact movements of the fish. Suddenly her heart raced, beating to the exact movements of a particular one. Hinotama watched as calmly, and stealthy, Haruka snatched the creature from the water with her bare hands and with such grace, that it resembled that of a heron. There had been hardly any splash, or any noise to tell what she had just done.  "Now catch nine more!" Hinotama shouted with a laugh, "I'm that hungry." Haruka threw the fish at Hinotama. "You wish, pig!"  Hinotama got a direct hit from the fish in the face. She stared at Haruka with wide eyes and a dropped open mouth, the fish slapping around in her lap.  Haruka looked off and tried to hold off her laughter. "How dare you!" Hinotama cried with a hint of humour, "I do hope you know that you eat much more then I do!" Haruka just continued to laugh, beginning to scout out more fish. Hinotama, pouting, flung all the items in her lap to the groud (including the still flopping fish), wiped her face that now stunk of fish, and quickly took off her socks. Getting up in a rush, she quickly rushed into the river and froze in front of Haruka with a grin. Haruka glared at Hinotama. "You wouldn't," she said stepped back. Hinotama stepped forward. "I could!" Haruka smiled and cocked an eye brow. "You think you can catch  me ?"    The three little boys....(argh gotta go. ill continue later)  The two girls lay on smooth grass, staring up into the sky. After soaking one another in the river, it was time to dry off under the warm Sun. Two fish were cooking over a small fire on one of the rocks near the water's edge. One of the fish had been caught by fluke as Hinotama had grabbed one from the river, throwing it at Haruka, but missing to have it flung under the tree where the first fish had been thrown.   *dis is not the ending, im gonna right more, i just wanted to show jade the funny scene :D l8r!* 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i dun get it...how can someone who says they love you so much...be so cruel to u...  ArV says: so fuck you for asking me that  u_u now i really feel sick...  my computer clock says 11:30...it rlly throws me off...  my time perception is messed up...>  u_u i cant sleep ne more...  ~A sick Hoshi 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The inn keeper's daughter, Hana, walked slowly and reluctanty into the men's sleeping quarters. A large room that had five sleeping matts sprawled over the floor lay before her. The room was a mess, with traces of clothes all over the place. Hana took a breath and stepped forward, gathering her courage. The worst they would do is rape her...right? After all, she was eight-teen, it wasn't unlike she didn't know what making love was. It couldn't be so bad with these men, could it? Mostly she was worried they would harm her, treat her badly, and never allow her to see her family again. The fattest man flopped onto the floor to sit near a table, filled with very stale looking fish, fruits, vegtables and soups. Hana frowned in disguist. The other men followed suit, as the fat man said to her, "Well missy, I guess your wondering why you're here and what we're going to do with you." Hana stood awkardly in the middle of the room; she lowered her head; tThe men laughed hoarsly. The fat man slapped his belly. "Well you see, us men haven't had someone to clean around here and we figured since you were an inn keeper's girl, you'd know how to keep a men's place clean!" The other men began crying out cheers of agreement. Hana widened her eyes and looked up at them in surprise.  "Oh, surprised?" the fat one asked, "What did you think? We'd rape you? Oh come now, little flower, we may be under that crazed Seishuu, and under that rather psychotic Saro, but we are good men none the less." "I'm just sorry we've been driven to this," a younger man said, "I do this to support my family...but without any woman to clean up..." "...It's just such a hard way to live," another middle aged man finished. The fat man smiled widely, his eyes lost in the grin, "We only ask you com here every once a week or so, right men?" Cheers came all around as sake was poured for all. Hana, still shocked, asked weakly, "Then why did you kidnap me? You could of just asked?" The fat man's face turned serious. "That is something such a flower as you would not understand." Hana nodded slowly and began to tie her hair back into a bun. She straightened her clothes and began her task, as the men lazily laughed and joked at the table. Hana was disapointed, it seemed as if her life was fully deticated to cleaning and no fun at all.  "By the way little flower," he suddenly called to her, "if I were you I'd watch out for Saro. He's never gentle with the ladies." "Yeah," said another voice, as Hana picked up clothes from the floor, "he considers women to be witches." "In fact, so does Seishuu," agreed another. Hana froze in her place as the door opened swiftly. Biting her lip, she wondered if it was Saro.  Haruka scaled the walls of the inn in silence and darkness, the dark Sky cloaked her as she clung to balconies, unseen by guards. Stretching out her senses and using pure instincts, she managed to locate the room where the famous Seishuu lodged. Famous for his mass murder of all those who were loyal to the deceased Lord, famous for his idea that all women were demons, witches, unworthy beings.  She stepped onto the balcony, making sure not to creek the gentle wooden floor. Pressing herself up againt the wall, just beside the screen door, Haruka listened to the sounds.  "You bitch, I'll enflict to you the greatest torture you could ever imagine," said a squeeky voice, that Haruka imagined was Seishuu. There was slight movement and a harsh cry that sounded similar to Hinotama's, and yet a bit different. The yelling continued, until it was completly cutt off into a muffled sound. Haruka's silver eyes did not waver, she knew it was dangerous to just rush into a room. Movement and grunting noises continued, pain seemed to fill the Night, and she felt she couldnt take it anymore. Reaching into her kimono, she pulled out a knife with a skilled movement, her whole figure taking on that of a shadow and flung herself swiftly into the room. Saro walked into the room, his compsure was unusually lazy, gripping his sword at his side with a firm hand. Hana looked at him with wide eyes, wondering his intentions. The men suddenly went quiet as Saro began to laugh. He asked, "Do you wish to redeem your sins?" Haruka slit Seishuu's neck quietly, his body flopping over in a sudden spray of blood onto the figure he leaned over...Hinotama. Haruka's eyes flashed to the three men huddled between sheets on the far side of the huge, luxerious room, and then back to the massof blood as flesh that lay before her. Hinotama had a pool of blood sprayed around her and Haruka frowned at what Seishuu had done to her body. Catching a movement in Hinotama's face, Haruka leaned down to the mess and looked closely at the face that shifted...  The door opened with a bang, Hinotama standing in the door way. The men in the corner whimpered and clung together as she slowly stepped in.  "Stay back Hana," Hinotama said, turning to look at someone behind her, "you really don't want to see this." Haruka let out a deep breath as she watched Saro's face become clear through what had appeared to be Hinotama's. His clothes took the place of what had appeared to be a woman's kimono. "An illusion..." Haruka mumbled as Hinotama sat by her side.  Hinotama smiled sweetly as she looked at her friend, the red fan tapping at her chin. "Clever?" she asked. "Quite," Haruka agreed as she stood up; Hinotama followed her. "Where you worried?" she asked, nearing Haruka, who had wondered over to the three boys. Haruka's cold eyes stared at her momentarily, becoming cold in the Moonlight that peeked through the open baclony door. "No," she said and turned to look at the boys. "What do you think?" Hinotama looked up as if thinking, tapping the fan on her chin dramatically. She suddenly leaned down and smiled warmly at the boys, who appeared to be only from twelve to fourteen.   "Do you want to die?" she asked softly. One began to break out into tears, as the other being gripped by the two other boys turned away.  The third one answered: "Please, you would do us much a great favour..."  Haruka passed a bag to Hinotama in the room of the small inn they had been staying at. "Where'd you get this lovely emboirded bag?" she asked, reaching inside to take out her male kimono; Haruka turned away as Hinotama got dressed. "The inn keeper's gave it to me as I favour; I said I would save their daughter," Haruka replied, crossing her arms impatiently. "Done," Hinotama said, letting loose her long hair. "By the way," Haruka said, morning light spilling into the little room, "did you take care of the others?" Hinotama blinked as smiled. "Oh yes," she said, placing bloody hashi (chop sticks) on the table, "the ones that weren't willing to repent...of course." There was a gentle knocking on the door. Three beautiful, young boys, that seemed rather pale and unhealthy, and in between the ages of twelve to fourteen, stood there with food and beverages.  The smallest one smiled sweetly as Hinotama approached. "Are you feeling better?" she asked, taking the items from his tray. "Yes, much better sir," he responded with bright eyes, "although, none of us seem to remember a thing of anything before this morning." Haruka also helped, a grin touching her lips as she turned away to place things on the table.  Hinotama smiled playfully, "That must be hard on you're parents! Make sure to work hard here in their inn for them!" The boys laughed and blushed, bowing deeply with a gratitude to these mysterious men they weren't sure of why they had.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A boy is not allowed to come out of his room until he finishes writing two essays.  He's out in 5 seconds.  How?  S.A. S.A.  -_- I wish.   My History Essay is due tomorrow.  I'll go work now.  Argh~ no sleep for me tonight.   -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       right now i feel like it's all just so - poinltess.  right now i feel like falling to my knees, and begging God to free me from this world, to free me from those corners where there is no escape, where i cannot do ne thing in my power to be freed, except for running away.   right now i feel tired. right now i feel lonely. right now i feel like the world is closing in, it's hungry jaws awaiting me. right now i hate all humans, for ever creating such a hell hole. right now i wish for everlasting peace, in a world where nothing exists, not even myself.   this is the escape, to simply, not exist. i think constantly our souls wish for freedom...but it's like life is the path to that freedom. i kno that very soon tho i will be back on the path again, ignoring everything that's thrown at me. a constant war thats silently faught within.  when will it just stop. i just want it to stop. when will the rose no longer prick me with it's thorns...so unexpectedly too...trapping me within itz grasping vines...pain.........swimming in a sea of pain. i remember this..dont u emerson..? im drowning..drowning......drowning...tasukete... 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm just annoyed that my mom says I'm doing nothing when I TRY TO WORK ALL DAY and am interupted by her CONSTANTLY to do other things.  GRRRRRrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.  I like this wireless keyboared though. Read my post on Anime North!!!  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is what I noticed.  http://www.r2vq.blogspot.com  and  http://r2vq.blogspot.com  Are different... they never were before...  I wonder what Google is doing...  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, Sorry for not visiting  my own blog .  With stress of the end of the year I haven't been able to get much time to read blogs or sleep for that matter.  My eyes burn twenty-four seven and my brain keeps shutting down.  I don't feel happy.  Not really... I feel tired.  I feel stressed.  I feel burning.  Can I finish the amount of units I need to?  Yes, but that will come at a large sacrafice.  I guess I should think about that later.  This weekend was...  +++ANIME NORTH+++  It was fun.  It was tiring.   My Notable Events &gt;  Karaoke Curse of the Fanboys Voice Acting Contest Q&A with Atsuko Enomoto   Karaoke  - Rei and I were supposed to do a duet to "Moment".  Unforunately they couldn't find a CD.  As a (litterally) last minute backup, Rei chose Tooi Kono Machi De, and I chose Heart ni Kiraboshi Sakashitare.  Baaad choice. Rei did great.  I on the other hand...  Well, let's just say it's good I warned the audience.  Keane: (As song begins - Serious Voice)  Warning...  During this song please, cover your ears. Keane:  (a bit later from Kyle's idea in an asian accent)  I have noo pwofessional twaining. Keane:  (a bit later after the dance - YES DANCE)  You might want to cover your eyes too.  After my song, Von got sick in the middle of singing her song... And she got sick baaad...  Poor Shoy-chan.  I'm not mad at you anymore btw. Also, Rei sat on my lap...  When I forgot there was a little packet of coffee cream in there.  :\  Ewww....  We were both wet baaaad.   Curse of the Fanboys  - Great panel.  A line of men read a fanfic to us (written in play format with a narrator to explain the actions) in such a hillarious fashion, even the self-insert-hater Von was laughing.  It was also a choose your own adventure type of story, so at times the audience had a chance to pick the next event in the story.  Guy 1:  Bukakke?  What's that? Narrator:  Should he learn what Bukakke is, or should we just leave it alone? Audience:  (well.. let's just say nobody said Choice B) Guy 1:  What's Bukakke?  Really, what is it? Narrator:   Well, it's easier to show you than just tell... (stands up infront of Guy 1) Guy 1:  (Screams in terror as silly string starts shooting from the Narrator's crotch to his face).    Voice Acting Contest  - Les Major had a little miniature audition for a new children's cartoon due out in a few years.  He chose random people from the audience to do parts of the script to see how it worked out.  Not so much random, but people who put their hands up.  :)  Les:  For the part of the village leader... (Keane's hand is waving almost frantically in the uber-front row) Let's choose you. (Pointing to an older asian guy.) Les:  For the part of the kid... OK you.  Only because you were first.  (pointing to a middle aged white man) Keane:  OH!  If THAT's the game! Les:  (Looks at Keane)  Yunno what, okay, get up here. Keane:  O.O  Really?  And that's how I became a Voice Actor.  I still gotta contact him to see if I did well...  He said he'd email us.  :)   Q&A with Atsuko Enomoto  - Definately fun.  Enomoto-sensei danced gave us an unexpected concert in the first half.  I have pictures.  :)  That was very fun.  The second half we were given the promised Q&A.  Although I was first in line, I gave the position up to somebody asking why Enomoto-sensei became a voice actress.  urlLink  My Question for Enomoto    =D  That was great.  =_= Now I sleep. -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today i took the day off to do some hw on the comp...cause at school comps are majorly hogged over, there are fights caused over usage of computers...  so i worked for a bit, then took a lil time off. i managed to finish one thing..now i got one more left.  i also have to type up a character chart for Macbeth, and write an essay...o joy.  right now tho im afraid to move, or even type, because my aunt is in the kitchen wid my other aunt and my mom....this morning my aunt was like, "ur aunt is coming over so hide!!!"  that's wat i did, but im SCAREEDD, i kno shes gonna come! *bites nails* where..do..i..go...o_o i want food, but they're in the kitchen, i could make a break for my room...that'd b...safer...=_=;;; but..wait..there's the closet?? wat if my parents give my location away? ill just say...i was working and listening to tunes..i didnt kno u were here...:O i think they went outside *que happy music*   *breathes* free...for now...i just dun feel like dealing wid that STARE and wat she has to say atm...--;; itz hard enuff hafin to motivate myself to work.i hear...movement...o_o PEOPLE ARE TALKING. BLINDS ARE OPEN ALERT! *stay perfectly still* *freezes*   er............i think im gonna start typing out my character chart....:S  my tummy hurts T^T  ~HoSHi 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       firstly and formally id like to apologize to jade-chan...im sry i didnt go to the game, i had no idea it was that day and where it was going to be held. val had told me it was maybe going to b at ward, but she wasnt sure...i didnt kno it passed, im sorry. i rlly wanted to go. i dunno wat else to say, but ive been meaning to ask u if u want to go wid me and lynn and maybe keane to see "Troy" saturday night, if that's ok wid u?  so besides my stupied mistakes, and on another note, id like to mention the change ive noticed in the air, not only from my surroundings, my situation, the weather, but also myself. it's surprising tho, i think i may be dillusional. i feel like there's something within me, stone maybe, that will never break. somewhere within there's still that persona that precieves myself as a warrior, or something like, it's rlly strange....ive also become more, closed up, more, mature? and i remember the day i woulda screamed in horror at the thought of being mature, heehee..but i guess i can still smile. i kno that a long time ago i agreed with myself to allow change to happen, inside of forcing myself against the tide. the first day, when i smelt it in the air, i was very reluctant, i was frustrated and angered. but now i stare blankly, unmoved at this change. someone stole my md player, btw, music has been stollen from my life. a huge change. i dunno when ill start to rebuild it. not only that ivebeen rlly bitchy lately, snappy, and prideful. separating myself (dilberatly) from the group. im a hermit man, a frikin hermit. lol...well ive discovered its because im pmsing....so forgive me all who haf faced my wrath. specially my boo, im sorry :*...well, on the bright side, i wont b on my period for anime north...and maybe everything will turn out good in the end. altho it's frustrating to see that when finally ur satisfied, things collid into u and destory it. o.o yeesh....besides that, ive realised i got a problem, that being that i A: cant finish a story B: have so many ideas flooding around in my head that i could spill out tonnes and tonnes of ideas...it's, so fun to tho. :S o well, ive made so many new ones since hino and haru...argh da stress is wieghing down.  ne way, since im not sure wat say next, ill just go off into my own lil world :P ne one is invited xD  ~HoSHi 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haven't posted in a while... I think I should, so I'll start again.  Nothing much to say right now. Just wish me luck on the calc and chem test tomorrow.  They mean a lot to me... a lot of marks in these two tests.  ~Vick  PS... I'll send you a 100 by 100 pic soon Keane haha.. tell me where to send to tho. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bloody jerk isn't online and I went on especially to make sure he didn't freak out.  So *** you snargles   April 8 I changed it so there ARE line breaks, you hardly use this ne way Boo, so :P  ~Rei  March I am encouraging people to post here as a Group Blog.  If you know anyone who would like to post (preferably someone some, if not most, of us know) then please e-mail me with information.  Emerson, please type your blog titles in the Title Bar, it made a small annoyance when I was doing layout.  OH!  If you're posting and you haven't submitted a picture, please do.  100x100 size.  :)  Thanks! -ArV --> 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've  offically  discovered the most boring type of writing imo. of all the things ive ever tried to write...this is by far the most BORING.  script writing..........seriously...it's killing me. i have to write 15 pages of pure crap in order to meet the "deadline" tomorrow.   *feels like beating up whoever created such a BORING format* ....im just trying to waste time....it's impossible!! wahhh how am i gonna finish.......T^T  on to other news...itz summer school time. meaning im freaking out trying to finish all my work. ye jade-chan, it started THIS week. so im busy till i finish....*twitches* seriously, this is like a ALL WORK zone. today i finished a unit, and as soon as i did i jumped to another one. my hand felt like falling off...*pets laptop*   right now im avoiding righting such a boring thing..but i kno i should just get to it and stop stalling..but hey..i thought checking around blog n' stuff would b nice...  u__u mizu-chan (lynn fyi)and i thought of a totally wacked but cool idea to go to europe. i think when i told my parents they went into shock or something. seemingly forgetting how old i was and just when i was graduating. mizu-chan's parents on the other hand were like totally crazy about it, they even got a tour guide book thingie for her...the world has gone crazy.   when i told my parents they came up wid all these lame-ass excuses, like, they wont let me travel cause im too young...which is not true cause mizu told me that one of her friends is travelling ALONE to europe this summer..indeedy..alone, and they said like, i couldnt get a passport...even tho mizu got one...-__-;; excuses...excuses..."u need to be 18!" NEWFLASH PPL, im turning 18 next yr! "no ur not!" YES I AM...."well...*mumbles*...*counts*...*changes subject"  wat i thought even FUNNIER was when my mom had issues leaving me alone @ home, even tho i had done it MANY times b4...  "mom..i can stay home alone *lifts a brow at her*"  "ur only 15!" she cries...-_______- me> O_O IM 16 MOM--TURNING 17 FYI  dad > *laughs* ahhh, yeah, look at u, wanting to be older, just wait, when u DO get older, ull want to be younger  *me cannot believe wat i am hearing, my own PARENTS dont believe im 16*  "I AM 16! WHY WOULD I LIE ABOUT THAT?" "Nooooo" they both say, and then freeze. "OHHHH...YOU ARE!"  *falls to floor and twitches*   here's another scene:   (this is her trying to consol my disapointment at their refusal to lemme go to europe)mom>>you know, most ppl who go to europe usually do it after they graduate...  me>> O_O............*says slowly* mooom...i hope you realize im graduating next yr.......... mom>> you are??? NO! ur not! me>>*says slowly* yes mom..ill b in GR 12!! i mit go back for a semester..but technically...im in my last yr.... mom >> noooo...and ur taking a yr off? *she's like this> o_o* me> yes...getting a job and saving up for uni mom>> oh..........which uni r u going to? me>> dunno. mom> O_O  so yeah, this has kinda got me like...thinking im in the twilight zone. man....at one point i was thinking...AM i 15...?? no NO IM NOT!   weeiiiirrrdd....  AND if ne of u wanna join in a petition to EUROPE, come get a job wid me and we'll save up 2,500 $ FOR IT! YEAAHHHH 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like another year has just flew by; it's been a much more dreary and tiring year than last year.   One major difference this year for me has been my overall attitude; generally, i've been tired and much less cheerful than last year. I wonder why that is so... maybe increased workload? Parents continuous nagging near the very beginning? The fact that there are more things to worry about?  Any one - or a mixture - might be the cause.   I won't bore you guys with a play-by-play recount of my year, as any who reads this would probably have read every other post i've made =P no point in restating what has already been said.   School - the academic part which my parents is fixated on - was indeed harder this year. I found that it took longer for each unit, and the tests were many times harder. Not to mention the exams. I didn't need to May/June rush this year, but the afore-mentioned nagging really challenged my calm =P   As for the extracurricular part of the year, the stuff that really stood out were the intramural sports; specifically 3-ball. That was really fun, and i'm definitely going for that again ^^ i swear, if there was one thing in this school year that did not have stress attached to it, it's 3-ball.   Other events were fairly fun and memorable too... all those little things that happen that make up the entire gr.11 experience... yes, yuki would say that it's all very boring, and maybe she would be right ^^;;   ah, and got to know a little too many people... keeping track of all of them might also be why it's been a tiring year, i guess yuki will be my major time sink from now on ^^   *looks bak* Wow, i took 3 posts last year to sum up the year... lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Let'see, since I haven't said much about recently, here's a not-so-quick summary:  - after my exams, many things went wrong on friday... i won't bother going into detail; basically couldn't get marks print-out, media is worrying me,  summerschool signup was not fun, and parents gave me hell for i forget what reason  - however! the anime party at the japanese restaurant was one thing that went right. It was nice and relaxing and too bad it was so expensive =P and too bad yuki couldn't come... and hoshi and r2vq ^^;; =P oh, and the rest of KKEY... and um... those... other... ppl that go to anime...   - mostly in my week off, i've been gunbound-ing a lot... want to get arcangel wings... so expensive =\ and the usual lj-ing, konquest-ing... and today, i did a massive multi-hour clean-up that left me drained. oh well, everything is nice and neat now.   - as expected, my dad wants me to do work to prepare for summerschool. he's also forcing me to wake early to prepare for school. yes... how bout we all spend our lives preparing for death. that way we'll all be nice and ready for the coffin.   - will try to read a bunch of books, play some duel monsters, create some kinda board game that i haf tinkering in my head, and watch X/1999 (anime that sounds interesting). Oh, and will try to get to CNAnime. Exercise, summer school and learning some computer languages are also on the menu  aaanndd that's basically about all... i could already imagine yuki telling me how boring that is... =P    EDIT: wow, blogger looks so nice now! kudos to google for making it so prettiful =P oh, and to keane, yup, i put my titles where it says title now ^^;; sry bout before, thought i'd be... um... coding-ish-ly...?   EDIT #2: noooo... it's not possible to archive the rest of the posts that are not visible on the home page =\ the blogger thingie prevents copy and paste in this edit section... *sigh* there goes a dozen or so posts >  i was able to back up the posts starting from this one to keane's "click here for anime north picture" post... anywhere from that point on to my "of memories and present" post is not back-upped 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well u kno, i think time flys by, and when i do notice, im momentarily like :| but then a second later i return to: meh.   i guess maybe there's a LOT of things i could tell u guys, but im just plan lazy. i dunno, does that make it harder for u guys to kno me? cause im too lazy to write about it? meh, im not complicated, least i dont think i am, or i dont try to be, i try to b as simple as possible.   ...that was confusing, wasnt it? i mean i confuse myself. why i do stuff is beyond me. God, i think i need more sleep. *looks at sleeping Dusty* she's so dammed cute...  well, wat was i saying? eh dunno, missed that train, let's see...i guess i can tell u about a dream i had last night. something about an opera, and a costume. masks. friends i dont kno in real life. running. dark big places. o_O seemed like a comedy. meh, no words to fully translate it.   *rubbs eyes* im thinking of using my tarrot cards to get dish out some lottery numbers. normally i wouldnt ever consider it, but it was something my dad said:   we were watching something on notradomus..however u spell it, and i said: "i dun get it, even if u had those powers, why would u wanna tell the future ne way?" "Yeah," agreed my dad, "but id try to win the lottery"   that kinda stuf wid me, and my tarrot cards haf kinda been catching my eye lately. wat the hell,, maybe ill try it out. i bet they feel neglected ne way.   ^.^   wow man, i feel sooo tired. *rubbs eyes* ^^dont worry tho, im otherwise my normal bitter self. lolzzzz  *hugs for everyone who reads this*!  ~Hoshi 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not right now...  but recently I've been tired.  I don't know why.  Hm...  What's new in life?  I might try to get a job at Rainbow Cinemas...  And we were supposed to watch Farenheit 9/11 yesterday but we missed it again.  :-s  Weren't able to take the bus.  Today was a slow day, I fell asleep for two hours... even though I slept in until noon.  I realize I'm getting lazier than during school.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hoshi held a birthday party in honour of Kas and I!  That was a fun day ^^.  Though my pants were soaking afterr Jade's surprise attack... grr.. :P  It was great to see (almost :P) everybody there.  And it was a terrific day involving pictures, presents and cross-dressing.  ...they made Kas and I do dares before opening presents... "Why don't you guys choose truth?"  "...because we're being filmed."  :D  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       NEW COUNTER.  IT'S THE SAME WEBSITE AS THE ONE THAT DOES THE MARY WARD SEMINAR SCHEDULE WEBSITE COUNTER.  GODDMANIT I HATE HATE>... AHTEATAETAJA......  -_-  I am GAH.  Von's back.  Party is this Sunday.  Hope everyone got the spam I sent out regarding said party.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       And so summer school is almost over. What will Keane do the rest of summer?  How does he ever survive?!?!?!  Vote today at...  o.o  And that's what I call... HEY WHAT'S UP!  I'm so... annoyed? I hate waking up to shouting... And now my mom was crying and screaming and my dad.  And my sisters.  So now I'm waiting... we're supposed to go somewhere... are we going? I dunno.  I said I wouldn't go with Trisha because we're going...  Parents have no respect.  Do they care about anyone else?  No.  So that was a birthday a few days ago.  And Kas's birthday is coming up.  :)  BTW.  I'M NOT SAD.  I feel nothing right now but annoyance... it's hot.  Well, Von's coming back on Monday or Tuesday ^^ Yatta!  And...  Grab one, and DQ something different.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome to ArV no Kifu version... uh... well it's not my design so I'm not putting a version number.  -_-  I hate my designs.  They suck ass.  I want to be able to do something like this...  *sighs*  So what happened since I last  really  posted?  I graduated from High School, got a job at the local Shopper's Drug Mart to help pay for my rent and hopefully I'll be attending University this year for Japanese, Drama and Media.  Okay not really.  I haven't visited Blogs in a while. I don't know why.  I don't feel as happy as I usually do.  What  really  happened?  OK.  Summer has come.  I'm still in school.  I should be out early.  And my computer's hard drive was wiped.  All my programs went bye bye.  Wonder when Von will get back from her HK-JP trip.  Anything else big and I'll post it.  -ArV 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>