<Blog>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I started this "blog" as a way for me to write something that strikes me as funny whenever I feel like it.  What I would write would forever be kept in the annals of hell that is the internet; never to be heard from again, like Yahoo Serious.  As you may have noticed I put quotation marks around the word "blog".  This is my way of creating a faux distance from this tool as if I am somehow above it.  I really think I'm much better than everything, including you.  I don't mean to think these things, it's just that, well, you don't know the difference between "your" and "you're" and that irritates me.  Because this irritates me, it then --in turn-- means that I am better than you because  you  irritate me and not the other way around.  On a completely different note, I thought of something odd when I started to write this but it wouldn't let me use it as the title, it was too long:  Underwater hyper-active flourescent monkey gymnasts!  We chronicle the adventures of these five glow-in-the-dark primates as they travel the Seven Seas performing their tumbling routines all the while they try to oppress their attention deficit disorder (with hyper-activity at no extra charge!).  Meet Zeke, Two-tone, Ray-Ray, Ernest Borgnine, and Mickey Mouse (no relation so I can't get sued.  Seriously, that's just his name, you want him to change it?  That's messed up).    I haven't worked out all the logistics of this, but it'll be huge.  Trust me.  I live in California and right now we've got all that Governor-related business going on.  I know you don't care --and by "you" I mean nobody since nobody will read this-- but here's my take on everything.  I would love for us to get another Governor!  I mean, Gray Davis has had a tough time, he could use the help.  Imagine, all the other states have one Governor but California gets two.  I guess that means we get one for each letter 'i' in the state's name.  It's a good thing Mississippi doesn't employ this rule or they'd have like seven Governors.  But Arnold and Gray Davis could beat any other pair of state's Governor's in a no-holds-barred steel-cage match.    On the same note, I swear to all that is holy in this world (i.e. Mary Kate and Ashley Olson and "Blue" from Old School) every time I hear some person in the media refer to Arnold Schwarzenegger as "The Governator" or anything like that, I cut off a finger.  The women at the old-folks home are getting mighty low on fingers.  Rose and Blanche are already out all ten, Sophia's down only two.  You hear that folks at Fox News?  You can save what's left of the hands of Estelle Getty if you will just stop trying to come up with clever names for Arnold if he became Governor.  I mean, honestly, isn't it already funny enough that he's actually polling well?  Do you actually have to try to interject some of your "humor" (see the quotes again? I'm a bastard) to actually add something to this story?  It kills me and it's slowly killing the Golden Girls.   As my first entry, I'm rather proud of what I've got going here.  It's long and strong and it's down to get the friction on!  I don't know how to end this, I need to come up with something clever to sign off with. Here goes!  Keep those pot handles turned in!  If you have any suggestions as to what I should write about --and I mean anything-- send me an e-mail at dirtiestbastard@hotmail.com   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Wild fires?  Or are they misunderstood?  Here in Southern California the tenth circle of Hell has just recently opened up and starting swallowing cities one neighborhood at a time.  Of course, every News Channel and non-news channel is covering this (I think the Food Network is running a special on how to cook outdoors or something).  As with any news situation, there's only so much to say.  Every channel tries to get their own angle on the story -and they all have some stupid name for it.  Right now ABC is calling it "Firestorm" which is pretty misleading because it's not raining fire from the sky.  Wouldn't that constitute a firestorm?  I mean, that would be a whole hell of a lot cooler if that was the case.    Back to my point.  This morning on the aptly named Today show (because it's happening TODAY), they had, of all people, Al Roker here in San Bernardino County covering the fires.  I don't know what their thinking on all of this was.  He's a meteorologist.  If a meteor caused the fires, then he's your man, but I don't think that's how it happened.  Again, that would be way cooler.  So, exercising his vast journalistic ability, Al Roker asked an "Eyewitness" to the fire the following question: "So, what's the fire like?"  I don't know what kind of answer he was looking for, but he got the answer that I would have given.  "It's really really hot."  Well, there you have it folks.  Investigative journalism at its pinnacle.   urlLink Al Roker , a previously chubby weatherman with the hard-hitting questions that you want to ask.    Al Roker will also be covering future "Stormwatch" and "Earthquake-storm-watch" happenings here in Southern California.  He'll be asking some of your favorite questions like: "So, the rain, is it as wet as it seems?" and "Now, was the whole area shaking around you during the quake?".  Al Roker, the reason weathermen stick to weather.  For things and stuff that I should write about (or for the Al Roker fans, not write about) e-mail me  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       In an apparently "really awesome" disappearing act, half of Roy's head managed to vanish out of sight and into the stomach of a 250 pound white tiger the other day.    So, Roy of the "Siegfried and Roy's International Steakhouse" chain of restaurants (and their magic act) has been hospitalized.  It turns out that doing "magic" involving massive amounts of rare white tigers is a little on the dangerous side.  Roy was mauled by one of the duo's white tiger's while performing on stage.  This would have been the only time that I would have wanted to dole out the $100+ to see that show.  I mean, imagine being able to watch somebody's who's been "asking for it the whole time" finally getting it.  And I don't mean that in a gay way.  He's been "getting it" in that department for years.  And by department I mean the Men's Department at Macy's.  And by Macy's I mean...nevermind.  Apparently Roy is in some sort of condition at the hospital.  This condition ranges from good to serious or critical.  I'm bad with medical terms.  I am sure that being in the hospital is not a good thing, so it's probably one of the other ones.  There's also the "Code Cinnamon" that I've heard of, but I think that was just on that gay porn I accidentally watched one time called "St. Ballhair".    I'm sure Siegfried is hanging out bedside with "Nip" and "Tuck" their two favorite white tigers.  I just can't wait until the footage of that shows up on the internet.  There has to be some sort of footage of Roy getting dragged around by his magical head.  Everytime I come around your city Bling Bling!  Any suggestions of what I should write about or comments in general (like don't write anymore) can be sent to  urlLink Me here   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Hot or not!  When I'm extremely bored sometimes I'll log on to Yahoo! chat and go there to mess around and see why society is crumbling before our very eyes.  There are so many hilarious things that go on in a Yahoo! chat room I don't know where to begin.  There are so many different types of people.   urlLink  This movie  shows the many types of people that you can find in a chat room, plus it's pretty cool.  Anyway, the first type of person that stands out is the guy that just comes into a room and cuts and pastes the following "19/m/714 IM me 2 hook up" over and over and over again.  Okay, that's no big deal, I ignore that guy, easy.  Then, ninety more of those guys show up.  By the time I'm done ignoring all of those guys, the room is down to about 10 people.  Next, I'd say of the remaining 10 people there are 7 Indian guys who only know the world "hello" and message things like "U are secky girl for me, y?"  I like to get these messages for pure comedic value alone.  I message them back gibberish just to confuse them, but it never works, they just ask for my picture.    Anyway, where I'm going with all this is here.  Sometimes, along with being bored, I turn on my webcam.  I turn it on because the response is hilarious.  I don't think I'm "hot", in fact, I know I'm not "hot".  That's not modesty, it's just the truth.  But, on the Internet, for some reason, I become like ten times better looking than I actually am.  I have had lots of women message me and literally tell me just how good looking I am.  Like I said, I don't think I'm ugly, but by no means do I think I'm hot or even "very good looking".  It's just hilarious that, in comparison to the rest of the men exposing more 10-inch penises than I ever thought was humanly possible, I'm hot.    So now, if I'm ever in need of an ego boost, I just log on to Yahoo! chat and turn on my camera and let all the gay men posing as women tell me that they think I'm good looking.  Everybody knows no women actually use the Internet.  This one wasn't really that funny, but I wanted to write something, so deal with it.  If you don't like it, you can go stare at some of those guy's 10-inchers.   urlLink email me  suggestions to write about. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Solid.  Solid as a rock.  So, like most days, I woke up with an erection today.  I find it interesting that this happens so often -but it's also disturbing.  I'd understand the erection if I was having a sweet sexy dream about some fine lady, but that wasn't the case last night.  Last night I dreamt (like I do a lot, actually) that I had telekinetic powers.  I remember me and some dorky guy (yes, guy, subconsciously maybe I'm gay, who knows?) from my a few of my classes were running from people in this hotel.  At one point it was dark and we needed light so I was able to make light with my hands.  What the hell is wrong with me?  I also remember that we were stuck on an elevator so I used my magical powers to open the doors with only the power of my mind.  Maybe I'm a subconsciously-gay Harry Potter wannabe.  Now that's a story.  Anyway, back to the erection.  I always find it odd waking up with an erection just because I'm wondering how long that's been like that.  For all I know as soon as I go to sleep, my wiener wakes up.  Maybe the lack of brain activity is a signal for all the blood up there to rush to my nether-regions and get to work.  I feel so dirty.  Maybe I'm pelvic-thrusting the sheets in my sleep -my cat takes a poking in a vacant orifice.  Really I'm just wondering what it's doing while I'm asleep.  I'm thinking about teaching it how to type so that while I'm asleep it can do my homework.  How cool would that be?  Sure I'd go through a lot of keyboards and the cleanup would be a pain, but I wouldn't have to worry about carpal-tunnel and MY PENIS WOULD BE TYPING!  Well, that's enough about my magical, subconsciously-gay, telekinetic, typing penis.  Drop me a  urlLink line  for ideas or hate-mail. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Naps  Naps are great.  Sometimes I'll take like four in a day just because I can.  Sometimes, when I'm napping, I dream about taking more naps.  There are times when I'm lying there, napping, and I'm struck with the thought, what are you doing here napping when you could be out doing something, but then, at the mere thought of the absurdity of the question, it exits my mind.  You know what else I like?  Of course you do, you're me, the only person who reads this.  Well, I'll put it in type just in case you ever forget what I like.  I really like lesbians.  They are awesome.  Granted, only the good-looking lesbians are what I'm really interested in, but lesbians in general are just awesome.  They have so much going for them.  I mean, the fact that they have the same pieces as the other person they're with, yet they still want to touch/fondle/caress/lick/burn/bite those other person's parts is so respectable.  Then, couple that with the fact that they put these things on video for so many of us to see, I mean, they have to be the most giving people in the world.  In fact, I'm fairly positive that all lesbians should be put up for Nobel Peace Prizes.  As we speak (and remember, when I say 'we' I mean me and me since nobody else reads this) I'm busy writing a letter to the Council That Decides Who Should Win Noble Peace Prizes (you think they'd make that more succinct) about this whole idea.  By the way, if you are reading this (anybody but me, somebody I don't know preferably), send me an  urlLink email  and let me know just how awful all of this is. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Mickey's severed head   Have you ever had to set a mousetrap?  I'm not talking about those new-fangled glue traps where the mouse gets stuck on it and tries to gnaw off its own leg.  No.  I'm talking about the old school mousetraps.  The mousetraps that look like medieval torture devices.    They're scary as hell.  Now, don't get me wrong, I'm a complete and total stud in all aspects of manlihood.  But, oh my God if I didn't almost pee my pants trying to set that thing.  And I had to do two of them!  It's scary because the stupid thing is more sensitive than a fat girl at a dance.  I don't even know if that analogy made sense, I just wanted to say 'fat girl at a dance'.  Anyway, now I know where the expression comes from about building a better mouse trap because there's no way in my life I'm setting another mouse trap.  I'll buy some nightvision goggles and a beebee gun to hunt them down instead of setting another mouse trap.  I also think I was afraid of it because the traps that I got looked all rusted and tuberculosis-inducing.  They were in a package and everything, but I think they were recycled or somebody left them out in the rain or something.  If that thing slapped shut on my hand (which it tried to do like nine times), I know for sure I would have had to go get a tetnis shot, rabies, AIDS (the new AIDS shot, coming soon), and a pink eye shot.  That thing was more disease ridden than (insert skanky girl name from your high school, ex-girlfriend/boyfriend, or Pamela Anderson's name here).  This has been a friendly public service announcement reminding you not to ever set a mouse trap because they're very scary and will probably result in you crying a lot because you're not quite as manly as I am.  Email me  urlLink here  for story ideas, suggestions, or to agree with me on just how frightening mouse traps are. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm going to make commercials...   I just saw what could go down in history as the most ridiculous commercial ever made. When I use the word ridiculous here, I don't mean that in a good way like, "Yo, that new eyepatch is ridiculous, Bluebeard. Go on with your bad self." No, I mean ridiculous like this: "That new machine that rapes babies is ridiculous." If there were such a machine, I'm pretty sure it would be just as ridiculous as this commercial I saw.  The commercial went something like this: Hi, I'm a guy selling Dawn Dishwashing liquid. For some reason we have a lot of dishes that we cleaned with Dawn all lined up back to back, between two motorcycle ramps. Now, Robby Kneivel has to jump them on his motorcycle. Yay, he did it. See? Dawn really works.  The commercial made no sense whatsoever. I guess Dawn had Robby Kneivel locked into some sort of a contract. Actually, now that I think about it, it makes perfect sense. Motorcycles + motorcycle ramps = clean dishes. If you ever watch that show on Discovery where they make awesome motorcycles, their dishes are always very clean. And they don't have dishpan hands.  In fact, I just thought of a new commercial. Stay with me. Closeup of a glass of red wine. Pull camera out to show the glass of wine sitting on a white carpet. A dog comes by and spills the red wine onto the carpet. A toothless man wearing nothing but a flesh-colored unitard smacks the dog in the face with his wiener and says, "Remember, have your pets spayed or neutered," and proceeds to sodomize the German Shepherd as Foreigner's "I Want to Know What Love Is" plays in the background. Closeup of the wine on the carpet and dog squealing in the background. FADE OUT.  Look for that on a TV near you. It should be preceded by a Dawn commercial with a guy jumping over dishes on a motorcycle.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Murderstravaganza Weekend!  The History Channel, this weekend, decided to run a marathon of Infamous Murders for hours on end (how else do marathons go?).  Aren't we giving these murderers too much credit?  I mean, it's really easy to kill somebody, the hard part is not killing them.  They should make a show about all the times that I restrain myself from murdering numerous people on a daily basis.  The following list contains people that have escaped my murderous grasp within the last week:  *The guy, the other day when it was raining kind of hard, who was on his cell phone getting on the freeway, not paying attention.  *The strange little boy in Best Buy earlier today who smelled heavily of B.O. and kept running into me.  A boy that small shouldn't have B.O. already, I figured his murder would benefit us both.  *The guy last night at work who paid with a hundred dollar bill for his $80 check and only left me five.  I'm actually still planning on killing that guy, the wheels are already in motion.  *Finally, that guy who got married to  urlLink Britney Spears  just because she needs to be single again so I can still put it in her without feeling guilty.  Sure, they're probably getting it annulled, but it's just to be safe.  There you have it.  Now that I see it in print, I don't think that would be as interesting as people who actually did the murdering, so forget what you just read. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Happy Insignificant Holiday to Everybody!  The New Year has come and gone and what do we have to show for it?  Well, you went and got yourself knocked up earlier in the year and got an abortion at the seven month mark, you disgust me.  But this isn't about you, it's about me.  In fact, this isn't even about me, it's about this stupid "Holiday" in the first place.  What did I do for New Year's you ask?  First, I'd like to thank you for asking, and I'm sorry about snapping about the abortion thing -- I mean, I don't have a problem with abortion, but seven months is a bit too far in.  Second, I'll tell you what I did for New Year's (and you'll like it).  I was lucky enough to work on New Year's Eve.  Since I work about a half hour away from home, and I got off at eleven (he totally said "got off") that put me home at 11:30.  What's a girl to do then?  I watched a movie (28 Days Later), masturbated, and went to sleep, and not in that order -that part you'll have to guess.  Actually, the masturbation part was the most fun, I played a game with myself you see.  I had on "Dick Clark's New Year's Rockin' Eve" and I tried to time it so just as the ball dropped and hit the new year, I spewed my man-goo across the television screen, covering all of the kissing New Yorkers as if I was some new, half-retarded Giant Horseman of the Apocalypse with a giant erection.  But that's not the point.  The point is that celebrating New Years has to be the stupidest Holiday around.  Not to belittle those who've celebrated it, I mean, sure it gives some people reason to drink (like they need a reason, filthy alcoholics).  What irks me about it, though, is its absolute insignificance.  Celebrating the New Year is like throwing a party, getting high, drunk, having sex with a bat (however you celebrate), when the miles on your car hit 100,000.  WOOOOHOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!EXCLAMATIONPOINT  Some people say, "But it's important because it's symbolic.  It's a chance to start over."  You know what, whore, you're lucky I don't punch you right in your smelly mouth.  You can always start over.  If you need some sort of fictional Holiday to tell you to do this, then I need you to remember that Groundhog Day is symbolic of a time when you need to send me a thousand dollars and give me lots of blowjobs.  So all day at work today, when my guests would say to me, "Happy New Year", I would stick my pinky in my anus and wipe it on the rim of their glass.  So if you were one of my guests tonight, Happy New Year to you too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The Passion of the Christ: Jesus gets served!   Last night I became a Witness.  I Witnessed our Lord and Savior Jesus Harold Christ getting his ass kicked for 2 hours and 10 minutes until, ultimately, dying.  What a gyp!  First of all, this movie wasn't even in English!  I'm pretty sure it was in Jewish because there were a lot of 'h' sounds where it sounds like you're spitting and I know that Jewish people like to do that a lot.  That's bad planning on Mel Gibson's part.  He should know that American's hate reading when they're at the movies; that's why we go to the movies.  Sometimes I read what was on the screen, but my eyes got tired.  Plus, there was some big-time blood and guts on the screen so I couldn't be bothered with reading.  I got the gist of what was going on.  This Jesus guy, or "Yeshua" as they kept calling him (Isn't that the name for the upside down e? It's not a good name for the "Savior of the world", it gets too confusing), was all sad and shit because people are mean.  Then, something happens.  I think Jesus is caught shoplifting and everybody wants to kill him, so they take him to the manager, some bald guy (I think it was Napoleon), and he's all, "Ok, kill him."  So Jesus has to carry the cross (totally wicked move on Mel Gibson's part, I don't think this was in the book --this is the one, good addition) to some hill on Tatooine where they're going to kill him with it.  He never fought back though.  If somebody did to me what those guys with the riding crops did to him I would have lost it and been all, "Step off!  Jesus!  Seriously!"  But, no, he sat there, bleeding all over people until he "died".  There was some sloppy editing too.  At some parts in the movie there were obviously clips from the movie "Powder" spliced in there.  How could this get past the editor????  Did anybody even watch the movie before they released it?  I talked to people afterward and they said that this was supposed to be Satan, but I think they were just covering for Mel Gibson's shoddy work.  Besides, everybody knows that Satan is red, carries a giant fork with him and he has horse legs.  From what I heard from people who know a thing or two about the book that this is based on (which is supposed to be a best seller), Jesus is supposed to be, like, a totally kick-ass guy.  I hate when they change things from the book to the movie.  The  well-dressed people that told me about Jesus that come to my front door at seven in the morning on the weekends every once in a while, seemed believable; they're really adamant about it.  They come and tell me about how Jesus saved the world or something, but, from what I saw, Mel Gibson must hate Jesus.  For literally about half the movie Jesus was just getting the shit beat out of him.  This is where I thought, Cool, he's totally going to pull a Neo and figure it all out and kick these guys' asses once he's done.   IT NEVER HAPPENED!   I knew the movie was coming to an end because all the music was getting all loud and shit.  Jesus was standing on the Cross all like, "I'm ready, Father."  I thought for sure that right here he would shoot lazers out of his eyes and fry all the bad guys dressed like Russel Crowe, but he didn't.  Mel Gibson royally screwed the pooch on this one.  I've never seen a better example of false advertising than this one.  I mean, those people that came to my house told me --they said he saved the world, he saved me, he saved everybody but the Jewish people because they control the banks or something.  I would have been upset if this is how the movie ended.    Maybe I'm jumping to conclusions, but, at the end, there was this total teaser that there's going to be a sequel.  Warning, there are major spoilers coming.  If you don't want to know what happens, don't keep reading, and if you do want to know, then keep reading.  If you're indifferent, go make a sandwich and think about it, then get back to me.     Okay, so, Jesus is dead at the end, right?  Or so you think!  It fades to black after his family was all crying and shit at his "dead" body, so people in the theater start to get up.  But NO!  There's a shot inside like a tomb or cave or something, and there's a sheet on a table in the shape of Jesus, but you can tell he's not in there because it's all flapping and shit from the wind that somehow got in there.  The camera pulls out from the sheet to reveal, that's right, you guessed it, Jesus, ALIVE!  He was sitting on the edge of the table that they set his body on with a face like he was so ready to go out and stomp some balls.  Then he sits up, all determined and shit, you can tell because he wasn't smiling.  This was like the only time in the movie when he wasn't smiling, so you know he meant business.  All the rest of the time, before he "died", he was all like "I love you, my brother" with a big ole smile on his face like he just farted and nobody else knew it was him or something.  But this face, this was one of pure ass-kicking determination.  The best part was when he got up to walk out and open up his can of Whoopass on all the people that thought they killed him, you see that, on his hands, where they stuck the nails, there are some totally killer holes where the nails were!!  You know he's going to use this in the sequel!  Dude, "Passion of the Christ 2: Getting Jeezy With It", is going to kick more ass than both Matrix Sequels and Star Wars Prequels combined.  I waited through all the credits to see if they were going to show a teaser trailer for the next one, but they didn't, but I can imagine.  Jesus goes back to the guys in the capes dressed like Gandalf and he's all, "Heeeeeeeere's Jesus!" (totally a callback to Jack Nicholson in "The Shining")  Then they totally start to cry and beg saying they're sorry, but you know he's not going to hear it.  He pulls one guy's head off and throws it at another guy in a cape, knocking his head off too!  Then the rest of the guys see it and take off running.   Then, in the next clip of the trailer you'll finally see Jesus start to hook up with that Mary Magdalene chick that I heard about.  I heard that he totally gets together with her and she's a hooker.  See?  He's like a reluctant hero.  He plays by his own rules, nobody else's.    Finally, in the last part of the clip, you'll see Jesus standing in the middle of the water with his staff all in the air shouting, "Behold, the only thing greater than yourself!", and he'll slam it down into the water and Part the Red Sea.  It'll look like he's standing in the middle of a tidal wave of blood that can't hit him because he's like a reincarnated wizard.  Then the music stops and on the screen it's all, "The Passion returns...Summer 2005" --"Directed by Ang Lee".  That's what I'm talking about.  I think this movie was more like a prequel than anything.  All of the serious, Destructo-Jesus action will come in the next one.  I also read somewhere that Dolph Lundgren is going to play Jesus in the next one, because he's supposed to be older and more German in the sequel.  I just read it, so don't take it as the absolute truth, but Oh my GOD, if it is, think of how awesome it will be instead of that guy from "Frequency".  If you have any questions or comments about this article  urlLink email me .  Or if you have any hot tips about the sequel, send them to me;  I couldn't really find anything online about it.  I looked it up under "2 Passion 2 Christ", "Passion of the Christ 2: The New Batch", and "The Passion Too starring Jason Bateman as the Werewolf", and found nothing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        It Taint What It Used to Be   The following story is absolutely true.  There has been very little hyperbole in the details describing the ensuing event.  Reader discretion is advised.  In fact, you probably don't even want to read it -it's disgusting.  Tonight, around 12:30, I realized I had had enough.  The other day, while grooming my man-area, I was working the area between the umm, brain and the turdcutter, also known as the taint or choad.  I ran into a speedbump that I know is there, a dirty, filthy skintag, but this time, I accidentally cut it.  I was wondering why I had started to bleed as if I had a tiny faux-vagina between my legs, then I realized that I had given a fleshwound to Skintag Sal.  Sal has been with me for about two years.  I've watched him grow; he's become a part of me, really.  I thought that he would be okay, but over the next couple of days, I realized that Sal was getting out of control.  Perhaps at the sight of his own blood, he was thrown into an Incredible Hulk-like state and began to grow, but by tonight around 12:30, I couldn't take it anymore.  Sal had to go.  It is very difficult to break up a relationship, especially when you basically spend 24-7 (twenty four hours a day, seven days a week for those who hate numbers) together.  I wasn't quite sure how to do it, so I did what my dad would do to me when he wanted to get rid of me.  I smothered him with a bag of ice.  After about 10 (ten, again, for those who hate numbers) minutes of what had to be the most emotionally difficult time in my life (you try being forced to murder your own baby...), Sal was unconscious, numb.  I poised myself.  I sat there -naked- on my bed, with a paper towel beneath Sal, to cushion his fall.  I may be a murderer, but at least I had the decency and respect for him to try to do this properly.  I reached out and grabbed the guillotine, a pair of fingernail clippers with I (heart) New York inscribed on the main lever.  I figured this would be the best way to do it, as the last image Sal's fading vision would see would be "I (heart) New York".  Oh how he loved the Big Apple.  I remember one time when he and I were visiting, we were riding the Subway from Times Square uptown to Harlem and we both fell asleep, in each other's arms, and wound up riding the train all the way to Brooklyn.  We didn't care.  We had each other.  This was how it had to be.  With tears in my eyes, I brought the clippers down to ready position -nestled on both sides of Sal's beautiful, innocent head.  With a forced smile and a single tear streaming down my cheek, I said to him, "Hey, buddy.  Next stop...Brooklyn."   In an instant he was gone.  I mean, his body was there, stuck to the fingernail clippers, but it wasn't him anymore.  The lifeforce that made Sal Sal was no longer there.  With one fell swoop our two-year relationship was over.  All I have to show for it is a little nub which I may take a nail file to tomorrow.  It's just too painful to have any memory of him around; it's much easier if he's gone.  Out of sight, out of mind.    I don't know how to dispose of the body, though.  It's sitting in front of me, on my computer desk, on a sheet of paper from February 5, 2001 of a Far Side comic-a-day calendar I use to write notes on.  I can't throw him away; Sal meant too much to me.  I will probably take him to New York and spread his ashes on the Subway.  On the A Train.  Our train. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "You got Served"...   So, in what I'm sure will go down in "The New Bible" as the first sign of the Apocalypse, the movie -nay, gritty independent film- "You got Served" starring none other than the four boys of the now defunct B2K musical extravaganza group, was number one at the Box Office this weekend.  It is probably no surprise to you that I have already begun hoarding food, water, and B2K's CD's to help me survive during this time of Armageddon.  I almost forgot...WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH PEOPLE QUESTION MARK AND EXCLAMATION POINTS IN ALL CAPS??!??!?!  I'm hoping against hope, and wishing against wish that people went to watch this movie as a joke. This was the most hilarious $17 million joke in the history of $17 million dollar jokes. Please. Somebody, confirm this for me.  This starts me thinking. What if 'N Sync (is it an apostrophe or a * there?)and the Backstreet Boys were to make their own superfilm. They could call it, "You have been promptly served, friend". This would follow the hilarious hijinx of two ultra-successful pop groups as they entered tournaments against one another to see who could suck more (editors note: when the author uses the term "suck more" here, he does not mean the movie with Bill Murray and Jason Shwartzman about a kid at a prep school who falls in love with one of the teachers there, that's "Rushmore". I can't believe you thought that he meant that movie. What are you, retarded?). I would suggest also calling this film "The great suck off", but I'm pretty sure that there's a porno with that name already. This would probably make a lot more than $17 million in its first weekend and I'll tell you why. The audience for this movie would be a bunch of white kids instead of black kids: Everybody knows that white people actually pay to get in to movies (editors note: when the author uses the term "black kids" here, he means those of african decent, not to be confused with the famous "Black Kids" radio show of the 1920's which featured all white voice talent).  Now that I've probably offended black people and gay people, and especially gay, black people (special shout-out to my homie Ru Paul all up in this beeotch), I think I'll finish this up. I love all humans on this planet equally, except for people that have sex with dead things, animals, or trees - I love them less. This is also with the exception of people who have sex with books, mud, and hippies - I love them more.  At least, with the inception of this movie, I have something to say to my tables after I've waited on them:  "Thank you very much. Have a good night. You suckas just got served!"  Then I throw four fingers up with two twisted in the middle.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        People that shouldn't be alive anymore   The following is all about people who need to take their own lives sometime in the near future:  People who think MadTV is hysterical (Stewart is funny, sometimes, but almost everything else sucks). People who support anything that comes out of George W. Bush's mouth.  If he said, "We should all give Kurt (that's me, the writer -- he doesn't say this part in parentheses) all of our money and lavish him with all the free boobies he wants."  I'd be like, "Fuck that guy.  He's an idiot."  Out of pure reflex; that's how used I am to him being an over-flowing bag of douche. People who tan more than they read (I don't read a whole lot, but I never fucking tan). People who read my Passion of the Christ entry and think I'm going to Hell. People who like cock-fighting (not gay people, I mean the stuff where roosters rip the shit out of each other --gay people are fine by me). People who don't appreciate Will Ferrell. People who use abbreviations like "lol" after everything they type online, even if it's not funny. (I'm going to school. lol.  It's going to be awesome. lol. --just fucking die). People who use 'U' instead of 'you', 'R' instead of 'are' and who type in all sorts of Tourette's Syndrome-induced sporradic caps lock usage like so: U r So GoiNg 2 HelL 4 TaWKinG aB0uT JeSuS LIkE ThaT!!!!111@ People who were offended by Janet Jackson's boob. (It's a boob.  I guarantee you that people'd be much more offended if I showed my pasty, white man-boob on National Television). People who don't always offer me sexual favors of my choosing (Goddamn Nuns). People who think Goonies is a bad movie. (No explanation necessary, "Heeeeeeeeeeyyyyy Yooooouuuuuuuu Guuuuuuuuuys!") People who rape other people without them asking for it (you know, by wearing sexy clothes or looking at you with "that look") People who dislike other people for having opinions they can't help but have (fucking idiots, what's wrong with those people?)  On that ironic note, I'm done here.  You've enjoyed what you've read.   urlLink Email me  thoughts, comments, pictures of you experimenting with your naughty self. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Amputees All Up In My Mind   Last week I had two dreams on two consecutive nights about amputees.  They were both in the third person too.  I wasn't a part of either of them.  I think that shows that I have so little self-esteem that I don't even include myself in my dreams.  In the first dream the guy from "Ed" was an amputee missing his legs Lieutenant Dan-style.  But in the second dream, the next night, some girl that was in a couple of my classes in the Fall Quarter was an amputee.  Instead of missing her entire legs, though, she was just missing her feet.  Then, instead of feet she had wheels --like wagon wheels, one for each leg.  She zipped around on the ground like Rosie from the "Jetsons."    If it came down to it, I'd fist-fight an amputee.  Not that I think it would ever happen, but I'm not about to stop my passion in life, hardcore Brazillian Street Fighting, just because you're missing an arm or foot or whatever.  Go cry to somebody who doesn't have your leg and stump in an Armenian double-folded chicken gizzard hold.  I think the only way that they'd get me off of them is if they touched me with the stump or made me look at it really close.  I might be able to deal with it if they touched me through clothing, but if it was skin-on-skin, I'd definitely have to back off.    That's all I've got.  Tonight I dream of butterflies and all the pancakes I can eat!   urlLink Email me  with question, comments, suggestions, or to tell me that you're an amputee and you're typing to me through your special, left-hand-only keyboard. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I want a famous face (that looks like it was hit by a bus)   In keeping with my MTV shows theme that I've got going on here, I want to yell at you about the show I Want a Famous Face.  I don't like to get all political and retrospective about things, but fuck.  What the hell does this kind of show say about the type of society in which we live?  People spend their own money so that they can look like their favorite celebrity through all sorts of plastic surgery.  The good part about this show, however, is that the people almost always end up looking like what that celebrity would look like if they had an extra 21st chromosome.  There are two that have gone down as my favorites.  The first one of these consisted of a pair of twins that wanted to both look like Brad Pitt.  One of them had the worst acne I've seen in a long time --and this is including my back.  They both got venires (big-ass fake teeth), and a bunch of work done to their messed up faces.  They even got their hair done by some fabulous hairdresser.  Of course, after surgery they looked, especially one of them that had implants put all up in his face, like they had been stung by a thousand super bees.  Then, weeks later it showed them at some party where their "friends" were saying things like, "Oh, they...do...look like Brad Pitt."  They were so paid to say that shit.  Unless MTV left out the part where all of their friends were stricken with glaucoma.  They then went on to try to get agents and head shots for their soon-to-be prospering modeling career.  The delusion in these two men would have been admirable to see in just one man, but in two men it is phenomenal.  I look more like Brad Pitt than they do and I'm a black female midget.  The second episode that I love is awesome in a completely different way.  By the way, when I say "love" I mean that I can't believe that this sort of shit actually makes it on TV.  It's sort of difficult to explain, so bear with me.  A guy, who loves Jennifer Lopez (J-Lo for all the people reading this that I fucking hate), and wants to look like her because he's a trans-something (vestite or sexual, I don't know the difference), gets his surgery to try to make this dream come true.  He's completely a man, though, parts-wise.  He's got a wiener that he eludes to later on in the show when he talks about how his "straight" boyfriend is in love with him.  Anyway, the fantastic part about this is that there HAD to have been a meeting where there was discussion on whether or not they had to blur out this person's nipples on TV.  Much to my surprise, and masturbatory disappointment, his (HIS --IT'S A GUY) nipples were blurred out.  Before the breast-augmentation operation they were blurred.  Since when is it not allowed to show man-titties on TV?  Anyway, this is how I imagine the decision to blur the shit out went:  MTV EXEC: So, we've got this guy who wants to look like J-Lo (he'd say this because he's an MTV douchebag).  MTV CENSOR GUY:  Okay, and...?  MTV EXEC: Well, at one point he gets a boob job.  MTV CENSOR GUY:  Jesus Christ, what's wrong with people?  MTV EXEC: I don't know.  Kids eat this shit up.  Anyway, he's a guy.  He's fully a guy.  MTV CENSOR GUY:  Peepee?  MTV EXEC: What? Yeah.  I think you're asking if he's got a penis.  Yes, he does.  MTV CENSOR GUY: Okay, let's pretend that's what I meant.  MTV EXEC: Well, I was just wondering if we're going to have to blur his nipples out.  MTV CENSOR GUY: You're telling me that this is somebody who is, anatomically, a man, 100-percent?  MTV EXEC: Ana-what?  MTV CENSOR GUY: Peepee!  MTV EXEC: Oh.  Yes.  MTV CENSOR GUY: But he thinks, inside his head, that he's a woman trapped in a man's body?  MTV EXEC: Yes.  He feels like he's a woman.  MTV CENSOR GUY: Blur it!  MTV EXEC: What?  But he's a...  MTV CENSOR GUY: BLUR IT YOU SICK SONOFABITCH!  MTV EXEC: I don't know why you're getting so hostile.  I...  MTV CENSOR GUY: Two words: Janet Jackson.  MTV EXEC: I'm not following.  Is this a...?  Oh, wait.  I get it.  Tito Jackson.  MTV CENSOR GUY: I don't think you do get it.  MTV EXEC: Oh, I thought we were naming our favorite Jackson.  MTV CENSOR GUY: What makes you think that, out of nowhere, I'd just start to play that game?  MTV EXEC: I don't know.  It's big around the office here.  MTV CENSOR GUY: Anyway, blur his boobs.  MTV EXEC: So because he thinks that he's a woman, because of what he's thinking at that moment, we have to censor his nipples?  MTV CENSOR GUY: Exactly.  It makes perfect sense, right?  MTV EXEC: Not at all.  MTV CENSOR GUY: Just do it.  I don't want to get calls.  MTV EXEC: Fine.    MTV CENSOR GUY: That ought to do it, right?  MTV EXEC: I guess.  Just curious, though, when we air our summer shows from the Beach house, and we've got all these guys wandering around with their shirts off, do we have to ask them if they feel that, deep within their heart of hearts, they are really a woman?  MTV CENSOR GUY: Err on the side of caution.  MTV EXEC: This is going to cost us a ton in Nipple blurring overtime money.  MTV CENSOR GUY: I don't care.  Remember, Janet Jackson.  MTV EXEC: TITO.  No.  No.  Jermaine!  Randy!  MTV CENSOR GUY: You're right.  It is fun.  The two men argue for nine straight hours and ultimately wind up dry humping on the desk.  That concludes this presentation of Executive Theatre.  Tune in next week when we discuss what went into the ABC show "The Swan".    Stupid makeover shows.  I want a makeover show of my own, but I want it in reverse.  I want to see if they can give me a cleft pallete and sew on a fourth and fifth nipple.  Maybe I'll even get that nose augmentation surgery I've always wanted.  I will call it "Quasimojo".  The tagline: "Nobody can resist that just-escaped-from-the-Belltower look!  Coming this summer following The Littlest Groom."  That was a long entry.  I'm proud of me.  I think I'm going to do this more often so I can feel like I'm writing on a regular basis like I should be.  If you want to talk to me about this or anything in particular,  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Stupid Ass Real World   I've watched the Real World since it started.  Sure, I'm kind of a vagina for this, but whatever, I'm over it, you should be too.  Over the years it has grown more and more ridiculous, but today --today my friends it has crossed the line.    The red-headed "punk" chick, Frankie, apparently cheated on her just as faux-punk boyfriend.  She couldn't stand that she cheated on him so she cut herself.  "I cut myself because I deserve it," she would say to the Asian chick that goes to my school.  I heard from a friend of mine at school, by the way, that the Asian chick, Jamie, is a pothead like there's no tomorrow.  Whatever.  I'd still let her make out with me and hump me if she wanted.  Not that I'd like it; I'd just do it because she wanted to.  But I digress.  So, apparently the writers --yes, I'm convinced that the stupid show has writers now-- thought that having Frankie --if that is her real name-- coming out of the bathroom and dropping a knife conspicuously in front of Jamie, would be a good, dramatic way to reveal that she was in there cutting herself.  Stupid goddamn show.  If I wrote something that contrived I'd cut my fingers off so I'd be forced to dictate that to somebody else and then, while it was being said aloud, I'd realize how dumb it is and ask for one gunshot to the skull to end my life for thinking of something that horrible.  And oh.  The show was prefaced and postfaced (I think that's what you call something that comes after --maybe I should have said bookended.  Yeah, it was bookended) by little PSA-(Public Service Announcement) type things with Dr. Drew from Loveline saying that cutting is a serious thing and that if you do it you're a dumbass with no self-control and you should get kicked in the face by a thousand professional facekickers.  I'm pretty sure that's what he said.  Whenever I see him on TV I mute it and make up what he's saying like my own version of "Whose Line Is It Anyway?".  So I've done that one time.  Long-story short, I fucking hate the Real World now and will never watch it again*.   *Until next week when somebody is totally maybe sleeping with somebody else.  It's going to be so awesome.  I need a girlfriend.  If you are like me and you bathe in your own feces or you hate the real world or you love it or you cut yourself or you like run-on sentences or you think I'm a hot piece of ass, let me know  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm not going to be able to sleep   Well, tomorrow morning at 9 a.m. I have to pitch my script to like three producers.  Right now I feel like I'm going to throw up.  This is so not cool.  I'm all antsy like a little girl who's having an affair with her teacher and doesn't want her mom to find out.  That's exactly how I am.  Except instead of me being a girl and having an affair with a teacher I'm nervous because what happens tomorrow could have strong bearing on what happens to me for the rest of my life.  I'm bad with analogies.  I'll have to work on that.  So, I think I have my pitch memorized, but not so much so that it sounds like Vicki from Small Wonder is giving it.  Wait a minute!  I wonder what  urlLink Tiffany Brissette  is up to.  I'm sure with a little searching online I can find her telephone number.  It would go over really well I'm sure.  Me: And now, to present my story, please welcome Vicki!  (cue theme music: "She's fantastic, made of plastic...") (Now thirty-years old, dressed in the same red and white dress, she stares straight ahead.)  Vicki (all monotone and roboty):  Thank you.  Once again, a big hand for Kurt.  (It gets all green-screen looking and her hand blows up all big.  Everybody laughs, a few even cry because they laugh so hard.)  I think that could happen.  I wish I could just fast-forward life until tomorrow at like 9:30 when I'm sitting in class, my pants soiled, totally relaxed because it's all over.  If I was a drug-taking man I'd be all over some of whatever helps people sleep.  I heard that heroine is good for that, or hookers.    And now I'm just writing more so I can pass the time.  If anybody reads this tonight, drop a comment and I'll give you directions to my house and you can come over and put me to sleep.  Especially if you're reading this and you're a horse.  This is for two reasons: 1) You're a horse that can read and I'd like to meet you.  2) You probably have horse tranquilizers.  3) There isn't a third reason, that's why I said for two reasons.  To top it all off, I didn't make the cheer squad!  There's always next year.  No there isn't.  This is it, my senior year.  My mom spent like 500 dollars buying me all my cheer stuff and now I have to return it?  Life isn't fair!  Interesting thought of the day: Every time a girl farts, a man loses an erection. Think about it, ladies.  Comments,  urlLink email , etc. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        People that stink   In life, there are stinky people and these people all have different malodorous content that makes them displeasing to the olfactory sense.  Man, I just dropped some serious nasal vocabulary on your ass, you better recognize, beeeeotch!  Back to the original point --there are some people that smell like B.O.  I'd venture to guess that this is the category wherein the majority of people that are referred to as "stinky" fall.  A lot of times this can be remedied, but in two cases that I've encountered, the only solution is homicide --and lots of it.  I've referred to it before, but there was this one kid in some store, he had to be like seven or something, who stunk well beyond his years.  Unless he was a hard-working midget, there's no reason that somebody that tiny should pack that much of a stench.  Truth be told, I have no idea how old the kid was.  I am really bad at telling how old kids are; I have no concept of what children should look like at certain ages.  That kid could have been seven or he could have been fourteen.  Anyway, the second guy that stunk was in Best Buy and I had to leave the row he was in because he smelled so bad.  But at least this guy looked like he should stink.  He had on overalls and I think half of a full set of teeth and, I can't read minds too often, but I'm pretty sure he was thinking something dirty, too.  Those people are your standard stinkies.  Then, there are people that stink for other reasons.  There's the old lady that wears way too much perfume --apparently in an attempt to cover up the fact that she is decaying before your eyes.  Then there's the guy that wears too much cologne.  This guy, I'm pretty sure, thinks that there is a direct correlation between how much cologne he wears and how much vagina he will be getting by the end of the night.  I actually experimented with this theory once and I passed out in the car on the way to the club.  But, on the bright side, I did wake up with messy pants.  So who knows?  Then there's the third kind of person that smells.  This person is the mystery stink.  This is the guy that makes you look around and say, "Is somebody boiling cabbage, or ass?"  Then, when you turn the stove off where you're making your famous boiled cabbage and ass enchiladas, you realize that the smell still pervades.  This type of person seems nice on the surface, but you know that the way that they stink can only be the result of something really sinister --like molestation.  Not that those who get molested stink, but those who commit the crime do.  I'll bet that people who molest people have an odor to them that is unlike most humankind.  I promise you that you have smelled the stench of a molester before and you knew that something was wrong with them and you couldn't put your finger on it.  Now you know.  They touch little kids.    Granted, there are people who occasionally stink because they just worked out or they stepped in poop, but this article is here to salute those that make it a fashion statement.  This article is a tribute to the perpetually stinky.  To those of you reading this who stink, I salute you!   urlLink Email me  or post your comments about the stink. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hawaii   Okay, I was just sitting here, minding my own business, pulling cat hairs from my urethra, when I heard American Idol on my TV.  Apparently they're replaying auditions or something and they're showing the auditions from Hawaii.  Now, I've never been to Hawaii, I couldn't even point it out on a map of Hawaii, but there's one thing about Hawaiians that I hate.  I hate how they pronounce their state.  Instead of it being three free-flowing syllables that roll off the tongue like the sounds of a thousand --no, a million--breezes, they split it up and give each syllable its own stage time.  It irritates me so bad that, when I hear anybody pronounce it like that, I throw my cat off my lap in disgust.  Those weird Hawaiians have their own traditions and customs that they should leave on their land-boats and not force upon us mainlanders.  I'll never understand throwing a pig in the sand to cook it.  That would just make it really dirty and you'd probably get bottlecaps and cigarette butts all up in the pig skin that you'd have to pick out later on.  Also, I heard that Hawaiians sacrifice their first born by throwing it off a cliff and onto a surfboard.  Interesting thought of the day: Graham Crackers were invented by Heather Graham on the set of  Boogie Nights .   urlLink Email me  or post your comments, beeotches (you can post anonymously). 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        It's time for some current events!   Nothing exciting is happening in my life right now, except for the fact that I went grocery shopping yesterday and bought some Orange Juice, so I'm going to write about whatever current events are on the front page of  urlLink Google News  right now.     urlLink Our first story  is about gay people marrying other gay people in Massachusetts.  I guess that the people that get married don't have to be gay, but then that would just be weird, so they should probably be gay just so they can avoid those awkward mornings after.  I will never understand why people don't want the gays to be able to get married.  It's funny because people against it always say, "Well, if you let a man (or woman) marry another man (or woman), what's next? a man marrying an dog?"  I don't know where this leap comes from.  As much as I would love to see this animal matrimony come to fruition, I don't think that that's the next logical step after allowing same-sex marriage.  There is no step after this except for trans-whatever people wanting to marry people, but I think that that gets fixed by letting any person marry any other person.  Anyway, my point is, let anybody marry whoever they want because I have fourteen flannel shirts for seven separate weddings that I am supposed to attend just sitting in my closet.  Set my closet free!  No, wait, I just thought of a better line.  Let me empty out my closet, by filling those of the people who are no longer in theirs.  It's a little wordy, but I like it.  On to news article number two (and I think the last one, this isn't exactly going gangbusters over here):   urlLink Gwyneth Paltrow had a baby!  ...And she named it after the thing that killed Eve after it fell on her head and she discovered gravity and Adam shot it off her head with a bow and arrow in the Garden of Eden.  Give up?  They named her Diaphragm!  Ok, I'm lying (by the way, if I ever accidentally have a child, I'm naming them Diaphragm.)  Apple Blythe Alison Martin is her name.  She has FOUR names, three of which qualify as a first name and one that doesn't.  The one that doesn't qualify is the one that they actually gave her as her first name.  They think that they're fooling everybody by giving her so many first names that people won't notice that her real first name isn't actually a name, but a shampoo scent.  Those tricky celebrities.  The best part about this will be eighteen years from now when she decides that mommy was too busy making movies and daddy was too busy making songs that play during sad parts in movies that now she has to show her parents what this did to her by bumping uglies with a one-eyed Honduran teenage girl in the four hundredth Girls Gone Wild video.    Now, I could make a joke about having a son and naming him Banana, but that's too easy.  It's a good thing I have the self-control to not say things like this.  I had some Captain Crunch about an hour ago and, surprisingly, the roof of my mouth is still in tact.  Sometimes eating that stuff is like eating glass except without all the nutritious content.  Interesting thought of the day: Babies are nature's way of punishing people for having sex.   urlLink Email me  or post your comments here (I had to delete all of them so far because people tend to get out of hand). 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Comments!   Now, all of my loyal readers, instead of me having to sift through hundreds of emails at a time to decide who is worthy enough to quote in an entry, you all can post comments freely!  Isn't that exciting?  I can't believe all of the fan interaction that will go on here.  It will be a varitable cornucopia of people who like to use the word "fag" in ways that I've never even heard before.    On to the real entry:  (This was inspired by a devoted reader requesting me to comment on this)  Have you ever had a Pannido from Jack in the Box?  If you haven't, I'll break it down for you.  It's this sandwich that's like nine inches long, but not very thick.  Well, for a sandwich it's not very thick.  It's more circular than it is rectangular.  If I were a guessing man, I'd say that it's got a diameter of between two and three inches (that's two and a half inches).  They're very delicious, but it's like somebody decided that eating a sandwich wasn't enough like giving a blowjob, and they had to change that.  I've never felt more like a gay man (or a straight man in a desperate situation, right, Ryan?) in my life.  But it's so tasty that I don't want to stop.  That must be what goes through their head when they're doing it, too.  Even when you bite down too hard the creamy condiment filling squirts out uncontrollably.  Like I said, though, they're so delicious that I can't stop eating them.  If somebody told me that they'd give me a free Pannido, but only if I ate it in front of a room full of masturbating men, I'd have to take the Pannido.  Heck, I'd even throw in a little bit of "minding the stepchildren" just to entertain my audience.    Interesting thought of the day: Sigalert is Spanish for car accident.  Okay, now it's your turn to post.  If you don't want to comment, you can always  urlLink email me  instead. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Amputees Redux   I received well over 100 emails about my last weblog.  The majority of them were supportive, but there were some detractors.  The supportive emails went mostly like this:  Dear Kurt,  I know exactly what you mean about amputees.  I've been a professional street fighter for over five years and I've been in the ring with approximately three different amputees.  There's something about them, maybe it's their lack of complete body-ness, or the smug way that they think they can "do whatever everybody else can do" that makes me want to hurt them more, but there's something there.  Next time I get out there and have to fight an "unfinished" as I like to call them, I'll make sure I punch them in their stump an extra time just for you.  Keep up the good work.  You're hilarious.  (  So-and-so   That's how about 90 or so of the emails went, but apparently I have a huge amputee following.  It's not that I really have ever punched an amputee, I just would, that's all.  But here's one of the emails that I got:  From: threefourthswhole@yahoo.com To: dirtiestbastard@hotmail.com  Kurt,  I can't believe you would write something like that.  Are you serious?  Why would you punch people just because they're missing body parts?  That doesn't make sense.  Besides, I'll bet you if you saw me on the streets you wouldn't pick a fight with me.  I'm 6'4", 270 pounds of pure man.  Sure, I'm missing my right arm, I have since I was born, but I would kick your ass with my hand tied behind my back.  I don't know what I'd tie it to, maybe my belt loop if I wasn't wearing the bicycle shorts that I always wear, but I'd figure something out.  I know, I'd use an intricate system of bungee cords and pullees that would ensure my hand would stay back there.  Anyway, I'd win and you'd sit there crying like the little bitch that you are, hiding behind your keyboard and handsome face.  Yeah, I said you're handsome.  There are some universal truths in this world and that's one of them.  I can hate you for being a full-bodyist (that's what us appendage-challenged call those who have prejudices against us), but I can also love you for looking like an angel.  Half yours,  This guy.  Well, there you have it.  Maybe you agree with me or you don't disagree with me, but we can all agree that while you may hate the inside, you've got to love the outside --I'm like a doughnut filled with a mystery fluid.  I'll give you a minute on that double negative I used back there at the beginning of that run-on sentence.   urlLink Email me  to let me know about other things that don't relate to amputees.  I can't deal with all of that email.  How about you email me and tell me about your day or a scary story or the situations in which you would drink your own pee. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Feeling Hot Hot Hot!   So, I saw  Fahrenheit 9/11  today.  Michael Moore will be happy to know that I saw his film and George Bush will be happy to know that I didn't pay for it.  I hope that I made both sides happy here, because that's what's important.  That chubby bastard sure is good at making a persuasive argument.  It's a shame I don't know more about things in general, or I probably wouldn't constantly be thinking, Oh, that's a good point.  I'm sure, like in  Bowling for Columbine , there's a lot of sneaky editing and things, but that's what a director does; especially a director who's trying to get his point across.    The reason I'm writing this post, however, is because I saw a thing on MTV News (the hardest hitting news source on television) about the film.  They interviewed three people (a black guy, a white guy, and a white girl) who said they were on the fence before the film, and then, what they thought about Bush after the film.  The black guy and the white guy were a little swayed, but not a lot, they were swayed within reason after seeing a piece of political propoganda (any documentary is propoganda).  But the girl was blown away.  She said, "This totally makes me want to become, like, more active in the political system so I can, like, really make a difference.  You know?"  She said she had voted for Bush in 2000, but definitely wasn't going to vote for him this time around.  It's strange what the film does.  It doesn't necessarily say, "Vote for Kerry," (he's not even mentioned) but, instead, it says, "Don't vote for Bush!"  I'm going to vote for Kerry anyway, because I voted for Gore in 2000 and I swear, if Bush gets re-elected in 2004, I'm putting the entire country on restriction.  No Nintendo for TWO WEEKS!  And I mean it.  No amount of sad faces or begging will make me change my mind.  I think that Kerry's new campaign slogan should go like this (since it's basically doing this without saying it anyway):  A vote for Kerry: It's not a vote for Bush!   Anyway, on a different note, that guy Ken just won his 20th straight time on Jeopardy.  He's the scariest Mormon Software Engineer I know.  Interesting thought of the day: Putting food coloring in your eyes does NOT work like liquid sunglasses.  It just stings a lot.  You can comment anonymously below or  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Dy-No-Mite!   Yesterday, I drove down to Oceanside to go see a pre-release screening of  Napoleon Dynamite  with a friend of mine.  He had heard that there was a free screening thing in San Diego so we left his house at like 5:00 figuring it would probably take a half an hour to get there or so.  Apparently everybody on the goddamn road didn't know we had a movie to make because they were DRIVING SO FUCKING SLOW!  Long story short, we got there at like 6:15, waited in line, only to be told, with about 250 other people, that there wasn't anymore room in the theater.  It was weird, though.  After this tiny girl came out and told all of us that, nobody moved.  It was strange to see 250 people all experience denial at once.  They were all kind of looking around, waiting.  I think everybody thought that everybody else will leave and then, when there's only like 4 of them left, there will definitely be spots in there for them to see the movie.  But, when 250 people share this idea, it doesn't exactly work out as planned.  So, my friend and I headed back to his truck.  See, he had a good parking spot at the mall.  It was the very first spot in like the third closest row to the mall.  This is prime real estate for this mall since the way that the parking is set up sucks.  So, he and I stand outside of his car for a while, sitting on the tailgate so people don't think that we're leaving and get excited and pause their car in the middle of the isle.  Then, he decides it's better if we go inside his truck and sit down.  We had to go when no cars were around so they wouldn't think we were leaving.  He's weird.  Anyway, so we're sitting there, trying to figure out what to do since it's about 6:30 and traffic will surely suck right now if we try to head out.  Then, all of a sudden, he decides that it's the perfect time to straighten out a problem he was having with his cell phone.  He calls the cell phone company, talking to them, being put on hold for like 10 minutes while I'm sitting there watching some dorky guy with a way-too-hot-for-him girlfriend frolic inside the mall all excited probably to go wait in line to buy tickets for  White Chicks  because it looks so hilarious.  I fucking hate Marlon Wayans.  He's as funny as a baby with cancer.  Anyway, so he's sitting there on his cell phone in the mall parking lot, with me sitting in the passenger seat, a hostage.  By the way, he's a big Mexican guy --this comes into play.  We've been there for like 15 minutes when a Mall Security Guard rides by on his bicycle.  Nothing says authority like  Ring! Ring!  "Pull Over!"  So, we got pulled over going 0.  The guy says, "What's going on, guys?"  My friend answers while on hold, "Nothing!  You?"  It's not a good move to backtalk a guy who's already so starved for some sort of power that he's taken to riding a bicycle, wearing a uniform, to exert some sort of authority.  My friend starts talking into his phone again, but, apparently, the Security Guard wasn't satisfied with my friend's answer.  I decide, so as not to bother my friend by talking across him, I'll get out of the truck and talk to the faux-cop.  As I step out, I see that there's another Mall Security bicycle cop on my side of the car.  The original cop yells out, "He's getting out of the truck" to his buddy on my side, like I'm some sort of a threat.  I think that they're taught in Mall Security Guard school that they have to state the obvious at all times.  So, I get out of the truck and explain to the now two guys that we're sitting there because we came to see a movie that we couldn't get into and now we're trying to figure out what to do.  Thank God I'm white.  They totally bought it and the kids we kidnapped lying in the backseat of his truck wouldn't be saved.  So, all because my friend had to fix his phone at that exact point in time, I had to almost murder two mall cops.  We ended up having a romantic dinner at IHOP, getting some Coldstone ice cream, and making sweet-ass love (or sweet ass-love, whatever) back at his house.    Also, yesterday, before I went down there, I decided to get an oil change for the first time in like 8,000 miles.  The people at Jiffy Lube didn't like that.  When I was paying for it, the guy behind the counter actually lectured me and made me feel guilty.  Fuck that guy.  Now I'm going 10,000 miles between the next one.  Making me feel guilty for ruining my own stuff.  That's a long entry.  I applaud anybody who made it through it; I barely did.  Interesting thought of the day: Shakespeare wrote all of his plays while on ye olde toilet.  He had Irritable Bowel Syndrome.  Comment below or, if you're a big ole fraidy cat, you an  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Heads are gonna roll!   Okay, this post is going to be in bad taste to some people, so you probably shouldn't read it.   Now that those people left (good, I didn't like them anyway), it's time to address some current events again.  This time, however, it's going to get as bloody as the inside of a surprised teenage girl's panties in here.  That's horrible.  Too bad my Back Space key doesn't work or I'd erase that.  Al-Qaeda (or however you spell it, even if I did find the right way to spell it, I can't fix it now) decided that they're going to behead people more often than reruns of "Friends" comes on.  They got Nick Berg a while ago.  I say, touche, Al-Qaeda.  Then they got this Paul Johnson fellow.  I say, it's getting kind of old, guys.  Now, there's some South Korean guy that they're threatening to behead.  You know, like my writing teachers have always taught me, you can only go to the well so many times until it loses its meaning and, well, it's lost its meaning.  I mean, granted, it's horrible that a guy is getting his head sawed off by some dull-ass blade, but it's just not as shocking as it used to be.  These Al-Qaeda guys are losing their bang.  At first America was thinking, Wow, they're so crazy and primitive, and I think Al-Qaeda fed off of this reaction.  Now, when I hear about another beheading, I remember that it's time to water my roses.*  *I don't have any roses; this is merely used an example to imply the frequency with which they lop people's heads off.  Anyway, to switch gears,  urlLink there's a non-government-funded spaceship  that's supposed to be flying into space tomorrow.  Call me cynical, but I think that this means that sometime tomorrow there's going to be a news story about the first non-government-funded body to decompose while re-entering the earth's atmosphere.  I hope it goes well and I hope they finally prove that there really is no such thing as outer space, it's all just a movie set like in the  Truman Show , but I have a feeling that it may not go so well.    There was something else I wanted to write about, but I can't remember what it is, so you'll have to deal with my two stories both related to death and destruction.  I'm a very fun person to be around.  I'm like a walking circus without all of the clown make-up and cotton candy, but with all of the weird feelings involved in the men's heads when they see the children.  Interesting thought of the day: You should never go to a place that offers surgery with discounts with coupons.  Especially if that place is a Pizza Hut.  Post your comments and you could win a special prize.  Or  urlLink email me  for a free proctology exam (well, a coupon for one). 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Earthquakes and Scientologists!   Well, I missed another earthquake today.  When I say I missed it, I mean that I didn't feel it.  It's not like somebody threw one at me and I couldn't hit it.  That's just silly.  You can't throw earthquakes, anymore.  Not since the great reckoning.  The guy on the news in that magic box that sits underneath my DVD player said that it was centered near San Diego.  I've lived in Southern California all my life and I love earthquakes.  There aren't nearly enough of them.  I wish that, instead of an alarm clock, an earthquake woke me up in the morning, because nothing says, "Get up" like your house collapsing around you and thoughts of your own mortality.    I always try to remind myself that, if there's an earthquake, I want to jump up and down during it to see what happens.  I always forget because I'm too busy running into a doorway or something, but, before I die, I'm going to do it.  I'm going to "ride" the earthquake.  I think it'll be fun until I land and my ankles break.  But that time in the air, with the earth quaking beneath me and me, weightless in mid-air, will be so awesome.  The other day, I decided that I don't know enough about Scientology, so I looked it up on this thing that I have called the internet.  If you haven't heard of this internet thing, you should look into it.  Not only is there a lot of unnecessary information and completely made-up stuff at your fingertips, but at random times, you get shown pictures of boobs.  Nothing could be greater.  But, I digress.  Speaking of digressing, I was reading some post on some message board somewhere today and somebody started a post on a topic, then followed it up with, "But, I digress."  Can you really digress if you never changed the subject in the first place?  You can't.  That person was a liar.  That's like me saying, "You're a dipshit and I hate you.  But, I digress.  The Romans were far better fighters than the Persians because of Hoplite armor."  Once again, my example-making abilities are far superior than the best of example makers.  Anyway.  No wonder people always make fun of Scientologists.  They believe some weird things.  Now, I'm just paraphrasing here, so I could be wrong, but they think that people are comprised of 72 beings each and that these beings were all alive at one time, somewhere in the last 4 quadrillion years (that's the actual number they used, I swear).  Anyway, and what Scientology does for them is that it helps them to discover the 72 people inside of them (this idea is not to be confused with world record gang bang videos --those people aren't very religious).  I think this is just an excuse for people like Tom Cruise and John Travolta to, somehow, get more money by claiming more dependents on their tax returns.  Those clever bastards, passing it off under the guise of a religion created by a guy who wrote  Battlefield Earth .    Interesting thought of the day: You can get herpes (and a lot of other STDs) from a corpse.  Just a word of advice.  Leave your comments or  urlLink email me .  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        School's Out, Welcome to the O.C., bitch!   As the title suggests, I had my last final today and I'm officially one quarter away from graduating.  This means that, this summer, I need to get myself a job since I haven't had one for a few months.  I'm surprised because somewhere along the line a job was supposed to have fallen in my lap for the summer and it hasn't happened yet.  I'm not exactly sure who screwed up here, but it wasn't me.  So, I'm going to keep looking on  urlLink craigslist  for a job for the next few days.  I'm going to need to throw together some fake resume because waiting tables usually doesn't work as a pre-requisite for a job editing somewhere.    Anyway, I'm sure Jesus will find me a job.  Ray Charles, in a ridiculous fit of jealousy, killed himself today.  Apparently he couldn't take it that a former President of the United States was getting all the attention, so he shot himself, nine times, in the face.  Let the "He didn't see it coming" jokes start flying.  Because he did.  He was old.  Duh.  Idiots.    The MTV Movie Awards were on tonight.  Nothing says anticlimactic like an MTV award show.  They do such a good job of making things seem like they're really not going to suck this time, but they always manage to make everything mediocre.  It's like knowing you're going to have sex with a really hot chick, only to get in the act and find out she doesn't have any genitalia.  Trust me, this has happened to me on more than one occasion and it's always a little weird --especially when I insist on stabbing a hole in her pelvis and "getting what I paid for."  I think that's the worst thing I've ever written.  Hooray for new lows.  The best thing about the show was how they had the midget dressed up like a gargoyle in the podium cage.  I don't know whose idea that was, but that person needs to do a lot more thinking for MTV.  I wish it was actually a child and not a midget, though.  And I also wish that that child was then sold into slavery in Thailand in exchange for two bags of plastic Army Men for me and each of my friends because that's what Dr. King would have wanted.  Interesting thought of the day: The buffet at all Donkey Shows in Tijuana has a vegetarian section as required by Mexican law.  Commentarios,  urlLink cartas electronicas . 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This isn't a doozy   I feel that I've overshot my abilities as a writer by proclaiming in one of my last posts that my next post (this one here) would be a doozy.  The entry between this and the one where I said the next would be a doozy doesn't count because I wrote it at two in the morning.  Anyway, when I look up the definition of doozy on  urlLink dictionary.com  I get this:  Something extraordinary or bizarre .  Quite frankly, extraordinary is overshooting it, so we're just going to call this a haberdashery.  Now, once again, this word shouldn't be used here because a haberdashery is a place where men's clothing is sold, but I think it fits much better than doozy.  Now that I've got that out of the way.  I was discussing reality shows with somebody the other day.  I don't remember who it was because everybody in my life that isn't me is pretty inconsequential, but nonetheless, the topic came up.  Me and this unimportant entity were discussing those makeover shows and I figured out why they suck: because they're done with people of regular mental capacity.  Now, if there was a retarded makeover show, let's call it  The Tard , that would be entertainment.  Seeing a grown-up retard dressed to the nines is so uplifting.  That's why I always watch the Special Olympic award ceremony.  Besides, wouldn't it be crazy for somebody to extreme makeover a screwed-up looking mentally-challenged person or person with Down's Syndrome.  I say great because they could let that retard loose in public, like at a mall, and nobody would think anything of it until they started acting like a giant drunk baby.  There'd be some pretty retarded girl (I don't mean that she's fairly retarded, I mean that now, because of the makeover, she's physically attractive) at a club or something, guys would start to come up to her to hit on her when she'd yell out, "I don't put things in my ears anymore because it hurts my brain."  Actually, on second thought, she'd still pass off as a "normal" functioning human being that one could actually find in a club, so scratch that.  Instead, give the newly pretty retarded girl a cattle prod and just let her loose somewhere, like a men's prison.  It would be fun for everybody.  I sure am glad retarded people can't read or I'd get my ass kicked supremely (retards are way stronger than normal people per pound).  Interesting thought of the day: Macaroni and Cheese got its name from a famous Renaissance comedy duo and not from its ingredients as one would assume; that part's just coincidence.  Comment away, tardmongers.  Or, if you want,  urlLink click here  and mash your keyboard until the window goes away. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Celebrate Good Times Come On   As one of my thousands --nay, hundreds--of adoring fans commented, Jennifer Lopez and Mark Anthony got married on Saturday.  Now, people celebrate things differently, but I thought that it was in really bad taste for them to ring in the passing of Ronald Reagan with a wedding.  Isn't that just throwing it in Nancy's face, really?  I'm sure I'm not going to be the first or the last person to give her heat for this.  I mean, I'm sure that this one is going to be forever because she has gone on record as saying that once she gets married, it's for life --but it's still in bad taste.    Speaking of Ronald Reagan, I don't know if you were as floored as I was by it, but I was devastated.  This is the most shocking death since Bob Hope.  Not since George Burns before him has a death come so unexpectedly.  It's a sad state of affairs in society when these people are struck down in the prime of their youth.  I don't quite remember, but I think that George Burns was killed while snowboarding in the Colorado Rockies.  And, sadly, as everybody can remember, Bob Hope was BASE jumping off of the Golden Gate Bridge when his chute got tangled and he plummeted to his death.  Then, finally, on Saturday, The Gipper was killed when, while juggling, one of his seven burning chainsaws was misthrown and crashed directly onto his scalp.  It's just sad.  These people are just doing what they love, experiencing life to its fullest, not sitting on some bed rotting away somewhere in a hospital, and BLAM, out of nowhere.  It's just tragic.  Unexpected and tragic.  Well, I just finished writing an awesome nine-page paper about  Fight Club  so I figured I'd drop a deuce on my weblog here.  Interesting thought of the day: Sarcasm is lost on 75% of all people --including you.  Curds,  urlLink whey . 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Fourth Day Straight   That's right, hookers and hoes.  It's a record that will go unbroken until at least tomorrow.  Tomorrow is the last day of regular classes, two finals next week, one paper and I'm done.  Only one class tomorrow and we're having a junior high-esque "party."  I hope we play Heads-Up Seven-Up.  I'll totally win because I look at their shoes when they walk by.    The neverending saga with my devastating injury continues.  So, yesterday, when I wrote that those pills eat the shit out of your stomach lining, I wasn't kidding.  My stomach was only bubbling and stuff yesterday; I didn't see a problem with that.  But then, this morning at five o'clock, after a solid four hours of sleep, I woke up with excrutiating pain in my stomach.  As I was telling my therapist that doesn't exist, it felt like that guy from Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom reached into my chest and was squeezing the poop out of my stomach.  So, I didn't get to go back to sleep.  It's interesting, though, this five a.m. thing.  Did you know that the sun doesn't just appear in the sky?  It slowly gets brighter in the morning.  It's weird and I don't recommend you experience it because, what happens is, later on, when the sun-beast falls back into the ocean, its power has a hold of you and you get really tired.  On a different note, a fun little anecdote about the finale of my screenwriting class follows.  And here it is.  I've been in my class for the entire school year --since September--so we've been together forever.  The class is different than any class I've taken since high school because you grow closer to these people.  Anyway, there's this chick in my class who's a real Christian girl.  She loves gettin' Jiggy with Jesus.  She has always had this unspoken shame that I could tell she felt for me because of the things I say and do in class (like the one time I cut open a goat and drank its blood in class all the while screaming about the great sun-beast).  So, she brought a few presents for three of the about seventeen or so people in class and she brought me one.  Well, technically she didn't bring them because she didn't show up, which is a whole different thing, but she had somebody else bring them.  She brought me a book of clean jokes cleverly titled, "Book of Clean Jokes."  Much to my surprise, the book is full of clean jokes.  I've vowed, however, to go through and, with each joke, change it so that it relates to either pedophilia, penises, vaginas, some sort of beastiality, necrophilia, dendrophilia, prison rape, or baby murder.  The reason for this is twofold: 1) All of the aforementioned are hilarious and 2) I hate books.  I wrote too much today, but I've got a doozy coming up next entry, so stay tuned.  Interesting thought of the day: If a woman pushes really hard, she can turn her vagina sideways.  Comments below or  urlLink email . 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        He hast posted thrice!   Third day in a row posting and I'm feeling like a champ.  There's been a lot going on, so I actually have stuff to write about.    Yesterday I posted about how I hurt my shoulder.  I decided to bite the bullet and go to the doctor.  I hadn't been to the doctor for years, but, since I'm insured through school, I figured it'd be better to go just in case.  Turns out, I'm an over-reacting drama queen.  Granted, it still hurts, but the doctor just said, in his beautifully broken English, "You hab tendonitis."  So, it'll be like two weeks until it's better.  He gave me some pills called Naproxen that you have to take with food.  They were real adamant about this.  The guy at the prescription-filling counter said that if it wasn't taken with food it could eat a hole in my stomach lining.  I didn't believe him so I ate like ten right there in front of him and my own shit started to seep out of my pores.  Turns out he was right.  These pills really have messed up my stomach, though.  I think that's because I'm afraid of taking them on anything but a full stomach so I eat until I feel like I've got one swallow left in me before I have completely filled myself up --all the way to the esophagus.    It's too embarassing to tell the story of how I hurt my shoulder to people, though, so from now on I'm going to tell people that I hurt it while I was saving a baby from a fire.  I was throwing it (yeah, I said it.  Babies aren't gendered people until they're like five) out the window and screwed up a tendon in my rotator cuff.    Maybe I'll write an entry tomorrow while I'm procrastinating instead of writing a rewrite that's due on Friday.  It will be great fun.  I hope you'll join me.  Interesting thought of the day: Shampoo doesn't taste the way it smells.  Comment instead of  urlLink emailing  me.  I get too many emails that I want to post and comment on and comments just make it easier. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Two days in a row!   Today went well.  Only one real producer actually showed up so it wasn't as nerve-wracking as I thought it would be.  He wasn't there to buy anything, but everybody agreed that my pitch went the best, so that felt good.  Enough of me making myself feel good.  I'm so much of a spaz, that I pulled a Sammy Sosa today.  I was laying on my bed, watching the Pistons-Pacers game and I had to sneeze.  I was on my side, with my left arm bent, propping up my head (so I was looking sexy as hell).  I sneezed and it forced my arm into a weird position, something popped and I'm not sure if it's still out of the socket, but it hurts so bad.  My rotator cuff is all messed up.  I took some Darvacet because it's a muscle relaxant, but I don't even feel any different.  The old Indian Chief sitting in a bed of fire in my room making copies of the Sunday comics with Silly Putty seems a little strange, but I figured that my room just got rented out.  It still hurts, though.  I'm such a little girl.  I can't believe I'm so inactive that I got hurt sneezing.    Interesting thought of the day: There aren't actually giant black lines seperating each state like it shows on maps; those are just there for reference.  Comment away, my little whore-gnomes.   urlLink Email  also. 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       That's a little wordy, but I'm sure that's close to the translation of what Michael Buffer says before  urlLink these fights  where orangutangs are forced to kickbox one another. That's right, I said kickbox. Now, the history of animal fighting is a long and hilarious road, but normally these are just referred to as "fights" not kickboxing. Cock fights. Dog fights. And the less popular and much slower paced Three-toed sloth fights. But calling these orangutang fights "kickboxing" implies that these monkeys (I know they're not monkeys, because orangutangs and monkeys are different species, but you know what? I don't care because it's all the same from behind if you know what I'm saying.) actually have some semblance of training. I imagine that the monkey dojo where they learn this is a lot like the Cobra Kai dojo in the karate kid.  Sensei: Pain does not exist in this dojo, does it?  Orangutangs in unison: AAAAAAAAAHHHHHH EEEEEEEE!  Sensei: Fear does not exist in this dojo, does it?   The orangutangs fondle one another's monkey cocks.    Then the blonde guy from Just One of the Guys pouts and feathers his hair a lot.   And....scene.  The promoters of the show say that the fights are coreographed and none of the monkeys get hurt, but I wouldn't step into the ring against an orangutang with boxing gloves on. That thing doesn't know the "not-in-the-face-or-in-the-balls" rule. I have no qualms about kicking a monkey in the balls, but I don't think he'd quite go down like a man would. I think kicking a monkey in the balls would somehow draw a lot more anger from that monkey than sending them down in a heap like what happens to a man or a small child who won't stop pointing at you and laughing at your head that's "as big as me, mommy." It's genetics, fucker.  So, stop the monkeys from fighting one another when they could be doing something much more productive like picking shit from each other's ass hair and shoving their erections through the chain-link fence at the zoo.  In other news, I got a call from some woman today. That's all. A woman called me. I actually came in my pants as soon as I heard that a woman was on the other end of the line. And it was free this time!  The good thing about having an uncommon or slightly difficult to pronounce last name is that you know right away when the person who's calling you is somebody who wants some money from you. So, she calls and mispronounces my last name, so I know she's going to want something, but I didn't know what fun would come from it. She proceeds to tell me that she works with a company called ARC. Whenever I hear an abbreviation like this, I always like to think of what it could stand for. Before she has a chance to tell me what it stands for, she explains that she's from a charity that's collecting for helping mentally handicapped children. Now, in the past few months, I've written a lot about retarded people (only because I don't know of many/any retarded animals or inanimate objects like a retarded sandwich or belt) so I'm convinced now that if I ever have children that they will be the most retarded children ever born. This, in a way, would make me happy because I always strive to be the best in everything I do and to have the MOST retarded children alive would make me feel like a winner. Anyway, after explaining that the organization has been around for 51 years, I realize that ARC has to stand for something like "Aiding Retarded Children" or "Aid for Retarded Children" or "Apples Rain Clock." The last one wouldn't make much sense so I'm guessing it's one of the first two.  The idea that this organization would have the word "Retarded" in their title blows my mind. Sure, maybe it's in keeping with the tradition of the organization, but it seems strange that they wouldn't rename themselves since everybody is so worried about being politically correct these days. It's kind of like if I decided to own myself a slave or two and when people asked me about it I just told them that I was "keeping it real" or "trying to bring back traditional American values." Trust me, I've tried this and it does not work. There are some things that people need to change and this organization's name is one of those things. Also, the organization (holy crap I'm using the word organization a lot) that is the most guilty of having a bad abbreviation is the NAACP. This is a group that's known for fighting for the rights of black folks throughout the country or world (I don't know where they work; I just know that their college basketball tournament is awesome) and they refer to themselves as the National Association for the Advancement of  Colored People . Really, Jesse Jackson? I guarantee you if I walked up to Jesse Jackson and said, "You colored people sure do have weird hair and are afraid of the water," he'd murder me into a million pieces. Only rednecks and aliens call black people colored people. I'm assuming aliens would call them colored people, I have no actual experience, but from what I've heard of aliens, they're very literal.  I saw  The Village  tonight, but I've been writing this thing for 45 minutes now and I don't want to get into it.  I'll write about that and  The Bourne Supremacy  tomorrow.  Interesting thought of the day: The reason chlamydia is called "the clap" is because an early strain of the virus caused the genitals to emit a noise very similar to a full orchestra performing Tchaikovsky's  1812 Overture .  This would often induce applause from passers-by.  Comment away.  I want to hear from you bastards who haven't posted yet, too.  I know you're out there.  This site's growing like the cist on the tip of my urethra that's threatening to push my urine flow back inside myself; so let's hear from you guys.  Or, if you've decided you've read enough and you'd like to hire me to do something for you (hopefully it's writing, but full release massage is negotiable) you can  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My copy of  The   Da Vinci Code  has been passed around from person to person over the last year or so--since I first bought it.  It has been read by a lot of people, which is weird because there's something so intimate about letting somebody borrow a book that's not there with like, a DVD, or a rubber vagina.  It has been from hill to dale and back again, but, alas, I've learned of its untimely demise.  While it has probably traveled over hundreds of miles and been in dozens of people's hands, it left this world in that very place it loved the most: the bathroom.    The strangest thing about letting somebody borrow a book is that you know that they're going to take that to the bathroom with them.  There's nothing else that's like this; especially because that book is going to be touched so soon after the person wipes their ass, masturbates, or washes the blood of a teenage runaway from their hands.  If I wanted to borrow something from somebody, like an umbrella, and I said, "Thanks, I'm going to go shit now and wipe my hands all over it," I'd never be allowed to borrow something from that person again.  But with books, this is understood and never discussed.  So, in a way, I'm glad that it got ruined.    My friend, who shall only be referred to as "Ryan," borrowed this book from me.  Now, Ryan's not really known for his library of books, so I knew it would be a while to get the book back.  I had gone to his house on a couple of occasions and seen the book sitting dangerously close to the toilet with the spine on the floor and the pages kind of fanning toward the ceiling.  This put the edges of the pages rife for gathering splashback from the urine that would be slamming against the porcelain.  I've heard Ryan pee before and he pees like he's trying to put a hole in the toilet or win that game at the fair where you shoot the watergun into the clown's mouth, so I knew that the book was in the process of getting ruined.      Basically, it was ruined when he tried to take it into the shower with him.  I guess their relationship had moved from just the occasional golden shower to the actual shower.  He says it was on the floor of his bathroom near the shower and the water spilled over on it, but I know the truth.  He was liking the book so much, that he decided to take it to the next level and have sex with it in the shower.  I did the exact same thing with my favorite book; I've ruined nine bibles this way.      I respond to reader comments:  Our good friend  Jimbo the Angry Clown  writes:   I just created a link and posted it on WinMx. I labeled it "Midget Porn" though. I figure this will provide you with much more interesting reader responses for you to comment on. I'm looking forward to the influx of angry Midget Porn connoisseurs that this will bring to the site.  That's the corner of the Internet market that I've been trying to reach out to, but wasn't quite sure how.  And you, much like tiny midget penises in the films they're wanting to watch, have filled that small hole.    Thanks, Jimbo, Flesh, and Mellody.  Flesh, it looks like your way worked the best as the woman who you donkey punched while screaming my website showed up and stayed long enough to comment.  I guess there's not much else to do but surf the Internet while you're waiting for your asshole to close up enough so that when you stand up shit doesn't just fall right out.    Comment below more stories about how you're getting the word of my site out (breaking the law is O.K.--vandalism a plus) or about whatever else you want.  Or, as always, you can  urlLink email me .        
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For the second day in a row, I'm going to write about things that the Japanese are doing because they're exciting, very far away, and talk in pictures.     urlLink This article  details how the Japanese have widened the base of names that children in Japan can be called. Now, this is why I love how progressive America is because for years I've called small children "prostitutes" and "buttocks" not knowing that somewhere in the world there was a place where people weren't allowed to call children such things. How else would I order my six-year-old callboys? God bless the USA.    As a result, the justice ministry proposed an additional 578 characters for names, but included dozens that most parents might view as poor taste, such as "Piles" and "Vagina". I can understand the disapproval of the name Vagina. Not only does it denote the woman's area of baby dumpage, but the Japanese symbol for Vagina is something like this: {|}. But Piles? I guess that could mean like Piles of Shit, but it's plural. Who would name their kid a plural noun? "Bandaids, stop pinching your sister, Lamps."   But this week, the ministry said public pressure had forced it to withdraw nine of the most controversial characters, including "Rape", "Excrement" and "Cancer". Who would name their kid Cancer anyway? There are some names that will automatically decide that person's fate for the rest of their life--this is one them. Like Jeeves, Bambi, or Jesus, Cancer would come with a certain expectation for that person's life to come. In fact, I think if I had a kid named Cancer, I'd be kind of happy if he died in, like, a gang fight, from AIDS, or from a heart attack just to prove people wrong. In the last sentence, when I juxtaposed "gang fight" and "from AIDS" I don't mean that he'd die in the middle of a gang fight as a result of his AIDS, I meant those as two separate situations. That would be a weird gang fight. Gunshots ringing. Screams. And one lone man, my son, Cancer, yells out, "Ouch! My T-Cells are too low" and collapses to the floor--dead.    I've written a small diddy sung to the tune of "My Favorite Things" from  The Sound of Music , about Japan's recent decision to ban these names.    Cancer and Ra-ape  Excrement too  One means forcing sex  One's fatal, one's poo.      Nobody invites my son  Piles to play games.  I wonder why Vagina  hates her name(s).   Okay, so I'm not good at that, but I started to sing it out of nowhere so I had to write it to get it out of my head.      I respond to reader comments:    Anonymous writes:   Rather than threaten to kill puppies if no comments are posted, have you considered killing horses instead?      That way you either get comments or the raw materials for icecream! Its a win-win situation. Well, Alcoholics, if I can call you by your first name, while this is a good idea if you're made out of money (or horses), puppies are so much cheaper in comparison to horses that I've been using them instead.  Besides, as a tribute to the Japanese, I'm going to make my own puppy ice-cream called "Cold Nose Surprise."  It'll be released around Christmas through Ben & Jerry's.    That's all for today, kids.  I received a lot of comments last entry, so thanks.  But now, it's like  Fight Club  up in this bitch and you all need to bring some friends to this website.  You can't tell them why, but you do get to punch them right in their stupid face after you tell them to come here.  I do this because they'll remember the website if they get punched in the face right when you tell them about it.    "The Toon dot Blogspot dot Com!"  Wham!  Right in their smelly head.    They'll relay the story to their friends about how their best friend just yelled, "The Toon dot Blogspot dot Com," punched them in the face, and ran out of the room screaming about how there are no retarded ghosts.    So comment me your stories about how you told/will tell people about this site (Mo, thanks for the link on your site--I checked it out.  A lot better layout than I've got here).  Or  urlLink email me .  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since, once again, life is boring and nothing is going on, I'm going to pull from the headlines around the world and comment on them.     urlLink In Japan , an exciting thing has happened--a revolution in confectionary delights! Japan, known for harnessing the power of the Playstation, tentacle porn, and karaoke, has developed a delicious new flavor of ice-cream that is sure to sweep the nation.     Japanese ice-cream lovers have swapped traditional flavours such as raspberry ripple for something a little more exotic - horse-flesh.    This is good news for all of the dinosaurs in the world. I know that dinosaurs and horses never coexisted, but I assume if dinosaurs and horses did ever live together, there would have been a lot of horses being eaten by them. Unless dinosaurs were smarter than I'm giving them credit for and they would ride the horses.   The new flavours are being promoted by the Japan Ice-Cream Association which has set up a summer trade fair.    There's a Japan Ice-Cream Association. There are people that exist in Japan whose job it is to decide the fate of the country's ice-cream supply. I guarantee you that they make like a million Japanese moneys a year. I work harder than they do and I don't make nearly as much Japanese moneys.     Here's the part of the article where I make wonderful puns about the ice-cream flavor.       This ice-cream sure would be good if you're feeling a little hoarse!  (read it like "horse" and it is hilarious)     And that's all I have.    Judging by the lack of comments to my article about retarded ghosts, I can only come to a couple of different conclusions.        The only people that read my blog are retarded and, thus, offended by what I wrote.     Everybody who normally reads my blog went on a trip to Peru to buy a kidney on the black market and they'd rather not talk about it right now. (This one is most likely)     You've all stopped reading because I've fallen in love with making lists on this thing.    I'm really tired and I don't think this article had as much punch as it normally does. I'd say the amount of punch in this article is roughly equivalent to the amount of punch a man would probably give to his wife's stomach upon finding out she's pregnant. You know--just enough to get the job done, but not enough to kill you.    Interesting thought of the day:  The expression, "Everytime a bell rings an angel gets its wings" from the film  It's a Wonderful Life  was originally written as "Everytime a bell rings an angel gets its wings or a woman decides to try anal for the first time." This was scrapped at the last minute when the director, Frank Capra, decided to ditch the sexually-explicit ending in favor of one that would get a better rating. Jimmy Stewart later added this line in to the film  Harvey .    No comments last time so a puppy has died a horrible death. It actually wasn't that horrible, I let him think he was going outside, but instead I threw him in the oven. So, please, comment below about whatever and I'll try to incorporate it into a future entry. Or you can always  urlLink email me .  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       While I was doing my daily three-hour meditation today, my mind wandered into the idea of whether or not ghosts actually exist. After an intense three hours, I've decided, and will convince you if you do believe in ghosts, that they do not exist.    There are tons of stories about ghosts. "Ghosts raped me in my sleep." "Ghosts moved around my picture frames and told me to pour gallons of milk all over old people." "Ghosts murdered my wife and her friend out front of my house and threw blood all over my white Ford Bronco." Out of all the stories you've heard of ghosts, you've never heard about retarded ghosts. You never hear about somebody who had an encounter with a ghost that went like this:     " Boooooo!  HAHAHAHAHAHA!  My pants make chocolate! "  The ghost scurries away bumping into walls and giggling.     There are no retarded ghosts! This, in effect, proves that ghosts do not exist. I do, however, have a couple of ways that this could be proved false.        If I learn that retarded people are immortal.     If I see a retarded person die and he leaves no body, but simply fades away like a Jedi.     If somebody can convince me that retarded people are incapable of being ghosts because they are, in fact, not people, but pixies.    These are the only things that would convince me otherwise. Until then, I will continue to believe that either the mentally handicapped are a soulless people, or ghosts don't exist. I do think that it would be great if all retards were immortal because I can just imagine a  Highlander -esque kind of battle involving lots of drooling and giant-headedness.    " There can be only one!  I bought a pirate!  HAHAHAHAHAHA! "    Interesting thought of the day:  The first raffle was held in 33 A.D. The first prize given out was a $10 Gift Certificate to the Olive Garden. The grand prize? A box of Jesus.    Comment below and convince me that either there are retarded ghosts, or other reasons that it would be acceptable to believe that retarded people can't be ghosts. Or you can  urlLink email me .  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       All too often, you hear people on TV or, if you know and interact with people in your normal, daily life, they say things about the war in Iraq and how they are either for or against it. Well, whether Republican or Democrat or some other form of political affiliation (Wigs anyone?), they always have one thing in common. The Republican/Conservative will say something like, "It is our duty to be in Iraq. I support the war and I support our troops." The Democrat/Liberal says something like, "I am completely against the war, but I support our troops." I, for one, can't stand the bipartisanship concerning this aspect of the war and intend to do something about it. That is why I have decided that I do not support the troops. Oh, I said it. I fully support the war, but the troops don't have my intangible, unmeaning support. I would prefer for the war to be fought by robots like in that kick-ass Will Smith movie ( The Legend of Baggar Vance ). They're all just over there for a vacation if you really think about it. You know, it's all warm and tropical-like. Then, when they come back, people applaud them and thank them for what they've done? I want somebody to applaud me and then send me to college for free after going on vacation for a few years. "Hey, guys, I'm going to go to Florida when I turn eighteen. I'll be over there drinking, partying, and having lots of sex with many vaginas (or, for the females in the armed forces--many vaginas), and when I come back I'll be twenty-one, in the best shape of my life, tan as all hell, and you'll constantly praise me for how great I was. Doesn't anybody else see something wrong with this? I mean, all too often the troops are seen as "heroes" or as having "done something for their country" when all they've really done is get to blow a bunch of stuff up.     I'm going to make up some bumper stickers that say, "I support the war--but fuck the troops." So, if you want to buy some, check back here; I'll have that set up soon.    Being in the Armed Forces is easy, but being a college student who actually has to pay for his own schooling so I can sit there in an air-conditioned building thousands of miles away from ever being shot at, now that's difficult. I'd like to see them try.    Oh yeah! They also get all sorts of awesome free entertainment. Conan O'Brien went over there and entertained the troops. I heard somebody reanimated Bob Hope's body and had him put on a show for them (dead puppets? fucking awesome!). Who puts on a show for me? I mean, sometimes, when I masturbate I pretend that my hand is a tornado and my wiener is Helen Hunt so it's like the mini stage version of  Twister , but that's as far as it gets really. One of my balls is Bill Paxton, one of my balls is Cary Elwes, and one of my balls is the cow. That's right. Three balls. Jealous?    I respond to reader comments:   This is a new section of the blog that will hopefully be used more often because it makes writing this thing a whole lot easier.      This one comes from Jimbo the Angry Clown:      Hi Toon!  I saw this pictuire and knew that you would enjoy it much more than anyone else I know.         http://www.nata2.info/humor/pictures/godkills.jpg      Now, first of all, we see that he calls the item he linked to a "pictuire." Some of you may think that this is a misspelling, but I happen to know Jim in real life and know that he is, in fact, severely retarded. It's pretty messed up of you to point out his misspellings. It's okay, Jim, you still get two Fruit Roll-Ups for lunch.    Secondly, as you can tell, the picture has been filed at that website under the humor folder so it's meant as a joke. However, I happen to know that it is 100% true that every time a person masturbates God kills a kitten. I'll even quote the bible:     He who doth covet thyself will have the blood of a feline on his hands. And, remember, this is me, God saying this, so I don't mean that in some sick way as a sexual lubricant. I mean that I will fucking kill a kitten. I won't just snap my fingers and kill it, either, even though I could. No. I will put on my kitten-smashing boots and jump into a laundry basket filled with kittens. Also, I weigh a good 200 tons, so that's some fucking dead kitten. So don't touch yourself; I fucking mean it.     --Shaquille 1:87    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just a couple of minutes ago, I was drinking a big old glass of hearty American milk. You know it's American milk and not German because it knows it's white and good, but it doesn't go bragging about it or killing Jewish people. Anyway, as I was drinking it out of my blue tupperware cup, I got near the bottom and found that there was something in the bottom of the cup. It was some mucuous-like substance that was nestled in the bottom corner of that cup. I can't tell whether it was already white before I began drinking from the glass or if it turned white by growing up in Montana.    Many things go through one's mind when this happens.    First, I thought to myself, Did I check the bottom of the glass? I always check the bottom of the glass. Then, convincing myself that what I just imbibed was not completey disgusting, I think to myself, Well, the milk didn't  taste  any different so it can't be that bad. Next I start to wonder if the thing that was stuck to the bottom of the cup actually came from the milk itself or, somehow it came from me. Finally, realizing it's useless and that there's nothing I can do about it, I decide to cut open my chest and pinch off my esophagus before the milk can make its way into my stomach. See, because there are times when one has to realize that there's ALWAYS something that they can do about it.     I write this sitting in my hospital bed on suicide watch because the paramedics and police don't quite seem to understand what I'm talking about. THERE WAS SOMETHING GROSS INSIDE MY GLASS OF MILK! How hard is that to understand?    Interesting thought of the day:  The xylophone is the musical instrument that is attributed to garnering the least amount of vagina. The most? Surprisingly (or not for those of you who play it), the sitar.    Comment below (you can comment anonymously if you like) and Jesus will love you, or you can  urlLink email me  and Jesus will kind of think that you're cool for a few minutes.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This gets political, so, some of you (Ryan) may not want to read this one.     Well, looks like Bush wants to move on from the overwhelming success he's had thus far in Iraq and throw more dead teenagers at Iran. He'll really show them, just like he did to Iraq. I mean,  urlLink the proof's in the pudding , Iran may have, accidentally, at one point, let some terrorists pass through their country before September 11.    What a bunch of dirty motherfuckers. You're going to feel the heat of an angry president with no sort of reasoning or access to the more complex, "human," thought processes. Having George W. Bush as president is like leaving a monkey in a room with a box of ninja stars and forty live chickens and expecting to open that door in a week and find everything in the room the way you left it. Then, when somebody asks the monkey why he did what he did, he poops in his hand and throws it at them.    I heard the real reason Bush is going to send the troops into Iran is so he can complete the "totally kick-ass" new rollercoaster that he's going to have built going from Afghanistan all the way to Iraq and, since Iran's in the middle, that's just as collateral damage. That W, he sure does love his coasters.    I just saw a commercial for  Spider-Man 2 , which I saw a while ago, but Doctor Octopus's robotic arms just reminded me of something. They look like metal versions of those paper things that girls would make in elementary school. You know, those things that would have numbers on the four panels, they'd tell you to pick a number, they'd swish it around, then pick a color, they swish it more according to the letters in the color you pick, then, finally, pick a panel and then they'd lift the tab to reveal to you something insanely interesting like, "You have cooties" or, as my mom called it, "Feline AIDS." The first documented case in humans, thank you very much. I liked  Spider-Man 2 , but it would have been cooler if that's what Doctor Octopus was chasing everybody around for--just to play his game with him. "Where's Spider-Man? He picked a number, but then he left, he has to PICK A COLOR!"    Interesting thought of the day:  Hammers were originally named such because they were made from pigs.    The naked massage sweepstakes is over with the winners being nobody (or everybody if you've seen me naked). The new contest will begin with this post. Those who comment may be entered in a contest to receive an original haiku on the topic of their choice as long as I receive 3 or more original comments per entry. This doesn't mean that the entries themselves have to be original, as I doubt my readers are capable of much more than repeating some mid-80's catch phrase like, "Cousin Larry, let's do the dance of joy!" What I do want are comments from 3 different people. Or, if you don't like clicking anything online that says submit because "you're not a pussy," you can  urlLink email me .  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I don't know if you've seen this commercial, but you have to look out for it because it's by far the greatest commercial that's on the air right now. It's a lot like the old days of the "I've fallen and I can't get up" lady, but better. The commercial I'm talking about is for a wheelchair/chair for really lazy people called the "Hoveround." It's basically like those things you see that they have at the grocery store, I can't remember what they're called, that are for old people to sit in and roll around in while they shop and smell weird. They advertise this thing as like the wheelchair for people who want to go where anybody can walk. It's good in theory, but they take it too far. The commercial ends with the announcer saying something like, "You can take it to the park (picture of somebody in the chair in the park), the grocery store (shot in grocery store), or even   the Grand Canyon  ." Then there's a shot of two old women whose wheelchair's have obviously been turned off, looking around while they're literally about two feet from the edge of the cliff. Apparently the Grand Canyon is a huge tourist spot for people who can't walk anymore and this company sacrificed the lives of two old women (who, let's face it, probably died soon after the commercial was filmed) in order to perhaps get the elderly extreme sports fanatics who can't walk. That's a big sacrifice for such a niche market.      I saw   I, Robot   today.    Possible Spoilers follow   (but, honestly, I'm saving you the money). I didn't want to see this movie because it has Will Smith saying great lines like "You   so   need to die." Yes, he actually says that toward the end of the movie. Will Smith, in the year 2035, becomes Buffy the Vampire Slayer while killing a robot. I think that sentence I just wrote is the first and last time that combination of words will ever be used in the English language. There was also a shot at the end of the movie where, after the world has been saved from the evil robots (the ones whose chest was glowing red; for those who don't know, in Symbolism 101, red means bad), for no reason whatsoever, the goddamn Blue Angels fly overhead and break off into different directions. Then the movie ends. That's how it ends, I swear. The Blue Angels, who played no part in anything in the film at all, make a cameo appearance 31 years in the future to cap off a delightfully ridiculous film. They could have had a ghost come out and shit on a painting of Munch's "The Scream" and it would have been just as relevant to the movie. The only redeeming part of the film is   Shia LaBeouf  .  Hopefully he goes on to movies that are actually good and not god awful like   Charlie's Angels 2: Full Throttle  ,   I, Robot  , and   The Battle of Shaker Heights  .  Anyway, one more downfall of the movie is that the director,   Alex Proyas  , who actually did a good job with   Dark City   and   The Crow  , apparently thinks the audience is full of complete idiots (he may be on to something here, though. Anybody who willingly goes to see a Will Smith movie expecting it to be Shakespeare has to have something wrong with him). The plot points and foreshadowing are hit harder than my future wife will be after I've got a six pack in me. He goes so far as to replay the key phrases over and over again. It's only an hour and forty minutes; I'm sure people will remember something that happened twenty minutes earlier in the film if it's only mentioned once. In closing, I give   I, Robot   six. I'm not sure what unit of measurement I'm using or out of how many units that six is, but, I think it's clear how I feel about the film, you can sculpt your own ratings system around that number. In fact, go ahead and comment it below. Or, if you disagree and you think   I, Robot   wasn't hideous, let me know.      Interesting thought of the day:    That famous woodchuck whose chucking ability has been pondered for centuries actually couldn't chuck wood at all. He had soft teeth and stuck to the much less dramatic and iambic pentameter breaking chucking of mashed potatoes.      Comment below like you've been so good at lately (not good enough for naked backrubs, though) or   email me  .  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Upgrades to this shit!      I came here to type to my increasingly large audience about something inconsequential and then I realized that they gave me more tools to play with on this thing.   So, I'm happy as a pedophile who gets a job as a Middle School P.E. teacher.      I think I eat hot dogs too much.  I mean, it's the only thing that I use ketchup on in my house and I've gone through a bottle of ketchup in about two months; this is by myself.  It's kind of disgusting to think about the fact that I've consumed enough ketchup in two months to fill two soda cans.  I actually walked out into the kitchen just now to check the amount of ounces on that so I could get it right.  You all wouldn't know if I'm lying about it, but I'd know and I can't have that.  It's even more disgusting, though, to think about how those two soda cans of ketchup pale in comparison to the amount of processed animal leftovers that I've taken in.  I love using odd units of measurement for comparison, so I'm going to venture a guess that I've eaten, in the past two months, two average, healthy, newborn babies worth of hot dog meat.  That's about fifteen pounds of beef or pork or llama (that's the english word for "almost like a camel", not the spanish translation for "s/he calls").  This, I feel, is a lowball estimate.  If I had never pooped in the past two months, that's another fifteen pounds I could have gained.  Also, I could have formed two meat-carved babies that I could have left in baby carriages in Central Park on a hot day in summer.  Man, I think I'm done eating hot dogs* and I'm moving on to meat art.    So,  urlLink Kobe Bryant  is going to stay with the Lakers.  This is good news to all the girls who work at hotels of cities in the Western Conference who would love to get raped.  This gives you twice as many opportunites as those who work in Eastern Conference cities.  So, you can write to Jerry Buss, the owner of the Lakers, and thank him for resigning (signing again, not quitting) Kobe and giving you the opportunity to have giant black wiener forcefully placed inside of your body and thrashed around like a crocodile with a meat-formed baby in its mouth.  So that was a stretch, but that's no stretch compared to how stretched out your lady parts will be once Kobe's done taking your rapeginity.  That's what he's coined it now so it doesn't sound as awful as regular ole rape.    Grammar and Punctuation Usage Technique of the day:  I realized I use contractions a lot, but, quite frankly, I don't think I use them enough.  Therefore, I will use them at innoportune times as right now I'm.  There's nothing like seeing 'I'm' at the end of a sentence.   You're probably thinking, This guy sure is bright he's.    I received comments two entries in a row, and, if I receive three or more from three different people, I will send out coupons for free naked backrubs to each of those who comment.  Or, you can  urlLink email me .  * as soon as the package I have is gone       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't drink.  I've never had a drink of alcohol in my life, but if I did, I sure know what I would use to drink my beer.  I wouldn't drink out of those sissy glasses.  No!  I would drink from a chalice.  If you don't know what a chalice is, it's one of these.      Can you imagine walking around a bar, with your shirt off, hairy chest exposed, wearing nothing but a loincloth and a smile drinking beer from that thing?  There is no chick in the bar that wouldn't be wanting to get to know you "biblically."  She'd be all rubbing on your chest as you imbibe from your golden chalice as she says, "What's bigger?  That big thing you're holding, or that chalice?"  See?  She'd use the ole switcheroo on you.  That means that you're definitely getting some.  Why will you be getting this massive amount of woman vagina (as opposed to man vagina --mangina)?  Because of your chalice.    I wrote that last paragraph in the second person because it makes you feel more like you're a part of what's going on in this weblog.  I hope to, one day, use this weblog as not only a source for entertainment, but as a self-help source as well.  "You won't let the guy at the dry cleaners yell at you anymore."  "You can stop eating cigarette butts you find on the street."  I'm like the internet Dr. Phil, but without all of the skin on my head that's not covered in hair.  I'd probably make my chalice all personalized like people do with their pool cues, fishing rods, or semen paintings of John Travolta.  I'd get my name engraved and probably encrust jewels and various etchings on the side of it.  It'd be like a class ring, but way more boss and capable of drawing in a hundred times more of the delicious beef curtain soup.  On a different note, I think that the guy who created Family Circus has gotten a little weird lately.      Comment below or I will hold up my promise to start eating some more puppies.  You all did a good job with the last one, but soon my thirst will arise again.  Or, if you like, and you want to get my information so you can hire me to write for you, you can  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, since money isn't free, it looks like I'll probably have to go back to Red Lobster (Whoopi Goldberg's Butthole) and try to see if the new GM will hire me.  When I quit before, I had to quit because I couldn't work the schedule they wanted because I had school.  Everything was left fine, but since I left, only three months ago, every manager that ever knew me is gone.  So, now I've got to go to this new GM, who I've heard isn't exactly the poster child for nice ladies, but, coincidentally, is the actual poster child for the new disease sweeping the nation, Hepatitis Orange.  I'm not sure what Hepatitis Orange is, but apparently it makes the person who has it a not nice lady.  Anyway, so I guess on Wednesday or Thursday I've got to go down there and make this lady understand that I'm the glue to her shitty, shitty working environment.  Unless I magically get a job writing between now and then.  It'll be fantastic when I finally start hearing back from those agencies who I want to send my screenplay to because then I'll feel so Hollywood.  That's when I'm going to start calling people things like, "Babe," and saying things like, "Ciao" and "How much does it cost to have sex with you and you pretend like you're a dragon."  Hollywood's going to be awesome.  Alas, I sit with my nine thumbs up my ass, opening my wallet over and over again hoping money will appear there.  I'm guilty of doing the same thing with my refrigerator when I'm hungry; it never works there, but I figure maybe money's different.  If you want to send me money, feel free.  It would be best, though, if you sent me various other items as I, unlike most of the world, deal in barter and trade.  The other day I got two butter churners, nine cattle, and my third wife for helping with a barn raising.  I can't wait until I have money again because then I can buy that monocle I've always wanted.  Interesting thought of the day: Ten out of Ten dentists are dentists.  I swear to God, if you all don't start commenting on this page (and it has to be people I don't know, I don't want my pity friend comments --I talk to you all the time), I'm going to start hunting each of you down and making you eat a bag of mystery poop.  I call it mystery poop because you know it's poop, you just don't know where it's from.  Or, if you want to give me money or items with which I can procure other items or abilities of another person, you can  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Disneyland and Prison Rape   Since I've been doing nothing but sitting in my room letting my facial hair grow until it starts to itch my chest while I wait to hear back from the 23 agencies to whom I sent my letters of inquiry, I'm going to write about random stuff.  'To whom' always feels too formal, but I can't end the sentence in a preposition, so I have to do that.  If you don't like it, you'll be to whom I send my bag of punches in the face.  A post on a message board I read was asking about bad birthdays that people have had, so I wanted to relate a bad one of my own.  When I was turning eleven years old, as was tradition, I went to Disneyland with my family.  It was an extra special birthday because my knee was hurting a lot leading up to that day because I'm a huge wuss and I hurt it playing basketball, yet, as soon as I stepped foot in the park, the pain in my knee magically went away.  This was going to be a great day, I told myself.  Skipping merrily through Main Street, we headed immediately toward Fantasyland because I was eleven years old and I think the first ride I wanted to go on was something like Peter Pan or Pinocchio.  On the way there, we passed by the Sword in the Stone.  I remember, in years past, how cool I thought the whole ceremony was and how I wished that one day I could be a part of it.  As luck would have it, the ceremony was just about to begin, so, my younger brother, mom, dad, and I gathered around in the front row as the ritual began.  They called up the first person, a man, probably thirty or so, pretty strong looking.  He tugged and tugged and could not remove that sword.  They called another man up, who looked a lot like the first guy, who tried as hard as he could, but, once again, no luck.  Then, it happened.  The man in the wizard getup pointed in my direction.  Butterflies filled my stomach and a little pee shot out.  He walked toward me with his hand out to pull me up to the sword.  This was it, I thought.  I'm going to pull the sword out of the stone on my birthday.  I love my family.  Can life get any greater at this moment?  I don't think so.  As I'm about to put my hand out to grab the wizard's hand so I can be escorted to be King for a Day at Disneyland, I realize that he's pointing at my younger brother.  So, he goes up to the sword, pulls it from its place deep within the heart of the Fiberglas rock, and holds it into the sky.  Trumpets and music played and the crowd erupted in applause.  The wizard draped a kingly cloak and crown upon his head and he had his picture taken to be picked up at Main Street on the way out that day.  All of a sudden, my knee started to hurt.  Fuck that birthday. Fuck it in its filthy Happiest-Place-on-Earth face.  On a different note, I got a collect call from a prison yesterday.  Too bad I couldn't understand what name he gave when he called.  I think I was still hung up on the preface of "You have received a collect call from some correctional facility."  If you've never had a collect call from a prison, it's really an experience you should go through.  There are a lot of options that you can do like block the prison from ever calling you again.  I was tempted to do that, because it was obviously a wrong number, but then I figured if he can misdial once, he can misdial again and I don't want to deny either of us.  I will learn his name.  I almost felt bad just hanging up the phone, but I didn't have the option to learn more about the prison inmate whose phone bill I might be footing.  If there was an option like "To learn more about what crimes this person has been convicted of, press 4 now."  I would have been all over that like the lonely, depressed bridesmaid on the wedding cake.  Alas, I could not further the relationship between myself and my unknown probable-murderer because there was no option 4.    If you're a reader of mine, "Ray Ray," call me again.  I promise I'll accept the charges.  Astoundingly Genius Moment of the Day: When I waited tables, a deaf couple came to the hostess stand to be sat.  The hostess, noticing the couple is deaf, promptly grabbed two braille menus and showed the couple to their seat.  You can comment (anonymously if you want, just look for the option to log in anonymously) below or  urlLink email me . 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw a commercial on TV for everybody's favorite "fancy" restaurant--the only "fancy" restaurant with a spittoon and a free Syphillis test at every table--Sizzler. The commercial was a lot like the commercials that Sizzler always have had, except this time, when they named the restaurant, they whispered it. It was so wistful and enigmatic that it was actually creepy. There were two women standing in the middle of a mall or knitting store or tampon factory or something like that trying to decide where they were going to eat. Then, one of the women hears the word "Sizzler" as if it was delivered on the wind by a dozen pixies on ecstacy. Now, if I'm standing somewhere with somebody, trying to decide where to eat, and I see them start talking and listening to nothing and they suddently respond back eagerly, "Sizzler! We MUST go to Sizzler." I'm not fucking going to Sizzler with them. I'm probably not going to lunch with them or ever talking to them again. And, if I have to go to lunch with them because they're my boss or my mother, I'm going to Soup Plantation or the International House of Water and Baby Food because they probably don't have knives. I don't know what else the voices would tell her, but it probably would involve knives and wouldn't involve giving me a sponge bath. In summary of this long paragraph, don't go out to eat with schizophrenics--even if it's Kevin Costner telling you he has to build a baseball diamond in his corn field.  Also, I went to get a haircut today. There's always something weird about haircuts because there's this forced closeness and intimacy with the woman (I know, men cut hair, too, just not my hair) who's cutting your hair. But, there are situations (for a straight guy or gay woman) that get really awkward. When the woman is standing ridiculously close to you and her boobs are right in your face, you don't know where to look. She has to know that her boobs are close enough for me to actually hear the hair on her nipples scraping against her bra, yet she acts like everything is cool. Worse than this, though, is that I always associate getting my hair cut with women with what I call FVS--Fat Vagina Syndrome. This is where the woman, who seems a little chubby uptop, cinches her waist off so as to create the illusion that she is not as fat as one may think, but instead she is big-busted. But, this illusion is proved to be just that when one's eye wanders below the waistline and sees that their vagina sticks out just as far as their boobs do. This same thing happens to big men as well and it's even worse on them because if they're wearing tight enough pants, it actually looks like they have no genitalia at all. They're like a fat Ken doll without the sweet smell of six-year-old hands all over them.  Interesting thought of the day: The next time somebody says to you, "What would Jesus do?" hit them in the eyes with a skateboard and tell them "He'd turn the other cheek, motherfucker!"  Then run away laughing, cuddling your cool-ass Nash skateboard.  Booyaah! That's all for today. Had somebody new comment last entry, let's see if we can get somebody else new this time. Or, if somebody has access to a website that brings in a lot of traffic, they can go ahead and feature me as their Internet Loser of the Year/Week/Life/Fortnight. Bye, bitches. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, with one quarter of school left until I graduate this fall, I checked my balance on my student account the other day just to make sure my financial aid was taking care of everything. I look at the damn thing and there's a charge for like sixty bucks in late fees. Wondering what I'm being charged for, I call my school and talk to some woman who I'm sure I called right in the middle of her lunchtime masturbation session, because she was a horrible old woman. She tells me that a Spanish Placement test (that I thought I'd test out of, but turns out I'm not as bueno con espanol as I thought) I took wasn't paid for. First, paying for tests is bullshit unless it's a pregnancy test or an AIDS test. Second, I asked the woman at the office when I took the test if financial aid would pay for it automatically and she said yes. So fuck them both. I talked the woman on the phone down from sixty bucks to thirty and a lesson in sweet make-loving like she's never had, but still, thirty bucks for a test that I didn't even fully pass is a horrible scam.  That wasn't particularly funny--I just had to vent.  Sorry.  Speaking of AIDS tests, I did take an AIDS test once and, I'm proud to say, I passed it with flying colors. I didn't take the one that most people take, though. I heard that the way most people do it is by giving a blood sample that then goes to a lab where they insert your blood into the vagina of a starfish and, if you have AIDS, the starfish turns into a thousand butterflies which disappear in a cloud of glitter. My source for this information isn't very reliable, however, because I heard this from a homeless man who jabbed an icepick into my eye to "remove the camera." The AIDS test that I took was easy. It went like this:   Question 1  Do you have AIDS or HIV?  (Check all that apply) []Yes, I have AIDS. []Yes, I have HIV. []I don't think I have AIDS. []I don't think I have HIV. []No.   Question 2  Do you like me? (Check one) []Yes []No []Only as a friend. []Only as a friend but maybe more than a friend.  I answered 'No' to the first question and 'Only as a friend but maybe more than a friend' to the second.  When the woman who gave me the test looked at my answers, she got all red in the face and started whispering to her friend who was sitting right next to her.  Then I pulled her hair and ran away screaming, "Jennifer has AIDS!"  Her name wasn't Jennifer, I just can't help but yell that out whenever I run anywhere--it's like those people with OCD that flip a lightswitch on and off eighty times whenever they enter a room.  I'm done now.  I told myself I wouldn't write as much and try to entertain as little as possible; I think I've done my job.  No comments to my long-ass entry last time.  I doubt anybody finished it.  So, do what you will, cuntsplosions.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This entry is going to be short because I realize that I write too much per entry and by the time people get to the end they're either laughing too hard or they're  urlLink watching something far more entertaining .  I've decided that my name is too boring and I'm going to change my name.  In order to spice it up, though, I'm not going to do much to my name.  I mean, I'm not going to give myself a whole new name like Sexass Bitchhumper or anything.  Even though that's a fucking wicked name, don't get me wrong, that's not what I'm changing it to.  I just think that, in order to make myself more exciting, I'm just going to change my name from "Kurt" to "Kurt!"; I may even do all caps there--for emphasis.  I just wish I would have thought of this back when I was in Junior High or High School.  I would have liked to be sitting in class knowing that a substitute teacher has to call my name, it goes something like this.  Substitute Teacher: Rebecca Clitoris.  Rebecca: Here!  Substitute: Umm, Jason DoucheBag-Zeta-Jones.  Jason: Here!  Substitute: Kurt Duggan.  *Silence*  Substitute: Kurt Duggan.  *Silence*  Substitute: So Kurt's not here?  Me: Ohh, you're calling me?  It's not Kurt.  Substitute: Oh?  Me: It's Kurt!   Substitute:  That's what I said.  Me: No it isn't.  You said 'Kurt.'  Substitute:  I...don't follow.  Me: It's Kurt!  With some feeling, motherfucker!  Substitute:  Did you just call me...?  Me: Did who?  Substitute: You!  Me: What's my name?  Substitute: Kurt!  Me: There you go.  You did it, Mr. Brown.  Substitute: You can call me by my first name.  (I always loved substitute teachers that did this)  Me: Cool.  What is it?  Substitute: Motherfucker.  That's why I thought it was weird that you already knew my name.  Me: Your name is Motherfucker Brown?  Substitute: Yeah, I changed it from Kurt when I was in High School.  Things like that are fun to type because I have no idea where they're going when I start them.  I just want to let the affiliates know that this entry is going to go long.  I have too much more I want to say on the subject of names.  So, already, I'm breaking my own damn rules that I made about quantity over quality.  Another thing I'd do to change my name is give myself a suffix or prefix that adds something badass that people would have to call me.  The first thing I would do is change my first name to Mister so that when people are being formal with me they have to call me Mister Mister.  As soon as they'd do that I'd just start singing, "Take....these broken wings....and learn to fly again, and learn to live so free."  But I'd really like to give myself a prefix like "The legendary" or "World Renowned Walrus Slayer."  It would suck to have to fill my name out in things where there's a limited amount of space (especially like the damn SATs where you have to fill in the corresponding bubbles with the letters--fuck that shit), but it would be worth it to have my name called out at the DMV to renew my Driver's License.  "Umm, could 'The Moving, Grooving, 170-pound Sex Machine Supreme Kurt Duggan' please come to the counter to get his new License photo taken please?"  Then I'd look around all coy and walk up there with my gangsta walk and be like, "You rang, ho?"  I'm so damn smooth.  This works the other way with suffixes as well.  This will be the second of two scenes that you can print out and perform with your friends or for your local church.  I'd be sitting on the Witness Stand (oxymoronic action in itself) in court.  Lawyer: State your full name for the record please.  Me: Kurt Duggan...  Lawyer: Okay, Mr. Duggan, I...  Me: I wasn't finished.  Lawyer: Oh.  Please, continue.  Your full name for the record.  Me: Kurt Duggan Can Beat Up Vampires and Has Totally Driven a Monster Truck Over Like A Hundred Cars Before and Is Pretty Sure That There Were Old People Or Maybe Some Dolphins Inside of Them And He Doesn't Care.  I don't have a fun ending for that one like I did the other one, but the fun part about performing these with your friends is that you can improvise the ending; that's why I left it open.  And, finally, here's a fun little story about how bad handwriting and the California education system can combine to make one of life's supposedly greatest moments into one of its most ridiculous and embarassing.  As I've mentioned before, my last name is mispronounced probably 95% of the time and it's only six letters.  It's pronounced Duh-gun, not Doo-gun (not to be confused with an invention I'm working on).  Well, at my High School Graduation, we were told to write our name out phonetically on a card and hand it to the woman who was announcing them.  I know that my handwriting is horribly shitty so I concentrated on getting my last name perfectly legible--to me.  I handed the card to the woman with confidence as I got ready to stride onto stage and accept life's passage into adulthood in the form of a piece of cardboard with my name written on it in computer caligraphy.  I see her look down at the card and look up at the crowd with a smile on her face (that soon would fade as I would actually pluck both of her eyes from her face and swallow them whole when she mispronounces my name).  She beams, "Kurt Dumb Gun."  The crowd smatters (I think I just verbed the word 'smattering'--and now 'verb') with applause and a few people yelling back at her pronouncing my name correctly.  I corrected it for her and made my march across the stage--leaving high school the way I had entered it: Awkward, embarassed, and covered in a strange woman's blood.  Interesting thought of the day: Broken glass, when used as a spermacide, drastically reduces the possibility that a woman will become pregnant, but drastically increases the possibility of a vagina filled with glass (another phrase you'll have to put in google in a week or so).  Drop some comments about whatever you want and don't be too disappointed that I already went back on my word.  Just think of me as your step-dad who "Really loves your momma and won't ever hit her again."  Or  urlLink email me .   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hoohah!  This entire entry is going to be about pee, specifically my own pee, so if you don't like pee, are allergic, addicted and don't want the temptations, or have a personal vendetta against pee because it clubbed your grandmother in the knee hours before the ice skating championships, you'll probably want to skip this one.  There are certain things that I eat that make my pee smell like said item.  For instance, whenever I eat cereal that's like Honey Smacks or Super Golden Crisp, when I pee later that day, I'm reminded all over again of what I had for breakfast.  I thought that the peepee chute and the poopoo chute were separate, so this confuses me.  Why would something that's getting turned into my poop emit its beautiful, sugary odor out of my flesh-pipe?  My stomach should not grumble upon smelling my own urine, yet it does.  But, don't worry, it doesn't taste a thing like what I had for breakfast.  It's just really salty and hot--like a latino woman.  I'd much prefer if when I ate Corn Pops that that would mean later on that day a latino woman would spew forth from my wiener.  Not so much because I'd "totally do her"--because I wouldn't, she's a human that came from my penis, I don't trust her--but because it would make me feel like I was a bottle that a genie came from.  Lord knows I rub that thing enough.  Yay for masturbation jokes.  My penis is a mexican genie's lamp.  I'll bet in like a week if you put that phrase into google, my site will be the only one that comes up.   Also, as I discovered a week or two ago, if you put  urlLink "Whoopi Goldberg's butthole"  into google, my site is the only one that comes up.  I'd like to think that my entire audience is composed of people who put that phrase into google and were initially upset that there were no photos of the Diva's balloon knot from  Sister Act ,  Sister Act 2: Back in the Habit , and  Eddie .   Then, once they gave in to the fact that they would not be finding the holy graille of Whoopi-porn, they stayed for the constant pedophile, sodomy and retard jokes.  I don't know how many of my tens of readers have taken those big-ass, smelly, horse-sized multi-vitamins, but I have, and they messed up my urinary tract something wicked.  I guess it wasn't my urinary tract so much as the color, scent and sometimes even the texture of my urine.  It turned my pee into a radioactive yellow.  This, I thought, was cool on one hand because I felt like I was a Superhero who, after a terrible accident in the bathroom of the nuclear power plant where he worked, was stricken with the superpower of radioactive urine that doesn't actually hurt his foes, but kind of grosses them out a little.  But, also, any time that my urine isn't the normal, crimson red that it usually is, it's a little nerve-wracking.  This gave me an idea, though.  I thought of patenting an item that could change the properties of one's urine.  There could be the color-changing line that does just what it sounds like.  It turns you into a black person.  No.  That doesn't make sense (but it did in  Soul Man ).  There'd be the traditional, primary colors, but then there'd also be the mood changing urine pills and the patriotic, Red, White, and Blue pack that, when urinated in the right sequence, forms an exact replica of the U.S. flag.  Also, another thing that has me pretty stoked about my urine changers, or, as I've decided to call them, "The Pee Dazzlers," is the one that changes the textures of one's urine.  There are a few of these.  One of them turns your urine into a thick, stew-like consistency (with your choice of soup flavor: Clam Chowder (the Red and the White) and Beef and Onion are in the testing stages).  Another will make your urine come out like Silly String so, you too, can feel like Spider-Man, if only in the confines of your sad, lonely, bacteria-laden bathroom.  But, finally, the one that has me most excited, is the pill that will change your urine into a steam.  Imagine being able to enter a room in a cloud of fog.  It's like carrying your own personal fog machine with you wherever you go, except this fog smells like breakfast!  Nobody take that!  I'm using it as the slogan.  Interesting thought of the day: The remote control was invented by a man who had run out of things to throw at his wife so she would get up and change the channel.  By sheer coincidence, the thing would have worked to change the channel on his TV.  He didn't discover this soon enough, however, as he bludgeoned his wife to death with it for not keeping Double A batteries around the house.  I ran out of slightly clever for the night, so please comment, especially if you're new (but the older folks feel free as well).  Or, I'll leave  urlLink my email  for all those who came looking for Whoopi Goldberg's butthole and are disappointed.  I'll send you pics from my personal collection.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The past two days I've seen two movies, if you do the math longhand, you'll come to find out that that's an average of almost one movie per day. It's close, but I think I'm rounding somewhere to get that number--it's not exact. I'm going to talk about the movies, but I'll try to steer clear of spoiling it for you (Bruce Willis is dead the whole time!!).   Das Village     In M. Night Shyamalan's fourth movie that's not a  urlLink shitty movie that involves Rosie O'Donnell as a homely nun who plays baseball  (I'm just guessing from the picture on the box, I had my fill of Rosie O'Donnell as a lesbian who plays baseball with  A League of Their Own ), Night (who I will refrain from referring to as Shamalamadingdong or anything like that because it's been beaten to death worse than Laci Peterson and her heathen baby) takes Joaquin Phoenix and  urlLink Opie's daughter  and drops them in the middle of a town that's full of Amish people and William Hurt's grizzly attitude and voice.   It's hard to talk about this movie without giving a lot away, so I'm going to make stuff up that doesn't really happen in the movie and review that.  Let's just say that I've read reviews of  The Village  and it wasn't reviewed that great.  I enjoyed it, but it's not one of those movies that you can watch over again like  The Sixth Sense  or  The He-Man  movie!  I was so in love with the He-Man cartoon when I was a kid, I think I experienced my first man-erection when I saw this movie in the theaters.  Anyway, in the pretend world of what happens in the movie, Joaquin Phoenix, who is a known necrophiliac, gets caught building a steam-powered robot without permission of the rest of the village.  The village people hate technology and cast Joaquin and his robot out of the village (now, here I'm referring to the people that live in the village in the movie, not the music group, but, it is a little-known fact that the Village People also hate technology).  Opie's daughter decides that she's leaving and that she's in love with Joaquin because she saw him in  Signs  so she's going to hunt him down in the woods.  But, the woods are said to be haunted by other known necrophiliacs and she'll never get out of there alive.  Then, at the end of the movie, Joaquin and Opie-ette are embracing in the center of the village after they've murdered everybody else and Joaquin has sodomized each and every one of them while singing "Let's Get it Started" by The Black Eyed Peas.  Now, I have to say that this took me out of the movie because how would he know this song?  They must have tried to cash in on the success of the song so they decided to screw realism and use it anyway.  But, the big twist at the end is that, while you thought that the robot was just a robot, it turns out that he's the only real thing there and he built Joaquin and Tom Bosley's granddaughter as his own robots because he really liked Gladiator and Happy Days.   And, the only thing that robots know how to do is build people-robots that sodomize other dead people-robots; it's like their fuel.  I remember at this part just shaking my head thinking, Knight, you've done it again, you clever bastard.  There's one final twist at the end that I won't give away here, but let's just say it involves a pie-eating contest, twenty sequential Michigan license plates, and a macaroni necklace.  I probably gave too much away right there; it's pretty easy to figure out.   Supreme Supremacy and Redundant Redundancy!   Matt Damon needs to always play a guy who's pissed off about stuff but doesn't really show it until he totally punches a guy in the throat before you can even blink.  It's like Matt Damon is two people: He's a regular guy who wears a lot of sweaters, but then he's also this totally awesome killing machine that won't hesitate to toe-punch a woman in the vagina.   Matt Damon is Jason Bourne, a...born...killing machine.  You see what I did there?  With the words and the puns?  Man, I'm on fire like that kid David who's dad hated the way he slept so he threw gas and a match on him in his sleep.  He's back and he's mad because people won't stop following him and making him be wicked cool in public by karate chopping guys in the eyes while driving a rickshaw.  I don't know why he's mad at people for making him show off in public; maybe he's just trying to be modest in front of his girlfriend.  If I could stop bullets with my mind like he can, I'd show it off all the time.  Maybe Ben Affleck asked him to stop being so cool so people would go see more of his movies like  urlLink Forces of Nature  and Matt's trying to help him out.   Anyway, there's lots of cool car chases and shaky cameras that make it seem like you're really there, videotaping it, and you have Parkinson's.  I love feeling like a character in the movie--especially when I get to be Michael J. Fox.  I think the people around me got mad because I kept yelling at the screen, "Doc, you're telling me you built a time machine out of a Delorean?"  In all seriousness, there was a woman behind me who thought her kids would really love to see an action movie at two o'clock in the afternoon so she just had to take all three of them with her while she sat there fantasizing about how Matt Damon would take her away from her shitty, scroungy-ass kids.  For the most part, the kids were fine, but about seventeen twentyfourths of the way through the film, the little boy, who was probably 6 or 12 or 9, decided that he was hungry.  Again, this would have been fine with me if the kid behind me ate.  I'm all for kids eating once every couple of days.  The bad part, though, was that the woman snuck some food in--again, I don't care, theater shit's expensive--but she snuck it in in the LOUDEST GODDAMN PLASTIC BAG ON THE PLANET.  And she couldn't just take the shit out of the bag and throw the bag on the floor.  No!  I'm pretty sure she was trying to get all of the wrinkles out of the bag because it sounded like somebody behind me was rolling around in a big-ass pile of leaves in my ear.  I'm not one to yell at people at movie theaters (though I do have a story about this that I'll probably talk about some time in the future), but I turned around, stabbed the kid in the throat like my new idol Matt Damon, and kept watching the movie.  The bag stopped making noise.  Here are my ratings for the two movies:  The Village  gets yellow and  The Bourne Supremacy  gets a Trapper Keeper with a unicorn on the front.  Word of advice of the day: When people say "I could care less," please end their life right there with whatever means necessary because they don't deserve to speak anymore.  Or you can calmly explain to them that it's "I couldn't care less."  I prefer doing the first one because I've looked into it and killing somebody is completely legal if the person who is killed is a moron.  It's like a Citizen's arrest but with murder.  Okay, I've given you all time to bring your friends here, now they must comment or I will start docking your pay.  Remember, you get to punch them in the face when you tell them about my website; how could this deal get any sweeter?  I'll tell you how.  If somebody comes here and comments saying that somebody referred them here, I'll give both the referrer and the referree (the one who is referred, not the person who always calls me for travelling--TWO STEPS, BITCH) a very rare strain of whatever STD they want.  I'm not like most people with STDs, I've become so used to them that I can pick and choose which ones I would like to give to people.  I don't want to brag or anything, but I've got  urlLink Bacterial Vaginosis --guys normally can't even get this.  It's like Pokemon--Collect them all! Or you can  urlLink email me  and tell me you're going to end my current unemployment.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>