<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
            Today I finally finished up building this wretched thing.  Last night I glued in what at the time was a perfect windshield.  After holding it down to let the glue setup, however, I noticed that I got two little spots of glue that ran down from the chrome frame that the windshield sets in; I can't keep anything nice!  In case you were wondering, in this photo the model is setting on the trunk of my fathers '57 (see photo in the last post.)  The color is called Tropical Turquoise. 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          This is my father's 1957 Chevrolet Bel Air Two-door Sports Coupe. Under the hood is a three-year-old 350 cu. in. Chevy crate motor, pushing out 250 horsepower. Setting on top of the motor is a Holley 650 carburetor bolted to a Edelbrock intake. Bolted to the back of the motor is a Muncie 3 speed manual transmission, and the rear end is the only original thing on the car. For more information about my dad's car, I have setup a  urlLink website  where I can post photos from trips that we take in the car.  In about 10 or 12 hours I will more than likely be in the garage waxing the front of the car so that bugs won't bake into the paint job on the hood when we go to Idaho. We will be driving this car over 2,000 miles to Coeur d'Alene, Idaho for the 2004  urlLink Bowtie/ Late Great Chevy  International convention without air conditioning, what fun! Yep, that right, no air conditioning because the motor runs "too hot" as it is, and adding air conditioning would probably fry the thing. Get this- while driving 5 MPH in a parade our car temperature gage is halfway between C &amp; H, however, when driving 80 MPH down the interstate in third gear the gage is leaning on H and you can smell anti-freeze. My mechanic father and I believe that the shaft in the water pump (which the fan blade is bolted to) is slipping at higher RPMs, thus pumping less anti-freeze/ water through the motor. At lower RPMs, however, the slippage is less, thus causing virtually no change in water temperature. 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today, or actually yesterday, I finished a devil model car I was building.  The model is a 1953 Chevrolet Corvette Panamericana racecar, however, it ended up being a 1953 Chevy Corvette with engine parts from a 1954 Chevy Corvette because I didn't read the instructions.  OriginallyI planned to make it a model that looked like it just rolled off the line, but after screwing up the paint job in two spots on the driver's side, and numerous other mess ups, it became the "Mexico Badger" Panamericana racer.  I have to admit that with all the race stickers on, it does look cooler, and thanks to a couple stickers on the drivers side, I have a perfect paint job.  I plan to enter this model in a contest in Idaho next week, so I will have photos of it in competition.  If you've made it this far in the reading you are probably interested in the model cars, so here's the urlLink  link  to the kit that I built in three weeks. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         In case you were wondering what the hell  urlLink Internet Explorer  is, it is the computer program that you use to look at web sites on a PC. Well recently my one-year-old 2.0 GHz HP computer decided to start freezing up every time I used Internet Explorer. The thing that pissed me off was that it decided to keep freezing up while I was working on a website for my fathers classic car club ( urlLink Crown City Cruisers ), so I virtually got nothing done after working for almost two hours. Finally I remembered hearing on  urlLink G4TechTV  about an  urlLink Internet Explorer  alternative called  urlLink Mozilla Firefox . After about 10 minutes of downloading, I started up Firefox, and I haven't used Internet Explorer since.  I soon found after downloading Mozilla Firefox that you can download thousands of different extensions, which are basically little programs that customize Firefox to your preference. Browser customization is probably the feature that I love the most about Firefox- something that the communist Microsoft Corporation hates.  Mozilla Firefox is what computer geeks call Open Source, which (as Dictionary.com puts it) is a method and philosophy for software licensing and distribution designed to encourage use and improvement of software written by volunteers by ensuring that anyone can copy the source code and modify it freely. This means that if I wanted to, I could write an extension for Firefox, possibly improve the software for some users, and share it freely. Open Source is the future of computer software, and will probably one day take down large corporations like Microsoft.  If you are interested in Mozilla Firefox, or any other Mozilla products check out  urlLink http://www.mozilla.org  for more information.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well since my "Official Website" was basically a failure, I have decided to just create a blog and set it up so it is my website.  THX 138- What is it?  It is the California license plate number on John Milner's piss yellow 1932 Ford Coupe (Deuce Coupe) in the 1973 George Lucas classic American Graffiti.  The reason that this is the name of my blog is because I am interested in cars,  urlLink American Graffiti  is one of the best movies ever made, and I couldn't think of anything better.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>