<Blog>



<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, from Athens. My name is Madeline Modeliste. I’m the big purse tottin, thick-rimmed lens-wearing girl, from Athens, you may have seen at your most recent concert experience. A friend asked me to write this here review. Why? Not because I’m the most articulate Athenian, but probably because he has a crush on me. But then again, who doesn’t.  I already know that I am going to get a lot of people saying that the two bands I reviewed are not jambands. But then again, what is a jamband anyway? What is a Grover or an Elmo? Well I guess they are monsters. Or are they Muppets? Or are they monster Muppets? You know what I mean? Cause I don’t. Anyway here it goes my first review:  For one reason or another, the town of Athens, GA has become a grooming house for great bands-bands of all different styles, yet all still distinctly Athens. We all know about the onslaught of popularity the town received after the B-52’s and R.E.M. turned on the lights for everyone else to see. We all know about the success of the rock-n-roll-raging, bass-bomb-dropping, soul-drenched-singing, locomotive trekking, and just good-ole-great-time-feeling Widespread Panic has enjoyed. But what now? What now for music in a town that lives, bleeds, and feels the panic&hellip;  At a Kevn Kinney show (the Former and current Drivin n Cryin front man) Kevn himself, was remarking on how he has been in Athens a long time now, and never before has the music been this damn good. And then, smartly he said, “so don’t tell anyone." And now stupidly I am telling all of ya’ll.  &ldquo;This town is nuts, my kind of place.&rdquo;  The music here is plenty abundant. For six bucks, I went and saw two up and coming bands of radically different sound and vibe, yet both with the same brilliant, can’t-contain-it-no-more energy.  The first was a free show at the Broad Street bar called Tasty World. The Tasty World has two places for music. One upstairs and you guessed it, one downstairs. The show I went to was (nope not downstairs-you guessed wrong) actually it was upstairs. Just about every Thursday this summer the band that is calling themselves Dub Conscious have been playing upstairs for free. People haven’t been paying a penny, but have quickly bought into their sound. They’ve bought into their feel and into their all-in-all-get-on-up-get-on-down-reggae-is-inside-you-rhythms. What started out as a group of 10 or 20 friends supporting their buds up on stage has turned into a 100 or so person grooving lower than you’d think time. (Mind you this is a summer in Athens).  I settled in, feeling out the scene. Lots of earthy folks, some fratters, some sorostitues, some elder Athens peeps, and a couple Rasta looking kinds. I tried to take in the tunes, see and understand what this band was trying to make with their music. That’s when I reached into my giant purse and jotted down a few words that came to mind. Not more than two sentences in, I got asked by some college kid, “what I was doing?” He wanted some of Mad Modeliste, but I wasn’t even gonna sweat this kid, so in my sweetest voice I told him to buzz off, and went to the back of the venue by the Ms. Pac Man to get my write on. It was there that I finally understood what was going on on stage, and throughout the venue.  The music was roots reggae, which at any second can drop into full on out dub reggae. Transing out on ya. The dub-c can get spacey. But never too far off, that you can’t see home.  &ldquo;Married to their roots here&rdquo;  The set up is a drummer, a percussionist, and that’s it. Just kidding, they have a drummer, a percussionist and a keyboard player and that’s it&hellip; just kidding again. To go with the drummer, percussionist, and keyboard player, they also have a bass player, and two guitarists. Both guitars can lead like a mother. But both are always very classy with their styles. Never jumping down each other’s throats, always adding exactly what needs to be added at the most precise moment. The shorter of the two bearded guitarists is the one that normally sings. A very unique honest voice. It is heavy and thick. Thick like maple syrup. And like maple syrup it’s better each time you taste it. All in all, this dub/roots rock reggae band is incredibly original, and has a rather refreshing sound. They stay true to the reggae they love and play it in their own voice, and should not be missed. I repeat,  should not be missed .  That was only the first part of my Drunken Athens Thursday night. The rest was something of a different sort. I headed on down broad St., jogged past the arches, stumbled all the way to the complete opposite side of downtown to the 40 Watt Club, where the Drive-By Truckers were playing.  These folks you called the “Truckers” are rough, southern and like to play LOUD! By the time I had arrived, beer and whiskey seemed to already cover the crowd, literally. Spilling appeared to be encouraged at a &ldquo;Truckers&rdquo; show. Yelps could be heard; both, from the crowd and the stage. But what seemed to come most from the stage was this intense southern sound. Now I am not going to compare them to Skynrd. Most would but I am not going to. In fact I will not even bring up Lynyrd Skynyrd's name in this review, because that would not do justice to the unique southern sound that the Drive-By Truckers have made for themselves. But let’s just say they would make Skynrd proud.  To say they are a guitar driven band is a bit of an understatement. They do indeed have a drummer, and a bass player, but after that there are at least three guitars going at all times. It’s a party up on stage. At one point, Patterson Hood, the leader of them Truckers, was so into his singing, he didn’t even notice a friend who frequents the stage, came up under his guitar strap and made a clean swipe. The thief played Patterson’s guitar while Hood continued to sing his lyrics and laugh about the burglary. The band always seems to give off this nasty, dirty, rock n roll time vibe. And Patterson Hood’s Alabama enriched voice and lyrics always tell it like it is. This band may not be for everyone, they may be too hard, too rough, or too loud, but none can deny their energy. And I was not denying it either, I was completely engulfed in the dirtiness, till some indie rocker kid woke me from my musical dreaminess, and told me, “ I really like your glasses.” You see I have these thick-rimmed black glasses that are really fresh, so of course everyone would dig 'em. I told him very politely, “ Yeah so does Patterson Hood.” Playing like Patterson was my man or something, ha. The kid got scared and smiled hesitantly as he found his friends.  The night was fun and energetic. On an Athens scale of 5, I give Dub Conscious a 4 Bluebird café tofu delights. And I give the Drive By Truckers 4 Ronnie B’s meat, veggie, biscuit lunches and half a drunken bottle of whiskey I found in a dirty corner of the 40 Watt club.  Till next time- Mad Modeliste.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, Madeline Modeliste giving ya’ll greetings from a place that many call The Classic City- Athens, Ga. I felt like chiming in to all of ya’ll music readers 'bout an interesting Thursday night I witnessed here in town. First off it should be known that I looked damn good this night. Some of you might be wondering of what importance does this have on the review? Well it just does. All right? I was wearing my faded-in-the-front jeans, lil' t-shirt, sneaks, and my purse (a big shiny purse). My contacts were an after thought, for I had my big black-rimmed glasses for seeing purposes (even though tonight was all about hearing, and only a little about seeing.)  The plans were to go head down to the Georgia Theater, where Jerry Joseph and the Jackmormons were playing. And the plan was working, for I found a decent parking spot, right on Broad- near Lumpkin. Got my walking shoes walking, and skirmished into a modestly empty Georgia Theater. Jerry Joseph and his Jackmormons hadn’t quite taken the stage yet, but what had taken the stage, was taking me back. There was music that sounded familiar and odd at that same time, comfortable and bizarre, Old School and brand new learning center. It was the music of Cody Chestnutt.  The young soul singer and his band inspired the lovely and stylistic Ms. Madeline Modeliste to bust out my writing pad inside my purse. What I wrote was illegible and would not make the review for it went something like this, “stragfdel, ins the deliegrad.” And it also went like this “musig witsv lerin.” What will go in the review, however, is this, “His music had flare, as if a fire ball was chilled by spirit, a flame put out by a soul drop.” Cody Chestnutt, dressed in funky soul driven psychedelic attire, played music. Cody Chestnutt, dressed in clothes, played funky soul driven psychedelia. Funky soul driven psychedelic musical clothes played Cody Chestnutt. Now, I know that might be a bit much to swallow, but that is what it feels like to try to describe his music. He sang with passion. At times sounding like he fell out of a 1970’s R&B Album cover. At other times ripping some rock 'n roll riffs. While his onstage antics certainly kept my eyes focused (through my thick rimmed glasses) his music at times had me drifting and looking around to see if there was anyone there that I knew? And of course there was. I saw Louie, and Jethro, and my friend Debo. Debo was taking pictures; Jethro was getting his groove on. But it was Louie that filled me in on a secret. You see there was a buzz about the winds. Down at the 40 Watt Club, a bunch of bands were playing, and one of them that was playing was supposed to consist of all the members of a certain band that’s name has the letters M. E. R. in it (with the exception of a member whose name rhymes with Jeter Huck). So a little after Cody Chestnutt finished, I grabbed my make shift cameraman (debo) and headed down the street to the Forty Watt club.  The show at Forty Watt was a fundraiser for a politician running for office under the political party of probably either Republican or Democrat, or Green party. But everyone knows that my political party preference is Violet. Well actually no one knew that, because I have never told anyone. But now, everyone knows that my political party preference is that of the violet party. Well, not everyone knows, because 5 billion people do not read this website. But everyone that is reading now knows that my political party preference is that of the violet party.  Upon entering, my ears heard rock 'n roll, and it was the good kind of rock 'n roll. Some good ole fashioned Athens rock 'n roll. It was performed by the Athens band-The Possibilities. Mike Mills was on stage singing with the band. The Possibilities don’t lead anyone on to thinking they are something that they are indeed not. It is nothing but straight up rock and roll-yo. I was digging it. The very next band that came on stage, however, was the reason I came running on down here. It was Curtis Crowe switching with Bill Berry on drums and percussions, Mike Mills on Guitar, joined by William Tonks on other guitar, and Paul Crumpy Edwards on other other guitar (the bass kind). They were on from the moment they started. Smiles were swimming through the crowd. Especially by the folks near were I was standing, when other R.E.M. member, Michael Stipe, could be spotted bouncing his head to the music just to the left of the stage. When the four on stage busted into “I am superman” Stipe could be seen signing along. But would the man they call Stipe-man ever get up on stage. Yes he did. And it sort of became a mini R.E.M. reunion. I say mini, because Peter Buck was not there and Stipe’s visit to the stage was not long. But it was sweet. It ended a great night of music for all in the crowd. But not Ms. Madeline Modeliste, uh uh, no it did not. For I was on my way back to the theatre before you could say hop scotch a scratch forth.  Jerry Joseph had taken the stage and was already ripping it up by the time me and my shiny black and white purse came a tregging, came a skipping, came a tripping trekking back into the sticky floored theatre on the corner of Lumpkin and Clayton. Jerry Joseph always plays well in Athens. He brings his 4.0 grade point average game when he plays here in town. The Athens Jerry Joseph steps up to the plate cleat by cleat, he drives his soul deeper to the core of his true inner feelings and has 'em sprinkle through the speakers so that each in the crowd feels touched with his tunes. He doesn’t hold back. Leaves it all right out there on the stage. And for that I respect him. Sometimes his pure intensity is a bit much for me to handle large amounts of at one time. But tonight, I was into it for the long haul. And boy was it worth it, for not more than two shakes and a liter later, out onto the stage bolted with pounding step after pounding step-the big bad wolf- I mean Big Dave Schools. Yes that Dave Schools. The bass bomb dropping, eloquently note dispensing, always on time checking, rhythm man from up above and down below- Dave Schools.  He added much energy to the theatre. It wasn’t that long ago that his band used to play this very venue many times a year. You could tell by how comfortable he immediately became. This could have also been because his obvious relationship with Jerry. Positive vibrations from their instruments and from their whole selves were being tossed back and forth on the stage like a friendly game of vibe badminton. But the friendly game turned nasty as the music took a spill to the darker side. Right where everyone wanted it to go. And the nastiness continued till there was none left for one to be nasty with. Show over. Till next time.  The whole night was a very Musically Athens induced night. On an Athens Scale of 5:  Cody Chestnutt and his band got 3. Three hot pockets from Jamaica mi crazy.  The Possibilities and Mike Mills band both got 5. You can’t get much more Athens than R.E.M. and the rest of those guys. Five Original “Sammie’s” from the Daily Co-Op on Prince.  And Jerry Joseph and the Jackmormons got 4 and a half. An extremely High score for a band not from the area. But like I said before there is a lot of Athens in him. 4 orders of chips and cheese dip from the taco stand and the half smoked cigarette that Schools left on stage and I saw some Spreadhead chick pick up after the show and put in her purse.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Ya'll, Mad Modeliste here. On a recent September evening, I found myself entering the 40 Watt Club here in Athens, GA., but it seemed as though I entered something grandeur and more peculiar than just simply the 40 Watt. And my assumption proved true- for I was walking through an Athens, GA time warp. The music my ears heard weren't the tunes of some modern day Athens Based band- no this was something much different, this was something original, something spooky and fun, odd and enjoyable, this was the music of the B-52's!  Some say there would be no music scene in this town if it weren't for these interesting Athenians on stage. And by the sounds of what I was hearing I don't doubt it at all. Moon dancing, heart thumping, frown shaking, smile making, whumpa whumpa noise raking were all going on at one time on this night at the 40 Watt. Momentarily I got lost, I got lost in the time warp, I truly felt like I was back in the seventies, back in a time when there were no bars in town, just house parties for kids that wanted bars, music for folks that wanted something different. My eyes opened but my mind was still set to 1977. The joy I felt didn't even come close to the joy I could sense bulging out of the eyes of these B-52 folks. And as I listened deep, I finally got it; I finally understood how it was true that these are the real ringleaders of the circus currently known as the Athens Music Scene.  They stand for everything music in this town means. Fun in the face of fear, silliness in an old Republican state. Athens is in a way an oasis of alternative thought in a vast Southern area of conservativeness. The B-52's music grabs this feeling and flies with it. But staying true to the gritty, Southern nature of Athens, their music has a hint of that rough, rugged feel that sweats down here. And that is what remains in most of the music that Athens has produced ever since; a sense of celebratory fun without forgetting about its gritty surroundings. I was swimming in the seventies, imitating the dance of the beautiful Kate Pearson, when some boy tries to pick me up. What is it with me and the 40 Watt Club, that every time I enter the building boys, hover to get a glimpse of me? Well, I wasn't going to let no drooling youngster ruin my time warp experience, so before he could finish his pathetic attempt of catching my attention I moved to the center of the crowd, a good seven feet away from him, from here I was once again thrown into the center of the time warp, feeling the warp engulf my body thrice again. "Love Shack" got everyone going as did "Roam," and "Rock Lobster," but it wasn't just the popular hits that the crowd dug, it was every moment of fun that was felt. And before we knew it, the show was over. Well this show was over but as for the night, it was putting on its wet cleats and getting ready for the second half kickoff.  Rain fell on me, smudging my make-up a bit (yes, sometimes I do wear make-up. I know, I know, I don't need it, but some times I color my face, anyway). I purposely parked my car near the Georgia Theater, so that after the show I would be forced to walk by and listen to the music going on, and the sound would hopefully lure me in.  And that is exactly what happened. The band on the stage lured me and my five-dollar fee on in, in to the sticky floored, dirty tasting beer, character-soaked theatre of Georgia.  The music lured me down even closer, closer to the stage...I walked down the right side to the floor, and "excuse me'd" by a sweaty dancing purple haired girl and eased my way into a comfortable area to get my listen and groove on. Or not, cause this is a review and if I don't want to get my groove or listen on then that is my damn right. But in this case I did indeed get both my listen and groove on. (in that order).  The band: Barbara Cue  I had heard a lot about this band, lots from various reliable and many not so reliable friends of mine. I heard things like: Oh Barbara Cue, that's that band that has that percussion player from Widespread in it, you know Schools or whatever, and they play straight up funk, right?" Also, I heard, "Those, them players that play in that CCR cover band." I've seen Barbara Cue a few times, so I have learned that those things aren't true. What I think may be true is that they started as a NRBQ cover band. They do have members from Widespread Panic, Bloodkin, and other Athens bands in them, and no they do not play straight up funk.  I tried pulling up my right foot to dance, but it wouldn't budge, the floor was just too damn sticky, and this is when I got to thinking about how nice and calming this music made me feel. Almost like I was relaxing on somebody's back porch on a cool fall day. Barbara Cue's music was a touch roots, a bit country, and all feel. It was light, but still contained much substance. They would jam, and sing with some southern drawl. They would play their guitars with smiles on their faces.  I was truly having a good time, when I thought to myself, "Shit, Self, If these guys started as an NRBQ cover band, I wonder what NRBQ sounds like?" So I decided to go find out, because NRBQ was playing at Tasty World a few blocks away tonight. Got my rain face on, and slid out onto Clayton Street. By the time I turned right on Jackson, my make up must have looked like a abstract art piece. But it didn't matter cause when I look bad, I mean real bad, like the worst I could ever possibly look on the ugliest street in Athens, on National Ugly day, even then I look damn good. And the proof of this lies in what happened as soon as I arrived at Tasty World.  The music had stopped, apparently an hour before I arrived. Some boy was standing out in front talking with the people working at the bar. He told me the scoop, on how it was over. He had a cooler of leftover beer. He claimed he was Jomo of Jomo entertainment. He said I could have the leftover beer; it was NRBQ's leftovers. Shit, I took it and walked. I don't care who he was and what he was giving me, I thought to myself as I walked through the rain, with beers filled to the rim of my giant sized purse, "He still ain't getting to study Ms. Madeline Modelsite.  On An Athens Scale of Five, you know the B-52s had got a perfect five. Five hours of recording at the local music friendly establishment Nuci's Space.  Barbara Cue got 3 and half. 3 shots of your choice from Nowhere Bar and that half a shot that the wussie at the end of the bar couldn't finish.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       09.23.76 | Cameron Indoor Stadium | Duke University | Durham, NC   Set 1 : Mississippi Half-Step Uptown Toodeloo, Minglewood Blues, Ramble On Rose, Cassidy, Brown Eyed Women, Lazy Lightning > Supplication, Crazy Fingers > El Paso, It Must Have Been The Roses, Music Never Stopped   Set 2 : Help On The Way > Slipknot > Franklin's Tower > Looks Like Rain, Eyes Of The World > Samson & Delilah, High Time, Dancing In The Streets > Wharf Rat > Drums > The Other One > Morning Dew  Hey there everybody, Madeline Modeliste here once again reporting from Athens. It dawned on me that many of my reviews have taken place at the Georgia Theater, and I have yet to give a detailed description of what the joint looks like, yet I give many details on what Mad Modeliste looks like. And in this review bout the Dark Star Orchestra I will once again overlook a detailed description about what that theatre of Georgia looks like in favor of a detailed description of yours truly, because that is still much more important.  I was wearing a black skirt with black stockings, black shoes, and you guessed it, a cute black shirt. My skin is rather fair (even though I’m not) so the shocking contrast of colors had boys heads swiveling round and round to get glimpses of me. Which was cool and all for a little bit, but after a while it began to get annoying.  When I was just a wee high school girl, I loved me some Grateful Dead, I went and saw them every chance I had. And when I did not have a chance to seem them, I somehow made it out so that I did get that chance to go see them. Them’s were the days, The Dead moved me (spiritually, not literally. Literally, I moved myself to Athens, packed up all my belongings in my car, drove it on into town and moved myself- literally). Spiritually The Dead always moved me to a happy place, a mythological place, a place that didn’t seem real at all- but seemed right. That is why I kept on going to see them. So when I heard about the Dark Star Orchestra coming into to town, obviously I was curious. Curiously I was obvious.  I moseyed my way in to the hard wood floored bar area of the theatre. Smelling patchouli, seeing folks spinning in danceable ways. The show had already started. I hadn’t missed much. I saw seven folks up on stage. Not one of which I recognized. But their music, their sound, their songs, I was very familiar with. The sounds I heard I was more familiar with than my own phone number. The music was that of the Grateful Dead.  Yes I know, you know, and the girl down the street with the funny walk knows about Grateful Dead cover bands. Folks, I must warn you, this is not like other Grateful Dead cover bands. If you close your eyes they aren’t even a Grateful Dead cover band at all. They are the Grateful Dead. It was striking. Folks around me began to fill me in a bit on how these folks- these Dark Star Orchestra folkies pick a Dead show and cover it as closely to the original as possible. And I could dig it. I saw what they mean. I meant what they saw. I felt it as I closed my pretty eyes. Garcia’s guitar made circles through my cranium. The music got a bit spacey and intense. I needed some air. So I worked my way outside. There were kids in their seventies garb, many with Duke hats, with their fingers pointing in the air asking for miracles. I shook my head, but I couldn’t shake what I was seeing. Yes it truly was the seventies. And I truly was at Duke University. September 27th, 1976, just outside Duke Cameron Indoor stadium. The music was so much like that of the original Grateful Dead show, that I found myself at the original show. I heard a kid in a homemade tie-dyed Duke T-shirt talking to a kid in a University of North Carolina hat saying, “one of these days we’re going to beat you, and it’s going to be sweet, man.”  But what was really sweet was the “It Must Have Been The Roses” that the band broke into, that pulled me back in through the Georgia Theatre er- Cameron indoor stadium doors. Garcia’s voice was like lazy left out butter- smooth, tasty and good with just about anything. It brought tears to many in the audience. The whole thing was real trippy, man. Donna Jean was up there dancing, Bobby on guitar, Phil’s off kilter bass patterns...I was totally into it, till a modern day UGA kid asked me if I had a light. “What the hell was that all about?!” I was so in tune with that 1970’s night, and then this kid had to throw me off my time traveling magic carpet. And to make matters worse, he was just asking me because he was trying to pick me up, not because he needed a light. I saw a friend of his bust out a lighter and light a cigarette as I lit his. He then proceeds to tell me his name, asks for mine, tells me he thinks I am pretty. Shit, as if I didn’t already know this, well I knew I was pretty and I knew my name, didn’t know his, but didn’t care to know his, either, what I really wanted to know was what song the band was about to break into, not any of this immature pick me up bull shat-shit. Took me a lil while, but eventually I was right back there in 1976 North Carolina. The band played on with all the pleasure and crispness of a mid 70’s Dead show. Most in the crowd weren’t born at the time that this show was originally played, but maybe that’s what made it so special, these kids got a chance to feel what it may have been like to be in that tiny basketball stadium back when The Dead was doing their thing.  I for one would dig catching these cats again. You never know if you are going to get a 60’s Pigpen show, or a Donna Jean show, or an acid test show...it’s all a surprise till the music starts.  As I left the show, people’s fingers where up in the air for a “miracle” to the next show. I got a miracle for you; I’ll smile at you. Not that my smile wasn’t showing throughout the night- very much on the contrary- my smile was all lit up because of Dark Star Orchestra’s incredibly, suspiciously, convincing replication of September 27th, 1976.  In the spirit of recent Ms. Madeline Modeliste write-ups, I decided my night was not over. There had to be a second band I could go and investigate. Without discussing it with my brain, my feet took me right over to the lil hidden away bar known as “The Watering Hole.” The music blared out on to the sidewalks and invited me on in. I did accept the invite, though I had no time to RSVP, I stumbled through the doors. The band that played was a local band, Fark-a-nookin. Three boys on stage trying to play blues-rock. The kids were actually up there on stage learning their instruments. I have no problem with kids learning their instruments, just don’t do it on stage, in front of me, and my blessed ears. At this point in the night, they had scared just about everyone out of the bar, except for me and the poor bartenders. Far-a-nookin was far from grooving. And I do not mean that in a polite way.  On an Athens Scale of 5, Dark Star Orchestra got a 3, which ain’t bad at all for out of town folk. 3 slices of pizza pie from Somebody’s Pizza (which is not around anymore, but was when the show took place).  Far-a-nookin got 1. They only got 1 because they are out of Athens. One crummy extra side of nasty ass mayonnaise from the very un-local joint McDonald’s. Better luck next time, boys.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      All I wanted to do was go to the Engine Room for a drink. I swear, that is all I had planned on doing on this Thursday eve. Instead, a groove rock girlfriend of mine convinced me to join her at one of Athens finest musical venues, Tasty World. The crowd that inhabited the bar/theatre was on a bit of the older side- for Athens, and a bit of the earthier side for anywhere but Athens. But that's cool; the looks of the others will just make me shine all that much more.  The band took the stage, and this girl, I mean; I should maybe say lady, or even better woman, sat down in front of a keyboard. Her style was something to be spoken of. And I don't just give out style props to any old hag walking by (even if that hag is dressed superbly). However, with this singer, this front woman of the band pH Balance, her style was poignant.  And when she started singing her style eased right in through her music. It was as if her dressing style was her walk, and her musical style an escalator. She walked right on up to that escalator and let it take her higher. And then she would walk on that upward moving escalator towards the smooth clouds, with a sultry voice and dynamic smile. Her keys were soft but with purpose. My groove-rock chick friend educated me on her name, Pam Howe.  Hmm? Ah ha. That is why the band goes by pH Balance. There is no silly Phish reference here, just straight up Pam Howe reference (or so I think). At any rate pH Balance impressed. Their drummer, and percussion players filled the rhythmic part of the soul funk they played quite impressively. And the bass was exactly what a bass should be in this kind of outfit- funk. Pam then stepped out from behind the keyboard and moved over to guitar. She played it with as much beauty as she sang, letting her right hand flail (out of an exaggerated down stroke). The band played a style of laid back, relaxed boogie that I may have never heard before. There was nothing forced about it. Pam set the tone and the others knew exactly how to follow with style. Pam's presence kept the attention of all in the crowd, even this pop rocker chick.  The music did not stop though. Well actually it did, for a little while. That little while was when the band broke down their equipment, the next band set up theirs, and when I, the lovely and sought after Madeline Modeliste paid a visit to the barkeep, "Hey Barkeep, get me one of those Stolie on the rocks will you?" Ahhhhhh, Stolie on the rocks.  And then the music started back up. It was different than when it stopped. This music was not that of pH Balance, possibly not even of the same genre. But the transition was smooth nonetheless. The new band's name was Basement. The outfit consisted of China Flats on the feet (or Mary Janes), smokey gray honeycomb tights, olive drab long skirt, wool gray turtleneck, pumpkin tinted sweater, and an amber dome ring. Oh shit wait- that is what my outfit consisted of. The musical outfit that now embodied the stage was made up of a drummer, a percussionist, a bass player, a keyboardist, and a guitarist. From everything I had heard the band's lineup recently went through a tune up or two. My ears heard no such hints of new musicians trying to learn their way. No, in fact this band was tight. You know that bottle of ketchup I just couldn't get open because it was so damn tight, well Basement was even tighter than that. Of course, the bottle was not really all that tight, I pretended not to be able to open it up, just so you could feel needed. Now, I do not mean to give off the impression that Madeline Modeliste did not feel that the band Basement was tight. They most certainly were tight. However there was something more to them that just their tightness.  Everyone likes to group bands together now a days. Everyone likes to get all genre'd up. For the folks that need that kind of musical organizing I will say that Basement falls into the same genre as Sound Tribe Sector Nine and the Disco Biscuits, the trance-rock genre if you will. However Basement does indeed have their own niche within this group of talented musicians. The boys in Basement never feel like a jam or a part of a song should last for too too long. Parts in their songs seem to know just how long to walk till it's time to make that right hand turn. Their music will build and ease till the new direction they move seems exactly right. But a listener shouldn't get too comfortable because before they realize it, the pulsating sound might make a veer left (which I like to call a "Sleft"). The guitar work spins web after colorful web in this new direction before the song takes a veer right (which I like to call a "Slight") and will rage with the rest of the musical make up towards the ever clear and victorious end.  Basement's music had this here, "retired" hippie chick grooving. The thing I really dug about this band was that there wasn't much fluff. They didn't spend all that much time on the happy, sappy parts of their songs. Basement's music most certainly spent serious moments on the darker side. The thing that really took to me, however was, how balanced the band was when dealing with any particular feeling. They never spent too much time or not enough time on one section. I call it trance rock for the short attention span.  The night ended, but the weekend was just starting. Although I never made it to the Engine Room that Thursday night, I was out again on this Saturday night, and I was feeling like tonight would be the night that I would be able to get a drink over there. That all changed when a friend dragged me into the Georgia Theater. The band on the stage was apparently calling themselves "Umphrey's McGee". I looked in and it smelled like my past, so I tried to continue walking on, but my friend would not let me go on. She paid for my ticket and all.  "Give them a chance Madeline, they are fun." My friend assured me.  And then I thought to myself "self" I thought, "just the other night, you went out and saw some music that you thought you would not dig, but guess what Mad Mode? You did, you did dig it, so go in open minded..."  Wise words from a brilliant mind, (my own). Now, going into the dark dank theatre of Georgia, I walked with hope of witnessing another memorable night of music. The band started, and my optimism shrank. The band played it's own style of rock and roll. But not the kind I have fallen in love with. Not the dirty Athens, leave a little feedback for the kids, kind of rock and roll. This here Umphrey's McGee was clean. Clean transitions, squeaky-clean guitar licks, clean rhythms.  "This building is too dirty to be playing this music!!" I screamed, but to no avail, the kids from the mid-west just kept on playing. And I am glad they did, because there were parts I began to like. Like a part of the song "All In Time." I really dug a part of this song. It got a bit dirty. The kind of dirty rock and roll that Athens likes. But just when it was getting deep into the dirtiness, it stopped. And it was then that I found one of my major problems with this band. They seem to change parts too much for my liking. As soon as I understand a part, they change it. And I know what a lot of you are thinking right now, "But Madeline, no more than seven paragraphs earlier you stated how you like Basement because they never stay in one part for too long."  This is true, I did state something like that, but that is because Basement's music did not force their way anywhere. They moved where the music wanted to go. Umphrey's McGee forces it's way into musical room after musical room without the slightest warning. Basement's turns were that of 90 degrees or 45 degrees or even slighter. Umphrey's McGee takes turns of 770 degrees or even 890 degrees. No knock. No phone call, no nothing. All of a sudden here they are.  Not to take anything away from UM, they can play their music making objects, and most in the crowd seemed to be having the time of their life. The dueling guitar work, at times, impressed the hard to be impressed. But for me, Ms. Madeline Modeliste, seven songs, was three too many. It was time for me to finally get that drink at the Engine Room.  Ahhh, Stolie on the rocks!!!!  On an Athens Scale of Five:  pH Balance got four. Not too shabby for a band from the other side of 316. They get four of the coolest threads from Uncle Albert's thrift shop.  Basement also gets a four. But Basement's four is four fatty burrito's from the Clayton St. burrito joint Barberito's. These four, however, were the four free burrito's the owner of Barberito's; Downing gave out rewarding the winners of the "find me at the S.E.C. championship game and get a free burrito contest."  And Umphrey's McGee gets two and a half. Not all that bad for a band from so far away. Two tickets to the upcoming North Carolina Phish shows, and the half empty glass of water I obviously was starring at while writing their review.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I had met Josh Moore on a couple of occasions. This was not the first. This was, however, our first conversation on sober ground, during the day, while most in the live music scene sleep.  We met outside his downtown apartment, and he quickly took me up to where his living quarters and office are. He wanted the interview to take place in his room (not trying to make him sound like a sleaze ball, 'cause his room is also his office). But Mad Mode preferred for the interview to take place in the living room. He had three large paintings on his walls, one done by local artist Catherine Zelski, one other by local artist/musician Tim Conley (of the Fuzzy Sprouts), and the final painting was a Scramble Campbell painting of String Cheese Incident.      MM: Hi Josh, haven’t seen you since the time you gave me NRBQ’s leftover beer, trying to pick me up. How have you been since? Has that trick been working for you lately?   JM: Um, nice first question Mad. Uh, no, that trick hasn’t worked. I wasn’t trying to pick you up. I just didn’t feel like lugging all those leftover beers up to my apartment.   MM: Sure, sure, save the confessional for the father. You and I both know what was going on in your head that night: give the young lady all this beer; she’ll surely be impressed. Ain’t happening with me.   JM: I’m not saying your not good looking, but I wasn’t trying to-   MM: Yeah, yeah, yeah... anyway, I wanted to start off by getting some basic background on you Josh Moore, founder, owner, and everyday operation manager of JoMo Entertainment (the active Athens and Atlanta, GA music promotion company). Where did you grow up?   JM: I grew up in Richmond, VA.   MM: At what point in your life, did live music become an interest to you?   JM: Probably somewhere around like sixteen, seventeen years old... started to go see shows in Richmond, Flood Zone.   MM: What’s that?   JM: It’s a venue. It’s called the Flood Zone, similar to the Georgia Theater.   MM: What kind of bands did you see there?   JM: Started off, mostly seeing Dave Matthews Band, then we got into a lot of the bands that were opening up for Dave, and Dave was playing with in other places. So that style of music, kind of the college rock you know, I’d kind of say it was the Aware compilation music. These bands were on these Aware compilations that we were really into.   MM: When did you arrive in Athens?   JM: I came down here for college when I was eighteen years old.   MM: And what brought you down here for college? You are about two years younger than me; I mean four years younger than me. So you arrived in '95. There were some good bands playing round here then.   JM: Damn Madeline. You’re 29? You look really, really good for 29.   MM: I know. Anyway, back to the question.   JM: Yeah, there was some great music here then. When I came to visit, there was so much music going on, and you know, this frat was trying to take me to these parties and stuff, and I just wanted to go see music. I came to visit before I decided to go here, and there was just so much music here, you know, I just had to go to school here. A lot of my favorite bands were from here, like Allgood, and Widespread Panic, Aquarium Rescue Unit, Catfish Jenkins, bands like that.   MM: How’d you get yourself into the business?   JM: My cousin John Moore was friends with a couple people down here in Athens that worked with bands. They were booking agents, and you know I think one time when I went home for Thanksgiving, my cousin John was like, "You gotta call my friends Mike and Nadia, they have a company called Madison House." And I called them, and started working for them.  My cousin was friends with these cats, so I went and met with them, and you know we just hit it off great. Me and the guy Mike [Luba] had a lot in common, he was from Virginia Beach, and was into a lot of the same bands, and Nadia was just super cool. And we hit it off the first time we met.   MM: Madison house, they’re the ones that manage String Cheese Incident, and&hellip;   JM: Yeah, at the time they were booking String Cheese Incident, Galactic, Jazz Mandolin Project, Belizbeha, Guster, Col. Bruce Hampton, a few other bands, they were just booking agents at that point. That was about my sophomore year, I started interning for them.   MM: How’d you develop that into having your own business?   JM: I worked for them a stupid amount of time. Just a like a crazy amount I put in there.   MM: A stupid amount?   JM: Not stupid as in it was a bad idea, as in a lot of time I spent there, probably 40 hours a week, if not more - for free - just kind of hanging around Luba and Nadia and getting to know them, just seeing how they do business and how they work, and they decided to move to Colorado once String Cheese Incident got big. They were going to start managing them, and they wanted to be based out of Boulder to be with the band. I was still in school at the time, so I took what I had been learning through working for them, which was basically selling bands to buyers, like what I do now. So I spoke to a lot of buyers, and when they moved I was like, I’m gonna try to do this until I’m done with school, and then when I am done with school I’ll move out there. But that didn’t happen.   MM: So you got so wound up in everything down here?   JM: Yeah, I enjoyed this.   MM: I notice that a good bit of the talent you bring into town could be considered "jambands." You don’t need Mad Modeliste to tell you this, but the three biggest groups of these kinds of fans are Deadheads, Phishheads and Spreadfreaks. At any time in your life would you consider yourself a Deadhead?   JM: Um, no I never considered myself a Deadhead, I was a huge fan of the Grateful Dead when I was in high school, but I was probably too young to like drop what I was doing to go to a bunch of Dead shows. I did go to a lot, but I only missed school maybe two or three times for Dead shows.   MM: How 'bout Phishhead?   JM: I definitely did a Phish tour once or twice in my day, like every show on a tour, but I wouldn’t consider myself a Phishhead, I definitely went through a hippie stage. There was a point in my life where I considered myself a hippie. And I think that worked into the Phishhead stage.   MM: So if you broke your knee, you would have gone on Phish tour anyway?   JM: Yeah, I probably would have done something like that. Probably would have sacrificed a leg for a Phish show.   MM: What about Widespread Panic?   JM: Um, same thing, I wouldn’t consider myself a Spreadhead, but I’m sure there were plenty of people that would have considered me one. Spent a lot of time and money at shows.   MM: Still in debt to Widespread, huh?   JM: Yeah I’m still into everything. That’s where my roots are.   MM: Of all the artists you booked, which left you with the most interesting experiences?   JM: Oh, Lee "Scratch" Perry, definitely, and then probably Biz Markie also.   MM: Why Lee Scratch Perry? What were the kinds of things that went on?   JM: Oh God, That was just like a freak show. So much weird stuff happened. You know when I was hanging out with him, I had to pick him up from the airport and drove him around all day, and the day of the show, and the next day I drove him back to the airport. And hung out with him during the day, it’s just, in that time period, probably twenty-four hours; I saw some of the weirdest stuff that if I told you, you wouldn’t believe me.   MM: Now you have to tell us.   JM: Um, I mean he asked me to take him to the grocery store, at one point, and I did, and he walks in, and got maybe 40 bottles of baby oil. He’s a little guy, and he was just like carrying around these... I mean, just more baby oil than you could possibly imagine ever needing. I mean, enough to fill a grocery cart, but he was carrying it around. And I have no idea what he was going to do with it, but he went in there with that mission to buy it.   MM: Tell us more Lee Scratch Perry stories.   JM: I had him in the back of my car. And I started smelling some fumes or something, and I turn around, and he’s just super gluing stuff all over his body, all over his face and clothes, and shoes, everything from CDs to quarters, you know, anything he could find he was gluing all over himself, dollar bills...   MM: What about Biz Markie?   JM: Um, Biz Markie, I put him in a little... you know, less-than-five-star hotel, if you want to say, and he had a limo pick him up from the airport and drive him to this hotel, and when he got to the hotel it wasn’t good enough for him, so he called me up on my cell phone and was like, "You need to come get me, I’m not staying here." So I went and picked him up, and I was on my way to take him to another hotel, he was like, "I’m hungry, can you take me to Red Lobster?" So I said sure, and I walk in, and of course all the waitresses knew him, they were all hugging him and everyone was yelling, "We love the Biz, everybody loves the Biz."   MM: I get that treatment at a few Athenian places I dine at.   JM: That I don’t doubt. Anyway, Biz sits down and he orders enough food for easily twenty people. You know, just lobsters and crab legs, and fried shrimp and seafood platters, and salads and biscuits and Cokes. I mean just more food, like if you and I went out with our fifteen closest friends we wouldn’t order that much food.   MM: I already told you no to a dinner date. And now you are trying to bring our friends in on the date that will never happen to begin with?   JM: Sorry Mad, thought that might work. Anyway, the Biz ate all that food by himself, I mean appetizers, calamari, everything, and then I took him to the mall, he wanted to go to the mall, I don’t remember how many pairs of shoes he bought, but a bunch.   MM: Was this all on your account? Was this all JoMo’s?   JM: I bought him the food at Red Lobster. I think they gave him a good deal 'cause it was Biz Markie, and they were having as much fun watching him eat it as I was. The shoes and stuff, and everything he bought at the mall, he bought on his own.   MM: Damn boy. Can’t even buy the Biz a pair of shoes? When I come back to town for my tour you better damn well be buying me shoes.   JM: Well, duh. Of course for you, Madeline.   MM: Just making sure. All right, switching modes from Mad Mode’s shoes to people that don’t wear no shoes. Having worked with SCI and Keller Williams, now I know why they have made references to you during some songs at shows in Athens. What was your reaction when you realized that SCI was singing; "JoMo rising" instead of "MoJo rising"?   JM: Um, I was psyched, it was great. That show itself was definitely one of the highlights of my career so far, just because we put in a lot of time decorating and just thinking of special stuff to do.   MM: Was it Halloween?   JM: No, it was just a regular show at the Georgia Theatre.   MM: Do you remember the date or the year?   JM: No, I don’t remember, but I remember they were playing big venues everywhere else, I think the next two nights they were doing two nights at The Tabernacle, which were sold out. And they kind of did this as a favor. You know, put in this little show, so we put a lot of money, time and ideas into it. And that was just a great way to end the night. And still every day, not everyday, but all the time, people are bringing me tapes of it, saying, "Have you heard this? JoMo rising."   MM: Which brings me to another question. Do you listen often to your shows? Live recordings of your shows? Or how often do you get around to listening to them?   JM: No, I usually don’t, I like to listen to new stuff. I try to always listen, I enjoy listening to stuff I never heard before, so...   MM: And back to that other thing with Keller. When he replaced Kyle’s name with your name on Tenacious D's... what’s the name of that song?   JM: [laughs] "With Karate I’ll Kick Your Ass." That was awesome.   MM: Yeah, so what was your reaction to that?   JM: I thought that was funny, 'cause I am a huge Tenacious D fan.   At this point in the interview, Josh had incoming phone calls, some of which his intern could not handle by himself, so the interview went on pause while Josh Moore became JoMo, and worked his promoting magic on the phone. Given this time, one would think that the first couple questions that I would ask when he got back would be the wisest, most thought-out, deep questions of the whole interview. Instead, I went dumb on him.    MM: What was the dumbest thing you saw someone do at one of your shows?   JM: Shit, that’s tough, let me think for a second... there have been so many dumb things; I am kind of stumped right now. Um, I saw this guy try to sneak in bottles of beer... Dumbest thing? I mean I’m having trouble thinking of one particular dumb thing. There are always so many people insanely drunk acting dumb, but um, I have people that always try to tell me that they work with the band or they are the tour manager, always trying to get backstage or get in for free.   MM: When they are obviously not, because you know the tour manager?   JM: Yeah.   MM: The smartest thing that anyone’s ever done?   JM: [long pause]   MM: Get there early to get good balcony seats?   JM: It’s definitely smart to get there early, but to me the smartest thing to do is to buy your tickets in advance, but that’s just me.   MM: Obviously, not all your shows are for hippies; you also have shows for country music folks, hip-hop heads and townies. For the sake of the folks that don’t live in Athens, would you describe what "townie" means?   JM: Um, a "townie" is someone who has lived in Athens for a long time, and doesn’t go to school here, and uh... there’s a lot of stereotypes that go with that. But, you know Madeline; you're somewhat of a townie yourself.   MM: Do you want this interview to be over!? I will just get up and leave if you don’t watch yourself. I am not a townie; I am a unique individual that happens to be drop dead Go-jess. I fall into no category but my own. I do hang with townies though.   JM: You know townies are snobs when it comes to music, stereotypically speaking.   MM: Yes, they like what’s not popular. Except, to their own circle in town.   JM: A mutual friend of ours used to say that townies dress in anything that is old school, is that still true?   MM: Yeah, I mean, they're not shopping at the Gap, they definitely go to vintage clothing stores and places like that. I recently went to a Three Dog Night show of yours in Atlanta, and --   JM: That wasn’t my show.   MM: Yeah, it was.   JM: No, I think I would know if it was my show or not.   At this point, Josh is becoming very difficult.   JM: Just because you are whispering into your recorder doesn’t mean I can’t hear you. I am not being difficult; I am simply telling you that I never booked a Three Dog Night show before in my life.   MM: Fine. Next question: what are some of your favorite non-jamband shows that you’ve had?   JM: Wilco last year was a highlight for me... working with The Strokes, right before they broke, was a highlight. Iggy Pop - legendary. That was fun. Would you consider David Byrne a jamband?   MM: No.   JM: Yeah, David Byrne was one of my favorite shows. Steve Earle last year was one of my favorite shows. I guess as far as the jamband connotation goes with JoMo, I started off working with jambands, because most of the bands I started off with were Madison House bands, which were jambands, and that’s were my roots lie. But today I don’t listen to jambands. I still like it, and I don’t mind it, but my tastes have grown more, I’m just kind of pigeonholed in some jamband category, but we do a lot of other stuff.   MM: You know this is going to be on JamBase, and you, I, and the Georgia Theater were all nominated for "best of."   JM: Yeah.   MM: You finished second in the promoting category, Georgia Theatre finished first as far as venue. How the hell did I only finish fifth?   JM: I don’t think people understand your style of writing. You know, you come off as very aggressive, but you’re really sweet inside. You just have that townie shell on the outside.   MM: That is very sweet. But no Josh, for the fourth time today, I will not go out with you. Best show that you put on with the smallest turnout?   JM: That is a good one. There’s been a few... we did this show with a group called Club D'Elf, which was basically an all-star band of avant-garde jazz players.   MM: Who was that? I mean I of course know, but for those poor souls out there that don’t?   JM: John Medeski, and just a bunch of other serious cats, and it only did like 150, 200 people at the most. Did a group called the Warlocks, which is a band I have been listening to a lot lately, kind of like Jesus is Mary Jane, at Caledonia, we might have had twenty or thirty people there. There’s been a bunch of really good shows that have had low turnouts.   MM: Now I am going to ask you about some local bands and I want you to give us your thoughts on them. Squat?   JM: I love squat, I’ve loved them since I was in college. One of the first bands I got into down in Athens.   MM: Dubconscious?   JM: They’re great, definitely, the hottest reggae band going. I’d say probably in the country right now.   MM: R.E.M?   JM: I was never an R.E.M. fan until I saw them at the Georgia Theatre do this special thing, and have been a huge fan since.   MM: Drive-By Truckers?   JM: They’re one of my favorite bands on the planet.   MM: Basement?   JM: Basement is awesome. I love the style of music they are playing, their influences are basically the same stuff I listen to, so I am a huge fan of Basement.   MM: pH Balance?   JM: I haven’t seen pH balance, but I have their record, it’s really good.   MM: Claire Campbell?   JM: Um, Claire Campbell, I have only seen once and I didn’t give her my full attention.   MM: You had her open up for...   JM: Yeah...   MM: Who was it?   JM: I can’t remember...   MM: It was that bald guy...   JM: Freedy Johnston.   MM: Yeah.   JM: She was great, but I didn’t give her my full attention so I can’t give you...   MM: Kevn Kinney?   JM: I love Kevn; He just has one of those classic voices that I will always love. I was a huge Drivin n Cryin fan. He’s just a great songwriter.   MM: Triple X hard drive?   JM: I think I stumbled into one of their shows, drunk, one night, and I was in the front row, like, fist in the air, rocking, so I’d have to say I enjoyed it. From what I remember.   MM: The Glands?   JM: That band should be huge. You probably love them, huh, Mad?   MM: Oh, for sure. Is it true that Ross Shapiro [of The Glands] was a fraternity brother of yours?   JM: Yes, he’s about eighteen years older, but yeah, I guess we’re considered brothers.   MM: He owns School Kids (local record store)?   JM: He manages School Kids, funny guy. A couple of bands in the jamband circuit are covering his songs.   MM: Oh yeah, who?   JM: RANA. They play a Glands song, “Living Was Easy.”   MM: Cool, and what’s the other band that covers their songs?   JM: Ehh, no, just that one [laughs].   MM: What are your favorite upcoming bands? Not necessarily local, just in general.   JM: I really like this band that is playing in two weeks here, called Interpole. Um, the Ravennettes are opening for them, and I have been listening to them a lot. Give me second, upcoming bands? Huh? I listen to so much new music I don’t know.   MM: Craziest thing that you’ve done to get a gig?   JM: This doesn’t sound that crazy, but I have offered way too much money to get gigs, on many occasions.   MM: That’s probably something that your audiences don’t realize when they fork out the money, that you have to put up a certain amount, and there are many shows that you probably lose money.   JM: Many shows. More than many.   MM: What’s “five in five with Willie Nelson” mean?   JM: Um, we had five cups of coffee and five conversations.   MM: That’s a lie.   JM: That’s not a lie.   MM: If it could mean something else, what would it mean? All right, you’re not budging.   JM: I burned five doobs with Willie Nelson.   MM: Huh?   JM: Burned five doobs with Willie Nelson in about five minutes on his tour bus, the red headed stranger.   MM: First thing off the top of your head when I name these things: Boubacar Traoure?   JM: [Jaw dropping...]   MM: John Bell?   JM: Athens.   MM: Barberito’s?   JM: Crack.   MM: Georgia Bar?   JM: Can I bypass that question?   MM: Yeah. Col. Bruce Hampton?   JM: Granddaddy.   MM: Kyle Pilgrim?   JM: My mentor.   MM: The fact that Firehouse is better than High Hat ever was?   JM: Bullshit.   MM: Jimmy Herring?   JM: The man.   MM: Willie the cop?   JM: Nice man, very nice man. He is... he’s written me many citations, but he’s got a few things on me which he could use and hasn’t.   MM: If you weren’t a music promoter what would you be doing?   JM: I’d like to drive the Zamboni for an NHL team.   MM: If you go out to a random show of an artist that completely blows you away, will you go ahead and try to book right way? Or if they have no reputation do you have to wait it out?   JM: No, I’ll go call their agent the next day. I’ve booked bands based on their live show. If I go see a band and enjoy it, I’ll try to book ‘em.   MM: Why a JoMo show?   JM: Because we care about each one of our shows, and make sure that each one is just run perfectly, and everything about it is done right.   MM: Who in the industry has influenced you the most?   JM: Definitely Mike Luba, of the people I know. Of the people I don’t know, there’s Bill Graham and Corin Capshaw.   MM: Corin Capshaw?   JM: Yeah, he manages Dave Mathews Band, and does a bunch of other stuff. But Mike Luba of anyone I know is a big influence. My cousin John Moore is a big influence.   MM: Strangest request an artist has made other than getting fifty things of baby oil?   JM: Papa Roach made us get him remote control cars. I don’t know what that was for.   MM: It was part of the contract?   JM: Yeah. You know, I think some of the bands ask for things just to see if we will do it. Like Guster will ask for a live goldfish, and bands ask for socks all the time, which comes off as being weird. But it’s actually quite a good request, because if you are on the road for a while, your socks start to get pretty nasty, to get a new pair of socks every night is probably a good thing.   MM: Upcoming stuff that you haven’t released yet?   JM: I'm working on some really cool stuff, and I’ll probably jinx it by saying it, because it’s not done, but I promised you Mad. I’m working on a show right now: a co-bill with Ween and Les Claypool at the Classic Center. That would be May 1st, which is the last day of school. So that’d be like the end of the year blowout. I’m working on a show for the Flaming Lips. Working on a show with the ******* at the ********. [Josh asked us to leave this out because it wound up not going through.]   MM: When’s that?   JM: April 18th. Working on a Badly Drawn Boy show, really cool artist from London, working on two nights of Nickel Creek at the Georgia Theatre. Working on a Funky Meters show at the Variety Playhouse. And you know we got a couple other big ventures in the works. Working on a cruise ship, festival cruise ship thing. Should be finalizing the details on that pretty soon. And the deal with that is we are gonna charter a cruise ship and take about ten bands out on it, and sail to a couple of different islands. Gonna be a festival on a boat, and now we are looking at bringing in a bigger name act to lay on one of the islands.   MM: Would it be a couple nights? Would you sleep on the boat?   JM: Yes, it’ll have cabins for folks to sleep.   MM: Can you preview any of the artists that will be on that boat fest?   JM: No, 'cause we haven’t started booking it yet, but to give you an idea, what we are working, what we are looking at bands like the North Mississippi Allstars, Robert Randolph, Karl Denson, Soulive, Keller, MMW, moe., those kinds of bands. It’s gonna be a jambands cruise.   MM: And what would be the bigger name band you’re trying to find?   JM: The band we’re hoping to fly in is ***** ****** ***** [Josh wanted us to hold this back], and have them play on an island in Mexico. We’ll fly them in, and every one will be on the boat, and take them to an island one day, and get off the boat and have the full production set up.   MM: Anything else? What do you want America to know?   JM: We try to keep our ticket prices low.   As I was leaving Josh pumped up the volume to his stereo and his favorite song was blaring out of his speakers: Don Henley’s "New York Minute."   That is not true.   MM: The interview is over Josh.   JM: I don’t care if it is or it isn’t. "New York Minute" is not my favorite tune, and I am not playing it on my speakers right now. Don’t print that.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings from Athens. Hundreds and hundreds of emails flood my inbox after each one of my pieces I write for this publication. Now, while most of them are praising me, asking for pictures, asking for dates, or are junk mail, there have been a few from music fans who think I have it plain wrong. To those folks all I have to say is: I do not have it wrong. You do. My opinions are so very true that they almost lose all semblance of being an opinion and kind of just jump right in step with fact. So don’t any of you dare question my authority and voice in this music world. All right? Good. Now that I have that off my back (which some say is the sexiest part of my body; I don’t know though, that is a tough tough question), time to review some music.  Went and saw Patterson Hood play a solo gig the other night. No, not that Patterson Hood, not the minor league ball player who is famous for striking out in his first 72 home plate appearances. I am talking about Patterson Hood: the rambunctious, story telling front man of the Athens-based band Drive-By Truckers. It wasn’t actually a solo gig; it was listed as Patterson Hood vs. Don Chambers. No, not that Don Chambers, not the former rightwing conservative Hawaiian delegate turned hot air balloon daredevil. I am talking about Don Chambers the cool, heavy guitar playing local rock star who digs playing loud. These were the two men that were pinned against each other in a bill labeled as "Patterson Hood vs. Don Chambers."  Who was going to win? How would the point system be set up? And most importantly, who was refereeing? Nah, just kidding. There was no battle, just two friends up on stage trading off songs. The drummer from the Truckers sat behind them playing a tiny little drum kit, while the two in front played some good ole southern guitars.  "Intimate" is how some would describe the Flicker Theater. Not Mad Mode though. She, who is I, would describe it as the hidden away living room that makes a closet feel large. It is so small that the amount of soul that the String Cheese Incident has produced in its entire career could easily fit in the room. So small, it is, that it makes the Caledonia seem big. It is so small that Dave Schools couldn’t even fit in the room.  Shortly after the show started, the single microphone (that Chambers and Hood had been passing back and forth between songs) was working on a "when I want to" basis. The men on stage decided to do away with the mic and just sing loud, without any form of amplification. Patterson told a story that I will never forget about a childhood friend who snorted too much glue. (A taper taped it - not on tape - or perhaps on tape. I am not sure but at any rate, get this tape to hear this story.) The story wound up covering the gospel subject. Which led Don Chambers into playing a gospel song. The man played and sang with a sense of feeling I don’t think I have seen before. He sang and played with passion, while remaining in his cool stance. He came off as such a cool dude, he probably wouldn’t produce a drop of sweat in a summertime Mississippi kitchen. His voice was somewhat sheik while his guitar was loud and rugged.  When it was Patterson's turn he’d tell a story and then burst into the song about that story, which suddenly had much more meaning. He finished off the night with "Sink Hole" (which will be on the new Drive-By Truckers album). "Sink Hole" is typical of a Patterson song: gritty, twangy, real and fun. The kind of song that makes you down your drink, order another one, down that one and order a round for everyone sitting at the bar. His music makes you feel good about going out and getting hammered.  The crowd was an atypical Athens crowd. Spring break let all the kiddies go home to their mommies and daddies, or make arses of themselves in Panama City. What was left was a crowd who came to hear some good ole home brewed music. There was only one boy in the entire venue that wouldn't leave me alone. And he still won't leave me alone! (Chauncey, stop bothering me. Yes I know I am beautiful, yes I know I am hipper than any girl you have ever met, I have heard it all before! Leave me alone!)  While folks pealed out of the Flicker into the thick dropping rain pellets, I made my way up on yonder to a lil' hole in the wall bar that shall remain nameless, out of respect. The band that played there, to put it nicely, sucked. To put it bluntly: couldn’t carry a tune if it was put in a nice carrying case with handles and all. They called themselves "Pittt Stopp," but I called them "Pleaseee Stopp." This local arrangement consisted of two guitar players (just figuring out how to do bar chords), a bass player with smaller fingers than me, and a very beginner drummer. They attempted to cover the Grateful Dead's "Eyes of the World," but it turned out sounding like “Who Let the Dogs Out.” I kid you not. The terrible thing about it was that there were actually people dancing around, like it was good or something.  So my great night of music turned very sour, very quickly. But oh well.  Till next time, Madeline Modeliste  On an Athens Scale of 5, the Patterson Hood vs. Don Chambers show got a 3.89: three Cubano sandwiches from the tasty Cuban food joint, Caliente Cab; and the 89 cents that I found in JoMo’s couch while I interviewed him.  Pittt Stopp got a one. Only because they are from Athens, and only because I have a heart. They get one free music lesson each from anyone that'll give it to them. Even though they need much much more.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My first review outside Athens took me all the way to a place called Atlanta, GA. I arrived at the Music Midtown festival Friday afternoon wearing my “vixen vamp” outfit, which consisted of a black skirt with exposed white stitching at the seams, and a matching-exposed white stitching-tank top, black bra ($100 retail-$10 new on ebay) straps exposed. The first musical act I wished to see was Les Claypool's Frog Brigade. The Frog Brigade brought their unique style of electrified quirkiness. You take away all the lyrics, all the costumes, all the physical actions and there is still something humorous about this band. The actual music kind of made a smirk come across my face. Ain’t no Steven Wright monotone comedy either. Claypool’s funny sound had muscles to it. At one point in his set, he busted out a skinny funny looking bass; unfortunately for our ears the gag didn’t go. This bass seemed to give Les electrical shocks due to the rain that had just begun. Oh well. I took it as a sign to see what else was out there. Getting a little groove in my step, I maneuvered my way through the thousands all the way to the complete opposite side of the festival grounds.  I arrived at the Fox 5 stage for the very end of Particle’s set. Particle brought their high energy “space porn.” At least that is what they call it. I however didn’t see any lunar licking, nor asteroid aching, not even a simple star tickle. But I may have heard it. The particle boys got an extra wave of energy (as if they needed it) from the oncoming storm. Lightning, dancing rain drops, and roller coaster gusts of wind came cruising from the back side of the stage and through to the other side where the crowd hopped on for the ride. The combination of the music and weather had everyone in the crowd getting down. And up again. And then back down. 'Cause they were dancing, you know? So, what I saw of Particle was good. They most certainly have found a spot for themselves in what the kids seem to be calling the "trance-rock" genre.  Next up: a DJ and then The Disco Biscuits. Unfortunately the woman upstairs wasn’t having any of it. She threw down rain pellets by the gazillions. Flashed her flashlight, and got thunderous strike after thunderous strike in her revamped bowling alley (it is now a rock-n-roll bowling alley). Two yellow and white tents were left empty. No one really knows what they were originally for. Now they made a perfect spot for keeping dry. Between the two tents, maybe 100 of us stayed rain free. Most of the other folks left the festival. The rain did not let up. Sometime around one or two hours later, the group I was with decided to leave. They said they got word that the festival was going to be cancelled for the night. I walked my friends to the gate to see what the deal was. After realizing that no one knew, I said my goodbyes and headed back to the tent (solo- and drenched). When I got back, the same folks were in the tent, but they told me that just a minute before they all had moved the tent from it’s current location on the side about row 50 to 10th row center. All this happened, and the tent was brought back to its original location in the short time I was gone. I didn’t believe it, but in a few minutes I would find out that they weren’t lying. It was about two hours into the delay when the brilliant folks in my tent decided to once again pick up our rain shelter and transport it to a prime location for The Biscuits. I walked in the now mobile tent to its destination 10th row center. I walked out when the tent again became stationary, only to find the rain had stopped. Security took the rain shelter back to its proper location just in time for The Biscuits to take the stage.  Brownie waiting for the rain to stop.  From rain shelter to note shredder. Yes the man they call, “Barber,” big hair, big guitar and all came out shredding. The Biscuits exploited the crowd's freshly rested, and soggy bodies and caused 'em to dance. Shit, I don’t dance to just anything. A music must invite me to dance in polite form. It must ask Ms. Madeline Modeliste’s hand to the ballroom dance floor. Either that or it must grab my hand and run like hell. Biscuits did the latter, because before I realized what was going on my legs were bouncing (yes, those legs, the one’s you just couldn’t stop staring at). There is something eerie about The Disco Biscuits music but at the same time fun. Something that brings the dark side out but puts a sly grin on the face of that darkness. The Disco Biscuits' music is trick. To take a phrase from the Wolof Language in Africa - I “dig.” I dug and kept on digging until I had to leave. Physca-trona-delica with a human pulse that just won’t stop thumping. They thumped, and thumped, and thumped 'til they woke all of Music Midtown up.  I got my get, and got on. Bisco still pulsated through my adorable little body, but I still had to leave. You see, Bob Dylan supposedly had started his delayed set. And I thought that the B-52's (my personal all time favorite band) were on as well. Unfortunately for my stupid ass neither of them had started and I missed the end of The Biscuits set for nothing! By the way, no one else is allowed to call me a stupid ass. I am the only dumb ass allowed to do that.  So, I get down to where Dylan is supposed to be on. But it isn’t Dylan at all. It is something very, very different. Something bad. Something so mediocre I could almost puke. Finally I did. The music of Sheryl Crow actually made me puke. But I still looked good. Shit, I had just finished puking and boys were still hitting on me. At any rate, I had to leave the area, I had to get away from Sheryl Crow, and I mean far away.  I stumbled around, cheap beer in hand, and fell upon a gem. It was the end of Steve Winwood's set. Randall Bramblett was up on stage with Winwood’s band. And they were playing them some "Low Spark." Well actually not some "Low Spark," but all of "Low Spark." Crisp beautiful rendition, which led them into a great version of "Dear Mr. Fantasy," which led me out of that stage area and back to where Dylan was set to come on.  Dylan was Dylan is Dylan. Always has been Dylan (except for when he was Robert Zimmerman), and always will be Dylan (unless he marries me and becomes Mr. Bob Modeliste- huh?). Anyway, Dylan. It’s hard to critique someone of that statue so instead I’ll just throw the idea of a Mad Mode Dylan marriage out there.  Before Dylan could finish, Mad Mode got her Athens boogie back and wandered back to the stage where the B-52s had already been rocking for some time now. D’oh! Oh well. What I saw wasn’t much different than when I reviewed them here. Which is just complete 70’s swamp funk, groove child, ageless, timeless, goofiness with a groove. Talking Heads meets “Monster Mash.” Shit was on. All in the crowd felt that fun from the front of the stage. The Athens rockers apologized for the short set due to the rain delay, and then asked what we would like to hear "Love Shack" or "Rock Lobster." "Rock Lobster" pulled in about 98% of the vote and hasn’t made its way out of my head sense.  Unfortunately didn’t make it back to the Bisco stage to see Sound Tribe Sector 9. Couldn’t make the trance-rock trio: Particle, Biscuits, STS9. But Saturday will bring a bunch more musical madness.  On an Athens Scale of 5: Particle got two and half energy boosts to go in their smoothie at Planet Smoothie. Not that they need any.  Biscuits got 4. Four, well Biscuits and gravy from Weaver D’s. You know that shit is automatic. Automatic for Mad Mode’s readers.  Sheryl Crow gets 1 chunk.  Steve Winwood and his band gets a 3. Three tapioca balls at the bottom of my bubble tea from Infusia on Broad.  Bob Dylan gets.... Wait a minute, I ain’t ranking Dylan that’d be a disrespect to everything that is American.  And the B-52s get a perfect 5, which is virtually impossible to get out of the Athens area, but they did it any way. They get five bricks. Five of the bricks that make up the wall that holds in the roots of the tree that owns itself just a few blocks outside of Athens downtown area.  Day two of Music Midtown found Mad Modeliste dressed in jeans and a t-shirt, and sneaks (I didn’t feel like dressing up again in front of so many folks. The constant attention that young boys were giving me was getting annoying.)  I braved the rain again, to go hear Jorma Kaukonen. The handsome strong chested looking man sung and played his guitar with gentile qualities. His band was called Jorma Kaukonen and Blue Country. Though it only consisted of him and a mandolin player. I believe the mandolin player has a more traditional name, but for now we’ll just call him Blue Country. Jorma and Blue Country played quite a few blues tunes that had that ragtime feel. The funny blues as I like to call it. Nothing better than some ragtime in the rain. He put a hic-cup in your step without ever scaring you. In other words, the music stuck with me for a long time. It was a good pick me up, for a long day ahead.  The next band I caught was none other than Die Trying. And on this cloudy Saturday at Music Midtown, they did just that, they died trying. This band was bad. It was sort of like Papa Roach meets my toilet. Kind of like how Papa Roach must have sounded at their very first rehearsal. Unfortunately for everyone in the crowd, this Sacramento based outfit was not in their rehearsal space. In fact this must have been there very last show ever. I do not know this for fact, but by listening to it for ten minutes I am pretty sure that Die Trying will never get up on stage in front of people ever again. Or at least I hope not. I did get a cool Die Trying sticker out of the deal, though!  By the time my sorry ass made it to the Z93 stage, Leftover Salmon was already on their last song. It sounded good, but I wouldn’t dare critique a band on a one song performance. Two songs- of course, but one song- not a chance in die trying hell.  Next on stage came a three-piece jazz band. It consisted of a stand-up bass player, a piano and keyboards player, and a drummer/percussionist. Of the three I’d have to say the mad scientist look went to the keyboard player. Not just his look but what he was doing with them keys too. Weird, fun stuff. The bass player grooved, with thick aggressive thumping bass lines, and the drummer was all over the place, seeming never to repeat a drum cycle in the exact same way. They went by their last names, something like Martin, Woodley, and Manchester. Or even sometimes by just their initials MWM? Something like that, I just forgot. What? What’s that? I hear you yelling at your computer but can’t make out what you are saying. Oh. MMW. I got it now, Medeski Martin & Wood. I know, I know, I was just messing with you. MMW, stayed in their groove for most of their set, not really ever getting too abstract (which could very easily happen at an MMW show). Their music was so rich on this day. It was thick and rich and proved to everyone Medeski Martin & Wood's musical achievement as a unit.  At this point I tried to make my way over to the V103 stage, but the boys would not leave me alone. I swear. I’d take two steps and a boy would come up to me like he knew me. He knew he didn’t know me; he just wanted to stop me to see if he could win me over. Ha. Nice try, got going again, but then, d’oh, another boy, another pathetic pick up line. And another and another. I kid you not, my trek to the V103 stage should have taken me five to ten minutes, my beauty had other ideas. Better luck next time Justin, Jason, Tito, Balou, Christian, and Boonkie Boonkie.  Finally I escaped just in time for Morris Day and the Time. Oww! Man, these guys were the funk. Not that I thought they actually played the best funk music- but they reacted like they did. They most certainly put on an entertaining show.  On my lovely little way cross fest-grounds to see Tony Bennett, I heard a tad of Saliva. I won’t even comment on Saliva. In fact the word Saliva belongs nowhere in this review, so take it out, pretend I never said Saliva. This review is officially 100% Saliva free. By the way, I think they sucked.  But Tony Bennett most certainly did not suck. From the second he dared to take a lounge step forward on the same stage that The Disco Biscuits tore it up on, you knew it was on. Tony and his band played the first song with monitor speakers on only (if that), barely anyone in the crowd could hear anything. But Tony and the band just kept on. Kept on smiling and playing like there was no technical difficulties at all. Many in the crowd shouted, “Turn on the speakers, turn it up!” “Your mic's not on, Tony!” “Die Trying Sucked!” and so forth and so on. Maybe 40 of the thousands there could hear him. Yet the man still managed to give the crowd a sly lounge style “thank you” after a normal crowd clapping part of the song. But then, second song, we had full power. Now everyone got the real Tony Bennett. His voice, band, and entire show were quite impressive. The only trouble I had with his show was trying to stop my laughter. Great time.  Before it was over I went back eastside (actually I have no clue which direction it was) to see Crosby Stills & Nash. The legends just didn’t stop at this festival: Bob Dylan, the B-52s, Tony Bennett, Saliva, and now Crosby Stills & Nash. Mixing new with old, CSN won over the crowd early. Like early, not early in the set, but early in everyone’s lives. Of course CSN won everybody over, everyone loves their music. This being said, and knowing this going in, I’d like to say that they did sound like they sound, which is exactly how I wanted to hear them. Thumbs up to CSN, wait a minute I don’t do that stuff, I do the Athens scale of 5, and on an Athens scale of 5 CSN gets a 3 and a half.  Three shots of their choice at City Bar, and the half broken heart I had when I found out that Neil Young was not going to join 'em.  Jorma and Blue Country get 4. Four minutes with me out on the town!  Die Trying gets negative 10. Give me my goddamn wasted 10 minutes back.  MMW gets Three. Rebecca, Steven, and Olivia, my three ski-bum neighbors who won’t stop talking about the snow, “Powder, dude, it’s so sweet.” So friggin sweet, then move back to Colorado!  Morris Day and the time get a 2. Two cheesy chicken wraps from Gyro Wrap.  Tony Bennett gets 3. Three Marvelous Uptown Stuffed Filet’s from Harry Bissett’s New Orleans Cafe.  On the final day of the fest, I saw a few really interesting musical acts, but all of these could be put in a shopping cart and rolled down a dead end street “straight to hell” for all I care. Sure, the Drive-by Truckers kicked mine and all the other fuckers in the crowds’ arses with reckless abandon (but that is nothing new). And sure Drivin-n-Cryin put on a top shelf performance as they usually do. Susan Tedeschi impressed the shit out of me. Not literally, I waited for that 'til I got home. But all this didn’t matter. All these great Sunday performances were an after thought for me. It wasn’t that they weren’t excellent, because some of them most certainly were. In fact I ran into our friend Jomo down there, and he told me that the Truckers had him rocking harder than he’s ever rocked before. However, there was one band that caused me to forget all of this. This band forced me to forget all that happened that day, except for them.  It all started with a bottle of red. Then my trek down to the ole fest grounds. Got down to the stage just in time for Gomez. Now I had never seen this band perform before, but it didn't make a damn difference either way. These boys from Britain came out with the sun. They shone their tunes on me, in me, all over me. Their music at a glance sounded like good ole earthy roots rock and roll. But with voices like that, you know they are from England. Then as if trying to confuse me, they threw a modern twist to their old age rhythmic sounds. There is nothing more annoying to me than a band that’ll throw ten gamillion different kinds of music together in a show just to prove they can do it. Nothing more annoying than the look on their faces saying, “Ha, see I told you we can do it.” Now, let me assure you, this was not the case with Gomez. They do indeed, touch the tops of old and new rock and roll, but all there music is distinctively Gomez. In the likes of great roots rock and roll bands such as Widespread Panic or the Band, these guys continually pay homage to the depths of the genre while simultaneously creating their own unique sound.  Their dynamics of instrumentation also was something to write home about (or in my case, write JamBase about). The show started off with a drummer, a percussionist, a bass player, two guitarists, and a singer. However, by the second song in the set, the singer picked up his guitar. Then by the next song, one of the guitarists switched to keyboards. The dynamics of their voices also was Mad Mode approved. Lead vocal duties were pretty much tossed around between three of them. All of which were intriguing. Did I mention they jam? Well at least on songs that called for it. But not in the “lead guitar noodling to nowhere” kind of jams. There jams were focused, all energy flowing, unit jams.  I could already hear it, “Damn Mad, you had nothing bad at all to say about Gomez’ set.” Well that ain’t true at all. It became so hot, by the end of the set, that I almost passed out. But I kept my composure and did not sit down on the grass. I would have if I wanted to, but I knew that if I did there would be some boys near by that might lose any kind of control that they may have once had, by seeing me sitting or laying down on the grass. So I remained standing. Other than that, Gomez rocked the shit super hard.  On an Athens scale of 5, Gomez got a 5. What?! Huh?! But Mad, ain’t that impossible? Don’t you have to be from Athens, and in Athens to receive a perfect 5? Well, duh, yes. Of course, unless you are called Gomez. Five weeks of recording at John Keane's studio here in town.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Athens, GA's population goes on a diet over the summer. Shredding calories as a chunk of the college kids go home. This brings out the musicians. Many times playing in intimate settings that just couldn't happen during the school year. It gives a chance for musicians to play last second shows with sometimes no announcements at all. Well we don't want that to happen to Athfest. That is why I, the lovely and petite Madeline Modeliste, am here to let you know about a festival of art and music in the Classic City.  With over 150 bands and tickets for the full weekend at just $12, Athfest - which takes place this weekend, June 19 - 22 - has to be the best deal going around. That comes out to less than 9 cents a band. There are also one-day passes for just $7. Ticket prices go up just a tad if you get them at the show. I am not one to hold back any truth, so I would like you to know that within this group of 155 bands, many of them are drenched with talent. Sure some of 'em might suck, some of 'em might smell like a freshly rinsed garbage dumpster (which still stinks), and some of them might stink like that same dumpster before it had been rinsed. But that is why I am here, your guide on this Athens adventure, your goddess - the lovely and single (cause I want to be) Madeline Modeliste. I am here to guide you in the right way.  Bands on Friday include: The Ben Mize Band, Cracker, Ceiling Fan, Dodd Ferelle, Elem N.O.P., and Viktor And Andrej.  Saturday the lineup includes but is not limited to: David Barbe, The Tom Collins, the Cindy Wilson Band (of my beloved B-52s), the Dictatortots, Boo Ray, Leslie Helpert, and a Hope for a Golden Summer.  Sunday's lineup has all the following freaks plus some more: Calliope Fair and Don Chambers.  For you JamBase freaks, here are my personal recommendations are:  On Friday Night, you might want to check out Hobex. They bring a lot of energy in their tightly spun band. Mixing organic roots music with electric spastic jamming, their show should keep your body shifting. And at Midnight at Tasty World, Park Bench Trio will bring their southern rock outfit and most likely work the crowd into a frenzy.  Head on down to the Georgia Theater on Saturday night: Basement will take the stage first with their slyly psychedelic, trance rock, pulse setting, quick time changing, free funk thumping, introspective thought provoking, music for the folks that don't want to hear 15 minute songs. Also, that night Aqualove will be letting out their smell of Zappa/Meatloaf-like rock operatic show with visuals that might remind you of P-Funk and smells that might remind you of the Healing art center. Also that night at the Jowja Thee-A-tore is about the hottest band going 'round these days in these parts and other parts like these parts: Dubconscious brings its heavy roots-rock reggae and delicately adds elements of psyschedellia, world music, and dub to make a unique brand of music that one can only describe as Dubconsciousy.   And on Sunday on the main stage: Bloodkin comes on at 4:20 (dude) with their hard rocking, southern charmed, Athens to the bone-kind of tunes. Just after that is what could be the highlight of the fest, a reunion of sorts, for a band called the Fuzzy Sprouts. The Sprouts, who have now morphed somewhat into Aqualove, are famous for always keeping their audience off balance. I will say it is rock and roll, with a lot of emotion, but I will not dare to try to predict it any further than that. Fuzzy Sprouts are completely different every single show! And as if that is not enough, just after the Sprouts comes the Kevn Kinney Band. Kevn has a matchless brand of folk-rock. His band will play the sweetest and softest melody ever written, and then take it to the hard feeling, fist in the air throwing, drink a beer down and then another one before the song is over, kind of tunes that make everyone smile.  Music is not the only reason to come to Athens. Art will be displayed and sold right in the heart of downtown. So there's plenty of reason to come down to Athfest 2003, the music, the art, and to see the city in which the beauty herself, Mad Mode, lives in. I can already here the questions coming via email, to answer them very briefly, "I do not know quite yet, what I will be wearing at Athfest," and "No you can not buy me a beer." But do indeed have fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I was the first to break the news of JamCruise to the general public, in an interview with Josh Moore (found here), I figured I should be the one to write a preview for it. So, I headed on downtown to see if I could get some quotes from Athens’ very own music promoter. Josh didn’t want to talk about JamCruise, he had more exciting news.  So, it’s left up to me to tell you about the first jam festival at sea. I am the one who shall tell you how it takes off from Ft. Lauderdale and over a five day (January 6th-10th 2004) stretch lands in Key West, Nassau, Bahamas, and makes it’s way back. It’s up to me to tell you that Keller Williams, Galactic, Karl Denson's Tiny Universe, Peter Rowans Reggaebilly, Umphrey's McGee, Particle, The Disco Biscuits, Tishamingo, Ming & FS, Jerry Joseph, Bill Nershi and Lisa Oxnard, Dirty Dozen Brass Band, DJ Z-Trip will all be freaking their funk for all the freaks for five full days. The music will take place at various stages within the cruise ship, (including disco party below), and some on land at the three tropical locations the boat will dock.  JamCruise radio will be pumping the boats airwaves in the spare time that the various talented performers will not be performing (and maybe it will broadcast those performances as well- Who knows? Shoot I don’t know everything, almost everything, but not everything.)  The bad news: JamCruise sold out in 45 minutes. And now for the good news- the same exciting news I said that Josh was telling me earlier. And here it is, from Josh Moore: "We are pleased to announce JamCruise II (January 10th-14th) riding the same journey as the first one, but with a different lineup. This line-up includes Les Claypool's Frog Brigade, Col. Bruce Hampton, Yonder Mountain String Band, Rebirth Brass Band, The Disco Biscuits, Galactic, Donna the Buffalo, Hackensaw Boys, Michael Franti & Spearhead, RAQ, and many more."  "The folks that already have tickets to the first, will be given the first opportunity to purchase tickets to the second JamCruise, with a discount. Then, if there are any spots left, the people that are on the waiting list will be given a chance to purchase their tickets. If there are still any tickets left after that, they will go on sale to the public."  So there you have it, another breaking story out of Athens, from the striking beauty Mad Mode.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      	A friend of mine gave me Cast Iron Filter’s new live CD- “Live From the Highway”.  I decided to go in my room shut the door and take a listen.  Never before had I heard their music, so every note that blared from the speakers was new to me.  This was going to be good for the review, for it left me with not an ounce of pre-judgment on this band’s music. 	The first track, “Ricky Dunbar” quickly introduced me to Cast Iron Filter’s sound.  It was what I would call electric blue grass rock.  Banjo’s roared, drummers banged, bass strings bent.  But nothing grabbed me yet.  Nothing put their hands on the lovely Ms. Madeline Modeliste’s arms and shook me letting me know they were there.  The music was actually quickly turning me in the other direction.  The melancholy-boring-ass-Sunday afternoon-direction.  So I turned the music up.  At the end of almost every track you could hear some youngsters clapping and yelling with approval.  Just who are these youngsters?  And where can I find them? I bet they’d really get a kick out of watching my tomato plants grow.  Their energetic screams lead me to believe they were watching Dylan or John Bell or something, but no, the screams were mere screams for Cast Iron Filter.  (maybe there was stripping going on, or something else that didn’t translate onto CD, this I don’t know). 	The music still bored me.  I don’t like comparing musicians to other musicians.  I don’t like when it’s done and I vow to never do it ever!  Ever never Ever! (except right here).  They kind of remind me of Blowie and the hootfish- the great Hootie and the blowfish cover band that I just made up in my mind.  No for real, the do have a Hootie and the Blowfish sound.  So, if you like that sound, than you may very well just love this disc.  But in my opinion the music is so blah that it is ugly.  Now I must say, I am quite the attractive lady.  I am not just saying that, it is true.  But the music was so half assed, that when I took a look at myself in the mirror, it even made me look ugly.  	Now I am not trying to say that these musicians’s are bad.  They most certainly are not.  They do have skill, they know their instruments.  But the movie Men in Black had a cinematographer who knew his camera, a director who knew how to direct, qualified actors, but the movie still sucked.  Cast Iron Filter’s “Live From the Highway” translates in a similar way, good musicians, good thoughts about what they are doing, but no umph, where umph is needed.   On an Athens scale of Five this albumn gets a 1 and half.  One old Hootie and the blowfish five dollar ticket stub from an old Georgia theatre show, and a half eaten Burrito from Barberitto’s (those damn things are impossible to finish) 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Sure I shave my legs but that don’t mean I’m racing.  And yes it is true, that a local wide eyed street goer might go years before they see my bare legs.  That doesn’t mean I am lying to you- I do shave my legs&hellip; it’s just that I look so damn good in stockings.   Still don’t mean I’m racing.   Every spring there's a weekend in Athens, Ga. where cyclists take over our Classic City, or at least add a bit of extra entertainment.  Downtown Athens hosts The Twilight Criterium bike races.   The track runs through Clayton Street and Washington Street from North Avenue to Lumpkin Street.  But those bike races don’t begin till Saturday, so let’s not get ahead of ourselves.  For your purposes my weekend began on Thursday night,  I had a chance to interview the Col.- yes that Col. &mdash; Bruce Hampton &mdash; somewhat retired!    While some of the interview is too eye opening to share here, and other parts of the interview are just plain bedtime material, there are a couple spots I have been dying to share with you, and without further adieu, I give to you the parts of the interview with Col. Bruce Hampton retired, that are not too eye opening, not to yawn- much of snoozy bed time material-  Friday brought Madeline new lived energy and a brand new spanking outfit.  Please do make sure you are sitting while reading this part as I did have two men lose all control of themselves and actually fell to the ground at the sight of me and my outfit on Friday night&hellip; I wore&hellip;&hellip;   urlLink Jomo Entertainment  in association with the City of Athens, put on a concert event on a giant stage planted on Washington St. and College Avenue.  The stage faced the arches, putting a thousand or two or three ( shit I don’t know how many people, what did you expect me to go around counting each and everyone?  Yes?!  Fine, I’ll do it next time, I’ll go around counting the people instead of enjoying the music, does that make you happy?  Good, now please leave my article…no wait not all of you, just the smart ass mother Faulkner who likes to see me count ) dancing young folks on Washington Street in or out of beer gardens getting down to Leftover Salmon.  The Salmon put on their fast time, high spirited, bluegrass festivities to many pleased fans. Was Mad Mode pleased though?  I’d say yes, but I’d be partially lying. If I said no, I’d only be telling a third of the half truth- multiplied by some.  So which is it Mad?  Were they good?  Or same ole same ole?  Little bit from Column A and a my glass is half full, please top my off thank you. Truth of the matter is, Leftover Salmon still puts on a fun show after all these years. The guys can flat out pick, sing, dance, lift folks spirits with their jangley mountain sound. I normally love when bands mix up their sound, no matter how slightly it is.  I enjoy when the pace of a concert isn’t a flatlining experience, however there are some bands that I prefer to hear just what they do good, the whole time&hellip; Leftover Salmon is one of those bands.  I would prefer for the band to keep it on cruise control with the fast paced ditty’s as opposed to the almost boring slower songs they worked into their set.  But all in all, it was an all in all great time- all in all&hellip; It was, by the way, just the beginning, by the time we left what might have been the last out door big staged concert that took place on Washington Street since the  Panic in the Streets  (correct me if I’m wrong), there were many options on what to do next&hellip; Skydog Gypsy was playing at last call with&hellip; &hellip; &hellip; and new ___ _____ band was giving it their all at Tasty World, it was to the Theatre of Georgia (AkA the  urlLink Georgia Theatre  where we were heading).  On a flatbed truck in front of the theatre the Band Grogus was supposed to be playing but since the bike cops said &ldquo;no&rdquo; to the idea, they moved the act inside at bar level&hellip; Now to say Grogus is a staple in the Athens music scene is like saying A banana is a fruit- D’UH!  This band of spiritual smiling people play jazz, but it’s not just jhazz it’s world jazz, afro Cuban Jazz at times&hellip; I’d go on and on about their playing and about Karl Limburg who leads the band on standup bass and vocals&hellip; but why go on and on when I can sum it all up right here just like this:  Bad Ass . Seconds after Grogus has finished, the Reason: Biodynamic played their opening notes from the main stage.  The Reason, is very closely related to local reggae band Dubconcious.  Sort of like how the spinal tap movie is related to  A Mighty Wind .   Lots of the same players, same vibe- different project.  And just like  Spinal Tap  and  A Mighty Wind  have different directors so does the Reason Biodynamics and Dubconcious.  The Reason Biodynamics lead man is Jay Murphy, brother of Sound Tribe Sector Nine bassist Dave Murphy.  The younger Murphy plays drums and is quickly gaining respect round Athens as a rare talent at his instrument.  His band lays deep yet subtle grooves curving around one another like a heavy breathing, frisky, spooning couple.  Heavy dub influences can be spotted in the Reason Biodynamics music, perhaps even heavier than the dub spotted in Dubconcious’ music  The Reason continuously keeps fresh faces falling on and off the stage.  Gigantic female voices, horns, DJ scratches.  The worldly tunes have some serious organic and mechanical sounds working together at the same time.  As for Dubconcious they have certainly been gaining momentum in not just this town, but others in the southeast as well.   Fresh back off a two week tour (including an opening gig for Sound Tribe Sector Nine), the Dub-C came out sounding tighter than when they left us.   Dubconcious has a way of expressing their strong political minds in their honest non-threatning voice.  Saturday certainly started in a strikingly similar way to most of Mad Mode’s mornings- a cold shower, a Bilini tinnie, the brushings of my three cats’ hair, and a bicycle ride downtown.  However that was about all that wound up being typical on this Saturday.  To the take off of an important leg of the Tour de Georgia.  American hero and Madeline Modeliste arch villain Lance Armstrong was racing.  I did my very best heckling, called Lance almost every degrading phrase I know and or could come up with on a 10:30 Saturday morn. My favorite, was:  “Your teeth cold, Lance?  Why then, are they wearing a yellow blanket”   As noon rolled around, you know I had to keep an eye on the NFL draft to see where my boy Dunta Robinson would be selected. And with the 10th pick&mdash; the Houston Texans select the very first Athenian to be drafted in the first round of the NFL draft&mdash; Mr. Dunta Robinson!!!  With Twilight came the the fast, fluttered Downtown bike races.  Much fun with a Stolie on the rocks.  The races ended, but the music was just beginning.  So which would it be?  A) Southern Bitch at the Caledonia, B) the Fuzzy sprouts doing their abby road thing and their Fuzzy Sprouts thing down at the Theatre, or C) Barabra Cue and David Barbe at the 40 Watt.  Or I could do something very un-townie-like and go to a Frat party.  What do you say?  Shall we? We shall, and we did.  And we had ourselves a time.  I’m not much of a huge Frat party girl.  In fact I swore I would never attend one, absolutely never ever, ever never! Except for this one time, because the band that was playing was non other than the Glands. And a show- they indeed provided.  The glands came out with fan favorite:  Living Was Easy , which some of you Mr. Show freaks might recognize from the David Cross documentary “Let America Laugh”.  The mixture of fratters, and townie folks alike quickly (and somehow) left the Athens stereotypes at the door (the door of the frat house- where fratters live- I might add).  Most of the folks filtered on to the lawn on the Lumpkin street side of the house and began to dig the Glands.  But then again what is not to dig? Pure rock and roll.  Sure some might call it indie pop rock.  And that might not be totally untrue, but it ain’t completely always true either.  They are a hard band to define because they cover so much ground in their rock and roll world.  One second, indie-pop rock, next sec beautiful ballad like love songs and the next jangly countrified southern ditties.  But it’s always rock and roll and it’s always led by crisp well mannered guitars.  Sure the guitars sometimes misbehave.  But they misbehave on purpose.  Like the genius who is also the class clown.  They know what they are doing.  The Glands make huge strides in an often cluttered indie pop scene&mdash;
     

    
</post>


</Blog>