<Blog>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Test  Test, Test, This is a Test, This is a Test because Laura is the BEST!  C-Ya
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Rant  Why am i typing?? i have no clue, other than i love the sound that this keyboard makes. its so cool!!!! but its really sensitive and the backspace is like, way over there and its small so i keep hitting the backslash accidentally, haha. im so bored. i need something to dew. my skewl site is down, so no skewl today either. and theres absolutley no one online on my laptop. stupid ppl that actually go to skewl. they make me cry. jessica dyed my hair  RED, not purple, RED *sulks*  stupid colour-blind pplz!!! *coughcoughBYRONcough* speaking of whom hes coming over after  skewl today as far as i know.  thats not very far, but still, i know wat i mean....i think.....meh. i love this program! no lil squggles under the words that are spelled wrong!! no spellcheck!!! i can dew WATEVA I WANT!!! MUAHAHAHA!! lol, i scare me  sumtimes. owell. im too used  to msn, i keep pressing enter when im  done a sentence, lol. im such a freak. how am i ever gonna get this to my blog if im over here??? im on the wrong comp to be dewing this.....owell,. ill find a way. Hey!!! my heat died!!! *cries* i want it back!!!! not fair!!!! =( =(  actually, no i dont want it back, its really really really hot in this room. the  temp was sposed to DROP  so what does dad dew? he turns the heat WAAAAAAAYYYYYY up. *dies* x.x   U know wat? im fucking sick and tired of my father calling me a goddamned lier (woah, that was a topic change.) but i am. every day hell say something, and ill remind him of it later and hell be like i never said that! dont lie to me, i dont  want u to lie to me, be honest, ur such a little lier, etc, etc. It gets really really annoying. and they  wunder y i like Adam's Song by Blink 182.   "I never thought Id die alone, I'll laff the loudest,  whod have known?" "I'm too depressed to go on, ull be sorry when im gone."  they suc shit if they dont see how well that fits my life. i have like no friends anymore, but thats ok, that dont really bugg me that much. what does is that the friends that i have laff when they hear me complain about  my father. I know hes like stupid and insane and shit, but its really really annoying when ppl tell u to let out  ur feelings and not  keep them all bottled in, but then u tell them whats bugging  u and theyre all like 'oh hes just crazy' or 'hes an asshole' and then they change the subject. u know, ppl say that when kids grow up wiht ppl putting them down all the time, they grow up to be abusive....does almost trying to put ur fist thru a  wall count as abusive? i wunder if the changer left a bruise where he hit me  with it.....or when he pushed me for that matter...owell, too late, theyd be gone by now, that shit was like last week. this week there  could be fists involved for all i know.  i dont really care anymore. its all shit. hey, my heat is back, yay. my life sux. someone kill me. im such a fucking loser, everyone thinks im always so happy and shit, but i never really am. id kill myself, but a)im a loser and im a chicken cuz i hate pain b)that  would just prove to dad that hes right, and hed be a  lot happier without me around  c)i dont think that it would go over too well with my friends.   Byron was all suicidal b4 i met him, and he found this quote thingie. it said something along the lines of 'suicide is not a  choice, it is what happens when pain overcomes resources for coping with pain.' well  guess what, there  is always a choice. always. and if i ever was gonna commit suicide, then it would be my choice. even  adams song says so "the choice was mine i didnt think enuf". im like obsessed with that song. but yeah, it would be my choice, and the more time goes by the  worse my  father acts, and the better that choice seems. look at it this  way. If u grew up with a nice father, and mother, and a big brother, but then ur brother moved out, then  got in trouble witht he cops and hadda move back in, then ur father starts  forgetting shit, small things, then big huge fucking IMPORTANT things, and  ur mother was in the hospital,  ur father almost dies cuz hes to stubborn to take his ass  to the  hospital when he has double pneumonia, ur mother starts having heart palpitations from all the fucking stress at home and work, ur mother also decides to  go for surgery, having u worried half  to death, she  has a few breakdowns,  u have a few breakdowns, ur  father buggz every single one of  ur  friends that walks into the house, and then buggz u all day every day  when theyre  gone, at skewl, y arent they here?? y dont ur  friends come over??? they should be  here helping u with this or that. i HATE it, y cant he just leave me  alone???? its sooo damned annoying. then again, mom also dropped a  bit of a bomb on me  a while ago. i knew that when daves dad left she took dave and went out west looking for him. appairently she found him. but  it didnt dew any good. so. they came back to guelph and settled in. then dad met mom, and they moved in together. now. heres the thing. my father is a fucking ass control freak. you wouldnt believe the shit that he does. if im not home  right on time he sends mom out to drive around and look for me. then he gives me an hour long lecture about y i shouldnt be late. if im not up right when he sayz in the morning, i get screamed and bitched at to get my 'fat ass outta that bed' and how ill never be a vet if i cant get out of bed in the morning. well guess what shit head, i will get out of bed when i fucking want to, i dont  need some gay ass fucking old  man to  tell me when to wake up.  if i have ot get  outta bed for something, i will, but if theres no reason to and i havent  been sleeping well, then  FUCK OFF. i cant listen to the music i like unless its so quiet that he cant hear it, and its such a small house that if HE cant hear it then neither can i!!!!! jesus. it pisses the shit outta me, i like the music that  i like, and  i dont care if no one else in this house does. ill listen to it as loud as  i want when im in my room, i dont care if u can hear it. if theres a  song i like on tv and i turn it up for ONE song, then piss off and let me hear it!!! if i dont dew everything his  way, then i get bitched at and threatened. like litterally, threatened. like 'im gonna blast ur fat face off if u dont....' litterally, hes said that.  i get called a bitch, a fat slob, an asshole, a jackass, a stupid idiot, a loser, a lier,  etc, etc. well anywayz, , the piont is that he was MORE controlling when he was living with my mother b4 i was born and they were married. well. mom got really pissed at his controllingness and she took david and went to grammas for like a week, and told dad to get his stuff out and go. which he  did. and that was good.  well, he weaseled his way back by helping  out with little things, staying  for supper, he  got snowed in once and slept on the  couch, and eventually, he and mom were back together. then there was me, and they  got married. mom told me that shes thought of just taking me and leaving, which i dont have any  problem with, none  whatsoever, but we cant go anywhere. we cant go to grammas cuz mom promised not to  drop her kids there, that shed  sort out her own  problems. we cant stay anywhere in guelph, or with anyone that dad knows, cuz hed forget the reason that we left and would be calling all over guelph looking for us. mom wouldnt stay with any family at all, im sure. and im not allowed  to verbally tell anyone this, but like, she wants me to keep stuff bottled in, but she tells me not too, a bit of a conflicting message there. moms been getting  some information shit at her  work and shes taken my father to the doctors office, and they think  that either hes had a mild stroke or hes getting alzheimers, so hes going in for a CT scan sumtime. i really dont care. that sorta scares me, cuz i usta love hanging out with  dad and fooling around and going places, but now  i just dont  care at all. i dont think mom loves him. she  doesnt seem  to. things that he does that she used to ignore, she now expresses her disgust almost as  clearly as i dew. theres  something going on that i dont know about too.  mom came out to the car crying last saturday and she cried for the whole drive to the barn, and ten minutes after we were there, but she wouldnt tell me what was wrong. i still cant figure it out, and i dont wanna press her for anything cuz then ill get yelled at. dad keeps calling her an asshole and a bitch too, and then he calls ME  more  stuff if i try to stand up for her. they had a fight on the way to the doctors office and also  IN the docs office, but i still dont know what about. They fight about me a lot of the time.  how everything i dew is bad or wrong and how everything is my fault. How  im so much worse then my father's other kids, and how shitty i act, and how im such a frreak cuz i dont go to highskewl like the rest of my friends. theyve been fighting about a lot of other  stuff too, but i dont know what all because they keep their voices fairly low. sometimes. ive been being a huge chicken and  running over to  jessicas house when things get bad. we'll go out for subs or whatever, and ill be able to forget (or pretend to forget) all the crap thats been going on. (I'm getting pretty damn good at pretending all sorts of dhit, i dew it often enuf. pretemd my life isnt shit, pretend my parents dont fight,  pretend that i still have a lot  of friends, pretend that im happy all the time, pretend that things dont bother me...but anywayz...) We spend litterally almost  entire days walking around guelph. just  walking around, not really dewing anything. I had to go home early from her house a few times too becuase  some asshole called like five billion times while i was still asleep, wanting  to know where i was!!! wunder who THAT coulda  been. yeesh. ive gone home once too cuz dad called linda frangoes (family friend) for some reason, and on the fone, he broke down and started crying and muttering sumthing about mom. from what she could understand, which  wasnt a lot, he was totally convinced that mom was out with another guy. that she was cheating on him.  he would not accept the fact that she  was  at WORK. so linda foned mom at work and told her  what was going on, and she  went home early and so i had too to. hes such an asshole cuz apairently hes thought this for quite a while. my mom is not a slut, nomatter what he thinks. hes such a fucking GAYLORD!!!! arg. i keep calling him shit here cuz i cant in real life or hed either punch me in the face, or bitchslap me, not sure which. u know what? tylonal  doesnt hurt. neither does ibuprofine.  ill keep those in mind, theyre both almost new bottles.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Cards  Know what? I hate card games. I hate Solitaire, Hearts, Freecell, I even hate Minesweeper...wait a sec, there aren't any cards in that! owell, I still hate it. *lil voice grins smugly 'that's cuz u can never wn any of them'* Damn right!! (wow, for once im agreeing with that annoying lil dude!) Nomatter how many times i read the rules and the tips, i can never figure out what it is exactly that im dewing wrong! solitiare isnt sooo bad, it just gets very very boring. anyone agree with me that microsoft riggs these things?!?!?! *lil voice kix me in the head ' they  can all win the games'* butbutbut!!  *cries*  Stupid cruel little voice making me cry all the time. gak. Imma gonna trade him in sometime, i jus gotta get around to finding the reciept...*voice stares, hypnotized, at small charred bit of burning paper. Sees me looking at him and quickly puts out fire, hides ashes and looks angelic* ok, scratch that idea....i wonder if i could pay them to take him back.... *gets kicked in head again* pairently not. owell. i have my ways, heh heh heh. *little voice is not unnerved* so yeah....i went to the mall today, yahoo! Went with Jess and we met Laura, Byron, and Chris there. we really didnt dew much...*singing* (dont ask) k, well, my typing skills have greatly diminished since i started this, so imma gonna leave now. Luvz ya, buh byez!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hewwo  Meza in a betta mood now, lol. i unno y, its not like anythings changed at all, but, meh. I guess cuz i got a cordless fone  finally , and becuz me and jess split the cost of the 8Mile dvd on the day that it came out. =) So thats all fine and dandy. I'm lonely, nobody's online right now other than jessica, and she dont count cuz shes always online. hmm, she gonna read this when im dun, mebbe i should delete that.....meh, too lazy to. *little voice starts singing 'guess whos back, back again'* =S and i thought  I  was the crazy one! *little voice glares at me and continues singing, this time right into my ear* well, there goes  that  eardrum.   SPRING HAS ARRIVED!!! im so happy!!!!!! =D mebbe thats wut my good mood is about! well....it really shouldnt be, cuz even tho i LOVE the weather, i walk around with like tanks and shorts on, so....yeah, i gave myself a sinus cold, which sux. and my ice rink melted!!! *cries* poor byron, ur white-out smiley face and 'Hi' are gone. owell =) Jess got offline....hmm....ok, well now i know i dont have to delete that, she'll see it here and join my little voice in beating me up, im sure. I have a busy weekend. I ahve to go riding this aft, go rollerskating at the forum tonight with youth group, im staying at jessicas house for the night, in the morning me and jess are going out for lunch with a friend that i havent seen since the first grade! then i have to dew allllll of my business homework, and on monday i go to get my teeth examined for braces! maybe i should go start my hw like now, b4 jess gets here.....NAH!! she can help me with it =). so anywayz....this is getting long again i think...sorta.....kinda....well anywayz, im running outta words, so ill talk to yall lata!!  Luvz yaz, buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ARRRG!  Thanx so much to all my friends that read that and couldnt give half a shit. i sure dew love u all. jezus christ. my life sux. i get braces monday. fuck life, bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       UNGROUNDED!!!  MUAHAHAHAHA!!! IM FREE!!!!!!! i lurv it!! haha.im ok, i swear, i hadda dohnut for brekkie this mornin, so, yeah, im HYPER!! hehe, my father almost socked me in the face the other day, i just stood there smiling. (he pushed me outta the way and i pushed him back so he got pissed.) and I GOT TO GO SEE THE HORSES AGAIN YESTERDAY!!! me and jess were riding for like 8 hours again, it was fun! She ALMOST got me to gallop fast, but i didnt. jess says that i only cantered fast, but i think i was galloping slowly. We were dewing a lot of jumping too, it was cool, other than we ride in a western roping saddle (its like 50 friggin pounds!!!) and when u jump u get the horn in ur belly a LOT, lol. Anywayz, we also rode Ponyta a lot. ppl who know me know how short i am, well, Ponyta only comes up to like my hips! shes so cute....cept when she rears and bucks trying to throw ppl off. lol. she got jess off and jess was right underneith her!!! =S it was unnerving cuz i hadda ride her after that! "we" had to muck out a stall that was litterally ALL horse crap, over a foot deep!! i was the only one who ended up dewing any of it tho, and i got 2 wheelbarrows full from only a little sqaure of it that got done!!!=S. anywayz, we rode right thru a thunderstorm, it was fun, hehe. WE TURNED PONYTA INTO A PUNK PONY!!! well,   I   turned her into a punk pony anywayz. I braided her mane, which is SUPER thick and its like parted down the middle, so its real thick on both sides of her neck, and since her forelock is SOO thick, i couldnt braid it, so i put it up in like a ponytail, but it went POOF and it looked punk, it was SWEET!! haha! so anywayz, i gotta go now, im going riding again, but this is my english saturday lesson, so...yeah, fun. anywayz, ill talk later, luvz yaz, buh byez! *little voice continues snoring....*
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bored...Lalala  There is nothing to dew, nothing at all. I hate being grounded, there's too much time for skewlwork and when ur done that theres nothing left to dew but complain about how bored u are to everyone, and then they all get mad and leave or block u and uve got absultively nuthin after that. *"thats cuz ur annoying and boring"* i am not!! *"u are so!!"* fine then, be that way!! *stalks off leaving little voice behind* *"Sheesh,  some ones in a grouchy mood today!" lil voice sayz as he picks self up off of ground and dusts self off* hmmph! well anywayz, ... yeah. *"ur dewing it again!!"* dewing...? *"being BORING!!"* oh. thats nice. Lauras gettin her hair chopded off at 4:15 today, lol. she was home sick today and ive been yackin at her. i get to go get ortho history dun on thurs cuz i need to get a 12 yr molar pulled if i want a slightly normal smile. so theyre gonna take a bunch of xrays and moulds and stuff and its gonna take an hour. i unno when the actual braces are going on tho, but to get the rays and that done is gonna be $500.00!!!!!!!!!!! *dies* *"YAY!!"* *comes back to life just to annoy little voice* *"awww!!" goes off and cries in a corner* aww!! owell. ill comfort him lata. nywayz, i should go now, ppl are complaining that my blog is already too long, so luvz yaz, buh byez!! *goes over to comfort little voice*
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Grounded  Me an Jess and Byron went to the forum skating, which was pretty fun, we all hadda good time. I kinda pissed mom off with my music tho. She was a lil late coming to get us, (she was at my Aunt's house visiting) but that was ok, we played on the snowmound. She finaly came and me an Jess were trying to convince mom to let By sleep on the couch and me and jess could sleep in my room. But of course, that was a definite no. (Quite a while ago me and jess had promised by that he could sleep over when we got the 8Mile dvd, which we now have.) Anywayz, mom said no and was getting a bit pissed at me again, so Jess decided we should go for a walk when we got home. I told my father that we were going for a walk around the block, and we left. Well we went to the end of the street, and yeah, he missed the bus. So we went down to Sleeman park cuz I didnt really wanna go home and he could just catch the next bus. But when we figured it all out, he would have missed that bus too cuz it takes a while to get to the busstop from where we were. So we stayed at the park for a while till I figured that my parents would be out looking for me and I got really freaked out cuz I knew theyd be really mad. So Jess got real nervous cuz we were standing right in the light, so we hadda go to near the trees where it was dark, which made Byron really nervous cuz in SA apparently ppl get jumped all the time. We were all pretty nervous by then, with no real reason. I was afraid of going home to my parents, Byron was afraid that we were gonna get jumped, and Jessica was afraid that my parents were gonna find us. Well anywayz, I was really upset cuz I knew how mad my parents were gonna be. So we decided that we were gonna go to Jessica’s house instead of mine. We had to go back to the skewl at the end of my street, down the other catwalk, down a dark street full of trees, which By didnt like again, it freaked me out too, and then we changed our minds and went a diff way cuz we were trying to avoid Cannon hill since we'd be seen really easy up there. The street we took anywayz still went past it, but it was the bottom, so it wasnt as bad. We were all sooo jumpy and it felt like a horror movie. Well anywayz, we were gonna go straight to Jessica’s house, but we figured that my parents might be there already, so we walked down paisley and went thru paisley rd skewl which has no lights whatsoever in its playground and it scared the shit outta me. Then we hadda get thru Goldie park which was not fun cuz its not lit very well either and its right beside the gravel pits and train trax, so a lot of mesed up ppl hang out there and it was like midnight almost (11:30 or so) when we were there. My parents werent AT Jessica’s house, but they had called, so I called back and my father said that I could stay there for the night. well mom came back anywayz, cuz my father neglected to tell her that I had actually called after all and she took me and Byron and dropped by off at home, and I got home and came on MSN, just kinda trying not to talk to anyone at home, but mom came in and was like interrogating me, and yelling at me and shit and I didnt know what to say and she basically wouldnt stop yelling so I basically broke down crying which was seriously very pathetic of me. I swear Im on the verge of a freaking nervous breakdown!!! Its either my father or my mother, and now i have nowhere to go if i have to leave cuz Jess's mom made it pretty clear that she didnt want my problems. I feel so bad for dragging Jessica and Byron into all this. We shoulda jus let him take his bus and let me be yelled at anywayz and then Jess's mom would still be fine with it all. But I was a wimp and decided not to dew anything right, as usual, and i got everyone riled up for nothing basically. At the time it seemed like a big deal not to go home, thats how fucking scared i was, but looking back now, i can see that i was just being a jackass and i dragged other ppl into it that didnt have to be there. im going to go beat myself up about this now, im not talkint to my mother, shes grounded me, Jess and By arent allowed near the house (Byron especially) and i cnat go out for lunch this week. well, i might be able to, but not likely. anywayz, ill write more later, maybe my mood will lighten up, im not making any promised tho, considering the fact that I cried myself to sleep last night reallllly late and now im supreemly grouchy. Byez.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Serious Note  That should likely be semi-serious, but I just dont think that i can get enough energy to deal with that little voice, so i shoved him in a box for now. mebbe ill let him out lata....mebbe not....its all good =) K, everyone knows about the war thats going on, right? if u dont then ur more dense than me, and thats seriously hard to dew. well thats buggin me becasue i have a LOT of family that are going to have to leave for the war if they start enrolling ppl. Theres also the deal with this SARS thing. For those of u who dun listen to the news that much, SARS is a respiratory ailment that gives ppl a really high fever and a dry cough. and the catch is that its DEADLY!!! there have been over 100 cases in toronto already, and 6 ppl have died from it so far there. Most of the skewls in toronto have been put under quarentine and they have to wear masks at all times to keep from spreading it to other ppl. they arent even all that sure that its spread by close contact, they think that it might be airborn now, if so, then there might be a LOT more ppl that should be quarentined that arent yet. there was even a person from the guelph general hospital that was moved becuz it was suspected that they had SARS, so now theyre closing all the hospitals in guelph for visitors and ppl checking in unless its really neccisary. (Guelph General, St. Josephs, Homewood.) and my mommy works at St Joes and yeah, if its closed down from suspicsion of SARS in the general, shouldnt i be a bit worried about her? they dont even have the medical masks to wear yet to keep from getting it!!! Well, while im on the subject of stuff thats stupid, annoying, scarey, or pisses me off, lets talk about the asshole idiot that i live with. he practiacally busted the fucking table cuz byron wouldnt move to the other side of the table right away. he didnt know that he was being told to move. father was worried that byron was going to ruin of hurt our video camera in some way shape or form, and i said that he was fine to sit there, and he said no he wasnt, so he ended up ordering byron to move, which seemed to confuse the hell out of him, and it got me mad cuz it really dont metter where the hell he sits!! so i tried to tell that to my father, but all he did was get really pissed and slam his fist doen on the table. so now im pissed at him. i was gonna slam mine down too, but i dont know what he would have done back to me it i had, so i didnt. i think that im going to be mean to my little voice and keep him in that box because i just dont love him enough to let him out. =) i think thats all that i have to complain about, meh, mebbe ill think of sumthin lata, lol. Luvz yaz!! Buh byez!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bored  laura talked me into updating this cuz im really bored and theresd nothing to dew. my spelling is crap cuz its like midnight, and im really tired, but im touch typing cuz its too dark to see the keys. y am i up so late? im such a messed up freak. owell, its all good =) anywayz, the time on these entries are all wrong cuz laura i dont think set me to the right time zone when she created this blog for me, haha. owell, do i care that much??? uhm....nope =) i cant think of anything to talk about now!! its so sad!! owell, a short entry cant hurt lol. looking at the length of the rest of this id say that im really glad that i can type fast, haha. anywayz, i think that im going to go to bed now. Luvz yaz!! Buh byez!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Things Just Keep Getting Better And Better  Well this is nice, my parents are refusing to let me hang out with/talk to/type to Byron. Lauras mom called my mom and told her that he got beat up at skewl yesterday and that he was a really bad influence on us kids and that all the parents were going to have to stick together for this. well he said that he didnt get beat up (yes i talk to him on msn anywayz, i dont care, ill still hang out with him too, just not here at my house, thats all.) and he also is pretty pissed that lauras mom is calling all his friends and now he cant hang out with like any of us it seems. i dont think that this is very fair, becuz as far as i know, by's never been at my house when hes been high, and even if he ever offered me even a cigarette, my parents know that i wouldnt take it. so i dont see what the point of not letting me anywhere near him is. it dont make any sence. it also dont help that my parents think that me and him are going out and thats y they dont trust him or me. i dont know, my parents are pretty messed up. but anywayz, i think ill be going now, its REALLY nice outside, its literally like 26 degrees =D Luvz yaz!! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Meeting ppl.....well....ok, person  Finally met laura chan yesterday =D. me and byron were the only ones that showed up! Jessica saw us on her way downtown to meet with ben and go to his house, and so she stopped and hi and then ben came so they left. us 3 decided that we had to dew something so we walked to what was originally going to be lisas house, but laura clayton was on the way, so we got her first. she was at least home, and she came with us to lisas house. well lisa wasnt there, she was at the library waiting for us apairently. well we went to sunnyacres park and we were on the swings for a while, laura chan went flying from like level with the bar!! she didnt hurt herself the first time, but the second time she kinda did a faceplant, lol. we were hanging upside down and stealing byrons balloons. by and laura clayton both blew them up and stuck them up their shirts and ran around, lol, twas an interesting scene. after we got bored with that, we lit a few leaves on fire, nothing major *halo lights up* *little voice kix halo and it flickers and goes out* ohhh, dang!! well anywayz, we also called lisa and told her to get her butt to the park. of course, right after we say that we go across the street to the convenience store and lisa walks past. i hadda run out and catch her fore she went to far, lol. she had her doggies with her too and they like laura chan. laura and byron got a 2L Pepsie and we drak a bunch in the parking lot (splitting it 4 ways with straws, lol) then we went to lisas house and hung out in the basement and we split the rest of the pop in glasses. well, laura chans mom called and we had to go back to the library. well after that i walked around the corner with byron to the busstop and then jess's dad pulled up cuz pairently i was sposed to be at their house. so he left and i said g'bye to byron and went to jess's house, had supper, and then she, ben, and i went to the forum, which was fun. Luvz yaz!! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bored at the Moment  I'm bored and jessica is screeching at me to update this *little voice covers ears* see?! even  HE  dun like it, lol. listening to a really cool song right now, its called Love, Pain, The Whole Damn Thing. i like it. well anywayz, im going to the movies with jess and byron later i think, as long as my father will still drive me out there...i have nothing to talk about, im like the only person that i know that still updates their blog anymore=S *little voice kix me in the head "thats cuz ur a lozer"* u know wut? we've REALLY gotta cut down on the time that he spends with laura chan =S=S but anywayz, its all good. well, im going to go now, cuz this will turn into a really long ramble that no one wants to hear *"too late for that"*   *glares at little voice* anywayz, i updated it liek u wanted jess, im going to go now b4 i get kicked in the head again *ducks as little voice tries to boot me in the head again* Luvz yaz!! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Oopsie  My bad, Jessica's thing that she was trying to get me to type wasn't a virus, Tyler was threatening me with all the viruses, so i assumed that wut jess had was one too, but all it was was a hackers code to get into my computer and get the work. not that that is any better really. but i just wanted to clear that up coz i wasnt meaning to make false accusations. Well nywayz, thats all i really wanted to talk about becuz theres nuffin goin on, not that there ever really is....but meh. Luvz yaz!!! Buh byez!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Tis Me  i changed my pw so hopefully jessica wont be able to put her 2cents worth in anymore. she wants me to send her my hw so that she can hand it in as her own with only a few changes to the sentence answers, but i wont cuz i sent her wut we did at her house and she thinks that we did more, but we didnt. so now shes threatening me with viruses and all kindza crap, which im not taking kindly to. she spent like 4 hours last night getting ppl to scream and yell at me and generally take her side in things. i offered to help, but she didnt want my help, so that was fine. but if shed gotten her ass in gear and actually started dewing the work that was after the bit that i sent her, then she would have had it done in like an hour, but she was more concerned with getting ppl to be pissed at me. she also tried a few times to get me to issue a self distruct command and my basic response to that, jessica, is:   SCREW YOU!   *ahem* anywayz, thats about all i have to rant about for now, if i think of anything else ill upate. Luvz yaz!! buh byez!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       RAMBLE!!!  Yeesh, i dun reamble nymore! the purpose of laura creating this was for me to ramble, hence the name RaMbLeS & sHaMbLeS. meza been ranting and raving and thats just not cool. meh...well, ive decided to ramble on till my fingers hurt from typing...no, thats not a good thing..my fingers dont get tired of typing, as im sure u pplz have sorta noticed...well nywayz....imma bit crazy, lol, i have a huge bouquet of lilacs by my head coz i picked em coz i   LOVE   lilacs and yeah, theyre sitting beside me, but i think that the smell is going to my head coz yeah, im like hyper and crazy and not normal.. *"when r u ever  normal ?!?!" lil voice rollz eyez* im not, thats my point, im more weird than i usually am, which is strange..*"well duh its strange, if it werent then it wouldnt be normal, would it now?!"* ... shuddup, i knew that! well nywayz yeah...it was only 2 days ago that i last updated this?!?! i thought it was like....longer....=S  *singing: I am slowly going crazy 6-5-4-3-2-1 switch! slowly crazy am i going 6-5-4-3-2-1 switch!* i swear theres no blood in my al-key-hol system! wheee!!! ok, ok, must be calm. the boredom is eating away at my brain and i dun like it =S. omgomgomg, yesterday was so much fun!!!...other then jess got me up early.....but yeah.. me and jess went to ben's ultimate frisby tourny and it was at heights, and as most ppl know, heights has like a lot of fields, lol. we went from one end of a field looking stupid, to the other end of the field looking stupid, to a diff field looking stupid and back again to the first field, still looking stupid =) then we went to play on the rings on the path between the first fields and the back ones. then we climbed the big hill there and looked around from the top of it and it was purdy funny coz i was looking in one direction and stated that it was all like forest on top of a hill, and then i turned around and said that the other way looked like it could be too, but for the fact that there were like 4 houses that we could see at the bottom of the hill. and jess said that mebbe it still was, but she wasnt paying much attention and i wasnt either, so i agreed, then alluva sudden i noticed that there was a church and it was the Church of our Lady, and thats downtown guelph! =S then i recognized St. Joeseph's church on paisley and then i knew where we lived, which is like, right there!!! =S so guess wut all us guelphians, we live in a forest on a hill!!!! lol. i AM ok, stop staring at me! well nywayz, after that....w/e it was, we went back down to the fields and started looking stupid again, jess used up a lotta time on her fone trying to figger out wut colours GC was so we could find tha team, but all we got was that they were green and white, and there were no white, so we were looking for the lime green ppl that we saw on the way in, and when we were walking to one of the farthest fields to the left (from the parking lot) theres a hill between em and then the green pplz started standing up and i was laffin so hard coz it looked like they was jus poppen outta tha ground as we got closer!! but we figgered they were GC coz ben came up to us and splained that the green was the senior team and that red (him) was the junior team. so we went and watched a bit, then we read, then it was lunch and me and jess were 'stalking' ppl trying to find an old friend of ours, whom we didnt end up finding *tear* so then we got bored and went to the convenience store after i got lilacs and stuck em in my ponytail, lol, cnya tell i love lilacs!? =D we got sumthin ta eat and went back to the tourney, but we lost ben again, so we walked around looking stupid and getting deja vu till we were both boiling coz it was hot n sunny, so we sat under a tree on the hill thing that had made it look like the green ppl were jus poppin up, and we read for a bit till i spotted them on the farthest field (closest to the highway) and so we eventually got up and went over, but it took a bit. they won that game, but nona the other ones, lol, they won 1 outta 4. well nywayz, ben stayed wit us after and we walked to the mall, we were gonna jus take the bus, but meh, nywayz, we were walking and then me and jess started pushing each other (i still win even tho im so short, lol) and then ben started pushing us into bushes, lol. (evil ben *glares*  *lil voice cheers*) then b4 we got to the mall we stopped at the park and played for a bit, lol, laura chan would like that park, theres a swinset on top of a hill, so ud go rolling really far if u jumped off from level with the bar!! we DID eventually get to the mall, where we hung out @ the dollar store, and then we got food and left, we were in quite the predicament tho, coz we were bussing home when i was specifically told not to, and my mother was driving around looking for us coz jess hadnt told her we were headed for the mall when my mom called so..yeah...well nywayz, we got home and im still alive, so yeah. sall good. my arms are really stiff from hanging upside-down on the rings at the skewl tho, lol. it was purdy damn fun =) and then today me and jess were gonna go for a walk behind the trax and then we were gon go swimming, but we didnt end up swimming, we went way off in a direction that neither of us had been before, surprisingly *lil voice looks shocked*, and we found flowers for chelseas skewl thingiehoosit, and then we found a buncha blankets and old clothes and yeah, we kinda didnt stay there =S (large amounds of ewww, and many vows not to go back there again) nywayz, we chased a bunny that ran away from us, lol, and we almost fell into the river a few times each. we finally started on the way back, and some kid stopped us and said that his friend was taking a shit farther down the trail, so, erm, yeah, we were pretty grossed out, and we walked on the edge of the river, which is like a 6' drop-off wall thing to the water, which is icky coz its water run-off that goes to sewage, but nywayz, the hill there is so damn steep that its really hard to walk along and so we like almost fell in, and ended up walking past the kid nywayz, but pairently he was done, and we kinda walked on a diff path the long way round him. so we were both pretty grossed/freaked out by those 2 seventh grade type dudes and we just kept walking away from them, and then we hung out at jess's and now im home and ive been typing for a really long time now and i didnt even realize it...owell *shruggz and lil voice falls off shoulder, gets up cussing, kix me in the azz and climbs back to my shoulder* y dew i put up with you?!?!? *lil voice looks innocent* yeah, thats wut i thought *glares* well, jess, ull have lotz to read now, so dont complain that i dont write enough (yes shes the only one crazy enough to want me to write MORE than i already dew,) well nywayz, imma go fore i go over even HER standards of annoying =P lol. Luvz yaz!!!!! Buh byez!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~*~Lalala~*~  Wow, am i ever bored, ive been updating my website a lot during the last week coz my skewl site has been down and ive had nothing better to dew. safe to say, im getting purdy sick of my Kazaa playlist =S i think i know the order of all 50 songs on it in order by now =S. arrg. not in the best of moods, the prob thing with jess is fine now, but ive been soo damn bored the past dew days, and i realized that byron dont talk to me nymore, phil dont talk to me nymore, neither does sarah (wolf), des, half my zone ppl, and half my vlc ppl =S so that kinda really sux. my mom jus went for her surgery and shes dewing okay, but still....  and i really want jon to come up in the summer, but hes still not sure if he can or not, so that makes me sad. my parents have been fighting non-stop, which is basically y i worry about my mom coz yeah, right after surgery, i dont think that a ton of stress is a good thing. i was so scared the other day that i literally stayed in my room all day cuzza the goddamned screaming. and i get to go see tara and lindsay, which kix some serious azz, but the drive up there is gonna really suck, its like 4 days in a friggin car. so lonely, no ones ever here anymore, like literally, i havent seen by in over a month...since the laura chan was here!! or was mini golfing after that...musta been, coz thats the last time i saw him....nywayz.., and jess obviously wasnt here for a while. lauras hardly ever here, she comes to go on my msn sumtimes, i dont think nicoles ever been to my house b4...no wait, i lie, she has been like once or twice...lisa hasnt been here since she wanted me to dew her hair last time...or maybe the last time she was here was when she was here with cory...oh i unno =S crystal i havent seen since grad, erm, the twins ive talked to like a couple times each, went to see Identity with Jess F. but other then that we dun really hang out...so u see my point? ppl try to plan out coming over and they'll just forget all about me, soo yeah...ppl. be like jessica, if u feel like coming over, dont call if ur at skewl or something, just come over, its fine. although i dont know y im even writing this coz the only person that reads it already comes over whenever she wants nywayz *coughcoughJESSICAcough* but..yeah, i unno. well nywayz, getting a little pathetic here, but yeah, nyone whos reading this, wish me luck with my parents, coz my moms only been home for 4 or 5 dayz and she and my father are already fighting worse then me and my father fight =S Luvz yaz, buh byez.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        MY TRIP!!!     Part One - On The Road    Day 1  Tee hee, im on my way to ALBERTA!! yay!! go me!! *ahem* ok, ok, i AM ok. a lil excited tho. ok, well...today was Sunday, June 8, 2003, and we were supposed to have gone to a Tunney family reunion thingie. We erm...started on our way! but then we uhm...kinda........got lost.....lol. we couldn't find Jane St. in TO....sooo....yeah. well i wasnt the one that was navigating, so it wasnt MY fault! then again, i didnt really help that much...i kinda....slept *grins widely and looks angelic* well anywayz....an hour - hourandahalf long trip ended up being...uhhh...like 3 hours or so, hence me sleeping. well ppl got annoyed enough that we couldnt find the place that we just tuned around and came back home for a few minutes. we werent very long because we needed to just call shane or dave and see if one of them could come pick us up from the airport in TO on the 21st @ 6:30 in the morning =S (our flight leaves at 1AM!!!!!   but we got a good rate =) plus its mommy's bday!! =D ) so anywayz, daves gon pick us up. then we went to the library and it of course wasnt open coz its sunday. so we went to zellers, and GUESS WUT I GOT?!?!?! I HAVE A CELL FONE!!!! =D=D=D=D=D wheeeeee!! ...unfortunately....i dont exactly have the internet at the moment, so i cant go online to get a # for it. when i do, ill post this entry and get my # and post it too. eminemyways...uhm...after that we got subs and went to grammas, and it was storming and it was awsome....we ate supper....we went to bed....well....they all went to bed, i typed...in fact i should go, ill try to write about every day, so jess, ur gonna have a LOT to read...i prolly wont write this much tho, if i can help it. Night all!   Day 2  Well, we got up at like six and were outta grammas by like...quarter after seven. we had brekkie, made sure we had everything and we were gone. well, we drove a LOT...i was stuck in the very back seat, and i got feeling pretty icky coz im not usually that great with long rides. i was ok tho, if anyone cares *little voice looks dissappointed* i slept for a while and then i was awake, but feeling a little better as long as u dont count the fact that i couldnt move my neck very well (it hadda crick *owie*) nywayz, we stopped and i took half a gravol and was great for the rest of the day. i also changed seats and i wasnt so bad. i think i was just getting used to the van. we passed some pretty amazing scenery! there were all these sheer rock walls that were streaked thru wit colours from the layers of the rock! it was awsome coz the highway went right thru em and u could see where they had jammed the rods thru to break off the rocks. we also saw a lot of swamp and some of Lake Superior. we got lost trying to find the b&b and of course, i was asleep again. Id been helping gramma crochet an afghan, gimme a break!! but we found it, then went to get supper, and we stopped at a park that was reaaalllly pretty, lots of picnic tables and a playground and swings and a pavillion and everything, but there were blackflies EVERYWHERE!!! they were SO thick! it was icky and bloody and justjustjust....*shudders* but then we went and got coffee (iced cap for me! =D) and i also got KFC popcorn chicken!! *drool* OMG i fergot how GOOD that stuff is!!! but yeah, then we came back to the bed and breakfast and read and talked a bit. they have a reallly cute doggie named Missy. shes such a sweety!!! she gives kisses, lol. but nywayz, we all took showers and went to bed. im on the floor beside mom, but the thing is that ive been touch typing the whole thing coz i didnt think that it was fair to keep them up with the light as bright as the one beside the bed. well nywayz, i should go, brekkie is @ 7 tomorrow morning and then we be outtie. (its like quarter to 11 now) ill try to be online if i can find a place along the way, but there is no way that i can garuntee it. not that it really matters seeing as ur not gonna be reading this till i find somewhere nywayz! =P well, i only wrote a lot coz its the first travelling night. btw, the b&b is just outside sault st marie =) we drove about seven or eight hours today, lol. were hoping to break manitoba by either tomorrow or the next day, and from there itll be smooth sailing, lol. gnight yall! luvz yaz!!   Day 3  Well, we got thru Thunder Bay today, which was purty good. we'll be outta ontario by tomorrow afternoon sometime. =D. we're at a motel outside dryden at the moment, and they dont have internet either *bawls eyes out* omg, i miss my msn!!!! all my friends!! and i cant call them coz i need the net to get my cell #!!!!!!!! *sighs loudly* well nywayz, weve all got the same room this time, and my fathers putting up a fuss about it. not that i really care, its all good here, lol. we saw some AMAZING scenery, but most of it was past by the time i thought to get my camera out! i did get a few nice ones tho, and a few panoramics =) not sure how well theyre gonna turn out tho, coz i took em all thru the windows...so...yeah. we did stop in thunder bay to see the Terry Fox memorial statue. it was really really cool! lol, they were painting the fence and they had signs everywhere that said "WET PAINT" and ppl were telling my father to watch out, but the smart one almost leaned against it anywayz. but yeah....i wasnt gonna write much, lol, so ill go for now, we hafta be outta here by 11, but i may just go out and sleep in the frigging car because my fathers being an ass. well ill try to get online soon, luvz yaz!!   Day 4  IM IN MANITOBA!!! WE MADE IT OUTTA ONTARIO!! lol. there are so many mixed licence plates here! theres like the ppl next door in this motel are from South Dakota, and theres ppl from saskatchewan, and ohio, and ontario, and alberta, and EVERYWHERE! tee hee. well nywayz, i thought that it was rather sad this morning coz yesterday we passed a whoooollle big huge area that had been burnt down in a forest fire, and today we saw a LOT of clear cutting. stupid frigging loggers *even little voice mutters under its breath* but nywayz, we got to manitoba around eleven i think in the morning, im not sure coz there was a time change either yesterday or today, but i didnt really pay attention to it. my comp sayz that its 11:22 right now, but the alarm clock sayz that it is 10:24 so...yeah. were gonna be going thru another time zone soon, and we were hoping to get to Edmonton by tomorrow, but gramma and grampa figgered that it would take at least 11 hours straight of driving. it was weird today, my father decided that he was getting out of the car for some reason and he opened the door as if he was about to get out, but heres the thing....WE WERE STILL ON THE HIGHWAY!! arrrg, so mom (who was driving at the time) pulled over coz he was really confused and aggitated and all sortsa crap and he got out and actually RAN away!!=S it was scary, i dont think ive EVER seen him run.....ever! owell, he was messed, so my moms really p.o.-ed at him for that and shes not feeling very well either, her tummy's sore. i got her to take half of one of my gravol tho, and shes asleep now, but the light's still on so i dont wanna be too long. lol, i get to sleep on a cot! arent i special!! *"Ur a reject!!" little voice pipes up* errrm....well theres that too....but *SHHH*! eminemywayz....I MISS YOU ALL!!! IT MAKES ME SAD!!!! I HAVE NO INTERNET YET!!! *bursts into tears* i still dont have the # for my cell yet either....sooo...yeah....well nywayz, i should go, i need to get a bit of sleep coz were getting up at 6 tomorrow, were kinda in the middle of manitoba i think and were gonna try to get as close as we can to Edmonton tomorrow, but i hope we dont actually get there, coz gramma called and cancelled our reservations for the first night. now...if my father hadn't have jumped outta the van and gone running, then we might have made it on time *glares at sleeping father* well nywayz, i luvz yaz!!! buh byez!!!! o yeah, one sec, lol, it be Wednesday, June 11, 2003, and it be my fathers birthday *half heartedly wishes him happy bday* and it also be gramma and grampas wedding aniversery!!!!=D *cheers, jumps for joy, brings them a huge cake and wishes them a very very happy anniversery* we had a nice dinner at the motel restaurant to celebrate, but since we havent been eating a lot on the road, and mom wasnt feeling well, we didnt end up finishing all of the food, so weve got a HUGE cinnamin bun and half of a small pizza still to eat, lol, it was good tho. nywayz, im actually gonna go now =P LUV YAZ!!! *waves* wait wait wait, i was also gonna say that the praries ARE really really flat, but i dont think that theyre boring..but meh....ok, im gonna GO this time, lol, NIGHTZ!   Day 5  AHHHH!!! IM IN ALBERTA!!! MUAHAHAHA!!! lmao, this is SWEET!! we made it after all!! it was purty sweet. we saw a buncha buffalo when we first got here. (btw, saskatchewan is kinda boring, i slept almost all morning, lol) we got lost another 2 times, but i was AWAKE for them!!! yay! lol, yeah, we took a wrong turn once and then we got lost trying to get to the hotel, we hadda pull into a truck place near the trainyard and a driver there was gonna give us directions, but he basically escorted us there instead! *"ur not special enough for an escort" lil voice mumbles* owell, i am now *smiles* well nywayz, I HAVE INTERNET NOW!!!! I LOVE YOU ALL, IMMA EMAIL EVERYONE!!!!AHHH!! ok, ok, but that will be tomorrow morning. tonight its really late and Lena (my cousin) is sleeping w/ me on the pull out couch in the hotel room coz her rooms really crowded wit pplz. i tried to get the # for my fone, but theres sumthing frigged wit that comp and it wouldnt lemme dew it, so imma hafta ask them if it might be possible at all, and mebbe they can fix it. so hopefully ill get a # soon and i can call u all!! (not that ur gonna see this for a while yet nywayz...but owell =) andandandandandandomgomgomgomgomg*hyperventalates* I AM GOING TO THE WEST EDMONTON MALL TOMORROW MORNING SOMETIME!!! =D=D=D=D=D OMGOMGOMGOMGOMG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! *takes a breath* I CANT WAIT!!!! WATER PARK!!! ROLLER COASTER!!! STORES!!!! SHOPPING!!! WHEEEEEEEE!!! *takes another breath* *ahem* aiighty, i think im ok now =) nywayz, i should get going before my father flips out again and starts yelling at me to get off the comp. I LOVE YOU ALL!!!!! NIGHT NIGHTZ!!!   Part 2 - At Edmonton      Day 6  omg, where to begin?!?!! wow!! ok, well, i spent like the entire day at the West Edmonton Mall, and it is AWESOME!!! its friggin HUGE!!! i LOVE it!!! i spent like 60 bucks and mom got back like $1.80 somethin, lol. butbutbut yeah, that place is friggin AMAZING!! ive got the starter kit for my cell fone, so imma get that activated tomorrow, and ill have to email the # to yall. tee hee, we got there and basically the first thing that i did was run for chapters, so i got a new book. well then i went to HMV, which is like 2 doors down right under famous players, and i got ANOTHER cd, (i got 2 on the road, dixie chicks and good charlotte) and now i got Linkin Park - Meteora. so i was happy, lol. we took a look at the water park, but i didnt feel much like going in because i dont do well on waterslides, lol, i end up half falling off the edges =S. but nywayz, we took a look, and then we went around the mall a few times and MAN! its a LONG walk!!!! lmao its sooooo big. well, we eventually got around upstairs and down a lil bit, and we looked at the dolphins. they made me soo sad, the poor lil things were in a tiny enclosement thing and it was too small for them. it wasnt even very deep, but it had a thing where u could go below and see them down there, like in free willy, and it was so strange, i just really didnt like it for some reason. well nywayz, breckon and clinton went to see 2 fast 2 furious, and we went mall trolling, and we also took a while to find the food court, but we got there and ate, and the amusement park was right there!!! =D=D OMFG, I LOVE THAT PLACE!!! most of the rides at first from the food court are for lil kids, but me and lena went on the big swing thingie. yes jess, the same one that almost made me sick at sportsworld. nywayz, i was fine this time, it was sooo much fun, lol. butbutbut, OMFG OMFG OMFG!! *freaks out* if nyone reading this has ever been to the West Edmonton Mall, or seen pics of Galaxyland, then u might have seen the Mindbender. its a fucking HUGE roller coaster, the only 3 loop indoor roller coaster in the WORLD!! k, now, if u know me, u know that a) imma chicken and that b) ive never been on a roller coaster b4. well, the Mindbender was a doosie to start off with!!! holy CRAP! i can NOT believe that i went on that damn thing!!!!!!!!! butbutbut I LOVED IT!! ill likely have whiplash from it, but i dont care, it was worth it!! when i saw the whole thing i told lena that i wasnt gonna go on it, and she said that i had to, so i did, lol. auntie shelley went on it too!!!!! lol, i screamed the whole way *blushes* I TOLD U IMMA CHICKEN!!! lol it was SOO much fun tho!!! i have a souveneir from it too, a great big bruise on my arm from the safety thingie that goes over ur shoulders. but now that i think about it, maybe that makes me lucky....i mean when i think about it...today was friday the 13th...i rode the last run b4 a mantenance check...its a full moon...my first time on a coaster....owell, i LOVED it. the pics dont do it justice tho, the thing is GIANT! and i left my cameras at the hotel, so i couldnt get a pic of it, and i didnt have the money to get them to take a pic of me, lol, it cost 2 bucks and i didnt have that much at the time. but MAN i wanna go do that again!! the first drop is the worst, and the g-force is evil, it snapped my head down b4 each loop and i couldnt get it back up =S not till the upside-down bit of the loop anywayz. but yeah, im still so surprised that i actually did that!! lol. nywayz, then we lost everyone coz we thought we were going swimming, then we werent, then ppl came back to look for bathingsuits in the car, and then they left and appairently told us to meet them by the whale, (a statue near the door where we came in), but we didnt coz we thought that they were coming back to get us, and i at least knew my way around the mall...how i knew, i dont know, coz i cant for the life of me find my way around gcvi, and i think that the skewl is just an itty bit smaller then that mall, lol. but w/e the reason, i went off to the water park, which is literally from one end of the mall at the food court, to the other end of the mall =S its soo long, lol, the mall takes up like 2 city blocks =S lol. but yeah, we found ppl and got straightened around and then we made dinner plans, gramma and grampa and auntie shelley and her kids hadda go to a special dinner at the church and we werent invited, so we had supper with uncle blake and auntie christine, and matt and adam, at the old spaghetti house. the food there is SOOOOOOO good!!! mmmmm *nummyfulls* lol. so then we went to get my cell fone starter package and once we got that we tried to find a timmies, but we couldnt find it so we gave up and i chose a card for tessa (the one thats getting married and the reasont that were out here, lol) and then we met uncle blake who took us back to the hotel, which is only like 2 blocks away from the mall, and he went back to stay with auntie christine and matt and adam. so weve kinda been hanging out here, and its been ok....uncle dennis and aunt carol are here now too along with arri and tamen. omg, has arri ever CHANGED!! i didnt recognize him at all, lol, and he like gave me a hugg and all i was thinking was 'who the hell are you?!?!?' lol. they went to a movie tho, so we really didnt see much of them. clint and breck were asleep...so we didnt see them either, but uncle richard is here and he brought al-key-hol wit him, lol. his brother david is here too. but yeah, it was a REALLLLLLLLYY long day, so i should get going now. ILL TALK TO U ALL AS SOON AS I CAN, I THINK IMMA SEND MORE EMAILS OUT TOMORROW!!!! =D oh yeah, and i might be going to bc!!! mom wants me to see the mountains, so we may take a lil day trip out that way and take a lookie. well nywayz, i hope to be on the internet later, so buh byez!!!! loves yaz!! night night!!   Day 7 - THE WEDDING!!   well, today was the wedding and i started out the day by reading like 2 whole books, then i went downstairs to go on the comp and i emailed the ppl back that loved me enough to email me =D. there wasnt too many of u....=S nywayz, then i came back upstairs and i started getting ready for the wedding. it was raining out and i think i that it was because they did the pictures b4 the wedding, so the groom saw the bride in her dress b4 the wedding, which is bad luck. but it cleared up nicely during the cermony, which was beautiful btw. it was really long tho, but i liked it. we mingled for a bit and then we went back to our hotel (which, by the way, is called the Executive Royal Inn) for the reception, which was really funny, they had comedy pplz come in but they were phil's and tessa's friends, lol. phil is really funni too, lol. (there were lotza embarrassing stories told for both the groom and the bride, tee hee.) then they hadda spin the Wheel-O-Love lol. it was different ways that they hadda kiss. then they had their first dance as a married couple and then everyone danced, excluding me...i was a wallflower, as usual. and then we had pics taken, and then me and lena and hali went upstairs to play cards for a while. erin was gonna come wit us, but she didnt i guess....i unno.....well, lenas still here and shes waiting for me to play cards wit her still even tho its 1 in the morning here, lmao. weve gotta be checked out @ 11 tomorrow morning and weve got a big present opening thingie at 10, but i dun really wanna go...nywayz, ill check my email if i get another chance and if nyone else loves me enough to email me then ill email them back, i want my msn!!! lol, nywayz, i should go now, ttyl!!! LUVZ YAZ!! nighty night! (ILL BE IN CALGARY TOMORROW)    Day 8  i unno whether to classify this day as @ the hotel or @ uncle neals, lol. i unno, am i allowed to do both? owell, ill just switch it tomorrow i guess, coz thatll be my first FULL day here. man, today went by REALLY fast, its like 11:40 here, thats 1:40 @ home, and my brain is still on home time for some reason. nywayz, lena slept over in our room last night and we had some fun, lol, we hadda go to sleep pretty much right away tho, so that made me sad, lol. but we got up in the morning @ like...i unno, 8:30 or 9 and lena went to her room to get dressed etc. and i watched tv and read a few pages in my latest book, lol. check out time was at 11 am, so we hadda get all of our stuff and put it in gramma and grampas van for the time being, so that we were at least out of the rooms. later we hadda transfer it to uncle normie's car coz hes the one that was driving us to calgary, ie his house, lol. nywayz, they were opening presents inside the hotel from like 10 till like past 1!!! it was crazy!! nywyaz, then we were sposed to be eating lunch, but i wasnt hungry so i bought byron a postcard from the gift shop and imma mail it to him i guess if i get a chance, but i needa email hima nd see wut his full addy is...=S lol, i unno, he hasnt returned nything that ive sent him so far, so meh. thats y i only got him a postcard, lol. *looks angelic*...*fails* =) but yeah...i eventually got on the comp in the lobby and ate a choc bar (hence the not being hungry) and i was on it for like not even half an hour when this lil kid starts staring at me, and she doesnt even ask if she can use the comp, she stands there for like maybe 5 mins and shes just staring at me, so then she gets her mom and all i hear is her whining that ive been there for like 2 hours, and she cant get on!! i was like wtf?!?! but i didnt say nything, lol, i just sat there and kept typing. so i finished my emails like another half hour later (the kid and mother had left after like 2 mins) and then the lil chick came back with her big sis (big sis was like, what? maybe 8) and they stared at me, so i typed faster and finished quick b4 going to eat, butbutbut, i was basically kicked off the comp by a friggin 6 yr old!!! well nywayz, i went and wandered for a few, and then mom came and told me to come and sit, i didnt have to eat, so that was all fine and dandy so i sat and talked and that was about it....but i was in there for like an hour or...no, i lie, i was there for almost 2 hours, if not more, and me and lena left a few times each, either getting food for her, or just wandering, or a bathroom break, and they were STILL there!! the one chick was soooo slow at typing, she was like going at one key at a time, like one key per minute =S it was annoying just to watch her!!! nywayz, i got LOTZA huggz!!! =D it made me so happy! lol, unfortunately, all of my cousins are freakin tall!!! except for tessa, i love her, im taller then her =D lol. but then we left, and we took Jay (the tallest one outta tha whole friggin bunch) coz he has an apartment here too, so we dropped him off...it was like a 3 hour drive in a lil car, like, one that has 2 seats in the front and 3 in the back, but there were 6 of us, so the front seat was squished...i was in the back listening to lp and gc, so i was perfectly fine, lol. well we got our things moved in kinda and we had an AMAZINGLY good supper, Rebecca is an AWESOME cook!! mmmmm, nummyfullz!!! omg, lol. so yeah, we basically had supper then sat and chatted for a bit, and now were all going to bed. i didnt have time to get my fone a number STILL, so i HAVE to do it tomorrow, arrrg, i shouldnt procrastinate, lol. nywayz, were sleeping in the basement, so its chilly here, but not so bad, theres 2 kitties, so if i open my door im sure ill have company, lol. but yeah, its like your room jessie, lol, but this is bigger, and by the looks of the bookshelf, id say that uncle neal has been using it as a workshop....theres a handsaw on the floor and a level and hammers and screws and nails and tape and wire and a drill and varathane and all sortsa neat stuff...but no books. well nywayz, i should go, im sure no one likes the long thingies coz there so boring and irrelevent to those reading them because they werent here, so y should THEY care?!?! owell, i love yaz nywayz!! *lil voice whispers "shes lying!!!!!"* oh will u be quiet *glares at voice, then smiles sweetly* night night all!! luvz yaz!!! OMFG, one thing, I GET TO GO ON MSN TOMORROW!!! I LOVE MY UNCLE NORMIE!!! lol ok, now, g'night!!   Part 3 - Calgary...mostly    Day 9  OMG I GET TO SEE TARA TOMORROW!!! AHH!!! =D=D=D=D=D i baked her some cookies tonight coz it be her bday tomorrow, so i got her a card, and shes always loved my mommy's homemade choc chip cookies, so we made her some, but they werent the same recipe, but i dont think it will matter too much. wow, i cant believe it. not at all. today was pretty much a la-z day and we all jus sat around and talked, i read and listened to music for most of the morning, and im about ready to murder my cdplayer coz it skippz now. it dont matter wut cd, or whether its got batteries or the plug-in, or whether the cd is scratched or not, it still damn well skipps!! arrg....owell...hopefully itll do me till we get back to guelph....but id almost rather get one here coz theres no provincial sales tax....owell, i spose ill have to live. I WAS ON MSN!! *sighs contentedly* unfortunately, i couldnt really talk to ppl because i was getting a # for my fone, WHICH IS NOW WORKING!!!!, and i was tying up the fonr line and rebecca needed the fone. but i at least had a chance to say hi to ppl....i should ahve changed my msn name too while i was at it, but i didnt get around to it....at least i dont THING that i did....no, im sure i didnt, owell, no one cares. ill hopefully be on msn again the day after tomorrow coz were going to see TARA and LINDSAY tomorrow!!!! =D=D=D omG!! were mebbe gonna stay the night in a motel or something and then were gonna take the route back to here (calgary, hence the part 3 up there ^ ) that goes thru the Badlands. were gonna see all the dino bones, so ill bring ppl home some i guess coz u can take the ones near the road, and appairently there are lotz and lotz of em. wow, its 2 in the morning back home....jon might be online!!! damn!!!!!!!!! arrg, he wasnt online when i was b4...and i couldnt talk much also because uncle neals comp is REALLY super slow. its dial up, but he got it a tiny bit faster by using a remote comp from the airport where he works. it was still NOwhere near my comp, and mine is super slow compaired to my father's even! well i shouldnt complain, it IS after all MSN were talking about here!!! ill have to try to get online sometime soon again, coz yeah, like i said i didnt change my name at all....mebbe ill see if i can go online for a little bit tomorrow morning b4 we leave...damn, uncle neal wont be here to ask, hes working.....owell, i dont think hell mind, i wont be on it long coz ppl are still in skewl for like 2 more dayz and nywayz, we have to leave by like noon at the latest, so...yeah...nywayz, i should get going for tonight...ill talk to yall soon if i can, call me on my cell everyone!!! well...everyone that i know that is reading this...erm....say maybe...jessica? lol, nywayz, the number is 1-519-803-2641 =D nywayz, i luvz yaz all and i miss yaz!!! ttyl!!!! nighty night!!    Day 10 - I SAW TARA!!!  Technically, today isnt today. since i didnt bring my laptop to taras, im writing about wut we did tomorrow....well..it would be tomorrow if this day were really today...basically, today is the 18th and im writing about the 17th, how bout that. nywayz, we lazed around uncle neals till about lunch time and then we were on the road, medicing hat bound!! jessica was my very first call on my cell....it scared the shit outta me!! that things damn loud!!!! lol, well nywayz, we talked for a few mins and then my fone rang again, and it was TARA!!! omg, i didnt recognise her voice!!! =0! *tear* but yeah, we talked for a few and i promised her that id email her back once i got into the Hat. well...we got lost 7 times trying to find her house -_-* but we finally got there and i called her on my cell and i was like, ull never guess where i am! and she had no clue where, so i was like IM OUTSIDE OF UR HOUSE!!!!=D and she was like no way, ur NOT! u cant be!! really?! serious?! and i was like, is there a green car out front? and she was like YES!! (it hurt my ears, she was LOUD, lol) and i was like, thats ME!and i saw ppl in the window of her house and she was like, one sec! and she hung up and ran out andandand yeah, it was AWESOME!! lol.even liam recognised me and he was only like 4 when they left!!! maryanne (taras mom) came out to say hi too, and yeah, it was awesome, so we went in for drinks, and lindz called, so tara was like, guess what?! and linds was like, is she here?!!?! lol. nywayz, she biked over, so that was cool...but b4 she got home, brenden did (taras big bro) and she ran out to the door to tell him, and he did NOT believe that i was there. i dont think he even believed it when he saw me sitting at the kitchen table!!!!! lmfao. his eyes were friggin HUGE!! it was funny. and then a while later, jim (dad) came home, and hes exactly the same, lol, hes scottish and yeah, he sounded like arnold shwartzernigger (yes i know its spelled wrong, shiaddup) a couple time, lmao, twas funny. but yeah, hes still big on the teasing and he was amazed that i was there aswell. katie didnt even know that i was there tho because she goes to the u of c (calgary) so she wasnt at home for taras sweet 16. (damn ppl are all so much older then me!) but yeah, we had pizza for supper and then we had cake, and yeah...lindz hadda go home, so we got a few pics (none on my camera tho coz i was a fucking imbicile and fergot all about the damned thing, so i didnt get pics of ANYONE!! *cries!!!!!!!!!* that makes me sad. very very sad. i feel so STUPID!!! *u r stupid, stoopid* ...wuts ur point? but yeah, mom got a couple of us, and so did lindz, so...hopefully thats good...mebbe i can get her to email them to me, or something...i unno, mail mebbe? *shruggz* nywayz, me and tara and brenden and liam and brendens...gf? friend? something like that, came too. and yeah...wut can i say, we swam. it was a lotta fun. lol, tara pushed everyone but me into the water. it was purdy cool, but i think that if i was closer, brenden woulda pulled me in (so i backed away...waaay away ) and yeah...it was too bad that the water slide was closed tho...there was 3 levels of diving boards too, none of which i had any inkling of desire to jump off of. brenden went off  the highdive, and tara was going to...but she didnt, brenden wanted me too, but yeah....NO!! liam did tho, and so did brendens friend (ill just call her that because my idiot brain cant member her name =S) well nyways, we did end up going in the wave pool and the round about thingie in there, and we went in the hottub too. so that was nice. after that we went and got out a movie (white oleander) and me and tara watched it when we got to her house. (it was pg so liam couldnt see it, and brenden and his gf..or friend, w/e, went out somewhere) so yeah, the movie went till like 11, so i went upstairs and slept up in taras room and she slept in katies room. i think i zonked out around 1 or something because i dont remember brenden coming home, and i know i was up again @ 4 because i looked @ my watch and it was bright enough to see it, so that made sence. someone closed my door in the night too, i think it was maryanne on her way out to work because i dont think nyone else would have bothered, except maybe brenden, but his bedroom is in the basement..sooo..yeah. that was about all that happened....butbutbut IT WAS SOOOOO MUCH FUN!! theyre all the same!! it was like going back in time to when she lived across the street and i could go see her whenever i wanted!! it was like no time had passed between us, and we were still bestest friends!!! =D it was sooo awesome to get to meet lindsay too!!! ack, evil person getting her braces off!! *glares* arrg....but yeah, i brought cookies for taras bday present too, and i think everyone liked them =) at least...i hope they did, lol, nywayz, on to today.....    Day 11  ok, now to write about today =) well, i hadda say goodbye to tara fairly early coz we hadda leave since she still had an english exam, *crosses fingers and wishes her luck* and she was like the only sone up...either that or still there...well nywayz, i got anuver hugg from her (i got huggz from lindz too =) *feels special*) and then we hadda go, but yeah, i cant believe that theyre all the same after 8 yrs!!! = | wow...nywayz, lol, we drove for over an hour, and its a good thing that i dont get carsick now (i havent taken gravol in a while now) so i was reading and singing like the whole drive, and we took a round-about way to drumheller, but the route we took was diff then the norm one. we stopped at Dinosaur Provincial Park, and holy fucking shit, im sorry, but the view from up there is nothing short of breath fucking taking!!! i can NOT believe that!!! besides the look on taras face when she ran out the door (lol) that was the damned most amazing sight that i have ever seen in my life!!!!!!!!!! omg, it was soo...arrg, i cant describe it, not at all, ull all just have to wait for the pics that i took. jess, ur gonna be dewing an AWFUL lotta scanning for me, lol. i dont think that ull mind considering wut ive gotten for ya =) so far ive gotten something for hmm..lets see 4 friends...byron, ben, jake, and jess....i thought id gotten stuff for more ppl then that, but i guess theres a buncha stuff for me in there too, lmao. nywayz..we drove around the park, and took some pics, which were awesome, im just not sure how many turned out =S im prolly gonna have some pretty messed up ones, but i guess ill live. i was reading these things along the way, coz they tell u about the little shelter things that u pull in and stop at along the way, and my friggin father starts blaring the horn after weve been there for like 5 seconds and the dumbass doesnt shut up, and he doesnt wait, he just sits there blaring the fucking horn, and annoying the shit outta me. i hated him!!! like, ive never seen anything that breathtakingly amazing (cept maybe jon, lol) and here he is, wanting to ruin the whole friggin thing for me, and yeah, i just hated him. so we went up to drumheller after that and saw their badlands, but more of the point was to see the dinosaur musium there, and lemme tell u, its totally amazing. its just breathtaking inside. i took a lotta pics in there, and im hoping they all turn out because they were really good. nywayz, we went home after that, and uncle neal cooked us supper (pasgettie, lol) and it was nummyfullz, so...yeah...that was good...and then i watched much music for a while, but i got tired so i decided to come down here and type all this up, and ive been at it for like half an hour now, and from all of the excitement, im REALLY super tired. i think im still shell-shocked about seeing lindsay and tara....it prolly wont dawn on me just how HUGE of a deal that was till we get to toronto, lol. nywayz, i should go get some sleep, i think were going to banff tomorrow, but i was falling alseep nywayz, so im not sure wut was planned now....btw laura, I SAW ONW OF UR BENDIE BUSSES ON THE WAY TO MEDICINE HAT!! lol, it was funkie!!! nywayz, ill talk to yall lataz tonight and ill try to get on msn if at all possible tomorrow!! if not then..i unno...ill prolly just see u when i get home because its wednesday right now....and so tomorrow being thursday if we go to banff and into bc....and then after that theres only friday, and then we leave on friday night at like 11 to get to the airport in time, and we leave on our flight at like 1:30 or w/e and then we get to toronto by like 6:30 (time change) and..hmm...yeah.....i hope to god that we dont do anything on friday if we go to banff tomorrow, im soooo damn sick and tired of highways =S nywayz, ill letchaz know wuz up asap, luvz yaz all!!! night!!   Day 12  well today was boring. we didnt go to banff acuz it was rainy and cloudy and icky and we wouldnt have been able to see a thing, so we lazed around uncle neals for a while...as in all day...and that was about it. im now about halfway thru my stephen king book, so thats a perk...no one called me on my cell....i DEW have voice mail u know...*cries* nywayz, yeah, we really didnt dew nything, but now that i think of it i should likely have repacked my suitcase, coz now ill have to dew it tomorrow and i was hoping to sleep all of tomorrow since were taking a red-eye flight....and then after that ill have to stay up all day on msn because DUH, msn withdrawl for 2 weeks!! need to get back into the habit!!! and then imma be going over to jessicas to watch the poltergyste 2 and the poltergyste 3 wit her and ben and ake since we saw the first one all together. i imagine well be having pizza or sumthin there too...so yeah. well nywayz, i wanna listen to some music tonight since i really havent indulged in any music listening other then cds, which have a very poor selection compaired to my mp3s....so yeah...nywayz, im sure tomorrow will be boring, but ill write about it and my flight on wut will technically be the 14th day (ie when i get home) and yeah...ill talk to yall lataz, luvz yaz!!! btw jess, i mailed u a postcard and i mailed byron one aswell =) NIGHTZ!    Part 4 - HOME!     Day 13...and 14 too i spose...its kinda all the same...  ahhhh, HOMENESS!!! ahhhhhh HIGHSPEED INTERNET!!!! *grins* im so haPPY!!!! lol, and movies tonight wit friends, so sall good!! arrrg, jess is buggin me to put this up, but imma write it like normal, sooo yeah. wow, ppl actually missed me??!?! *feels loved*   *"dont get used to it"* wuteva *shruggz* well nywayz, yeah, yesterday was pretty much like th day b4, we were just lazing around all day until uncle neal came home and we ate some of mommys homemade chicken soup, but it wasnt quite as good as home...owell. yeah, then after that uncle normie took us out to his weed patch. he calls it that coz its a piece of land that isnt really big, and its covered in weeds (ud wunder, wouldnt ya?) and yeah. uncle neal got the land when cathy tried to get it, but she lost, she still has ppl bording horses on it tho, and he lost a buncha $$ from that because the horses ate a couple of trees that he had bought that were worth a fair amount of money. i wouldnt want my horses turned out in that tho, its rusty barbed wire with tons of prairy dog holes EVERYWHERE! *shudders* damn beasts! well nywayz....imma feel bad if a horsie gets a leg broke, but hopefully that wont happen. uncle neal is gonna prolly sell the land and get money from realestate ppl who'll build houses coz the weedpatch overlooks a nice view of the mountains, which we never got a chance to really drive out and see. nywayz, i said hi to tha horsies and we left. we repacked everything @ uncle normies and then he drove us to tha airport and showed us all around where he works (he works at the airport if i didnt mention that already) yeah...uhm then we went thru security and i hadda take off my damn belt cozza all tha metal arrrg and i hadda get my laptop outta the bottom of the bag to show them it and it pissed me off coz it was a huge pain in the ass to get it out and stuff, lol. but yeah...the plane ride was kinda like a glorified rollercoaster cept really boring. but it was still kinda fun. and yeah, we brought our own food, so we didnt have to eat ny of that dippy crap that they give u, lol. but yeah, we got to watch the sun rise thru the clouds and it was really beautiful! but yeah, taht was about the most exciting thing that happened...other then the fact that i was the only one that left the overhead light on to read ALL night long and im like the only one who didnt sleep on the red-eye, lol. but yeah...we found dave after we landed but it took a while coz my luggage was the very last one out, of course, so then we booted it back here to guelph coz dave was late for work, lol. but my face is a friggin mess from all the crap that ive been eating lately, lol.....owell, i spose ill live! well...i should go so that jess can read this WHOOOOLE thing for she tears my head off for not having it posted =) so, ill ttyl, luvz yaz, buh byez!!     THAT WAS MY TRIP TO ALBERTA!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hewwo  y am i updating this?!?! owell, im bored...thats about all i have to say....LAURA AND NICOLE, GET UR ASSES IN GEAR AND UPDATE UR BLOGS!! lol. there like....OLD! and byron, uve gotta call me...or...SOMEthing!! i unno, ill prolly call u tomorrow or somethin....not that u even read my blog, so screw that...nywayz, i should go now, ttyl, luvz yaz, buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Bored  This was just one of those days that nothing happened! it was soooo slow! i could have done my skewl work all day, but i thought that i was going to lisas house, which i didnt, then i thought that i was swimming, but nope, then i thought that i was going berry picking, but my mom fergot about that, so we didnt get to go to that either. about the most exciting thing that happened was that i went to the mall the other day with nikki-bop. but yeah, theres nothing to do. I at least finally got byron's trail ride planned out! lol. were going this saturday. weve been planning this trail ride for like 9 months now!!! thats crazy!! lol, i actually owe him 3 rides, the one that we were sposed to meet on, the one for his bday (that was april 7th and hes getting the ride for it saturday) and then my birthday wich is comin up in august! lol. i know u all think that im crazy to be typing that there, but...im not!! *dances around the room, falling over many many things because its very hard to dance in a straight jacket (straight jacket?!? whered that come from!?) when ur in a padded cell (wut!? whered my room go?!) with the nice young men in their clean white coats observing u (ok, this is getting freaky!!) like a bug in a jar* byron neva reads this, so im safe *(but just in case) huddles with eminem and HIS straight jacket in the corner* Anywayz, I should go now b4 i cause more trouble to myself *little voice plots evil revenge against the world* i want to rule PEI!! thats all i want, i swear!! *lil voice glares at me* oops! i mean...*looks angelic* we arent planning a total world domination in which the little voices of the future will rule and enslave all of man kind! *little voice kicks me* imma be quiet now.  Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Feeling  Okay, i think that i am offically going insane. I dont know what I feel anymore because it doesnt seem like i feel anything. ppl who have known me for a really long time know that i used to adore my father. he used to be the sun the moon and the stars. and now it makes me sick to my stomach to think that i used to think that way. The only feeling that i can dredge up for him is a very strong sence of hatred, which i need a stronger word for....loathing maybe? and a small shard of dull pain. i hate that man with everything in me. he is embarrasing and he harasses my friends. he freakes out about the smallest things and he wants to control my life. hes got a mental disorder, i know, but the fact is that i really dont care. I dont care that hes sick and that he cant control his actions or words anymore, i just dont care. he doesnt help his case miuch when he gives away my fishing pole and my lures and all of my other fishing stuff to the kid next door! i know it prolly made him really really happy and everything, but there was a few hundred dollars worth of fishing stuff there! My mother is seriously depressed and now suicidal, which isnt good with a full bottle of tylonal/codene3 and a lot of other perscription meds in our kitchen. its not a good thing to have them there for me either particularly because i dont know how much longer i can carry a mentally unable father and a permanently broken down mother to keep this sham of a family together. I'm already falling apart. I hang out with other ppl as much as i possibly can, im not at jessicas house as much any more, but ive been hanging out with lisa and cory a lot lately. its a lot of fun being able to go over there whenever and just hang out. i think im overstaying my welcome tho, she and her mom seem to be getting kinda pissed at seeing me walk in the door almost every day. Ive only seen laura like twice this summer, and neither time was for very long. One highlight that id like to point out was going to see Pirates of the Carribean with lisa, cory, and byron. that was a hell of a movie!! i loved it!! appairently were gonna go see it again sometime, but the guys just wanna play the shooting game after it. ive been talking to jessicas mom about a lot of the crap that has been going on lately, and that seems to help a little bit, tho not as much as id like, because even tho ill talk once in a while, it doenst get rid of the feelings. and now im getting in shit for never being home, but if i am home, i get into just as much shit! i cant do anything right, not that any teenager can seem to be able to do that, but i dont know what to do anymore. I need to get away, but I dont have anywhere to go. Loving life is not possible anymore. i dont think that it has been for quite a while now, i just never realized it till now. And Jon sent me an email like 2 days after i last updated this and basically told me that i was never going to see him or hear from him again. I sent him an email back saying that i at least wanted an explination about that, but i havent gotten an answer yet, and i dont think im going to, but ive been considering emailing him again. when i was talking to byron a little while ago and i mentioned that, he started flipping out on me and saying that i should stay away from jon and not emial him or try to talk to him again because he was prolly a rapist that was going to come and rape me and then kill me and i dont know whether to want to bitch slap byron for being an ass, or wonder y the hell he got so protective all of a sudden, coz he knew about jon a loong time ago...i dont know anymore. ud think that the shit with my family and the crap with jon would make me sad, eh? well all it does is make me....not feel i guess....its not hatred for jon, i still think i love him, and for my father it is hatred...but its not as simple as that...or maybe it is and i just cant see it...all i know is that i havent shed a single tear over either of them and i dont think that ill be able to. i havent cried about losing my friends, and ive been considering going to GCVI, but im not sure about that yet. I havent cried at all about anything other then the season finnally of Dawson's creek, or the occasional sad song that ill hear..but thats not crying about myself. i dont talk to any of my friends about this kind of stuff anymore because they get very bitchy. i dont blame them tho, they have just as many problems and i dont need to add to them. I dont see why im still here because, in all truthfulness, i am the one and only thing keeping my mother from either going crazy and killing herself or, the better alternative, leaving my father, and if it werent for me, she would never have married him in the first place. shes told me this herself a few times. Id like to leave or run away, or just not wake up one morning...i know its terrible to say, but things would really be better off that way...unfortunately, it doesnt look like any of those things are possibilities for my future, so i guess im stuck here.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Back To School  I hate those words. They are the epidimy of EVILNESS! owell, i dont go back to skool till the 16th, so wut am i complaining about?? =P well, the end of summer was, shall we say interesting. The very last week was pretty hecktic. i started my riding lessons again, then we all decided (we all being cory lisa byron and me) to go camping, but that had to be postponed, and then they had to go to GCVI to get lisas lil sisters schedual on wednesday, then gramma came here with a bday cake for me!! =D it was yummy! people came back from GCVI for cake and stuff and then we all went for my Bday trail ride!! it was so much fun!! =D =D right away when we got back we left for the trailer. I havent been up there since i was eight years old!!! i cant believe how much i missed it!!! me and lisa were sposed to sleep in the main cabin with my parents and the guyz were sposed to be out in the bunkhouse, but the first night they all got scared, and we were all pissed off at my father (he pulled over every 2 seconds on the way up, turning a 2 hr drive into a 5 and a half hour one!!!!) so we begged and pleaded until we were all allowed to sleep in the bunkhouse. nobody really slept much the first night tho. we left the lanterns all on fairly high and the windows shut coz it was cold, but the fumes from the lamps got me and lisa sick. so its liek 2 in the morning and were all sitting outside because were not feeling good. then we finally went back inside and fell asleep (i think that the smores that we made and all the laffing because 4 hotdogs fell into the fire and my parents didnt end up eating any didnt help our stomachs much...plus laffing at the guys because they were scared shitless to go anywhere, and byron refused to go out of the cabin or away from the fire unless he was clinging onto me and a lantern, hehe) but i hadda get up like an hour later to go to the bathroom, and its like a 5 min walk in the dark to the outhouse because u cant see and its all rocky and slippery and stuff, so i poked everyone to try to get someone to come with me, just for company, and everyone was like friggen dead, so i went by myself, and ppl were surprised that i wasnt scared....but i like grew up out there, i like the woods, even at night!! lol. well anywayz, the next day i got up at like 7 and went to go get my book and some coffee, but coffee wasnt ready yet, so i brought my book back to the bunkhouse (IT WAS ONLY 10 DEGREES OUTSIDE!!=S) and i woke lisa up when i came back inside, then we started talking and woke the boys up (oops!) so cory got up, but byron just grumbled and grabbed my arm and used it as a teddy bear, which didnt work because id prefer to keep my shoulder socket in place, so i hadda climb up onto his bunk and sit there with him till he decided to get up, but i think i fell asleep at one point because i layed down and then cory and lisa were like....being annoying, lol and they woke me up. aroung 11-ish lisa went to the bathroom and came back with the good news that the coffee was ready, so i went back since i was too lazy to get dressed yet, and the rest of them followed soon after, byron being the last one out of bed of course, lol. we had something to eat then went back to get changed (me and lisa did anywayz) and we got out bikes and biked into town...the hill into Wiarton is sooooooo fucking awsome to ride down!!! i LOVE it!!! its really really steep....but it was a long way to get out there, lol. we went down to the docks and saw where i thought we were going fishing, but it turned out that we werent going there, we were going somewhere else instead...the river where my mom caught some huge small-mouth bass out of season, lol. anywho, we also went to a convenience store and bought firecrackers and sparklers, and pop and candy and food. then we biked back to the trailer (cory biked up the hill, me and lisa walked all the way, and byron walked about halfway.) it was a fairly long ride, but we all made it. when we got back it was like 1:30 or 2 in the afternoon i think, maybe a bit later, and mom and dad were back (they went into town too, in the car) and so we had KD for lunch, then we went fishing, then we went swimming at Sauble, then we got Ice Cream and Subs, and we went to the docks to eat them, out where we used to fish, and we fed some ducks and tried fishing there too, but no one caught anything and i was afraid that i was going to hook a duck. (cory hooked a water snake by the river and we gathered quite a crowd of ppl that were fishing to look...he got it in the belly though, trying to bring it closer to see wut kind of snake it was because it wasnt a garter snake. someone thought that it was a water mocason, so he was being really really careful not to get biten...unfortunately, it pissed on him instead and we realized that it was a fox snake instead. his hands REEKED!!) anywayz, we went back home and got the fires going again and made more smores, this time with chocolate that lisa bought at the store, and they turned out a lot better because it was a hersheys cookies and cream bar which is thinner and melts better. we also had chippies and i think cory attempted cooking hotdogs again, but i cant remember. but then i ate too much and i didnt feel well so i went and got a gravol and went back to the cabin (after we put out the fire of course) and then lisa wanted her hair braided, so i did that for her, then cory decided that he didnt feel well, so i took him back to the cabin for a gravol and he got an empity beer bottle aswell, so we got back and we all played spin the bottle for a while...i thought that it was just cory coming up with an inventive way to kiss me (hes been trying all summer) but appairently it was byrons idea? *confused* well anywayz, not long after that we all got into bed, but i couldnt sleep and neither could byron, so he turned on a lamp and i read for a while, but then cory got grouchy, so we turned it off and i fell asleep like, instantly and i slept all night long. we left the windows open a bit too, so no one got sick. next morning byron got cold because cory stole his sleeping bag, so he climbed into my bunk and decided that i was a teddy bear again, and fell back asleep!! lol! we eventually all got up and packed up our stuff and got everything in the car and the truck and ready to go. the drive back was long again, but i slept thru a lot of it because cory was smoothing my eyebrows with him thumb, which my mother used to do when i was little, and it puts me to sleep like that *snaps fingers* we got back to guelph in time for everyone to go home and shower, then we had to wait for laura chan to get here and then we all went and got movies to watch at byrons house for his movie marathon thingie. well, it started out well, the guys got the tv into the basement and we watched Basic, which confused us all, and then we went and moved the tv into the other room after watching 8 Legged Freaks, which i bruised my knuckes during (im terrified of spiders, and when they all come out all at once i started chewing my knuckles) laura and byron went upstairs to warm up some pizza pockets and they were gone for a while...anywayz, lisa was asleep in the other room, so me and cory were watching Candyman, which scares him, lol. so he was slightly clingie because he didnt really remeber the movie, but i did, so i was half warning him about parts that were coming up. after candyman i put in we 3 kings i think and i fell asleep thru part of it...laura and byron having returned like ages before...but when i woke up i really wasnt feeling well, and lisa had given up the bed thing to laura and byron and layed on the matresses in the rec room with me and cory, but then i hadda get up to run to the bathroom coz i thought that i was gonna barf, but i didnt, and when i went back, i was shivering and i couldnt stop...i think i scared cory because he kept telling me to calm down and stop shivering and stuff, so he eventually got up and asked byron where the gravol was, so i took one, and i still wasnt feeling good, but it made me sleep a little bit at least. at about 6:30 when i STILL wasnt feeling well, i called my mom and got her to come pick me up from byrons house. i slept somewhat more at home, but i kept thinking that i was at byrons house, and when my mom came over to wrap the blanket around me, which i didnt want around me, i yelled "cory" thinking that it was him doing it, and my mom thought that i was calling  for  him =S that woke me up quick enough =S but then everyone came over at about 11 or so to see how i was doing, and my father was a fucking asshole bastard and started yelling at cory and screaming that he knew what cory'd done to me, etc, etc, thinking that he raped me or something and that was a load of bull shit, so cory was yelling back asking what it was that he had done, and it sounded like he was ready to punch my father and that my father was ready to fight back. then lisa stepped in, sounding extreemly pissed off, saying that all we did was watch movies, which was technically true (cept for when we went to the park to light off cherry bombs and laura had a smoke) laura chan was out on the deck and apairently she started crying, and byron was just inside the door, but he didnt say anything at all. they all left because the old retard kicked them out, but my mom followed them to the street and tried to comfort laura, which didnt really work because she ended up crying too. anywayz, when she came back in she started yelling and screaming at my father saying that he didnt know what he was talking about and that that was the last straw, he was terrorizing kids and he should never have accused cory, and hed upset laura, and that he was gonna be outta here and everything. i liked that fight...id like it more if she followed thru on everything because she said that he would be gone in like a week and, guess what, big surprise, hes still here!! He also called the fucking cops to come down!! ugh!!!! i hate that man!!! he said that mom was going crazy and screaming at him and everything and that there was a guy who did something to me. the cop came and he was at the house for like 2 hours, talking to both of my parents, he finally got the story straight from my mom who asked him if we could send him to the homewood or something, but appairently thats not how that works, so the cop eventually left and my mother wouldnt speak to anyone like all day long. well anywayz, i got better that night and went to lisas house for cake and ice cream because they were celebrating lisa's and rachel's bdays that night. i ended up sleeping over because i was there pretty late and i rode my bike to get there. byron was there too, and sometime, the next day i think, we were all on the trampoline and cory went to jump over me, but i moved or something and he landed on my eye and then fell off the trampoline but his foot caught in the pad a bit and he ended up tripping and landing funny on his ankel which broke off part of the bone. so lisas mommy took him to the hospital and they said that if the swelling didnt go down in 3 days he hadda go back and they might have to operate...but he was perfectly fine. he came back the first weekend after skewl started even tho he wasnt really supposed to, and we all went moonlight bowling at woodlawn bowl and i got 3 strikes in a row!!!! =D =D the third one won us a free game, i think i won two or three and lisa got the other one....if i only got 2 then either cory or byron got the last one. butbut yeah. it was SOOOO much fun!!! lol. and it was only my second time EVER bowling!!! =D whee!! *little voice kicks me* dammit! well anywho, yeah...thats about all thats happened really....my life is so uninteresting...im going to kill my father, i forgot to mention that he ripped out my speakers downstairs!!! im hoping that they still work because i finally got my launch up and running again and then the fucking retard decides that the music was too loud and he wont even wait till the end of the song, which is what my mom said i could do, he just stomps in and yells and rips out the speakers and yells some more, so i yelled back and i think i pissed him off pretty badly because he looked like he wanted to hit me. but uhm...yeah....oh the other thing that was weird was that this morning i got my marks thing, cept that all i got was the Virtual Learning Centre Honours Certificate....there was no report card, so i know that my mark is higher then 80 coz i got honours, but i dont know how MUCH higher, lol. well anywayz, this is REALLY long, soo imma go now! Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Poem...   I got bored and was looking around in my old comp and i came up with this poem. It's pretty old, and things have gotten a lot worse in my little world since i wrote this, but owell, its going up anywayz.  They see me as though thru a foggy mirror only a shadow of myself. Wear my heart on my sleeve  put myself aside for others  my feelings collecting dust on the shelf. I cant be what they want me to be though i try i cant live the life they want me to Ill listen to the music i like Ill live how i want ill pass highskewl without setting foot in the skewl. my dad'll call me shit but i wont care ive had enough of this life my friends will leave but i wont  care its all on the next roll of the dice. Its all or nothing and the way things are going i dont thinks its all this life screws most ppl but some get off  easy while the  rest of us crawl no one really cares i know that now it seems so obvious to me it doenst really matter none of it does so the rest of u can skip with glee for all i care cuz it dont matter to me anymore it  never will i drift away into my own world its all going black as my blood i spill 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       New Years!!   Okay, so im jus a lil early....hush! Haha, in a few hours there'll only be 24 days till xmas!!! ya man!!! that means that theres only 26 days till Jack comes down!!!!=D yay! *dances around the room till lil voice hits me on the head*...*rubs bump on head* but uhm ya, Matt's comin down too!! ya Matt, ur in my blog!!! ur so special!! lol. (hes been buggin me relentlessly to update my blog and my website for like ever!) So ya, Jack and Laura (Chan) are coming up fro New Years and Matt might be comin too....thing is, we're not sure about laura comin yet.....she has yet to make up her mind. But Jack has said that hes coming down, even if he has to go as far as to get rides from sexually questionable truck drivers, lmao. im not completely sure where everyones going to sleep tho....when it was just laura and jack coming it would be laura in my room, me on the couch and jack in the basement computer room on the air mattress.....but now that it might be matt too, i guess he and jack will have to share the air mattress, or else ill sleep on the floor in my room, laura will have the bed, and matt or jack will be on the couch....well have to see how exactly this all works out... but uhm ya, i told Matt that id update this, and something tells me that hes going to be awful happy that hes mentioned=P hehe. but uhm ya, ill write more when it gets closer to New Years and xmas coz i also said that id update my site, since i havent done that in like...AGES! lol. Ttyl! Luvz yaz! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Holidays...   I was at ma grammas today and saw the family. it was fun. i like being able to see everyone together at the same time for the holidays. its one of the less depressing aspects. one of the more depressing views is realizing how little u mean in the world. lets play a little game. i call it who matters more. k, we'll start with the ppl who are pretty much my best friends. cory and lisa matter more to each other than either to me, so chalk two up for the other side. then theres the guy that i had my heart set on for the longest time and whose now getting married at the ripe old age of 18...who matters more now? obviously not me. prolly never was me to begin with. laura clayton doesnt talk to me anymore, same with nicole and judy and malorie and megan and pretty much all of my old friends, so i guess i dont matter much to them either. come to think of it, it even goes as far as jack. who matters more, me or laura? hmm, lets see, uhh...laura! wow, was that ever hard. my mom cares more about her misery and self pittying denial of happiness and acceptance of depression than she does about me, and even im a traitor. i care more about the fact that no one cares about me than i do about caring about myself. not that that makes any sence  whatsoever to anyone but myself. it feels like im never going to find someone for me. anyone i meet online will be either too far away, a rapist, or a backstabbing cheater whose name still makes my heart wrench because of all the promises he made me. whatever happened to coming and visiting me in the summer jon? hmm? and leaving me something really close to u to proove to me that u were comming back? oh wait, i guess i kno the answer to that dont i. brittany happened. u even told me that u wished u had ur virginity back because u wanted it to be with the quote "right person"....do u have any  idea  how much that hurts? how it tears me up inside? of course not. but then it doesnt matter because im just some kid that lives across the country that actually fell for u and u had fun leading on for a while till u got tired of it. and its funny coz it doesnt even matter if it matters or not because ull never read this anywayz. unless of course i gave u the url, which im not planning on dewing. i havent cried, not for u. and i wont. it just doesnt seem like im ever going to get a chance at like anything.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       CHRISTMAS!! YAY!! life....ugh   twas xmas today! which was great, lol, i got lots of awsome stuff and i had a great time. Unfortunately, life as of lately hasnt been anywhere near so aimiable. it seems like every single thing that i look forward to lately is being taken away. last month or the beginning of this month or something shane was sposed to take me to the royal in toronto coz he missed giving me a bday prezzie, and he was gonna take me coz ya...big brother and he lives in toronto so it would have worked....but that didnt work because he was workin. so that got cancelled. then matt wasnt allowed to come down at all for new years, which made me sad. and lisa was like flipping out about it for ages and whining somewhat, which got a bit annoying, but meh. so that sucked. then laura kept changing her mind about coming to guelph and i finally got her to agree that she would stay so thats good at least....but jacks gramma got sick so he missed his xmas and hes in NY visiting her in the hospital, so hes not allowed to come for new years!!! *cries* this really really sux. im really glad that laura is coming, dont get me wrong, but i really really wanted jack to come! i was really looking forward to meeting him. we had like the whole week planned out, and now lisa and laura arent getting along very well, so were all split up and nothing that was planned is really going to happen after all. i didnt even get half of what i wanted for xmas....like stead of batteries and lip balm, each of which i have a tonne of, mom could have put that like 10 bucks toward a game for my gameboy or something, i donno. i shouldnt complain tho but i kinda wish id gotten more, or some stuff different or something, i donno. cant seem to shake the feeling of disappointment but i donno y coz it takes me a really long time to list everything that i got for xmas this year. i guess im just a spoiled brat. too bad. well, theres a buffy marathon on right now, so im going to go cuddle up in my new blankey and watch it since theres nothing better to do.  Ttyl lataz! Luvz yaz!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Week With Laura!  Haha, last week was awsome! laura was the only one that ended up coming down at all, and she and lisa werent getting along, plus i didnt really wanna go to lisas new years thingie, so nobody went cept for tenesha and cory, lol. nywayz, yeah, we did a whole buncha stuff, including walking for like 3 hours to get coke and sharpen our (well....technically mine and jack's skates coz yeah, laura stole his, lol) skates and get coke for laura coz yeah, coke-a-holic, lol. and then we went to the movies that night and saw Lord Of The Rings: The Return of the King, and yeah, it was awsome!!!! and the next day we like....biked 20 mins (wind resistance, very  billowy and byrons/my bike kept like dying on the way there, so yeah, laura hadda keep stopping to fix the chain...) to get to the West End Rec. Centre, and then we skated for 2 hours then we biked home again....uphill this time! lol! well....we kinda cheated, we walked up the hill =P we watched movies for New Years and i think it went candyman2, silence of the lambs.....to finding nemo!! lmao, that was a jump, but it was funny...and then we watched pirates of the carribean...so yeah, it was fun, and we didnt go to bed till like........late, liek really late....we watched movies most of the next day too i think, and we went to my grammas house on friday and she got to meet tessa and milena, but for some reason phil wasnt there and neither was taman or arrie.....it was strange.....but yeah, fun..i lost at pool, of course, lol. and we watched the velvetiene rabbit, which i havent seen in like forEVER!! lmao, omg, i used to LOVE that movie sooooooo much!!! lol. uhhh yeah...not much after that, but i took laura to riding and i got her on a horse! *is proud* not that i really did anything....i asked if shed like to ride and she seemed kinda indesicive, so i was like ohhh, cmon!! and yeah, she rode, which according to her mommy and to jack is like a huge deal, lol. so yeah, she went home after we got back, but it was really really fun having her here, lol. and ive been invited to go and stay up at her house at some point in time, lol, so sall good =) Anywayz, i just felt like typing for some reason and yeah, good times, so y not write about it? but yeah, i gotta go coz sleep and ..... yea.....sleep......=P Ttyl!! Luvz yaz! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm FREE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  IM FREEEEE!!!!!!!!!! theres no school for two months and theres no exam and mine are done and no school for 2 weeks and easy courses this semester and i get time off and i dont have to wake up and i LOVE it and and and *hyperventalates and falls over dead* *little voice: 'well thats the end of that!'*   HA!! no!! *comes back to life and flicks little voice away!! AHAHAHAHAHA *points and laffs*   wheeee im hyper and i dunno y....lol, dan and jake jus left, we were hangin out this aft, we and david (jakes lil bro) went toboggonning and then we went to rent out a movie and we got IT for some reason...its a crappy movie, but meh....good story, crappy animation, we'll put it that way. the books better.....ive said that a lot tonight =S anyways, yeah, we got thru that movie okay, and then we watched Ice Age! TY KWAN DODOS!!! eh laura?!?!? lmao! *ahem* yeah, jake fell asleep in the middle of it tho, lol. ive made a buncha new friends lately man! theres dan, john, rob, joel, and some other person from msn, lol. its pretty funny, me and rob have waaayyyyyyy too much in common tho man, its pretty creepy!! lol. were both like on msn 24-7, we like the same music, even country! and yeah, its funny. theres not really much to talk about....lol, not a lot really going on lately...wheeee....HEYYY!!! we were sposed to go skating man!!!! i fergot about that! ....considering jake fell asleep on my floor im guessing he forgot too and yeah, dan never mentioned it so meh. i didnt get to ride chester!!!! *cries* they made me ride reesiekins instead (reese for all of those who dont understand the nicknames i have for horses, lol) it was fun tho, a bit of a change-up i spose. and hes soooooo much more comfy than chester!! yeesh! hehehe, im dragging ppl for a trail ride as soon as the weather's good enough =) not sure who all im taking but a tentitave list would be dan, john, jake, rob, ben, jess, and .... and .... hmm....cant be lisa coz cory just moved in and hell wanna go coz theres a whole bunch of guys going...uhhhhm gah, there was someone else that i was gona invite...omG! arrg...meh, ill think of something, im not taking all those ppl out on the trail while its still cold out coz ppl will only complain man. but yeah, forcing them later, lol *laffs maniacly* *people run screaming* *looks angelic* uhhhh yeah, so im bored, did i mention that before? ooooo, it looks as tho my space bar has decided to unstick itself man!!!! *knocks on wood* yea, i dunno......im boooooored! lookit, its a saturday, not even holidays yet and im BORED! arrrg! lalala......whoa man, everyones getting sick!!! laura clayton, now laura chan, matt, crystal, lol. lotza themz! whoa, pairently dan and jake are comin back tomorrowz.... innnnnteresting....i spose that means i cant go back to sleep after i get up......dang! meh, i shall live....as long as neither of them comes near me with show or pours water on me to wake me up =S or makes me run around outside in the snow..MATT!!!!!!!!! lol, uhm yeah, im sure ppl think im totally screwed in the head, and i wouldnt want to ruin that image now, would i? =P Ttyl, luvz yaz!! Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Saturday…    Well, last Saturday (yesterday) was interesting to say the least…my wrist is now purple =S… k, maybe I should technically begin this from the Friday……k, well, me and dan and john were hanging out at my house and we were invited over to jessicas house to play board games and yeah, just kinda hang out…well that was fine, we played like taboo, kurplunk, pictionary, life, clue, and madgab. That took us till like midnight but somewhere in there…I dunno, mebbe in the middle of pictionary or something, jessica went and asked her mom if we could all stay the night, (ben was there too) and, surprisingly, sandy said yes! Lol. So after madgab, me and jess went downstairs and watched a little TV before we fell asleep, but appairently crystal and the guys were up all night long watching TV and having some discussion about ice cubes and they did a science experiment =S. so we got up early…well….fairly early…and jessica and her daddy and chelsea went to the barn and sandy drove us home a little later that day coz yeah, twas very very cold outside! I was gonna take john and dan to the barn with me, so we were watching Ginger Snaps (I taped it at home) and yeah…..stupid freaking tape cut off the ending, which was around like 12:30 or something, so I hadda go get dressed and then was waiting for like ever for david to come, getting more and more pissed off at my father by the second because he was being so stupid about everything, saying over and over that dan should get a job…like what the hell?? Anywayz, he was really really really starting to piss me off and yeah, not much that I could dew about it but yeah….trying to sit there and ignore but got a huge-ass headache so I went and took a tylonal, which was good because it was like 2 o’clock and my brother was NOT THERE! So im like freaking out that ive missed my lesson, and fathers being a fucking retard and yeah, guys were kinda freaked out by all the yelling at this point I think. And then Perfect by Simple Plan came on so I like turned it up a bit, not even all that much really, and he stomped in and was freaking out that it was too loud and I should turn it down and all that crap, which of course made me put it louder because he wouldn’t let me hear just the one song. So he went for the TV and I told him not to and he almost hit me so I got really pissed because john and dan were still on the couch and yeah… so I went to stop him and whatever I did gave me whiplash which is still hurting like a bitch, and he almost hit me again which was really starting to piss me off and he pushed me so I pushed back and he was like threatening me and I was screaming at him not to threaten me again, which he did anywayz of course so I shoved him outta my way and stomped to the back door, threw on my shoes and coat and went outside and sat on the corner of the deck, slamming the door fairly hard on my way out of course. And yeah, dan and john were dressed in like record time, I swear! And they came outside too, I think john thought I was crying or something but I was still just sooo pissed off, so we went around the corner of the house, me kinda not talking that much coz yeah embarrassed and they had a smoke. During which time my father came outside like eighteen freakin times and im still yelling and swearing at him to get his stupid ass back inside because hes such a loser and I hate him and all that and john keeps popping up inbetween me and him and he was like caaaalm down, noo, no, take a breath, no! don’t yell! Caaalllm! And yeah, it was funny, lol. And then we moved farther along the house so maybe he wouldn’t bug us as much, but that didn’t quite work, so dan stood like RIGHT in front of me and yeah, his evil 6’3” tallness kept me from seeing my father so I wasn’t quite as pissy but I could still hear him so john did his little make me laff thing again and then I gave my father the finger for like the last thing he said or something and john was like nooo, theres no need for that now! Like all shocked and it was freakin funny!! But yeah, we eventually went back inside but only long enough for me to get changed and get a twenty so we went to coffee time and I got dan a pop and a donut. Then we went across the street since they had a little bit of breakfast at jessicas house but I didn’t and I got a sub and they split one…now they both wanna give me 20 bucks coz ive payed for food for them twice and the movies once…..but yeah im only letting them pay me ten each for movies coz that’s all I said they hadda pay me for, lol. Anywayz we ate and then mom called me and she was home so we went home and hung out for a bit, my wrist really starting to hurt by this time, and we jus like sat around for a while, then john wanted to watch the Lion King 2 so we did and cory and lisa came over too. For most of the movies, we watched like 2 or 3, I cant member, dan and I were using each other as pillows….it worked quite well too tho im not completely sure how seeing as hes a full foot taller than me =S…but yeah, anywayz, then I ferget what happened but ppl moved around and john was beside me on my left on the couch and lisa was on the other side of me and she put her legs over my lap and her feet were like on johns stomach and hes asthmatic (he also smokes which don’t help), but anywayz, cory came and jumped on my lap, which drove lisas feet into johns stomach, which set him off on an asthma attack, which scared the crap out of me because ive only ever seen jessica and lisa having asthma attacks and theirs werent nearly that bad =S….it didn’t help that mom has no idea about what to dew to help asthmatics and yeah….he eventually calmed down and was breathing enough to get out to the car and mom took him to lisas house because yeah, he has a blue puffer same as lisas but lisas house was closer. So yeah they were gone like half an hour and im freaking out and calling like every 2 mins to make sure hes okay but no one was answering the fone and yeah….then dans mom came coz he didn’t call to say where he was and he was in trouble so he couldn’t go bowling and he went home…and shortly after that I finally got thru to lisa and she said that they were on their way back home again so yeah, all was good and john was okay now, still a bit shaky that’s all. So he came back in and yeah, we were trying to figger out who all was going bowling because john still wanted to go but we needed one more person for a party discount. So we called megan and got her to come and john sat in the back with me and lisa on the way to her house and used me as a pillow and slept for like five mins, lol….then we kinda hadda squish a little for megan to fit too, she sat in the front with jake and the rest of us were in the back, me still being used as a pillow, lol. But yeah, we played jus one game at the alley, which I didn’t completely lose at least! I beat lisa!!…..shes the only one I beat…but I beat lisa!!! lol. john didn’t wanna go home yet but when we caught the bus he went anywayz so he woudlnt get into trouble…plus his light was on so he didn’t have to sleep outside, lol. Me an lisa went back to her house and yeah fell asleep on the couch watching movies, but my neck hurts a lot from that now =S bad idea. But yea cory came over and I like slept all day long and cory and lisa watched some movies, lol. But yeah, not such a bad day today, they stayed for supper and we watched the second pocahontas movie at lisas whim and then shrek, lol. They went to lisas hockey game and just got back a few mins ago, they tied, 2-2, lisa didn’t score, but she was close. I should likely go tho because I have to walk cole to skool in the morning (oh joy of joys, waking up early =S) but yeah, if I don’t sleep again im going to be beyond bitchy and that wont be good =S .  So im going to post this a day late because I cant get into my msn or internet upstairs and yeah its kinda really stupid and annoying and id love to kill it but I cant so meh. Im hoping that dan can fix it tomorrow coz pairently hes comin ova, lol. And then theres the church sleepover on Friday =D that’s gonna be fun, get a chance to hang out with like rob and pplz and yeah. But nywayz, night night all ye faithful readers! Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Another Busy Weekend, LoL   This weekend was sooo much fun man! lol. on friday, me dan and john went to youth group for the sleepover thingie and omg it was sooo much fun!!!! jess was there but she hadda leave after a bit, there were just a few too many ppl there. anywayz, megan and jake were there, and rob, and.....and.....i dunno if there was anyone else....BEN! ben was there too, lol. anywayz, we played like double dutch and stuff at first and chinese skipping and the boiz played basket ball and then everyone went upstiars to watch movies. there were six in all i think we counted. there was bruce almighty, the truman show, indiana jones, prince of egypt, pass it forward, and contact. i fell asleep, well not sleep, but like half awakeness for about....half an hour or so of contact, but thats all i slept, lol. and then we took rob hom with us, lol, and we went to the barn that afternoon for my riding lessons and i was riding chester, YAY! i LOVE that horse he was AWSOME! he was like perfect and yeah. jen took a kewl pic of us all with ma babi boi (the horse, lol) and yeah it turned out sooo well....cept that rob was hiding!!! not fair!!! lol! anywayz yeah, its on my website on the homepage, lol =). yeah, after that we came home so i could have a shower and then we went out to stone road mall to see ginger snaps II origanally, but then we couldnt convince mom to stay with us, so we saw you got served instead and it was freaking AMAZING!! omg omg omg omg, i LOVED IT! the boingy rubber band man!!!! lmfao!! i wanna see that again! lol. but i gotta save to go to ginger snaps so yeah lol. anyways, movie ended at like 11 at night and we missed the bus by like 2 mins, so hadda wait for half an hour to get the next bus, so we were in the square like 15 mins later. so like quarter to 12 and john was acting all screwy and like drunk and high and funny as fuck and hadda call mom to say that i was bringing everyone but jake home because rob missed his last bus and he didnt wanna go all alone anywayz, and john and dan were locked out. so father was being a retarted fuck up about it all, but ppl seemed to deal with it fairly well considering =S uhm but yeah, we all eventually got up and went...arrg....whered we go? ohh yeha, skating!! lol, that was fun man! then we went to blockbuster, got finding nemo, went to johns house, watched it and Freddie Vs Jason and then we ended up walking to dans house and staying there for a while where i got used as a pillow because there were none around =S but then i wasnt home till like 11 and mom was a little ticked but at least im not grounded or anything. dan and john are sposed to be comin over sometime tonight i dunno when tho....meh, sall good, lol. aaannnywayz, i should talk to the ppl that are chatting to me on my msn, so i shall update again some other time. GO LOOKIT MY PIC ON MY HOMEPAGE IF U HAVENT SEEN IT ALREADY!!! GO! NOW!! lol Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Arrrrgh!   I would really like to know what is up with jack. hes always pissed at me lately, and as far as i can tell its only because im not online as often now because i have friends. i go online while theyre here so that i can talk to him, but he gets pissed then to because appairently im "distant" when i talk to him and theres ppl here. I can't keep everyone happy! people here are talkin to me and throwing things at each other and im trying to be referee and still pay attention to who im trying to talk to online. i havent been on for the past like three weekends because ive been out with friends and jack seems to be jealous of that because the friends that i have are all guys. i understand that he would rather that i hang out with chicks, but i dont have many friends that are girls. in fact, at the moment theres a total of three =S but when theres no one here, hes pissed at me for either not being here or for being "distant" so how do i keep everyone happy? is it even freaking possible?!?! i have no patience lately, with anyone or anything, and i really care about jack, but this is beginning to remind me of someone else and that's really annoying. i just wish that things were okay again. especially since its beginning to look like he'd rather hang out with crystal on march break anywayz. he doesnt seem to get pissed at her. should i even care? maybe i should just say fuck it and get mad back, thats what id do to anyone else... i dont understand. if anyone can explain, this would be very helpful. jus hurts my feelings i guess that he flirts back with her in front of me, when hes pissed at me. yet of course hes still allowed to be pissed because i have friends that are guys that i dont think of as more than friends... that doesnt make much sence either... ugh, fuck i wanna go out now, im sick of all of this, and my fathers being an asshole, wow, when is he not?! and i dunno if anyones coming over, so technically i cant really leave. meh. basically no one reads this anywayz.   Bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       He's Gone...   This afternoon was weird. I'm still shell-shocked. Started being woken up at six in the morning by my father coming into my room and bugging me that i should be up to walk cole to school, even tho i didnt have to take him this morning. he was convinced that i had to take him and that i was an ass for not getting out of bed and going next door. i was gonna get in shit for not taking him and i was going to be in a ton of shit if he had to walk alone, acording to him. this went on for about four hours till ten in the morning when i finally got out of bed because i was sick of it and id heard the mail lady getting father to sign for a package, which was my Sony Atrac3plus, so thats awsome, and i went and got it and disappeared into my room coz jack stayed home from school to keep me company today. of course he didnt want me playing with the walkman because he thought that i was going to get shocked and hurt myself or some such foolishness, so i turned it on and drowned him out for most of the day till i started at my hw. i was talking to jessica online just before mom got home and she was asking me if i was coming over with rob when he got here and i was completely lost, i didnt think that i was going anywhere, not that i knew of anywayz....and so when i asked mom when she got home she told me that yeah shed called sandy and arranged for me and rob to go over, but she wouldnt tell me why, not even give me a clue and it scared me, so i said that i didnt want to go to jessicas house. i dont really know y i didnt wanna go over, but if rob hadnt been there id have been at the park the entire time till mom called me, so i guess jus wandering around was better than being stuck in a house. before we left, father gave me a twenty and said that he wanted ten dollars back because i wanted to get a sub for supper. we went to the park and i played on the munkie bars for a few mins, and then we went over to the dollar store because the batteries that were in my Atrac were old, id had them in my other walkman and they were like dead, so i got new ones and then we went over to subway.....well.... I  went to subway, rob went to the dentist office between money mart and joey's coz his aunt works there so he stopped in to say hi to her while i got food. when i was done eating, which took me a while because i got my normal foot-long, we went back across the road to the dollar store because i saw some cool fake nails that i wanted, hehe. i should have gone into the other dollar store too, DOH!! hindsights twenty twenty tho. i can go another day. anywayz, we were wandering around near the doors when mom called and said that we could come home now and shed explain but that was all shed say on the fone. so walked back home again and in the door and mom was on the fone, so me and rob went into my room. like ten mins later mom told me to come here and she told me that theyd taken my father to the Homewood. its only really temporary there, until we can find a suitible permanent place, but hes out of the house now. mom started crying and said shed done it for me because she wanted me to be okay. the people that she was talking to were frightened that i was going to really piss him off one of these times and that he was going to hurt me. or that he was going to do something foolish like take the truck and then other people would have gotten hurt. and she started crying harder because she said that hed driven david away, she didnt need him driving another one of her babies away, that had been her biggest fear. and at that point i was crying too and rob came around the corner and left again but i guess he was more uncomfortable in my room alone than he was out with the crying chicks, so he came back and gave us both a hugg and when mom told him that the police officer that had come had barely fit thru our livingroom doorway, he generally lightened the mood by pretending to be that big, but he jumped too high once and actually did hit his head pretty good. we ended up just basically watching TV....dave came over and ordered us all pizza, of which i only had two slices and am now supremely full because of the sub i had before aswell. the only person that i told about it was jack and yeah, he offered to listen if i wanted to talk about it, and i dunno, theres not much to say really, he was there when i left and he wasnt there when i got back, and i didnt even break his twenty so i was sposed to give it back to him....i dunno, jus irrational thoughts that make no sence really....im not as happy as i thought that id be...i dont know what i feel really. jack was asking me if i was ok and how i was doing and everything but i really dont know how i am. i wasnt expecting this for another like month or more, even up to a couple years. im like...numb was how he put it. i havent decided how i need to feel about this yet. its taking a while just for the news to sink in, i mean, mom told me at 5:30 or so and its now 1 in the morning and i still dont really believe it. i dont know whether to jump for joy or break down again. y do things have to be so confusing? i thought that things would clear up when this was all over and he was gone, but it hasnt. ttyl, buh byez.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...What's a Title That I Haven't Used Yet....?   I'm bored theres like nothing to dew today and yeah. Long day tho, tiresome. Father's being an asshole, completely and utterly. A week ago tomorrow a chick came for an assessment to get rid of him but he wouldnt even sit down to talk to her, so i think that he should be out of here soon, but trust me, it's not going to be soon enough. Jack offered for me to go live with either him or laura at some point if i have nowhere else to go. but yeah, according to my father's convinced that i am pregnant and that i am screwing every guy that comes into the house. its pissing me off like a hell of a lot. im appairently a slut and all that and grr. jus long day because he keeps like trying to talk to me and tell me that the police are going to arrest me for my new belt because it has spikes on it and all that shit and its beginning to really piss be off because he wont give any of it up. he also thinks that hes going to be calling the cops on dan because he wears three inch screws on his wrists. matt's coming again on march break again appairently and so're jack and laura tho laura wants no part of it. i have no idea what all we're gonna be dewing but i kno that it will likely include skating or going to the forum coz i wanna see matt get to fall on his arse, lol, and possibly a trail ride if the weather's nice enough by then which i seriously doubt but yeah.....annnnywayz, i wish my father would be gone by then because it would save everyone involved a lot of grief. unfortunately i doubt that that will happen....and i think im going to go insane....i already had one happy little breakdown last week, and yeah, dun really need another one.......anywayz yes, i have nothing else to talk about really so i shall go.....im sposed to be dying rob's hair nywayz... Ttyl, luvz yaz, Buh byez!!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       March Break   Okay, so I know its a little bit after march break but yea, ive had stuff going on and yea, school and evil and yes i like my excuses, hush u!! lol. anywayz yea, march break was awsome man! laura was down, but neither jack or matt ended up coming *tear* but yea, matts been bugging me to update this for AGES now and i think that i should. k, well laura got here on the monday and we ended up jus like lazing around the house and watching a few movies that night, rob was there too, but he like hid in my room, lol. it was kinda a boring day. tuesday i believe we started making plans and stuff but they werent working so well. i dont really member a lot of what we did come to think of it....Dan came over one day...John was over the next day...jake was over a lot too, and rob barely left, lol. but yea, *thinks* rob stayed over the same night that john did, and that was the night that we went to the movies and that was friday night i think....we saw Taking Lives and its soooooo good! it made me a touch jumpy tho, haha. we also went bowling twice that week, once with john on the friday because robin was here and we took john and jake and me and laura and robin and alex went. the other time was me and laura and jake and rob and crystal, lol. that was a ton of fun too. id gone jus a few days before that midnight bowling with cory, lisa, sherry, rob, jessica, and tenisha so yea, my fingers were about dead, specially since when we went with robin and them we bowled like 5 games and in one i ended up being the extra player for me and laura, lol. it was crazy. we also went out to the barn coz yea, me and my riding lessons =P. *tries to think of what else we did*.....meh. lol, the orgy type thing on the floor and playing jenga on my ass!! haha! oo, thats something else, lisa slept over at some point because i did her hair up in perm rods again and she brought over ultimate jenga and ppl were playing it and then she accidentally left a block of it here and yea, the next day ppl were like all sitting on me in the middle of the living room and jake kept throwing the block at me and it was like hitting me in the boob every time and yea, owwies, and then crystal was like poking me in the boob with the block, which yea, again with the owies and then ppl thought it would be fun to use the cases from the many movies that we'd rented to play jenga on my ass =S funny yes....fun....for me.......not so much so....but yea. did lotza shtuffs, so yea, funnerz, lol. but yea, i should go, steph wants me to watch House of 1000 Corpses with her and its 2 in the morning =S Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SHOW!!!   Yipes, i havent updated this in a LOOOOONG time man! grr, im having some serious typing difficulties. ok, i think im good for now. aanywayz yea, not a lot going on lately, scared myself today because i got an assignment done early and thats very unlike me, lol. but yea, IVE GOT A SHOW COMING UP!! sorry matt, ur not likely going to like this entry very much becuz its going to be boring, specially since u arent COMING and ur not going to BE HERE and i dont get my KRISPY KREAMS!! *glowers* eeeeevil evil person.  but yea, i dunno, im soo nervous man, its going to be crazy! specially if we're riding outside because its been getting nicer out and and yea, they tilled the outdoor arena last week so we might be but if we dont get at least one lesson out there before the show, the horses are going to be so insanely hyper =S specially coz yea, the horse that im likely riding for the show is chester, and he's half thoroughbred, in other words flighty, strong-headed, and FAST. so yea, bad combination to mix that with hyperness and outside.  plus i dont know what class im going to be riding in yet, i was going to let the instructor decide for me. if its something with like, x's for fences then it wont be so bad, but my horse doesnt turn when he gets going for the bigger jumps =S its an interesting ride shall we say. Im going to the barn early that morning to braid mains, im doing chester's, aspen's and probably koolio's because jen's not good at braiding and she pawns her horses off on me half the time, lol. but yea, ooo, that reminds me, i have to go and buy elastics soon!! hmm i should write that down.....owell, either i remember or i dont, either way. i can steal elastics offa emily or jen if i have to. anywayz yea, i should get going for tonight, wish me luck!! Ttyl, luvz yaz! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Pressure   Before I get down to actually entering something here, let me just say that my show was awsome! I rode Chester and I got a 4th in equitation, a 1st in jumping!!!!!, and a 4th in the last jumping class. I was sooo happy that i got the first and chester was soooo good! the only problem with the equitation was my stirrups were too short, and in the second jumping we took the first fence a little big and he didnt completely get his lead changes, his front legs changed, but not his back. but he was nice and controlled and he had pace but he wasnt running away with me at all, so technically he was going really slow for chester, lol. But yea, all of that's fine and dandy, but its not what i came here to write about. As has been previously mentioned in this blog, my father is now residing in the Homewood. He finally stopped being angry with my mother enough to let her come and visit him. She was going fairly regularly and then she stopped a little and he was freaking out so bad they had to drug him to keep him calm. Appairently he asks for me and about me every time someone goes to see him. Even my brother went...he went before my mom even did. Everyone's so proud of being such a "big" person and going to see him even after all that he put him thru over the years, including driving him out of home at the ripe old age of 16. my grandparents want me to go and see him, and my brothers all want me to. my sister knows why i wont go, she and i had a couple talks at subway before he ever left and she knows what its like to be a daughter instead of a son. but i basically have my entire family after me to be as much of a person as daveid and go and see him because hes asking for me and im going to feel sorry if i dont. well excuse my french, but i dont fucking care if hes asking for me. nor will i ever care. my daddy died a long time ago, and i never got to say goodbye, nothing can change that. the man that lived in my house for 2 years and is now living in the homewood is not my father. they have no idea what it was like living here with him for all that time the way that he was. it was even harder because it was like my daddy was here but it wasnt him, not at all, and hes completely dead now, so what would the point of visiting this stranger be? I hate having all these people making me feel guilty about this. its stupid, if i want to go then ill go, until then, if that day ever comes, they need to back the hell off. i cant even explain to them that i wont go because i hate him, because then theyd think even less of me than they do now. which i dont really need, and they dont know how i can justify that i hate my own father, but its not all that hard really. they just have to call u names for long enough and put u down enough times that u finally snap and theres no going back to mend that break, its there forever. i dont know, i wish people would just leave me alone and let me get on with my life instead of trying to get me to revisit the past coz u know wut, fuck the past, its behind me, hakuna matatta, etc. And fuck everyone who keeps fucking compairing me.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Semi-Conscious   I have no idea if thats how u spell conscious at the moment and im too lazy to push that stupid spell check button, lol. they always tell me that my spelling sux ass and yeah, annoyingness. If none of what i write makes any sense, its crystals fault, lol. im being threatened with like whips and on pain of death if i dont update, lol *laughs nervously.......dives under desk* im listening to hoobastank - the reason....its a good song....my brain is dead...what was i talking about? *little voice boots head*...owwie....doopid dentist, tightened my freaking braces and owwies and i wont be able to have solid foods for like a week. he like broke the bone that was blocking on of my teeth from moving and i yeah, felt it and ughhh *shudders* icky. *does a little dance* solitaire needs to die. like, literally. *goes in search of the person who invented solitaire holding a large heavy blunt object behind back* ...i should yeah...go now b4 im seen as completely insane and shipped off to the loony bin.....hehehe men in the clean white coats....basket weavers sitting smiling and twidling there thumbs and toes and THEYRE COMING TO TAKE ME AWAY HAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!!!!......*runs away* Ttyl, Luvz yaz!!! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ugh, It's like 10 mins later and i have a headache   people don't even see what the hell theyre doing to me, do they?? no freaking wonder people think what they do of other certain people. those doubts i mentioned before? growing. people dont even see what theyre doing to other people either. i dont get it. what is this freaking morbid facination with making everyone hurt as freaking bad as you do? im NOT in the motherfucking mood for this shit, and people know that im not doing well with whats being talked about because of the simple fact that im not talking. ud think that'd give them a clue, eh? not appairently. no one asks y im not talking, no one reads this blog, no ones going to care whats written here. there are no names so people cant bitch at me about talking about them. not that ppl are going to read this anywayz, cept maybe for two, possibly 3. no ones even likely to ask if i updated, or to actually read it if i tell them that i have. i wonder y i even care. maybe i just give up believing in people. maybe ill just kill my msn and take it off my computer completely and turn into a little hermit who wont leave her house other than to see her horses and ill write in this blog and itll be my only link to anyone. no people, no pain, sounds good to me...no being let down, no being put down, no hearing people talk bad about other people, no hearing people talk bad about themselves, no more caring. "Love is giving someone the power to distroy you, but trusting them that they won't" well maybe all my trust has run out. Maybe I will end up taking out my msn. unless things change i probably will.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I dunno...   Oh man, everything that everyone says today has been rubbing me the wrong way. Just little things that are really starting to piss me off. Everyone's in shitty moods, and theyre making everyone elses moods worse. Little people continuously trying to get onto the trampoline, dogs freaking because they were out back with the trampoline and people jumping, ppl being moody and grouchy and taking jokes the wrong way. my computer having problems that people dont bother telling me about or rebooting my computer to fix them, plus being booted off msn constantly. things people have said about other people and me trying to defend them but having every defense shot down, which in turn makes me doubt things. little snide comments that get under my skin, things that i wasnt sposed to hear, but i did anywayz that piss me off. my mom being pissy because ppl keep scratching our new car and she doesnt want to have to get a freaking paint job for the damn thing when we havent had it for a freaking week yet! her also being touchy coz ppl dont leave right away and she wants to get home coz shes tired. comments about other people before people leave that really really piss me off and of course the person making them leaves so i cant defend myself or person comments were against. confused feelings that no one seems to understand. friends depressed, other friends upset because of parent troubles, jealousy, back to the doubting things. I don't know, i don't know how to deal with everything and people expect me to and on top of that to help everyone else and I just dont know how and im not getting any ideas. if people want me to deal instead of running from my problems and bottling them up inside until i completely break down, they better start giving me some freaking ideas or im just going to say screw it.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *Shruggz*   I can't think of a title, I'm too lazy at the moment. I don't really have a reason for updating, I just got really bored and yeah, here i am. I realized I don't update this very much anymore. I really should. I also noticed that I have a lot of journals! a couple are like brand new and have never been written in, but yeah, its pretty crazy. Stupid teachers creating evil life-long habits! I should collect all of my journals up man, and like keep em in a box or sumthin so when i get all old and wrinkly i can take em out and literally re-live my childhood!! i like my idea!! coz like, ive got my teddy bear one that had a lock on it but the lock broke, ive got my kitty one, ive got myhorseback riding one, ive got a couple just loose sheets of paper, ive got my current one, and ive got *counts in head* at least another 4 that are still empty! lol. i get ones that look cool or have lots of paper. The only thing is i dont get as much of a chnce to write things down in the other ones as i do here coz im online all the time or out with friends. i also write more personal stuff in diaries because yeah, no one's ever gonna see em cept me. I wish I could write in them more often though, I think I'm going to start literally setting aside an hour or something before I go to bed just to write about my day or about the week, so that I at least write regularly, even if not often. Writing has always helped me. That and listening to music or screaming out the lyrics, depending on if I'm upset or angry. People think I'm strange for that, but I'm not really, I like a lot of the messages in songs, and others i love the beat or the anger because it helps me work mine out. I write a lot of poetry too, I should copy all of mine off of my computer and my website and throw it in one of my other journals thats not being used yet and it could be my poetry journal! This is like a project for me to do over the summer man! then id be able to write down like, all of my poetry, even what's not on my site and it wouldn't take up computer memory, which i desperately need. i can also pick and choose what i want on my site...this ideas gettin better and better!!! lol. i dont know, i think im the only one who posts a blog entry about journals *shruggz* hehe, matts gonna be scared. to him i am the "butterfly effect person" because everyone knows everyone because of me. so he doesnt want me reading my journals, like, ever because hes scared that hes going to wake up one morning and be married to micheal jackson, lol. (this makes more sense if uve seen the movie). but yeah, i plan on reading them all when im older, hehehe *grins evilly*. so matt, ill let u live out this life, then read the journals and ull be married to micheal jackson!! then ill live that life out and then ill read em again and ull be married to cher!! (ohh, im mean!!=D) then ill live that out and read them again and ull end up with like *tries to think of an ugly person* *light bulb springs up on top of head....grins evilly* then ull wake up married to someone like Justin Timberlake, MUAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!! and then since u survived all the tourchure, ill read my journals again and let u end up with elisha cuthbert (did i spell her name right this time??). see? im not such a mean old troll after all, am i now? =P  I'll have to remember this idea sometime like next month after exams are over! it'll be a good way to pass the time till summer school starts up. anywayz, i don't really have anything else to say, so i shall be going now! Ttyl, luvz yaz!! Buh byez!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last Entry   This is my last entry, this blog is causing too much shit with other people. From now on I'll write in my normal journal and that way i can write literally everything without sensoring because of people's feelings. Either way, have a good life y'all, buh byez.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>