<Blog>



<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jamming on the alarm clock, Einishi groaned as he tried to get up from his bed. He blinked a few times before glancing at the calendar next to his bed. It's already the third week of school, but he's only gone to school once--on the first day.  He debated whether he should go to school or not. What's the point? He's going to miss classes afterwards. But the un-lazy size got the better of him and he decided to attend classes, at least even for today.  He made his way around his small apartment, searching for his school bag. Everywhere were either unfinished bags of potato chips or piles of clothes. He should start fixing up his apartment soon.  Once he found his school bag, still intact from his first day of class, he hurried on to the kitchen, heating a leftover plate of pasta in the microwave. Tapping impatiently for the pasta, he just decided to take a short, nice bath.  -----  Maybe that short, nice bath got a little carried away. He glanced at his watch as he raced to his classroom. Fortunately, the professor was late and he found the class still a mess when he got there.  Pretending to walk slowly, he wondered why someone else was already in his seat. He couldn't have had  that  bad memory to forget his seat. Shrugging, he just walked over to the nearest empty seat, near the door at the back of the class.  Ichirou-sensei, their homeroom teacher, arrived shortly. He was a man of a tall and slim stature, and donned fashionable glasses, in his middle thirties. He immediately began taking attendance. "Deguchi Einishi--oh, sorry," he said when he got to Einishi. He quickly made a mark in his record.  Einishi raised his hand. "Present."  Ichirou-sensei blinked a few times, before changing the mark on his record. He probably thought Einishi wouldn't be going to school for the whole year, since the latter did miss currently 99% of his classes.  A girl with long hair, which Einishi believes he had never met before, came in late. "Sorry, I'm late!" She bowed to the sensei. She turned to go to her seat, but gave Einishi a look before settling in a seat in front.   She might be the president of this class... Am I that rare to be found in class?  Einishi thought as he rested his chin in his hand.  "As you all know, today is the day we will be deciding the representatives for this class," Ichirou-sensei announced, making it sound like something to be excited about.  Weird enough, the class began cheering and chatting excitedly as the sensei announced that. Einishi might have missed something--surely he did. He was the only one not getting hyped up about this.  "May I ask the president to lead the voting?" the sensei said, nodding at the girl earlier. "Kobayashi-san?"  She stood up, and Einishi could tell that many guys liked her, since they all stared as she walked to the sensei, with her long hair flowing behind her.   Kobayashi?  Einishi thought, racking his brain. He didn't remember anyone named Kobayashi, but he could understand if she was the president. All the guys there voted for beauty, and she might have already gotten to know his classmates--probably even more than he knew them.  The sensei whispered a few notes before leaving the classroom.  "Okay," the Kobayashi girl started. "This is a new school rule, right? So at least in this regard, we're equal." She flashed a smile. "Shall we begin the voting? We'll start with the girls."  A guy immediately raised his hand. "I nominate Kobayashi-san!"  "Hey, I was just about to say that!"  "Too bad then."  "Eizo, trying to get a jump ahead of us?"  Einishi could hear the guys fighting over that petty thing. He sighed.  A girl stood up. "I nominate myself, Tamura Miyako." She had quite a competitive and threatening glare at Kobayashi, but the latter just smiled and wrote Tamura's name.  Einishi had always known that Tamura was the popular type who'd never lose to anyone, and she supported that lifestyle by garnering female followers.  "Anyone else?"  Even if he missed a decade of classes, Einishi could easily catch up with current happenings. For example, that time he could tell that all the girls were envious of the attention Kobayashi gets from the boys. Basically, all the guys voted for Kobayashi and all the girls voted for Tamura. And since the guys outweigh the girls in class by a number, Kobayashi won.  She smiled sweetly and blushed a little. "This is too embarrassing. Thanks, guys." She erased the voting results. "Now, time for the boys."  "I nominate myself!" said a guy in front whose hand shot up immediately.  "No, me!"  "I nominate me, Yoshikawa!"  "Tsujimoto Hisaki!"  A few more guys tried to vote themselves to get the representative position. What's so exciting about that? If Einishi wasn't mistaken, that meant having to go to interschool meetings and all that boring stuff...unless they're thinking about being paired up with Kobayashi. He couldn't help heaving another sigh as he smirked.  "Wait, you guys! I can't keep up," she said exasperatedly as she grinned. "Can you slow down?"  Tamura stood up and stomped. "This is getting out of hand, president. Are you sure you can handle this?" That was such an expected remark from last year's class president. "Maybe you should try to ask help from others and not hog everything for yourself."  Kobayashi smiled sheepishly innocently. "Sorry, I'll try harder."  "This is not going to work! Everyone is voting for themselves! Why don't you just list everyone and put one point for each?" Tamura said with an insulting tone. "That's what you want, right?"  Regardless of Tamura's rudeness, the guys still continued their riot.  "Stop it!" Kobayashi shouted. She was red, as she continued, "Sorry, but you guys are getting out of control. Why don't we just let the girls vote?"  The class was silent. No girl wanted to cooperate with Kobayashi either.  "I'll choose then." Kobayashi surveyed the class, before finally laying her eyes on him. "Deguchi Einishi." 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>