<Blog>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So here is what happened on Saturday, I was suppose to have a yard sale today but ended up not doing so a friend and I took her baby and some kids she was watching to the annunal Fine Arts Festival at our local high school.  While I was there I ran in to a guy that knew my older brother, I can not believe that he knew who I was because he has not seen me since I was like eight years old(lol).  After we left the Festival we went to eat lunch with my friends mother and then went for ice cream with the girls.  Then I had to come home and pack some more of my stuff to move in the next 2 weeks.  Well, that was my Saturday...I'll write more on Sunday, hopefully something funny will happen......laters 
      
</post>

<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm a nut.  Here a couple highlights of my week....being hit on a Lowes, having a wreack with the limestone at High Meadow(that was so funny) after that I thought my mother was a pod person cause she did not care, watched my mother bowl(thats a sight to see, lol) and sitting at the tire place all of Friday(I was there for hours and made friends with all the guys working there, lol).  We also had an online team meeting for the JWST, let me tell you that was sooo much fun.....I'll post some more tomorrow......laters
      
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm here, you know you love me, lol.  So i have not had a car for a few days cause I took it in on Thursday to the Ford place to get some things done to it.  My mom and I were getting ready to go pick it up on Friday and my moms car decided to break down in the driveway, so we had to get someone to drive us there, lol.  And now it is Saturday and I'm stuck at my house while my mom is running errands for Easter Sunday at my Aunts house, let me tell you that will be a lot of fun.  I get to dye easter eggs at my nieghbors house tonight, I'm so excited I do this every Easter.....Well, theres my random thoughts for the past few days.....laters
      
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sorry I have not updated for a few days...its been a really werid last 3 days.  Okay, first on monday I got ready for classes and guess what happened? BOTH my classes were CANCELLED!!!!!!  After I left the college, I was driving down the road and was stopped at a red light(in a turn lane) when my light turned GREEN, I was turnning and this white truck came out of no where and almost hit me...I was like what the HELL!!!!  Then I went to work(not to exciting but oh well).  On tuesday I really did not do much but sleep and study for a test I had today(wedensday), I also on tuesday went to see how the house is coming along( a few more days(YAY!!!).  Okay so Wedensday, I got reay for class and went to take my C.J. test(it was so easy), LOL.  After the test I went to my Govenrment class, where I got a little upset b/c of what some guy in my class said about NOT supporting the troops fighting the WAR!!!! I was like WHAT???....I think you should support them rather we think this war is a good or bad thing, ya know?  After my classes I had to drive my dad around cause he did not have a car until 5pm....and at 7 pm my mom and I went out to eat and now I am home writing in my online journal about my wacky days, LOL........these are my random thoughts for the past few days.....laters
      
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, I'm back.....more random thoughts about my days ensue......here we go.  Ok, so my day sucked I had to work, it was so boring.  I also ripped my contact how dumb am I so I had to drive home with one contact in to get my glasses then drive back to work.  After work I came home and made some phone calls and at 8 pm we were suppose to have a JWST EC meeting but Heather did not show up(AGH)....she does it all the time it is starting to piss me off.  We are suppose to be a street team but Heather makes it more like a fan club and not about the MUSIC like it is suppose to be......sorry I go in to rants sometimes.  So, back to my day, I waited for like 30 mins and she did not show up.  I have class tomorrow(that should be fun).  Now I'm writing in my online journal because I have nothing better to do.  These are my random thoughts for today......laters
      
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back...I know I have not updated in like forever, I have been really busy though.  This last week I saw some great tennis, met alot of great people and got hit on by some pro tennis players.  I went to the Men's Clay Court matches in Houston, all the matches were awesome...Andy did not defend his title though, he was beat by Andre in the final on Sunday.  I also thought I would let you know that Mardy Fish is like now my fave....I got great pics too, it was so fun....laters
      
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey peeps, I'm back......I know it has been a month since I last updated(sorry about that).  Well heres what has been going on....my family moved homes, our first move in 20 years, so it was a big one...LOL.  The first weekend in May I had to work, all weekend(it sucked) and it was also my friends birthday on the 3rd so of course I had to go to a bar for that.  Then the next week I had finals and the articles were due on the 10th for the JWST Newsletter that I publish.  Then on May 18th, I went to the Ford family picnic with my best friends family, that was so much fun, I had a blast.  Last weekend I had to go to Oklahoma for one of my cousins wedding, it was a lot of fun...I got to see people that I have not seen in like forever and I got to hang with Dana my favorite cousin, who is getting married in  July and she says she found me a very cute guy to walk down the asile with, so that should be a lot of fun....well that is what I have been up to, I'll keep it more up to date, I promise...laters
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My computer crashed at the end of May and my mom and I finally got new ones(Gateway Rocks!!!), so YAY to that....we are no longer sharing one, which is why I think it CRASHED in the fist place, LOL..  I also had to set them both up and that took like a day and half...that was a lot of work, but now I'm back on line.  On saturday, my mom and I went to meet my friend and her mom at Willie's Ice House for a girls night out and then my mom and I went to see "X-Men 2"....what an AWESOME movie that is, it looks like they left room for a thrid one(which is totally cool with me)...EVERYONE should go see this movie.  Sunday was really UNEVENTFUL except for the fact that we had an EC meeting, but it was pretty short only took about 10 mins.  For the past two days I have been running around like a chicken with their head cut off trying to get ready for Dana's wedding shower that is at our house on sat. the 14th....that should be fun but right now I'm just tired and there is no time rest.  Well, there were my random thoughts about what I have been up too....laters
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey peeps.....Whats going on?.  Well, nothing much has really happened since I last updated.....One GREAT thing though JWST is on somewhat of a vacation cause the founder is out of town....it is good to have a small break, LOL.  On Thursday, I had family night with the Stumpners and some friends of theirs it was so funny and a lot of fun.  Then on Friday I had family not with my family and it was at the same place I went on Thursday.....Also on Friday it rained like a BITCH and I had to drive home in it.  On Saturday was Dana's shower. Andy Roddick BEAT Andre in the semi of Queens Club on Saturday, that was the BEST feeling in the world cause he has never beaten Andre.  And, finally on Sunday at Queen's Culb Andy beat Seb. to WIN, YEA ANDY!!!!!  Now I can't wait to see what happens at Wimbledon, ANDY is favored to win the tournment....that should be some GREAT tennis....these are my random thoughts for today....laters
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So here's what happened today....NOTHING, all I did was sit at home and watch tennis.  It was GREAT though Andy won and so did Mardy Fish......I don't write about Mardy much but he is great.  During Andy's match, Greg had a MAJOR meltdown up 5-2, 15-30 on Andy's serve and from then on the match was Andy's.  He now plays the #25 seed, Andy is the heavy fave in this one....let's hope(LOL).  I got paid today, that was big...let me tell you.......I was like totally out of money, I had to beg my mom for gas money.  I also went tanning to get rid of this bad back tan I have in time for Dana's wedding in a few weeks.....that is all that happened today.....laters
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since I last updated, I have been sick with like a tummy bug......it SUCKED MAJORLY!!!!  I was not able to eat for like days.  On Friday, Glenda and me went to get a drink at Rancho Grande....b/c sometimes we just need one(LOL).  We just end up talking about whatever but its like we see each other everyday so it is not like we really need to update eachother on our lives.  On Saturday it was my sister-in-laws b-day dinner and we went downtown to The Aquirium...it was AWESOME, to be surrounded by all these live fish....it was very surreal but cool.  Monday was my parents 30th wedding anniver. so i went to lunch with them and let them have a date that night....30 years can you believe that.  Tomorrow, ANDY plays his second round match at Wimbledon.....it should be intresting considering hat the guy he is playing is from GB and they share the record for the fastest serve ever at 149 mph......a match of HUGE serves is to be expected......I'll update more later, enough random thoughts for today.....laters
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys i'm back......so here is what has happened the last few days.....I have been watching Wimbledon, ANDY RODDICK had been kicking ASS.....he has a great chance to win his first Grand Slam.  It was also my birthday on June 28th, the BIG 22!!!  The best gift I got was tickets to the tennis Masters Cup in Houston.....that is going to be awesome I can not wait.  Other than that I have been watching some great tennis on television and that has been tiring but GREAT!!!!  GO ANDY!!!!!  That's all for now....laters
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      OH MY GOD!!!!....I'm so sorry that I have not updated in forever, just have not felt up to it.  I have been really busy with work and getting ready for Dana's wedding in Austin....I went to pick up my dress and the people at davids bridal lost my paper work, man was I pissed off...it took them half an hour to find my dress.  So we had a JWST EC meeting and now I'm mad at Heather cause she is doing a quarterly newsletter for JWST, when doing that was my idea in the first place when we first talked about doing a newsletter and me being the EDITOR of it.....now she is making it all her idea and also making it about money for her and her family, AHHHHHHHHH, it just makes me so MAD!!!!!!  I'm also suppose it get a NEW co chair that I don't want unless it is Chrystina but that won't happen, she is getting a new one to....she does not want one unless its me either, I just want to disban my committee and be her co chair, I think I would stay sane that way.  Tomorrow, I'm suppose to watch my cousin Haylie, that should be a blast, let me tell you....I'm not looking forward to it at all.  Also tomorrow there is a new MANDY MOORE dairy coming on and I can not wait to see it....she talks about ANDY RODDICK(her boyfriend of I think a year, I can not believe it has been that long already....this year has flew by man).  She has a lot of TV appearances coming up and I plan to catch as many as I can because she is just the best....I can not wait until July 18(that is when her movie 'HTD' comes out)I hope it does well.....that is also the night of Dana's reharsel dinner and the the wedding is the 19th(saturday).  Well there are my random thoughts for today...I'll try and post before I go out of town to Austin.....laters
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...its has been a werid couple of days here....I have mostly just been getting ready to go on vacation and packing and everything.  Tonight(Friday), we had family night at Rancho Grande and everything was going good until I got home and decided to go get a movir cause I was bored....On the way back for getting the movie I was at a stop light and some guy rear-ends me, I was like oh my GOD!!!!....I am so mad right now.  Thats all for right now, Ill post pics of the wedding when I get them done...I will also post pics of my vacation in Tahoe and Cali......There is the randomness for today...laters
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     urlLink Which How to Deal character are you?   Today I saw 'HTD'...it is really good everyone should check it out....to find out which 'HTD' character you are go to sarshdessen.com and click on the journal link.....laters
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...I'M BACK, lol...you know you love me.  Well, the wedding went good I met some really awesome people and had a GREAT time.  I'm really tired cause I did not get much sleep the past 2 days because we were so busy with everything and just hanging out with the guys.  I'll post pictures when I get them back so I can remeber them, lol....well, I'll post more when I have time to figure out what all happened.  My random thought RULE THE WORLD!!!!!!......laters.....Kayla
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink     urlLink Which Teen Movie Queen Are You?     urlLink     urlLink What's Your Designer Style?    urlLink     urlLink Which Literary Heroine Are You?    check out these quizzes they are AWESOME....laters
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry there has been no update.  T went to Cali for a week then got home and was home for a day and then went to my brothers and I have just been really busy this last week.  I'm getting ready to start my new job and that is just taking all my time up.  Also I have been working pretty hard on the JWST to get my committee all in order cause I was gone for like 3 weeks in a row.  I have most of my picks up on my yahoo photos page...they are awesome, well I'm a little tired....I'l post more later....laters
      
</post>

<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing remotely cool has hapened since I last updated this with quizzes.  Its almost September, which is cool...right now the US Open is going on and Roddick looks to WIN his FIRST GS, so GOOD LUCK to him and HAPPY 21st BIRTHDAY, hope you had a good time.  I have been getting up ay freaking 6 am so I can have my friend to work on time and frankly I'm kinda getting tired of it, plus I spend all my money on gas and she has yet to pay me back half of what I have used so far, which pisses me off.  Well, there is my rant and random thoughts for the last few days...laters
      
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      here are some more quizzes I found, check them out......   urlLink     urlLink Who's Your Josie Alter-ego?     urlLink     urlLink What's Your Perfect Teen Movie?     urlLink     urlLink Who's Your Clueless Love Match?   
      
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ANDY RODDICK 2003 US OPEN CHAMPION!!!!!!  I'm beyond excited, congrats to him for this amazing feat.  He cried which I thought was wonderful.  He also climbed in to the stands to his box where is coach and friends were seated, he then went on to find his parents, girlfriend, Mandy Moore and her family on the second level.  It was AWESOME, WAY TO GO!!!!
      
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, sorry for not updating you on what been happening.  I have been like UBER BUSY, with work and social life or NOW lack of a social life cause my b/f and I broke up on SAT...how nice is that.  So basically it is all about work right now and thats it....laters
      
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       According to the  urlLink Which Something Corporate Song Are You?  Test...       which SC song are you.....check out this quiz...I am Babies of the Eighties
      
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      check out this great band and go buy the cd out Oct. 21        Also while your out that day pick up Mandy Moore's Coverage also get the Limited Edition CD aswell.  Come join www.mandyteam.com and help get the word out.
      
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      found new quizzes....check them out.....laters     Neutral: Harmony and balance is key. You don't look at the world in a negative or positive way and you'll never judge or assume a situation- you just look at the facts. People like you are peaceful and accepting.   urlLink Made by  Sara      urlLink   What color do you see the world in?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You're Most Like The Season Winter ...  You're often depicted as the cold, distant season. But you're incredibly intelligent, mature and Independant. You have an air of power around you - and that can sometimes scare people off. You're complex, and get hurt easily - so you rarely let people in if you can help it. You can be somewhat of a loner, but just as easily you could be the leader of many. You Tend to be negative, and hard to relate to, but you give off a relaxed image despite being insecure - and secretly many people long to be like you, not knowing how deep the Winter season really is.  Well done... You're the most inspirational of seasons :)    urlLink   ?? Which Season Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      
      
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1.WHAT COLOR ARE YOUR KITCHEN PLATES? all colors  2. WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING NOW? The Bell Jar  3. WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE PAD? Tomball Regional Hospital and a pic of the new tower  4. FAVORITE MAGAZINES? People, Teen People, US Weekly, SI, Spin, RS, Blender  5. LEAST FAVORITE SMELL? trash  6. WHAT IS THE FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING? do i have to go to work?  7. FAVORITE COLORS? Lime Green, Purple, Grey  8. LEAST FAVORITE COLORS? pee yellow, puge green  9. HOW MANY RINGS BEFORE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE? whenever i get to it  10. FUTURE CHILD'S NAME? to many to choose from  11. WHAT IS MOST IMPORTANT IN LIFE? Living like it the last day  12. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA? Chocolate(MS Swiss Chocolate)  13. DO YOU DRIVE FAST? sure do  14. DO YOU SLEEP WITH A STUFFED ANIMAL? yep  15. STORMS - COOL OR SCARY? scary  16. WHAT TYPE WAS YOUR FIRST CAR? a Ford  17. IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON DEAD OR ALIVE? Derek Jeter  18. FAVORITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK? Amaretto Sour, Smirnoff Ice, GoldShloggers  19. WHAT IS YOUR SIGN & YOUR BIRTHDAY? Cancer, June 28.   20. DO YOU EAT THE STEMS OF BROCCOLI? don't eat broccoli  21. IF YOU COULD HAVE ANY JOB WHAT WOULD IT BE? spots photogragher   22. IF YOU COULD HAVE ANY COLOR HAIR? alburn  23. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE? thought so......but nope  24. FAVORITE MOVIE? A Walk to Remember, Princess Diaries, A League of Their Own,  Beaches, When Harry Met Sally, Sixteen Candles, Breakfast Club  25. DO YOU TYPE WITH YOUR FINGERS ON THE RIGHT KEYS? nope  26. WHAT'S UNDER YOUR BED? nothing......i think  27. WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE NUMBER(S)? 2, 7, 15  28. FAVORITE SPORT TO WATCH? Tennis and baseball, skating  29. WHAT IS YOUR SINGLE BIGGEST FEAR? loneliness  30. SAY ONE NICE THING ABOUT THE PERSON WHO SENT THIS? probably one of the few people who understand me the most in this world  31. PERSON MOST LIKELY TO RESPOND? The ones who love avoiding work  32. PERSON YOU SENT THIS TO WHO IS LEAST LIKELY TO RESPOND? everyone  33. FAVORITE CD? John Mayers, "Any Room for Squares"  34. FAVOURITE TV SHOWS: Gilmore Girls, One Tree Hill, Friends, Happy Days, Threes Company, Mork and Mindy  35. KETCHUP OR MUSTARD? ketchup  36. HAMBURGERS OR HOT DOGS? Hamburgers   37. FAVORITE SOFT DRINK? Sunkist  38. BEST PLACES YOU HAVE EVER BEEN? London  39. WHAT SCREEN SAVER IS ON YOUR COMPUTER RIGHT NOW? "Damn the Man....Save the Empire"  40. BURGER KING OR McDonald's? McDonald's, just cause they are cooler   sorry had to fill this out......i'll upate more about my crazy life friday......laters  
      
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey peoples....sorry I have not really updated, I have just been UBER busy with my work and just life in general.  Everyday I go to work from 9 am to 5 pm then I either come home and work on street team stuff or go out with my friends or go to a family function and sometimes I'm just to tired to update, sorry.  I am super happy though this past week I got my Masters Cup tickets in and I so can not wait, I'm taking my dad for his birthday.  I have also been trying to plan a birthday for my mom's 50th, which is hard when you work with her and are around her all the time, LOL.  The coolest thing that has happened since my last big update is that my brother got PGA US OPEN tickets again and we are headed to NYC for a week i June....but thats not all my friend Chrystina is coming to visit me for like the whoole month and is also coming with us to NYC, I can't tell you how beyond excited I am for this....it will be MAJOR FUN!!!!!  Well, I'm tired...have to get up early in the morning, I will try and update more...I PROMISE.....laters
      
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      OH MY GOSH...I'm so sorry I have not updated in like more than a month.  Let me see what I can remember, lol.  Okay, so since I last updated a lot has happened to me.  I go to work everyday from 9 am to like 4:30 or 5 pm and then I come home so that is just majorly time consuming, lol.  Lets start at the beginning....I got the newsletter out on the 15 of October and have basically been working on street team stuff all the time.  on October 21st Mandy Moore's new CD came out....it is called 'Coverage' and it is totally awesome even my parents LOVE it, the CD has been getting GREAT reveiws and she is just the nicest person on earth, lol.  On the 25th of October I went to the Texas A&M v. OSU football game A&M lost but I still had fun with my brother, he is such a BLAST to hang with, I love him....okay sorry back to the present, lol.  On November 1, I was in Victoria visiting my brother and we went to El Campo to a place called Greek Brothers and watch a band play, they are the Jarrod Bringham Band and they are and were AWESOME.  On November 6th, I went to the Tour of Champions Golf Tournment with my dad, it was so cool b/c we got to hang with the ABC TV people and watch them at work, which is so cool.  Then it was FINALLY time for the MASTERS CUP, this was the GREATEST tennis thing I have ever been to.   Okay to make a very long week short I saw some of the best tennis I have ever seen in my life in Houston and the best part was this is my home town, lol.  Andy played some nice tennis and so did Andre but Federer ended up taking to coveted MC title but all was not lost on the American side as the Bryan Brothers took home the doulbes title and the #1 year end ranking, Andy Roddick also finished the year at #1, so CONGRATS to all of them.  While I was there I saw Rudy T.(old Rockets head coach and my mom shook his hand), Carlos Moyas coach, MANDY MOORE(andys girlfriend), Mardy Fish and a whole lot of other really cool and nice people.  And another thing Mardy Fish is the coolest, he is so nice to email me back....I'm now a fan for LIFE, lol.  Then on the 21st  it was my brothers birthday, we had a lot of fun, lol...there was the BAND(JBB), who again were just so great and the nicest bunch you will ever meet in your life, lol.  And I just got back from thanksgiving in Austin, no it is back to work and everyday life.....laters 
      
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey....I am so DAMN bored its not even funny.  Right now I'm doing chores at home b/c my mom says its raining in town so no driving for me, lol.  And another thing that sucks right now is my social life or LACK of social life....I really do need a man, lol.  Today is Mardy Fish's Birthday, so HAPPY B-DAY MARDY!!!!  Also tomorrow is my mom's, she is turning 50.  I think we will go out to eat and then on Friday her big party is coming, YAY!!!!  Well, thats all for now...more randomness to come later......laters
      
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Louisiana is your state, or should be anyway.  If you don't like it, too bad because that just means you put the wrong answers!  Other than the humidity it's OK.  Just as long as you live in an somewhat urban area away from hicks.    urlLink   What State Is Perfect For You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      heres a new quiz check it out man...its awesome.....laters
      
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey.....so Wensday, Dec. 10th was my moms birthday(50th), on Friday we had a KICK ASS party....it was GREAT.  Then we found out some really BAD BAD news and that kinda ruined it but thats okay.  So, my brother was in town and we were all kinda dealing with what happened....they left on Tuesday(Dec. 16th).  We have a office Chistmas party tommorrow, and I need to finish shopping and get my nails done and need to go get waxed....I'll do that in the morning, lol......I'll post more later......enough randomness for now....laters
      
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm sorry I did not update sooner, it has been a WILD few days....I had a GREAT Christmas  and New Years, it was so much fun, lol.....I'm so excited I got the best gifts for Christmas.....here is a list of some: a new TV w/ a DVD and VCR, tickets to the Mens Claycourts in April, a DV cam.....those are my faves.  I also found out that I get to go to Vages with my parents for the 2004 ERA convention.......that is going to be so much fun, I can not wait for that......theres my randomness for the last few days.....hope you had a great holiday season......laters
      
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm going to a JONNY WAS concert in LA....GO ME!!!!!....LOL.  I have plane tickets, hotel and my concert ticket is at will call at the club, I'm UBER excited.....so I will be getting ready to go to LA and working mostly......when I come back I'll be posting pics and a review of the happenings......thats all the randomness for now!!!!!...laters
      
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a freakin BLAST at the concerts....the guys are great, the show was awesome and i made some great friends.....Also, the Pats KICK ASS, Tom Brady rules the FUCKIN world....he is officially "the MAN"....LOL......and Ted Jr. is so awesome I love him...you are great.....theres my randomness for the day, I'll post more later.....laters
      
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't think I have taken this one yet so here you go, LOL      -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      How evil are you?   I'm 30% evil.....Not so Innocent, lol thats a song   You try to stay away from evil deeds but succumb to temptation every once in a while. You aren't quite on your way to hell but you certainly have some explaining to do.     You belong in the movie Seabiscuit. You have great determination and will power.    urlLink   Which movie do you belong in? clh     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You are going to marry Brad Pitt. He is always friendly to anybody he ever meets and he is very talented as an actor. He is also very sincere and friendly. He will respect you until the day he dies. Congrats!!    urlLink   Which male celebrity are you going to marry? (now 12 (i just added more, and still more to come!)results that have pics!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      More DRAMA ensues for the street team, LOL....Heather is like so overly dramatic its not even funny....sometimes I'm like what the HELL is wrong with you.  So now the co-founder have to have a meeting to decide what to do with this drama......the funny thing about it though is that 2 of the co-founders were talking SHIT right along with everyone else....so this could get intresting, LOL.  Sorry I have not updated in a while....I have been making money and sleeping mostly.  And more GREAT news Chrystina is coming in May too...she is staying for like two whole months....SO AWESOME!!!!!...you have no idea how much i need this right now, it is what gets me through my days.  I have not talked to any of my "friends" in like ages....she is like the only real friend that I have right now......I know that was mushy......SORRY......anyway I'll post more about the drama later when I know what all Heather is going to say.  There is my randomeness for the day....laters
      
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back....hope V-day was good for some, mine sucked, I was with my parents all weekend...so no lovin for me.  I have to go to work tomorrow ven though it is presidents day, it will most likely be slow again....slow days suck ass.  I'm going to Vages next week, this should be fun...I have never been, I'm also going in Oct. for CC b-day....hopefully.  Speaking of my BEST FRIEND, I really NEED her right now and I wish May would hurry up and get here...b/c SHE IS THE BEST(Chrystina, that is, lol).  Well theres my randomness for the past few days....laters
      
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm going to Las Vegas for the convention, this should be intresting.....I have to keep an eye on my dad, lol, he will gamble to much my mom says.....well I'll be back Sunday, more randomness to come then...laters
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm back from Vegas.....I came back a winner so all is good, lol. It was a lot of fun we learned a lot and meet some great people. On Sat. we went to the Marige hotel and saw Jay Leno do stand-up...that was so funny...I had a GREAT time can't wait to go back....more randomness to come....laters 
      
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay so sorry I have not been around much....my computer had major viruses and was VERY SICK, lol....it was fixed for a few days but then crashed again so I had to do I complete rebuid and now am in the process of putting pics, links back up and catching up on email...again I'm SORRY...more randomess later......laters
      
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy April, sorry I have not posted in a while but I have been majorly busy with work, I know thats a cop out but what can you do, LOL.  I have one more week until my week off for the claycourts at Westside Tennis Club, should be a blast.  Speaking of tennis Andy Roddick won Miami today, that 100 points to him in the race and over half a million in prize money, way to go Andy.....Coria had to retire in the 4th due to back spasms, but congrats to Andy anyway.  Up next is Davis Cup vs. Sweden the Houston Claycourts, GO ANDY and MARDY!!!!!  I'll write more randomness later tonight......laters
      
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey peoples.....sorry I have not posted in awhile.  Ok starting with the middle of April the claycourts were great WAY TO GO Tommy Haas!!!!!!! it was so great, I met lots of people and had a great time having tennis players make me drinks, I will do it again, LOL.  Ok now in to May, on May 17th Chrystina arrived in town and we have had a blast so far and can not wait to go to New York next Sunday, I will write about that when we return.  Other than that it has been work and more work trying to get everything down by the time we leave for NYC.  Oh yeah, on Friday we went to dinner for Allisons birthday dinner with her parents since we will all be in NYC on her actually birthday and I found out that my brother and Allison are having a BABY, I'm going to be an AUNTIE!!!!!  More randomness to follow......laters
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Countries I visited:       urlLink create your own visited country map   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide  
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      states I have been too:        urlLink create your own personalized map of the USA   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide  
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh my, I'm so sorry..I know it has been a month.  Well NYC was awesome starting with TRL, Good Morning America, and the two braodway shows "Wicked" and "Hairspary"...they were awesome, we wnt to dinner at a very nice restaunt in NYC for Allison's birthday, the big 30!!!  When we got back, Wimbledon was starting that Monday(June 21st), then it was my birthday on the 28th we went to eat and then CC and I went to a movie that night, so much fun.  On July 3rd Chrystina left to go back home, im so bummed about that, I miss her so much.  On July 4th, it was the final for Wimbledon and Andy put up a huge fight against Roger taking him to 4 sets and showing that he can play with the likes of a Federer, Im so proud of him for that, he has come a long way since losing to Fed in the Semis last year and can only get better.  Monday, July 5th I had off work and it was just a relaxing day , I went to the movies with my cousin to see DOGDEBALL, it was so funny, everyone should go and see it....well that brings me up to date with just about everything so Ill have more randomness tomorrow.........laters....
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have updated my photo albums on yahoo, check them out:  &nbsp;  urlLink http://f1.pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/kdwhit/  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       a survey i thought was cool!!!!   Peanut butter or jelly- peanut butter Coke or Pepsi- coke Drive or walk- drive Traveler or homebody- traveler Good or bad- depends Skydiving or bungee-jumping- both MTV or Comedy Central- both Ice or roller skating- neither Nike or Adidas- Adidas Purse or wallet- depends on where im going Dark hair or light- depends on my mood at the time Chocolate milk or regular milk- neither Tall or short- taller Tan or fair skinned- tan Blue eyes or brown eyes- blue  Books or movies- both Comedy or horror- both Bath or shower- depends on my mood Lights on or off during a movie- off Theater or video- theatre Red or blue- red Top or bottom- bottom Morning or night- night Glass half full or half empty- half full Chocolate or vanilla- chocolate Cat/dog- dog McDonalds/Burger King- both Metallica/Nirvana- nirvana all the way BBC /ITV- BBC Sky/Cable- Cable MTV/VH-1- both Straight/gay- straight Black/white- black Left handed/right handed- right Mom/Dad- Mom Neighbors/No neighbors- im in the middle North America/South America- both Football/Rugby- both Gold/silver- …SILVER!!!  CD's/cassettes- CDs TV/cinema- TV Video/DVD- DVD Glasses/contact lenses- contact lenses Brown hair/red hair- brown Chinese/Italian- Food? both Ocean/sea- ocean Sun/moon- moon Plane/boat- plane Early bird/night owl- night owl Jaguar/Mercedes- Merz Yellow/blue- blue Windows/MAC- MAC Eminem/Dr Dre- love them both Buffy/Angel- neither Basketball/Baseball- Baseball  Wax/shave- wax Curly hair/straight hair- straight Mars/Snickers- Snickers   
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       right now my life sucks...I just went through one of the hardest things in my life this week, i lost a really close family member and my fiends dont even have time to talk to me when I call them cause i need a pick me up.....they are always busy or doing something with our other friends....and everytime I ask someone to go somewhere with me they come up with an excuse to say they can not make it or something like that, the only person that will go with me is my mom, but I dont want to go everywhere with her, ya know.....I guess it is to much to ask that friends be there when you need them, but I thought that is what friends do or are suppose to do, even ones that dont live near you of for that matter in that same state.....but maybe I'm asking to much......I guess thats my rant for today...laters   
      
</post>


</Blog>