<Blog>

<date>29,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well i had another great day today.  i actually dont remember much about the school day b/c right now that seems like a long time ago.  ohh yeah i do remember i have a test in boshers tomorrow that i forgot about but o well i dont feel like doing anythign school related tonight.  after school we went out to football practice.  we had about 10 more ppl that we did the first day so maybe our team will get up to 40 ppl this year.  it was hard again today we ran and ran and did pushups and ran some more and did situps and ran the rest of practice.  tomorrow we get out helmets so that gonna be cool.  and right after school elizabeth donovan asked me to go to right to life of jackson banquet thing that they were serving food at for service hours so i decided to go.  after football i came home my neighbor called me and was like hey i found somebody to make a coustom box for you subs in ur trunk and so that was great and then me and ben left picked up donovan at the school and went to the thing.  we were serving food and messin around and then they gave us free food it was cool.  there was also this really annoying stuck up 11 yr old that everybody including lee wanted to beat it so that made the night really funny and then at about 8 or 8 30 most of the ppl left but i figured why not stay and clean up.  we went and played some super nintendo and chilled upstairs while the speeches were going on and then we had to go clean up so i ended up finishing at 10 15 and it was actually fun cleaning up i got about 50 free pens and some bead type things.  ohh yeah and ben had to leave and i was suppostried.  ohh e to get this girls # for him but i was talkin to her and i had to go clean off a table and then i got back and she was like i g2g so then i didnt see her again sry ben i kinda yeah and the whole time we were cleaning up i was messin with donovan that was fun too lol she hates food that other ppl touched.  and after all that im back here again sittin typing this talking to bryndan and kristin, who i havent got to talk to in awhile, sore from football and about to go to sleep well that was the extent of my great day i hope yall had one too ttyl.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a Great day!  well it started out good just b/c i woke up rested.  then i had lots of energy all day and nothing at all bad happened all day!  we missed most of english b/c channel 1 was late and then math i ate pizza and didnt pay attention and religion we didnt do anything in spanish we got to work out our packed and then chemistry we did something i understood and art is always fun and i was hyper throught the entire day.  after school we had football i forgot my shorts so i had had to practice in my boxers not really i just went home and got a pair of shorts and bryndan and reggie came with me but i even had a good time a football.  we ran and ran and ran some more and did some pushups but it was fun. i got accepted to the madison junior ambasador and then i won the elections for treasurer but i still think jabrina should have won she had a better speech.  ohh yeah and i got home and created the pattern for a blue flame design that im putting in my trunk with my subs its gonna look so cool and bryndan is gonna help me out with it.  well thats about it and i havent started my homework so i better go not g'night.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      guess who just called me.  well actually erin just called me but before that guess who just called me jessica just called me.  yepp it was cool just thought that was kinda neat after that last blog i had.  today seemed very long and depressing i woke up at about 11 30 and then andrei and lutz came over to do spanish.  it was the most boring thing we worked for 4 hours and got about 1/2 way done it sucked!  after that i went to curch and saw mark and lee and patrick and nick liz and nate there that was cool. and then i came and was for some reason depressed i think itw as b/c i didnt have anything to do but then i ate some icecream got on the computer and started talkin to a bunch of ppl and i got in a better mood so it turned into a good day just in that short amount of time.  OHH YEAH ben can play football!! haha its gonna be great i wanted him to play last year but he couldnt and i think hilton is gonna be able to play to football it gonna be great fun this year but im out im really tired laturz!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well this post didnt work last night b/c the blog site was messed up but luckly i saved it ... Well its 3 in the morn and i just got home from prom....Bryndan spent the night last night and we had a good ole time even thought i wasnt feelin really good :)  Donovan and kathrine yall are fun.  then when i took bryndan home i went a picked up my flower for prom and came home and got rdy.  then when i was leaving to go to prom i had to urge to stop by jessicas and say hey b/c i was all fixed up and i wanted her to see so i did. it was cool but seemed kinda weird at the same time.  then we got to prom early so and we didnt really feel like going in so i went to get coffee so i could stay up.  it worked for the most part i was wide awake until about 1 then i started crashing.  ohh yeah but at the dance the food was really good!!! and they had good cheesecake!  the music and stuff was pretty good to and it was fun at first i was kinda shy but then i started dancing more so it was all good.  then after prom we were gonna go to the mcfarlands for breakfast but we didnt see anybody so we left.  i was guessin brendon stopped on his way home and i just didnt feel like sitting there waiting.  then we were gonna go to salonas but they hadnt finished the senior breakfast yet so we just went to catie caskeys for about 30 min and by that time after all the driving around she had to be home.  so i took her home and came back here and that was about the extent of my prom night.  i was hoping there would be some nice after party but noope so that kinda did suck but o well i still had a good time.  for some reason lots of things latley have been reminding me of jessica.  just little things i see or eat or do.  its happening a lot more than it was just thought i would throw that in there to tell everybody i dunno why.  but i need to go now b/c im about to pass out from being tired and i gotta do some stuff tomorrow, including the damn 16 page spanish packet, so i will write some more some other time. later and g'night.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well i had a good day today.  my life is full of lots of little interesting things right now and i dont know what to do about alot of them.  i went to go see jessica yesterday! it was the first time i saw her in 2 weeks.  she had finished our little scrapbook.  it was nice talking to her again i had been missing it a lot!  i think it was good i went too b/c im pretty sure she thought i was mad at her which i wasn't.  maybe we will become good friends! ... i wish i didnt get nervous when i said i speech infront of i bunch of ppl. i dont know why i got nervous b/c i knew everyone in my grade but i still got nervous when i did my treasurer speech o well its still all good.  i went to go work out after school today for the first time in about a week and a 1/2 which is a pretty long time for me it felt good to be back in there.  i always feel better afterwards. my life has been getting jam packed of stuff latley. like this weekend i have almost no free time already. i think need more time to do nothing or just lay around or go to the pool which isnt open yet but i wish it was.  ohh yeah almost forgot football practice starts on monday!! yes im actually happy about it i miss football when its not football season so it will be nice to be back on the field practicing again.  im sure i wont be as enthusiastic about it when i start running at them but o well.  one more thing, i love my tux.  i went and picked it up today i wanna buy one now it was fun wearing it i looked all cool and different lol.  tomorrow is friday yay!  g'bye
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Easter break has been great fun!  i know i probally missed alot back at home since i was gone to dallas (like the 3 doors down concert :( ) but even though i havent had much time to spend with my friends i had a great time in dallas. but hey i have all tonight and all tomorrow to spend with my friends.  my entire family hasnt been together in awhile and it was fun to get all back together in dallas.  i think i probally ate as much on this trip as i usually do in about a week, it was great.  ohh and other good news the insurance said i can just cash the check for my hail damage!!  cash in the pocket :) i dont think i had anything go wrong ( ohh except the trust compant concert got cancled for tonight but thats not all bad) at all so far this easter break i hope everybody elses was as good as mine and i know im looking foward to my extra day off tomorrow!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i had a good night i went to go work out and then i went running ( for some reason i actually enjoy running now its weird i used to hate it) and then i came home and ate 2 dinners and now imjust realxing and i packed as i already told ya ne wayz g'night and everybody have a good easter i will be back on monday from dallas.   ohh and i have the best friends just thought i would tell everyone that.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well school was pretty good today.. i think well im pretty positive i failed my chemisty test along with at least 3/4 of the rest of the class so its not that bad.  i'm packing right now to go to dallas, i get to see my sister over spring break but that means i will be gone from thursday all the way to monday and i will only have tuesday off but o well i guess 1 day is better than no days.  ne way i have to go finish packing so i will talk to yall later
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok im back now time to tell the story... SORRY story had to be omitted due to personal concerns i didnt mean to hurt ne body if u really have to know u can ask me but i doubt u would b/c its not all that interesting :P
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey everybody i just decided to get a blog but i dont have time to write the story of my life for the past week and a 1/2 right now cause i need lots of time but i will catch yall laturz
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This post was mean so i decided to take it off i didnt i hate it when i hurt ppl u didnt really change i know ur still a great person
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha i just ate for the first time in 24 hrs
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      UHHHH!  dont ever get food poisoning i think ive thrown up more in the last 14 hrs than i have my whole life.  i just weighed and im 8 pounds lighter than yesterday afternoon.  :(  this sucks really bad just though i would tell yall and now i dont get to work either b/c im so sick.  o well i guess thats about it hope everybody is doin good i love all yall who read this b/c im sure its not to many lol.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well howdy!  im sooo tired!  im about go to bed and its not even 9.  last night was interesting to say the LEAST. i think i will just leave it at that.  i must be pretty holy right now b/c ive gone to church the past 3 days in a row.  friday for that bacalauriate thing then sat to run the soundboard and now sunday i went with erin to conformation mass.  i got there 45 min early and so did erin so we went to go get a card for henry who she isnt trying to steel from brittney she was just proud of him lol.  then afterwards i took her home and we told our past few days stories like we always do.  it sounds like her and taylor are doin good aww so sweet.  but then she drove my car and then i went home.  it was a pretty calm day.  now im going to sleep b/c im passing out and dont feel to good so ttyl i g2g to work tomorrow g'night.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday was my last day of school and it was a good day.  after school i went to julips with erin katie bryndan mark trip and chris.  then i went to the party on the big house boat for 3 or 4 hours and then i came home and went to tripps party and then i went over to the after party at michael gray lewises and then i brought elezabeth and 3 of her friends home and then i came home.  then today i slept late and then sarah and ruth came by to get some ketchup from me and see bryndan.  it was nice of them to stop by though hadnt seen them in awhile.  then i went to get info on my job for the summer. i start early on monday fun fun but at least i get 200 a week!!!!!  then i went to the bacalauriate mass it was cool too i chilled with erin alot of the time i love hangin out with erin i dunno the always makes me laugh.  then after that we came back here and me and bryndan went to fazaloies with some friends and then this is the good story: MY episode of the fast in the furious: WOW!! my heart is still beating faster than normal.  me and bryndan just got back from rollin, mark katie and lacey came too.  but when we were leaving, after a wonderful roll all the trees were covered!, we saw a car commin up behind us.  so we left like normal ppl like nothing was wrong.  then went a little faster and the car did too.  then it came right behind me and bryndan said "Oh Shit its the cops!"  and i was freakin out so i slowed down some but then we realized it was just the day patrol.  and they cant arrest you so we floored it and mark did too.  we were goin down the street at about 80 and the day patrol man was too then he went into the left lane on a 2 lane road his tires were screeching and dust and leaves were flying everywhere.  so he was goin the wrong way and marks truck wouldnt go faster which was probally good since he had ppl in the back of it, but i was stuck behind him with a day patrol man speeding next to me and then he was gonna try and get inbetween me and mark to seperate us and get at least one of us in trouble so i sped up and stayed right beind mark then about 10 sec later in the chase a car came up goin the other direcetion in his lane so he had to slow down to get behind me and me and mark floored it again and left him and then as soon as we were gettin out of the neighborhood he had to turn to stay in his little partol area and then we went to katies house.  we said bye to everybody and then as we were leaving her neighborhood we saw a real cop flying down the road and we hoped he wasnt looking for us.  we then carefully and slowly got on the highway and came back to my house.  wow that was exciting. i hope yall had as fun and exciting night as me!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a good night!!! :D  and i think bryndan did too. ohh and what i said about not being happy on my last blog thing .. that was only for about 20 min now life is great again its the extremely happy feeling and no im not on any drugs lol.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i did good on chem!! yay i almost doubled last semesters grade lol! im really not happy right now i wish i was and i still act like i am but im not:( i need to get out of the house have some fun and get my mind off of things
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      *Never Forget to be thankful for what you have* Ok im back from the prayer thing.  wow i really enjoyed it i wish more ppl would have the guts to have prayer services with their friends. i was able to thank God for the so many things he has blessed me with, talk to God and my friends about whatever i needed to get off my back, and ask God or my friends for help in anything i needed.  and yes i started crying during it.  im so thankful for all of you. erin, katie, chris, tripp, mark, and of course bryndan, i would be sooo much worse off without yall.  haha i let erin drive my car it was fun stuff!  ohh yeah and about the jessica delema i was having.  for right now i think i made the right decesion.  it seems that both of us will be happier if we dont date but can still be there for eachother when we need someone to lean on.  i had the gut feeling after my long prayer service that pretty much told me.  but i better go to bed b/c even thought it seems like summer is already here, i still have to go take exams tomorrow! ughhh! not lookin foward to it but hey its alright i think ive done good so far this year on my exams!  Today turned into a Great day!  Life is good! Friends are great! I Couldnt be doin any better right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well tonight was interesting.  i dont know if i did something good or bad tonight.  i probally wont be able to tell you for awhile i do know it was confusing for me and im sure it was for jessica.  i could tell that the times we were doin stuff together she was never happy.  i thought it was me or something that i was doing so i figured she would be happier if we were just friends and not dating anymore. and i thought it would be easier on me b/c im always trying to please her and since i couldnt make her happy i was getting frustrated. so i told her that and when i did she told me that it had been just because she felt smothered by me and that i was being to close to her.  so then i wasnt sure if i should try and change that and keep dating or just go ahead with what i was planning on doing.  it ended up that when we got off the phone that were just friends again.  i dont know if this will last or if things will change again or if its even for the better or not.  i didnt have a gut feeling tonight i wish i would have had one, it would have made things easier, all i know is that i dont wanna hurt her or make it hard on her b/c i still care about jessica and her feelings.  and i know i still have feelings for her.  i just wish we could both express our feelings and everything be good and happy.  i guess life is just not that easy for anyone these days.  i express the way i feel in completely different ways that the way she expresses the way she feels and thats where our conflict is.  i dont know if at first we both were immune to it or if we were so in love that it didnt matter but not it seems to always mess things up the way i am mushy and the way she never sees us that way.  i will probally write some more when i get home b/c this is flowing really easily and is good to get out but right now i have to go see erin and katie so i will be back later buh byess.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Happy birthday Katie!!! matrix reloaded was awsome.  i saw it last night at 10 30 and then tripp got a flat tire so we had to change that and then i came home and finally got a good night of sleep!! 9.5hrs!  life is great i dont know why but seems as though everything is good.  even though exams are commin up tomororw i dont seem stressed out like i usually am.  i was studying for math but bryndan passed out so not im just kinda sittin here and deicde to write on here.  probally about to call erin and see how to do some math problems.  summer is gettin so close i can feel it commin up! i think its gonna be the best summer.  This school year has been really good when i look back on it.  my life changed soo much throught the year.  all my new friends and all my new experience.  when this year started i didnt have a whole lot of friends outside of st joe and i also didnt have much of a social life.  Jes was the biggest change that happened this year.  she changed so many things in my life for the better.  im glad we didnt end up not talking any more because that would have been a big loss for me, i would have lost one of the best people in the world.  i met so many new great ppl i dont know how i went on without them before i have such a good time with all yall casey, allison, kegan, MK, courtney.  then at st joe i even made lots of new friends. Erin, your one of my best friends now and ur always there for me.  im so glad we got to be good friends. haha we always have the same problems. then mark, tripp, katie, donovan, kathrine i love hangin out with yall. i dont wanna forget everybody that i was already friends with before this year too yall are all great (u probally know who u are).  but through it all bryndan has been there with me we both went through ups and downs and i dont think we could have done it without each other.  i want to say thanks to everybody for everything!  my life wouldnt be the same without any of u.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      well ive been really busy latley sry i havent posted anything but i bet only about a total of 3 or 4 ppl read this but hey! its ok though.  jubilee jam was fun saliva was great.  darren is an asshole i actually was about to beat him up and i wish i would have but thats about it for the day b/c i have to go find some energy and find something to do or some ppl to hang out with tonight so i will write later. ohh by the way screw all u ppl that dont have to worry about exams! laturz :P
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      That was scary, my mom just went off on me for talking on the phone to jessica when i was suppose to be studying for math.  i think that was the first time that had ever happened in my entire life.  i pretty much talked my way out of it so its ok but i guess i better study ohh yeah i had a good day today it was cool and not alot happened but im out to do my homework.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      well its been awhile i was putting blogs up here every few days and i dont know what happened.  LIFE HAS BEEN INTERESTING AND GREAT LATLEY!!  i couldnt remember all the stuff i have done since my last blog if i tried.  about all i can remember is this last weekend.  jessica was probally the highlight of my weekend.  friday night we had the sports banquet it was cool i got most improved player in football :) and then that night i spent the night a tripps and we had a big water balloon war lol.  then the next day i woke up and it was carwash time!  i had a great time at the car wash workin the corner and washing the cars and all i think the highlight of my carwash was when jessica came though i wasnt sure if she was going to go or not b/c at first i knew she didnt want to but she came.   i just gotta say wow she looked damn good! lol but i talked to her for awhile and washed her car and all and i got really burnt.  my sholders still hurt today.  then  after the carwash i went to a pool party and ate and then went to church and then out to a mexican restraunt all this was with bryndan.  on sunday i dropped him off at home and then came home.  i was waiting for a good time to call jessica so about 100 i called her and we decided i would pick her up to go get coffee at about 2 30.  we went to cups in the mall where i was hyper the whole time lol and i got a pair of shorts and had coin races in the little things if u know what im talking about and she won lol.  then time flew by and it was time to take her home then when i was about to leave she said something about getting back together and i couldnt stop grinning it was amazing i still remember the words she said.  im glad she said it b/c i wasnt sure if she still liked me so i didnt wanna say anything so we talked about it for awhile and pretty much figured stuff out later that day and so me and jessica are dating again but its not as serious as it was b/c im gonna be gone most of summer and i dont want her to be tied down to someone that gonna be gone she needs to have a fun summer.  bryndan thinks im whipped b/c i took jessica back that easy but i cared for her and was always with her for 7 months and i couldnt just stop doing that the feelings didnt ever go away for awhile i tried to make them go away but all i did was push them down for awhile and now luckly i dont have to do that anymore i can actually express what i feel again!  that was about it that happened in my weekend now im sitting here at the computer still all happy and putting off studying chemistry.  but i guess i better go study b/c its on everything since january lol yeah im screwed.  but i will write again some time byz!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      well i just woke up but i woke up in a really good mood so i figured i would wright something on here.  hows everybody doin.  life is great i had another good day yesterday.  there is some confusing stuff goin on in my life but i still have it good.  i didnt have any homework last night either so that was great.  me and jessica talked for about 2 hours and then me and donovan talked for about a hour after that nobody else i called would answer the phone so i just went to sleep at about 10 15. i hope ben can keep playing football b/c his grades in chemistry arnt that good and he is suppose to raise them in order to play or so his mom says.  it wont be as fun without him.  but i guess thats about all i have to say so hope yall have a good day.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      work may be hard but ive never laughed so much in my life lol.  im really tired tonight after we got home from work me and byrnadn decided to help this lady sod her yard and after doing about 1/2 the yard we got 40 bucks each it was cool but im so worn out.  kegan called me and asked if we wanted to go to abners.  i was glad she called. so then we went to abners and met up with a bunch of our old mc friends it was fun.  i hadnt seen them in awhile. i saw jessica there but it seemed different in a weird kinda way but it was cool i didnt really talk to her that much i was talkin to  other ppls!  hahaha she made me laugh though.. then we all went home and i dropped 2 ppls off and came back here.  i dont think elizabeth likes me i was just talkin to her. o well. i'll live. and still be a happy man.  but ne way i need to go to bed so i will c yalls laturz.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a great time in cincinattie!  it was a fun wedding and i got to chill with elizabeth alot.  i i had a great weekend.  i dont wanna go to work tomorrow.  i spent all my money today on my car and then when i got home i realized that i didnt need to.  i realized that the old thing i had still worked but o well the new one was better so i kept it and now i have an extra.  aww bryndan and kathrine are on the phone just thought i would say that.  ok i gues im gonna go now so i better go bryndan wants to write a blog since he hasnt done it in awhile.  life is goin good hope urs is too.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Life's goin good right now... Well these past few days ive enjoyed.  its been the easygoing stuff ..  thats what i like lol.  they have been pretty fun and relaxing.  basically i quit my construction job .. i would have had to next week for football ne way but i went ahead and did.  sooo i have free time and an excess of sleep again!! ohh my car is back! i spent a few hrs today and yesterday getting everything back and putting fuses and stuff in to make sure it doesnt happen again.  im almost done i just have to get one of those things that turn ur cig lighter from 1 to 2 thingies if u know what i mean.  last night and tonight i have just kinda been goin to see ppl.  yesterday me and bryndan were gonna go to chases "party" but we heard it was no fun and saw a line of 5 cars leavin so we didnt even go.  me and bryndan chilled with sarah and courtney.  it was alright we went up to wendys and i saw mark and lee with his new jeep.  after that we dropped them off and i wanted to go see jessica and see how camp went and all so we got over there around 11 25 and stayed for 30 min and then we came back here and bryndan headed home.  today i worked out and finished a book. then tonight i went out and chilled with cory and sarah e.  it was fun! it was me and bryndan again lol and then bryndan was headed over to see sarah b so i just headed home and got here early which my mom was happy about lol.  well that what been goin on with me latley hope the close of yalls summer is goin good to.  im off to my room and then to bed. c ya later.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well today, actually now it was yesterday, wasnt near as bad as it started out being.  i had  a reallly bad middle of the day and got all sad over what i guess wasnt that big of a deal but like normal i got over it really quick.  then i went to church and then to the spy kids movie with my neices it was like 2.5D insdead of 3D it was some crap lol definatly glad i didnt pay to see it but i think my neices liked it.  then i went to go visit MK after i fed the neighbors dog.  me and MK talked for awhile, she has an awsome new cat lol,  and then i got home about 11 35.  I called katie and we talked for about 2 1/2 hours, im glad i met her up in DC but 2 bad she doesnt live here:(.  now im writing this and heading off to bed.  hope everybody had a good day!  buh byees  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well im just sittin at melissas (my sister if anyone didnt know)  babysittin my ass off lol.  im just chilllllin since the kids are asleep and i dont wanna read now.  i got bored and just decided to post this.  i will c yalls later.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      today was kinda boring .. i woke up at about 9 30 for some reason and couldnt go back to sleep so i just stayed up.  i worked on stuff that im gonna put in my car when i get it back and then lizzy called about 1 and she came over and i installed her stero and she gave me some speakers for payment.  u know u miss ur car when u start working on other ppls lol.  ne wayi did that and that was about it. i helped cook some shrimp creol and it was really good and now im just sittin at home i just called mk and i may go overthere just to say hey since i havent seen her in awhile.  thats about it i guess ohh yeah tirrionna called me tonight! lol ohh andi promised my sister i would babysit tomorrow night so thats my plans for tomorrow.  ok well im gonna head out i will catch up with yall later.  byes
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Football camp is ova!  damn it was hard. the eitire time i was there i had about 1 hour of free time and i played video games at the LSU union center then.  the day we checked in we even had a practice.  the practices were about 3 hours 2 times a day and then every night we played actual football games for about 1 1/2 hours after dinner.  thats 7 1/2 hours of football a day. i got soo tired.  all i did was eat sleep and play football but im in good shape now.  i felt so small there.  i was one of the smallest ppl there. but i did gain some weight while i was there.   85% of the ppl were over 6 ft and over 200lbs. there were some 6 9 350+lb ppl they scared me!  ne ways im glad i went it was good for me.  my travels this summer are finally over.  im finished goin places its kinda sad b/c now i realize school is commin up soon but o well im almost looking foward to it b/c i havent seen alot of my friends from school all summer.  i went over to lizzys last night to see her DC scrapbook it was great i still miss all my friends from there.  we were talkin for a long time im glad were becoming better friends.  i got home about midnight then.  ohh yeah i got all my pics from enigneering camp .. damn there are some funny ones if u wanna see any just tell me and i'll either come over and show u or email some to u.  well im about to go to walmart or at least find something to do until lifting weights time (uhh more football lol :P ) write laturz ~ bye byes    P.S ~ DMX - X gonna give it to ya get    is a song that gets u really pumped up for football i just found that out at camp
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm headed to football camp as LSU this morning.  im hopin it will be fun, but i think it will be b/c if its not, nobody will want to come back and go there to college lol.  Everybody have fun while im gone!  i'll miss yall and hope to talk to u soon laturz.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well i was talkin to all my friends from NYLC and i figured i should mention them .. hey to Lauren i will visit u in cali.   Annie and Hannah yall are great i will make a road trip up there one day, Joe (lol ur a strange one), Jay (Fire :)), Lance, David, Brian, and Andrew, yall were cool roommates!, Kaila, Kimbrell, Rob, Elizabeth, Madeline, and Lizzy (All my mississippi friends) Matt u were my best friend!, Katie it was fun i miss ya! Alicia (caucus H!) megan jessica judith and victoria.  Jennifer thanks for teachin me how to dance.  Adam Elise, Victoria, Molly, and Christian yall King Group!!  Amethyst, Rebecca (Bex), and Aliza.  Kim lol u spoil ur boyfriend to much.  Tierionna my wife hahaha.  Heather and Sara.  I Miss all of yall Now my friends from the beach! Hey to Carly and Emily we have to chill more now in jackson.  Alicia and Natalie! Ashleigh and Brittani well come visit when trent does.  Brittany and Meghan we loved hangin out with yall.  Cara and  Berry.  Lauren lol it was fun.  Megan and shannon yall were both cool. Courtney hey!,   Cant forget Katie who came down to visit me :) Mine as well thrown in all my friends from engineering camp .. go white team .. Cody coconuts!, Elizabeth (shorty), Lance, Reed. Kenny, Bryndan and Henry, Stephanie i had a great time, Tim u were halarious, moose ( u and melody lol) melody, Dana, Laura, Mary Katherina, O.B. we gotta hang out in jackson, and michael. I Hope i didnt forget too many ppl miss yall .. wow i met tons of ppl this summer its been great!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      well my car is dead for awhile they have to order a new wiring harness thats gonna take a long time to do. :( *sniffle* im gonna miss it.  i have to find something new to take care of lol.  it depressed me for about a hour but im over it already im happy again :) .   o well i g2g hopefully im gonna go out somewhere tonight. peace out homies 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      BACK FROM THE BEACH.... ahhh it was soo fun i dont know how to explain it. well here are 2 words .. nonstop fun.  me and bryndan were havin the time of our life down there sayin out till almost 2 everynight meeting new ppl everyday.  if u wanna know stories from the beach ask me directly .. lol they are more fun that way ohh yeah i dont have work tomorrow! but my car is in the shop i swear it must wear a screw me over sign like bryndans or something but o well life is still great.  i wanna go to the new walmart tomorrow :) i hope everybody had a good time while i was gone.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      its sunday and im bored .. i dont have anything to write about so i just figured i would say hey to whoever reads this....  i wish it was sunny outside .. its ok though .... the week of the beach of approaching and will be upon us soon
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It has been an incredibly long time since i wrote a blog i hope everybodys summer is goin good!  i know mine has been.  there have been 2 main things that took up my time since i last wrote a blog.  engineering camp and NYL confrence in DC.  both of which were about 5 times more fun that i thought they would be.   Engineering camp: engineering camp was soo cool me and bryndan went and we thought it was gonna be like school, but we got to have fun the whole time well except when were were learning about really confusing or boring stuff.  we did some really cool stuff though like simulations and then we did fun stuff like played in the mud and went bowling and swimming and went on a boat in the mississippi.  the last night was the best everybody stayed up till about 5 in the morn and we watched movies and stuff.  lol old school was a great movie if u havent seen it, u  need to.   there were some really cool ppl too!  i was glad to get back from engineering camp though i missed everybody here and i missed being able ot sleep on a bed instead of an army cot which wasnt to confortable.   when i got home i started working out for football and working again.  i slaved away tuesday through friday and then happily got my check on friday and cashed it so i could spend it all in dc.  then i packed all day on saturday and went to tell alot of ppl goodbye before i left then me and liz were off on our plane to dc.   DC when we got there it really sucked.  we waited at the airport for 4 hours for the shuttle to come pick us up and it never came. it wasnt as bad it sounds thought b/c there were about 50 other ppl waiting also so i was meeting ppl while i was there.  after sitting there that long me and 6 other ppl that i had just met decided we would get a minivan taxi to bring us to the hotel so we found a cool driver named cj and we loaded up 7 ppl and all their stuff and went off on our 1 hr drive to the hotel.  i met 3 ppl that i became good friends with on the taxi ride to the hotel.  we got there and got our rooms and everything and i was staying with 2 cool guys but i got there last so lucky me got the rollaway bed the whole time.  it was better than an army cot though.   throught the week i kept mettin lots of moreppl and we had speakers and went and toured the city and i even got to meet some goverment ppl it was cool.  they let us in places that regular tourists ppl dont get to go.  ohh our bus .. the first 2 days it was hell .. literaly.   the air was broke and inside out bus was hotter than outside and it was 95 outside. it was insane but then they got us a new bus and we got to watch the goonies! ohh yeah and we got to go to sixflags and a oriles baseball game!  both of those were soo much fun!  we had 2 dances also they were great too.  i prettymuch learned how to do a body roll lol.  then the end of the camp was commin close it was the last dance and i was dancing with katie who i met about 1/2 way thought the camp she was soo cool i miss her!  she lives in AL. but ne way that last night was soo great i'll always remember it and all my friends from NYLC, too many to name right here. on the day when everybody was leaving there tons of people crying.  katie was crying and then me and lizzy ended up crying on the bus to the airport (jeans, orange shirts, and tears) i didnt want to leave all my friends they were soo great.  i got home and i was all depressed but then bryndan and ben spent the night and they cheered me up some and then on the 4th i shot tons of fireworks and blew lots of stuff up and bryndan, ben, patrick, and brad all spent the night.  it was great fun! then today i didnt wake up till 12 30 or so.  everybody left and then i went over to erins for 2 1/2 hours and i showed her all the pictures and stuff and told her lots of stories then i went to church.  ohh yeah and then i called katie from NYLC and we talked for 45 min or so and then lizzy came over and i showed her my pictures too.. she wasupset that she ddidnt get hers back yet.   I hope i didnt bore everyone with that long entry but i figured i would catch everyone up with my life.  I hope urs is going great! peace
     

    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight was good well most of it although stressFULL at times!!  i think i did good on trig and personal finance and we had football for about 45 min, and the rest got rained out.  I forgot my physics binder and i have a physics test tom so that really sucks! then we had meet the bruins.  there was free food!! haha i had 3 sandwitches and a hotdog.  Then i came home and did some religion homework and kinda studied for a bit.  Then i called folks well jessica and thats when it kinda got stressful but it worked out or i think it did.  i think tomorrow will be a good day.  we have out football scrimage and then were (me and bryndan) are goin to the mc game and i get to see jessica dance!!! she been tellin me about it alot so i cant wait.  after that i think i have to come home though b/c my sister is commin into town and i "have to spend time with her b/c i never get to see her" so my parents say.  but thats what up in my life right now so im goin to bed i really need some good sleep.  hope everybody is doin good.  *peace out to all my homies* :P
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      well... life is good right now.  nothin is really goin wrong, except i read a journal thing *corey* cough cough and i was not liked :(  lol, but if that the worst thing then im doin great in life.  im still in a good mood if u cant tell.  i had act class tonight that was funny again.  i got to stop by jessicas and give her her belated birthday present.  i think she liked it :).  we get to go watch it this weekend!!  ohh and its gonna be a extra long weekend!  football was easy b/c of the temp.  tomorrow at 630 is meet the bruins. fun fun! actually its never that bad b/c i get alot of free food! i got 2 tests and some homework to do but guess what.... im not gonna do it tonight hahaha im so busy i just dont care.  ok well im gonna head out hope everyone is doin good if u actually read these things u can call me some time b/c nobody ever calls my cellphone ne more its depressing haha.  im out! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      IM SOO BUSY!! ahh ok im good now.  so whats up everybody?  not a whole lot here.  The past few days have been GREAT.  Espically sunday, i spent i long time with jessica i feel alot closer to her now.  ive been in a really good mood and nothing can really get me down even my 5 hrs + of homework.  everything seems ok.  football is goin good.  hey its the 25th it would have been a 1 year anniversery today of me and jes today.  but its all good really it is.  but hey i already got to go i have to go finish a watercolor study and do physics and its already 11 30.  i'll try and write again soon. byes  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well school is getting into full swing and it kinda sucks but its better than the first day b/c im gettin used to it.  This week has been pretty good i guess.. i almost died at football at monday, tues was a little better and today was really good (probally b/c i finally got to play my fav position, middle linebacker).  School isnt hard at all at least so far.  its just it takes up more time that last year .. maybe b/c i do all my homework lol.  Tonight was the act, sat, psat prep thing once again!  i picked up erin on my way there and then dropped her off again (sry katie i stole her from u for the night hahaha).  it was alright i was gettin really ADD though.  i got sooo bored probally b/c we were learning about fractions whooo! lol but at least i had some ppl to talk to.  I got to leave football early for it too its all good.  after that i was gonna go to get jessica a present b/c her b day is tomorrow but everything was closed so i guess i'll give her a belated gift.  hope she doesnt mind.  I have a feeling tomorrow will be a really good day and the rest of this week.  Tomorrow is special teams day at football and then after football me and bryndan and hopefully ben (he got in trouble but i dont know how much yet i havent heard the word) are gonna head over to swensons for jessicas party.  free icecream! yummm.  ok well im gonna head out and get a good night of sleep .. i need one ttyl!  hope everyone is havin a good school year so far! laturz!  P.S. - sry if i didnt call u tonight (or latley) and i usually do.  i am and have been really tired and overworked.  but i still love u  :-)  :~)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a long day or at least it seemed like it with that act class thing.  but today was also a good day! i figured some things out today and it went really good. i even did all my homework so im startin the school year out right. g'night and everybody have a good day tom. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well my first day of school went pretty good except for realizing how freekin busy im gonna be all year long and even more so during football.  everyday - football till 6 15 then afterwards mon - ap  history thingy, tues - work out, wed - ACT class, thurs- Football dinners, fri- football games.  wow theres my whole week ok that enough complaining its not gonna be that bad really.  my teachers all seem pretty cool, dont have any mean ones or anything.  yesterday doesnt even seem like it was a school day. this weekend has already been really long.  ne way ... yesterday (after school) was great. we had a really good football practice and then i went and ate some dinner and then i went over to jessicas and we watched some movies. it was fun!  ohh yeah and my momma got a new car yesterday its perty!!  i has a bunch of cool buttons that do stuff lol.  im to scared that i will wreck it so i havent driven it.  lets see .. today was good too! i woke up and me and bryndan and reggie went to a vollyball game at our school and then we helped my sister move a tv and she paid us for the work we did awhile ago and then we went to walmart and the we went to work out with reggie brother (rod) and then me and bryndan and sarah e and corEy and tina (our new german exchange student) all went to see pirates of the (i dunno how to spell it).  it was good again lol.  then we all went and got coffee and goofed around lol.  they were slow on my coffee so i get a free one next time!! oh yeah and bryndan taught tina to play checkers.  then we all split our paths and went out seperate ways except for me and bryndan of course he is spending the night lol.  ive been pretty busy latley but its been good! laturz
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was good except for football.  i felt like i was gonna die but i did get some cool gloves and a face mask thing.  first i had to chean my room and i mean really clean it (even the closet where everything gets thrown! ahh)  but it wasnt that bad and now they carpet cleaning ppl can get to all the carpet.  then b4 football i went to go see how sarah e was doin with her gettin her teeth out and everthing. she was doin good or so it seemed.  after that i had to head out to football.  the whole team was suckin in up after this weekend i dunno what it did to us.  but then after football bryndan came over we both got cleaned up and he headed over to ruths and i went to pick up jessica and we went to the movies.  pirates was such a good movie!  after we picked up some coffee and went to her house to meet up with kegan and mk and bryndan.  they all got there and we hung out for awhile it was great fun. poor bryndan he got hit in the eye with a rock. i swear he has the worst luck with stuff but bryndan .. ur the funniest person i know lol u  always make me laugh.  then i got attacked by a cat and mk couldnt figure out how to put my car in gear hahaha (she wasnt pushing on the break) but then bryndan headed out ray came over and then i headed out right after that.  i forgot to tell my parents that i was gonna chill overthere after the movie so they were kinda upset but its all good now. and now im gonna go to sleep and get some rest so i can actually have a good practie at football tomorrow!  im out   :~)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got home from shreveport tonight and ive been busy ever since i got back.  as soon as i got back i went to church and then to o charlies and then swimmin and then played monopoly until midnight and now im home.  it was a good night.  it was me and katie and erin and bryndan and tripp the whole night and victor, Q and chris all were there some of the time.  i had some good food and i never get to hang out with katie and erin like i used to so it was good to go do something with them for a change. :) poor erin i think shes having taylor troubles again but i dont know for sure. ne wayz im gonna head out and to go sleep.  if i wake up i may catch an early movie b4 football but if not i will go probally go see sarah e.  g'night everybody ~peace 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      damn i just messed up my entry i had a nice long one goin but now its not gonna be as long.  football has been most of my life this past week.  its been every morning and afternoon and then ppl have just been stayin at my house inbetween. ive got in really good shape though.  then ive just been doin doin random stuff after football everynight.  3 and 4 nights ago i was chillin with sarah e. and her friends that was fun.  we got to play in a new maxima .. i like those cars.  2 nights ago i had a relaxin night at home and just talked on the phone from 9 till 12 to a bunch of diff ppls and then last night we got chased my sarah b's physo mom.  it was scary. me and bryndan had to jump out of the car and run home a 1/4 and mile and pull some 007 shiznet so we wouldnt be seen lol. and then afterwards we took courtney home out in deerfield. she was cool i didnt really know her to well.   then today we only had 1 practice it was hardcore he hit really hard for awhile. me and bryndan almost killed each other haha. and then tonight me and bryndan went to a cookout on the resivour and the played some interesting card games out there too.  i seemed to always end up in boxers :).  then after that i went to go pick up jes at a party over in canton and me and bryndan went in i saw a whole bunch of ppl i knew and then i had to leave and she got picked up at my house so i wouldnt be late.  and bryndan is spendin the night 2 night and i gotta pack to go to shreveport LA tomorrow.  its my gparents 60th wed ann.  damn thats a long time lol.  well im gonna head out i'll c yall laturz. :p 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My Lan party is over .. it was fun there were about 5 ppl that came that i didnt even know but it was all good and it was fun.  i hope everybody that came had a good time. i g2g soon so my life since my last blog:   ive just been hangin out with friends, workin for my sister, runnin from the cops, playin halo, goin to walmart, reading, cleaning my house and recleaning it this morn, thinking about stuff, and chillin at home.  ive had a good time. im out ~MJG
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      AHH we won!!! 32 - 8 it was great.  the whole night was great (excpt for the camps lol but i just had to work though them :P) ne way i will write more when i get some more time.  life is good and fun.  hope yalls is also! ~MJG
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      we lost last night (bad) but i had a great time playing!  lol. poor bryndan got a concussion or something of that sort b/c he sure couldnt remember what he was doing lol.  life has still been doin really good latley.  i dont get to see jes as much as i would like but i guess some time is better than none! and i think were gonna get to do something tonight!  blahh i had to wake up at  8 30 this morn to go help out at the church ... i really really didnt wanna get up!  i survived though and now i dont know what im gonna do but im going to do something so i will catch yall later.  have a great day! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had a great birthday!! thank you to everyone who made it a good day (that would be everysingle person that wished me happy birthday today :) ).  football even went good, even though i think i pulled my groin doin something but its alright i can still play.  i didnt get to much 4 my bday but not much is exactly what i wanted so it was great.  jes came overtonight and so did my sister and my neices it was fun lol.  but i didnt do anyhomework tonight i just plain didnt feel like doing it so i didnt lol.  its my night off so its ok.  ok well i think im gonna go listen to some music, relax, and then go to sleep.  yall have a great day.  :)  Mood: i feel like "everythings perfect" Music: Dave Matthews - Tonight lets be ... Worry: none!   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a great day! we lost our game last night though.. (thank you to anyone that came to see us play) The game just sucked b/c we almost came back in the second half but then we fubled twice. i heard the dance team did good thought so thats cool.  and jessica came to my game! and i got to see her afterwards.  i was soo tired after the game though so we just chilled for a little bit then she had to go home and i passed out.  then today my mom made me a 9:00 haircut... yeah 9 o clock in the morn!! omg it sucked but its all good i made it though.  after that i came home for awhile and cleaned out my desk dawer and found a bunch of stuff i didnt know i had it was kinda cool.  then jessica came over at about 1.  we made (and ate lol) some cookies for bryndan for his birthday which by the way is tomorrow if anyone didnt know (Damn big 17) and then after showin jes my new shirts for a while we went over to her house for a hour :)... and then from there i went to church which i was almost late for :p lol but i made it.  we ate the best fish after church tonght lol i love food!  now bryndan is spending the night and we are wakin up early tom to go to new orleans!! hooray its gonna be bryndans birthday.  i hope the saints win, look for our football team on tv! my birthday doesnt really seem like a big deal to me this year for some reason.  o well lol.  life is going great right now. im always happy and looking foward to things and ppl.  despite how busy i am and how things are around here, im still fairly relaxed.  i hope everybody who reads this is havin a great day and a great life.  i'll talk to yall later. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey folks!  whats goin on?  im at school right now in personal finance lol.  out physics test got cancled!  life is goin really good for the most part.  Ive been trying to spending time with jessica latley .. i always feel like i dont have anything to worry about overthere:) i love it.  Bradlys dad died which really sucks it got me thinkin how blessed i am for all i have and that i still have it all.  Ive just been up to the same old stuff latley though.  school and football.  i asked jessica to our homecoming and then she asked me to hers.  im lookin foward to it! its gonna be fun .. wow a year ago i was looking foward to the same thing.  omg im almost 17.  i dont feel old enough to be 17.  september 16th!  its commin up fast i think it will be fun even though i doubt i will feel different.  ok well im goin back to eating my 1st sandwitch b4 lunch so i will catch yall later.  Come to our football game this friday!!! its at st joe!  im out laturz.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Whew! its been a long time since ive had a chance to write anything at all on here.  life has been good though, busy like always.  ive had my good days and bad days mostly good though.  school has actually been alright.  i was tryin soo had to make all a's but i didnt i think i got 1 b that i know of in damn boshers history class but o well its ok at least its better than i usually do.   football kinda sucked for a little bit but it got better.  we still have only won one game but we played really good this past friday against a 8-0 team.  i was glad and its fun again.  yesterday was great i spent the whole day with jessica we went over to her family renuion in LA it was nice.  i think her family liked me which is a good thing lol.  they were all pretty good people.  ok well i wanted to write more b/c i have more to say but my rents are naggin me to come down and eat lunch with them and i just ate breakfast but o well i'll go ne way.  i'll try to write more often peace out!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today went good! but it has already been a fairly long feeling week, hopefully it will speed up soon.  I think i kinda made myself have a good day, i relaxed alot at home and actually played hard at tennis (ya know releasing those endorphins lol).  A good day is a good day though.  i think im going to go to bed early again like i have been, it has been very good for me getting at least 9 hrs everynight.  i like it :).    ps- teaching math to ppl who dont enjoy math is difficult lol it sure takes patience but i have to learn it somewhere :P (u know i love ya!)  g'night everyone have a wonderful day tom! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday summary - took SAT all morning (think i did fairly well) - went to my sisters (discussed tree house plans) - went to jessicas (i think we worked stuff out) - rode around till really late (tipsy; good thing bry was drivin)  Today summary - got only 6 hrs sleep - woke up at 9 30 - went to shoot rockets - rocket got destroyed ($$$ down drain) - angry rocket team went to play tennis - went home cleaned up and went to church - ate then confirmation class (which i really needed and enjoyed) - took the long route home and thought some too - going to sleep at 9 30 yay! (didnt do homework at all boo!)  lol well that was very consise.  hope yall have been doin good.  i guess i cant complain here.  im goin to bed. g'night and sweet dreams!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whew... my blog sure has caused some drama overhere so i may discontinue its use for a small period of time and just let whatever im thinking stay in my head and not come out of there, its alot safer there hahaha! ok well i well write on here some time in the near future (prob what happens not feelings along with it).  Oh yeah!, friends are great i dont know what i would do without em (all of you!!)  And Im Off ...  to get some brain sleep for the SAT tom morn.  g'night :)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dang! two blogs in one day that crazy.  well today went good, it went by really fast and i got out early and got inducted into the natl honor society (where afterwards i went completly picture crazy it was fun:) and all that jazz (haha thats a good movie).  after all my phonin last night apparently i was phoned out b/c the only person i talked to was bry for 2 min and i didnt even get to talk to jes tonight (well actually i kinda tried she just didnt answer any of the 3 times hrmm....i really hope nothings wrong!) its kinda sad not talkin to anybody b4 i go to bed.  o well im soo tired it doesnt matter that much (i guess).  i didnt really have anything cool to write about ohh yeah my sister called me from ATL and we talked for 25 min earlier tonight (i really wish she still lived at home =((  ) and we built alot of the rocket today both of those things were really good.  any who, im headed to bed, nighty night young ones talk to you later.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Goodmorning everybody!! :)  amazingly i woke up very refreshed this morning after going to bed at 12:15 (late for me).  it seems like it will be a good day today also, we have church and i get out early to test food and i think were gonna finish building the rocket today also! all good things.  yesterday was fairly good, right after school i went to work out but ended up playing tennis for most of the time and only working out for 30 min or so but hey it was fun.  then i made a quick trip home washed off and then tutored jes in math.  that was ok.  we were doin our own hw a lot of the time.  i just dont know though something hasnt felt right deep inside me latley and so i have really been trying to figure it out and i cant it bugs me.  humm well after i got home from that i talked to matt, (who i woke up) erin, katie mac, and david (about the rocket of course)! that was all fun but then i headed to bed, interesting day huh lol.  o well i cant complain. have a great day! buh byes.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well howdy doody to you!  tonight im feeling exausted, confused, cautious, and some word that nobody has made up yet to describe a feeling.  i dunno whats up, i had a good day though, we had a retreat and a tennis match so that means no school and it was all relaxing and everything but i just felt all weird tonight (mostly when i was talkin to jes) and im cautious and confused on trying to figure out what it means, those two things end up making me exausted and then that other feeling that there is no word for it well i dunno how to describe it either so yall can just pick a random feeling and i prob felt it some time tonight.  o well i'll just tell myself im ok and it will all be good and go pray or listen to music and go to sleep and hopefully it will all be back to normal tomorrow (hopefully).  matt if you read this sry i didnt call u back from yesterday, i will tom im just too tired tonight.  everybody else im goin to sleep so i'll catch up with u cool catz on the flip side (WO.. where did that come from! :P )
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I like tennis now, it was fun!  although we didnt win (at least the one that counted for real)  i can actually tell i am gettin better at it and that makes me a happy tennis player :) !  we have a match tomorrow also so that should be good.  Ohh today was also an easy day and i got out early, tomorrow we have our retreat, so no classes and then thurs im gettin out early also.  its great, espically the timing since im getting sick of school during the 4th quarter.  We had prayer group tonight, it was good.  i realized i kinda got further from god the past few weeks i dunno i guess ive just been cluttered with other junk so im gonna try and get that back on track in the near future b/c everything is easier then.  humm anything else .... ohh trip gave me my CHRISTMAS present tonight at prayer group, he said he has had it sitting at his house forever.  its a really cool nike visor and ppl actually told me i looked good in it so i may wear it! (hats in the past just havent been my thing).  well i think thats about it ohh i went to walmart also on my way home to get the new mercy me cd and some swiss cheese hahaha what a combo but they only had the swiss cheese to i got it and headed home to make my lunch for the retreat tom (what a massive sandwitch i packed).  i hope bryndan get back soon its just not the same without him here i also have his assignments to give him (what fun :P) ok well im headed off to bed i will catch yall prob tom or some day close to it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a good day.  lets try and remember what happened here.   oh yeah amazingly after goin to sleep at about 2 i woke up at 9 and so i decided to go to 10 30 church.  i dont like that one very much too many distracting kids lol and they would fall and make me laugh.  then after that i came home and had to make sure i had some clean school uniforms and stuff and then just layed around for a bit.  then i went to walmart and then jes' house, she re arranged her room and so i helped her move some stuff back in there, there was some really funny old stuff that i found haha.  then i got a smoothie with jes and headed to church after i dropped her off at hers. i ended up gettin there early so i called katie and i got a number for somebody lol guess who and then headed into church (wow twice in 1 day) at about 7.  they tried to answer some wack questions at our class and me and my dad both think that they were wrong but o well.  ok well im gonna get rdy for school and call some more ppl now hope bryndan is doin good up there.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Spring break (espically while matt was here) was completely awsome.  it may have just been that i ended on a high note but i has made it all seem good.  The campout at the lake was great!!! it was me tim clem bryndan and matt, ben showed up for a little while also but he went back to hannas house lol (whipped *whoopish*).  while at the campout at our lake we watched the sunset, the sunrise and had a halarious and fun time in between, i got some great videos and pics that i wish i could post on here.  then the day we came back from the campout, me bryndan and matt headed to b-ham alabama to meet up with our nylc friends.  it took about 4 hours to get there but we finally found katies house.  first we went out to dinnner with a bunch of her friends (guys were outnumbered 3 to 1 hahaha :) including bonnie who was stayin at katies and then we went to the baseball game then starbucks and then to the b-ham outlook, which was freekin amazing and i wish i had a place like that i, i could fall asleep on the hill everynight, i wouldnt even need a house out there.  it was soooo cool.  then while sittin up there 6 of us just talked about deep stuff like life and friends.  i really enjoyed it.  then after that we dropped off one of katies friends and headed back to her house where me matt and bryndan got rdy in our section of the house.  then we stayed till 5 30 in the morn watching blow and all talking and eating and all that.  after 1 hr and 30 min of sleep they woke us up and katie and bonnie headed off to school and we had breakfast and started heading back.  ohh and if you read this katie, thank you again for letting us visit, i know we all enjoyed it and you and your family were all so nice to us while we were there!! and i really try and keep in touch!  when we started heading back, it was weird, i felt like i would see them the next day or something but i realized i wouldnt and i got really sad, the exact same thing happened when i dropped matt off.  i said see you later but that usually means a day of to but it could be 2 or 3 years and i have sooo much fun with that guy.  i just got sad and emotional although i didnt cry lol.  then i came back here and insanly played tennis lol i was dead with only 8 hrs of sleep in 3 days.   ohh and then b/c of my lack of sleep and emotionality (haha dunno if thats a word) i ended up gettin in a fight with jess well it was kinda of fight, they never last over a few hours but i broke my phone when i threw it against the wall and its missing apart not, its kinda funny but not at the time.  i think were all good now though and she is commin back today, i just wish she hadnt told me somethings that she did while she was down there, nothing like hookin up with ppl but still it was frustrating, i just leave out anything that i think will make her mad but she didnt o well we pretty much worked it out and i still cant wait to see her.  ohh yeah i would like to say bryndan is crazy, right after he drove my car back from B-ham, he left to go to kentucky to visit another friend and this was after 1 hr 45 min of sleep for him.  i hope he doesnt crash!! wow that was a long one but well im goin to play tennis with hilton lutz so i will catch u guys later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im back again, wow im doin good at this blog thing i realized its b/c i dont have as many ppl to talk to, people are out of town or busy with other people, but o well.  wow its 130 in the afternoon and im already really tired.  me and matt are just sittin around overhere talkin.  about life, friends, relationships, and everything else that comes up, its great, we always have good advice or at least he does lol.  i think were gonna have to start gettin rdy to go campin tonight though and im not lookin foward to it as much as i was.  i want some quiet time and i dont think it will be too awful quiet out there, i have been doin stuff nonstop latley but o well the drive tomorrow will be good.  i can listen to music and relax then.  i havent got a chance ot talk to jes today but hopefully tonight i will. tom will be tough though b/c i will be in alabama.  ok well im gonna go and i guess get stuff ready to head out to the lake.  i will catch yall later again.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey again folks.  im really tired but im goin out again with bryndan and matt, i must be crazy.  the lan party went well but there were a couple of people missing b/c they were out of town.  and poor bryndan i feel bad for him he always gets blamed for everything, admittingly sometimes it is his fault but alot of times it isnt.  i well hope he knows we dont mean anything by it.  Mat came into town today yay!  weve been hangin out.  ohh... i finally got to talk to jes today!! i was glad b/c i missed her yesterday its all good now i just cant wait for her to get back.  ok well were leavin to go meet some of bryndans folks so i will be back laturz i dont know if i will be able to write another one when i get in or not. im out
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You dont know what youve got until its gone (even just for a week!). I think i was almost too used to jes always being there whenever i wanted to talk or whenever i wanted to see her.  But at least shes havin a good time down there or so it seems lol.   enough about all that stuff, i wish i wasnt allergic to grass and all the other outside stuff, everytime i go out to the lake i start getting sick! it really sucks! i cant barly breath right now and i think i am gonna go to sleep at like 9:30 or so tonight.  im just really tired. ohh yeah! lan party tomorrow and matts commin in yay!!!!!  ok well i guess thats a good place to end so i will catch yall later im off to bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *quote of the day* Be happy while you're living, for you're a long time dead.  (very true!)  Today was went really good except for the weather.  It was too cloudy and rainy.  IT wasnt very eventful though.  I didnt really do anything until 11 30 when i started cleanin up from the family that was overhere.  Then at 12 i got to talk to jes that was good b/c i had felt like talkin for awhile, sounds like shes havin a good time too :) im glad b/c i was kinda worried she wouldn't i like it when she has fun with all her girl friends.  After i talked to her, i semi worked out b/c i was lazy and then sat around illegally downloaded about 35 songs (i went to the music billboard and just got most all of the top 10's lol) and then burned a cd and then i showered and headed to church.  I was figuring i would just got home but then tripp katie and erin showed up and invited us out to dinner.  At dinner (at Ocharlies) it was Nick (clem) katie erin tripp mark lee quinten and then chris showed up and so did jermey.  Bryndan was at church but he never came to dinner,  he was out pimpin the ladies lol.  its all good though im good with my current lady situation.  and THEN after that (yes there is still more haha)  me and nick bought almost 100 worth the groceries for the xbox lan party on tuesday and the camp out on wednesday.  it was great fun at walmart.  now im home writtin this thing.  What a nice day huh lol.  dammit lol i forgot to call matt george again!!! that my friend thats comming in town on this tuesday.  ok well im gonna head off to bed it was nice writin again and apparently somebody reads this b/c i had a little post thing on the bottom yay! :-) even though i dont know who it is lol.  ~thats all folks~
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhhh! spring break is here! and i am really glad.  well the first few hours of spring break were good and now the first day went good also.  Last night i spend most of (lol) the night with jessica and that was good except for when she was pouting then i just had to wait it out.  But i still really had a good time, im gonna miss her alot 8 days is a long time but then again it isnt, it just depends on how u look at it.  o well i just hope she has a good time down there (i think she is already).  Today was alread really busy, no time for relaxing for me.  right when i woke up, which was way to early for when i went to bed, i got ready to go fishing and i was at the lake from 9 or 10 until 3:30.  but then again i only really fished for an hour or two rest of the time i was gettin the bon fire ready or eating with bryndan.  Then after that i went to go play tennis with hilton and got more sunburned, ohh yeah and he nailed me in the chest (accidnetly lol right) with the ball it felt like i had got shot!! then me and bryndan rode around tonight well actully i drove around and bryndan and sarah b rode around lol that was interesting.  it was a good first day thought i didnt get to talk to jes all day though :( o well tom i will hopefully be able to.  g'night im out.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ummm i forgot how to work this thing!! its been forever, bryndan you inspired me to start agian i saw that you still wrote in yours and i also figured its a good way to keep in touch with some of the ppl that i dont see as often as i used to.  Well life hasnt changed too much since i last talked, im still michael, havent lost any arms or legs, still live in the same house with pretty much the same friends, but i don know how to build a 3d house now!  it may seem boring but i usually manage to entertain myself fairly well!! ok enough of the blabberin.  im spend for my first new entry im about to head off to bed and i will just have to try and remember to write to yall soon.  hope everyones life has been doin good!  if you ever feel like callin my number is 594-9172, at least for now, bc my phone is a P(eice)O(f)S(hit) and it only works when i need it to least but i will eventually get back to ya.  G'night and laturz.  ~Michael
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another fab-u-los-o day at school (espically for a monday!!) I think its gonna be an amazing week with prom and all! first period wasnt to fun b/c i thought i would be at a honor roll breakfast but they cancled it grrr. lol but after that everything was great! lets see, we didnt do anything in english, religion, history, and i painted in art.  lol it was fun. im sooo happy about how my art project is turing out!! i wanna paint more doors haha.  for some reason im amazingly hyper! i mean i ran for 40 min earlier today b/c i didnt want to die at spring training next week and now i have even more energy.  im goin to get my tux tonight too!! hooray im gonna look all spiffy lol.  ok well im goin to do more fun stuff. good bye mi amigo!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A good sunday. i just got home from church, confirmation class, and jessicas.  The college fair this afternoon was bunk.  it was sooo boring and nobody came all i did is sit around and talk to folks.  i did enter for a 500 buck scholarship whew hew! lol.  lets see oh yeah jes told me about the party up at ole miss, it definately made me excited about going to college but it made me think about how hard it will be if we try to stay together then.  ok well im off to sleep i already did ALL my homework (thats an amazing feat for me) good night folks and sweet dreams. ohh yeah and ITS PROM WEEK YAY!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good sunday morning to ya! wow its nice out today (again!) i was just gonna say hey b/c i dunno i felt like it lol. hope everybody got home safe last night.   well im about to go work on a paper outside.  hope you have a fablous day!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was a good day in the life of michael gaston today.  It all started out when i woke up at about 8:30.  i got up read my little purpose driven book and went down and cooked some breakfast, egg and bacon wraps to be exact. as i was eating i got a call from bryndan and me and my mother picked him up at wendys, along with my neice katie, on the way to sams.  It was at sams that we played with things, got free samples and finally, got the seniors presents.  after our adventures at sams, we came back to my hizzouse.  when we got home, my father was, once again, was alsleep and not responding, and at this point we left to go fishing, it was suppose to be with ben also, but he stayed at hannah's and disbanded us once more.  we didnt do a whole lot of fishing, we mostly just absorbed sun, which by the way greatly improved my tan!  after the lake we came back and bryndan was dropped off at steffany's  (sp?) house by myself.  after this i left, all alone, and began my journey to find a party.  i called callie, then lizzy, then bryndan, then hannah and i finally had the answer, two parties (mikey or marjory) i picked the latter.  it was great fun, me and callie rode together (less gas and safer driver) and the whoop juice was good, i was greatly dissapointed at the fact the jessica couldnt be there though (but i bet she is having a great time getting hit on at the frat parties), a few of her own friends were even there (casey, amanda, and sarah).  after the party i came home and that brings me to my current state and position at the computer.   HAHA i dont know why i typed my blog in that manner of speech but i just wanted to be different tonight and well it was.  ok well im headed to bed now.  Good night folks
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The day itself went well today, but tonight i feel like blah.. im just ready for bed, i guess after being outside and mowin the grass i just used up all my energy.  i think im gonna go read something good for me (which i got out of the habit of and really want to make myself get back into) and then go to bed (and yes i know its not even 930 yet lol but o well) G'night i will talk to yall later.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well today went really good! i dont know why exactly (i mean it was my first day back at school) but it did lol.  all my classes went really well (except english he got pissed at me and i threw by backpack lol damn u mr greene!!)  and they went by fast also! then after school i dropped a simon off at the courthouse, went home for a bit to get changed etc. and then went back and worked out for about a hour.  it was a great workout (i think thats what got me so happy lol) and then after that, i went and watched our tennis team play a match while i just talked to a few ppl for a while.  I found out i finally weigh a constant 190 now!!!!! yay!! about time.  ne way next i Got home ate (a whole lot!!!) and went to give jes some pictures. stayed there a little ova an hour. while i was there we kinda decided that we wernt compatibale for marriage b/c she wants a diff everyday type life that what i wanna or planned on having.  that was an odd thing.  and now im here, gettin rdy to go to bed early! :)  tomorrow im only going to one class so that will be good to. haha! ok well im out catch yall laturz! have a wonderful day!  Sorry it was so long about nothing much again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It is such a beautiful day outside, the clouds are few but nice, the sun is bright and warming, the leave are a fresh young green, the sent of freshly blooming flowers and moist ground, you can hear the birds singing even from my window, and the cool (almost cold lol) breeze are all soo nice today.  ok well i wanted to seperate the good blog and the bad blog so im just writing two for today lol.  I had a great time at the beach with jessica and her family over easter break.  there were a few times in there where it ended up getting kinda boring (what can u expect when u are with older ppl lol) but overall it was good.  poor jes though, she got worn out easily on this trip, i wish i could have given her some of my energy so we could have gone and done more but o well it was still great fun.  She did get a hole in one twice haha oh and i got some cute beach pics too! ok buh bye for now :)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      u know what im tired of, im tired of my dad going getting really depressed and just sleeping, its like when he gets in that mood he changes to someone else and isnt even my dad anymore.  All i want is to have him stay one way or the other really, then i would know what was going on for sure.  i would give up about anything if he would always be his happy self just wanting to go do stuff with me all the time and actually being able to.  About every thrid day by noon on that day he is just different.  when he is like this, one day i can be talkin to him and we talk about going to do something the next day and were gonna go do it but then he goes to sleep and acts different b/c apparently he is depressed again.  i dont even know if it is depression but whatever it is, it blows and i wish i could get rid of it.  all it does it stress my mom out and frustrate me.  today alone besides when i saw him right after i woke up, all he has been doing is falling asleep and slurin words and stuff.  And if hes like that when my friends are over my mom just takes him to the back room and he just chills there so she wont be embarrased.  o well.  sorry about last night folks... yeah..
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      we;;; this is my6 fiurst drunk blog! lol hahahaha bry is on the phone now. u was plannin on writing a blopgh about the beach with jes niut i guess i will have to do that some tother time. i cant type to good reight now.  i cant even feel all my body parts but its ok b/c ewe ran out of drinsks so u dont have to worry abouts us drinkin too much ok well nbry wants me to come and c whats up so i willll takklk to yall later buh byes muah lol hehe buhe ohh and i guess g night and have a good day at school tom ab/c we dpnmt have schoool tomorrow lol haha. e[peace out !
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well overall, it was a pretty good weekend!  i sure dont have anything to complain about.  Ohh well i guess i could complain i didnt get to see bryndan all weekend b/c he was so busy with everybody wanting him (girls espically lol) he went to two proms, took the act, and had work all in one weekend. that equals the social life i have in about a month!! lol o well its all good.   today went well though, i went fishing and then came back and picked up the jes (lazy sleeping in bum haha) and went back out there and fished some more.  thats really about all i did today ohh and of course palm sunday church service and confrimation class.  and then walmart and TRIED to get the rocket to work right  BUT it didnt do what i had in mind.  o well im off to bed i dont feel like doing homework so i'll do it in the morn right b4 its due (then it will be fresh in my mind for class lol) ok well g'night.  love you guys, whoever reads this.    PS. --- i got a BB gun its so much fun it will entertain me for at least an hour per day. (i think i killed an innocent fish :( with it though ) i got a big scope on it too.  (i feel like a terrorist :P)  haha wow i feel like a 6 year old maybe thats b/c i sometimes act like one too. g'night again!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      YUMMMM!! i had an awsome steak dinner tonight it was really good! and to think, i didnt think jessica could cook.  well she proved me wrong lol.  today went well i rebuild out entire rocket (very painstaking) took the ACT (not to bad reading was no fun) and watched some movies. tom should be good too, im plannin on goin fishin, drawing, church, and maybe some tennis if time permits.  good night folks :)  ohh yay easter is almost here!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fairly good night! stations of the cross went really well!! just kinda hung out rest of the night.  lazy day.  went to the dresden exhibit (reccomend it!) and just sat around at school, didnt to too much. now im goin to sleep to get rdy for the ACT tomorrow :) wish me luck lol.  G'night fellas.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happiness is contagious!  So, be happy and spread it!  (unfortunately, so is unhappiness so you better be happy or else lol ) ~michaels made up quote of the night
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *smile* :D  It was a fablous day!  well it started when i woke up this morn, i woke up without my alarm, which always makes my days better b/c i dont have some annoying noise waking me up and then i was like damn i have to go to school now but then i remembered i didnt!! so i got rdy and left to go pick up bryndan to head to the habitat for humanity house we were working on.  It was such a good day to be outside working! it was a great sky, a great temp, and everything else.  it was even fun workin out there, we build a bunch of stuff and i build a very nice chair out of scrap wood it was funny lol even had a back to it.  there goes me and my building stuff again   :-)  Me and lauren and lee and quinten and bryndan were all havin fun all day, ohh and a old friend from nylc kimbrel was there from JA! then at about 3 45 they let of off there (which was ab an hr early) and me and bryndan cruised away with the windows down just chillin hahaha and i dropped him off at home went to go get some gas and vacume my car (with a broken gas station vacume that didnt suck like it was suppose to) whew sorry this is a long one.  but when i got home after that me and my dad went to go work out together up at the courthouse and we sat george, trent, alex, and faibanks all up there.  i messed around lifting weights with them for about a hour and then came home for 10 min and headed to get a haircut (which was way too expensive and not very good) and then that ends me where i am now, writing this thing after a nice long shower.  so yeah ive stayed busy but it has all been fun, now i just need to go call a few ppl and head to sleep after that.  no real school tomorrow either! we have the dresen exhibit yay!! ohh and im preforming in the stations of the cross on friday night at st richards at 5 30 if anybody wants to come up there im gonna be one of those mean guards lol.  ok well im off to use the tele lol and then prob be asleep b4 10 again (im lovin this goin to bed early thing) if you got this far in reading then your a good friend (or are incredible bored) lol and thank you :-)  buenos noches senors y senoritas.  Hasta mannana!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey folks! whats goin on? not much here, im just chillin in dallas! hooray guess what, matt george and his friends from OK are commin down here and im goin to hang out with them tonight at speed zone, the same place we had brandons suprize b day party yesterday.  he had no idea, it was great!  This has been a very relaxing and fun family vacation.  ive got a bunch of just chill time by the pool and by myself where i can just think and wonder.  it will be good to be home tomorrow though (only for a day haha) but still.  ok well im off to take a nap, i ate a couple pounds of lunch, uhhh mexican food lol. ok well i'll catch yall later.  peace, much love, and something else fun?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The past few days have been really good! exams all finished up and were pretty easy, were out of scholl, i have been able to relax a lot, and ive been hanging out will all my friends.  now im headed to dallas to see my sister and my broinlaw for his suprize bday.  thats should be a fun one! i gotta go finish packin 4 the trip now and i'll be flyin outta here pretty soon!  Life is good!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was fairly good! i pretty much worked non stop all day.  at 930 i started helping hilton move his cousin to a new apartment, finished that and got unexpectdly paid! and then went to go help mr harkins lay sod and stuff, changed hiltons flat tire on the way there lol, and then worked there till about 4 or so. went to swim for about a hour and then came home and finished building and painted my new sub box.  it was really a fufilling day today.  i always like it when i have something to show 4 all the work i do, now i have 100 bucks in my pocket from all that work and a brand new flame covered unique sub box! hooray for me! lol.  oh and i got a lot of sun! i hope tomorrow is good, and kinda busy, i gotta stay entertained these days. i think im going swimming again.  ok well im headed to bed since it was such a hard day workin. g'night and much love to whoever reads these things to the end :)!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today's school day was great! well besides that it was school.  we watched movies in 2 classes and did nothing in all the others! i really need summer to be here now.  my big topic for today is that me and jes are further seperated. i think i remember something about only communicating once a week now.  i have a feeling im going to get really bored and depressed in the next few weeks even though it was kinda my idea to do this, so yeah if u read this give me a call if u know something to get me out of the house.  its the little things that i will miss though! now when i get bored, i will stay bored not go to jessicas. nobody to always miss me, tonight i felt soooo lonley it was insane! i really didnt like it at all. ive been kinda second guessing what i had earlier decided but i think i need to try and stay apart 4 now.  then i will know how i really do feel.  i just need somebody i can talk to! gahh! on a happier note.  at least the weather is good now.  im starving but dont really feel like eating so im gonna go to bed 4 now.  good night my friends!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hummm.  i dunno what to think about today.  it wasnt a bad day, we were just kinda there not doin much at all. i got a bunch of unexpected awards today, that was nice! after school i started makin a new thingy 4 my car, haha u know i was bored then i went runnin.  When i got home, things were really stressful around my house, some of u prob know why, so i said i was going to jessica and just went to watch the sun set for 1.5 hrs up at our lake, i took lots of good pics!  then after that i ate at jessicas.  that felt kinda weird tonight, not the food but just being there. i really dont know what to think about us right now.  i dunno if we should just be friends or keep dating for awhile or what. im emotionally confused.  she will prob read this and get all upset but i really am just trying to figure out what i think is right for me at this time. ok well im goin to use the phone! im out, g'nght!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nice day here! today was my rents 30th wedding anniversery so that was kinda cool, and it was katie mallettes b-day (sexy 17!) that was fun too, i gave her a cd w/ a cd case.  it was a really nice day up until the sky fell out!!! omgosh it rained sooo hard here.  ohh yeah and i went to the doctor today, they gave me a z-pack, some nose spray, and alegra D, and took an xray of my sholder and told me my collar bone was kinda seperated form my sholder.  no workin out for 2 weeks!!! ahh, o well i guess i will do situps and run for 2 weeks lol.  tomorrow is my neices birthday yay! i get to go play at chuckie cheeses haha it will be great fun, im sure i will get harassed by her little friends like i do every year though.  i hope everyone that reads this silly little thing is having a blessed and wonderful life! love yall i dont know what i would do without my friends.  peace out and good night! MJG
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This past weekend was crazy! i dont know if i can deal with that many people at my house anymore.  get-to-gethers maybe should be located at some other place these days.  saturday night i had 12 people spend the night!  whew.  o well.  i think they all wore me out, not to mention i was sick b4 they even came over, so i ended up sleeping from 8 last night to 7 this morning.  11 hrs of sleep it was great.  it made school alot nicer also, all alert and all.  today a got to work out (actually life weights) it was great fun i havent done that in a long time i missed it.  my sholder is still messed up though :( no fun.  ok well im gonna go do my homework (i still have 2 weeks of school grrr.) and just relax, make some phone calls, and enjoy life tonight!  buh byes!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was a great day! i didnt really go to school today except for about 1 hour. that sure was nice.  i was "working" for junior ambassadors today.  i had to sit a hole number 16 on the golf course with my own little cart and let ppl bring be water while i watched to be witness incase somebody made a hole in one! it was such a difficult job but i think i did a pretty good job.  today was also our last day of football practice. we had a big practice game thingy.  i didnt think i played that well today but bryndan sure was doin good. tonight i went to bops with bryndan.  erin and katie (who now work at bops) made me a yummy milkshake and me and bry sat and talked to ppl and laughed. it was fun. and now im home.  i really dont wanna go to school tomorrow though.  im terribly tired and bored with school! o well i might survive!  it was kinda weird tonight not talkin to jes. humm just decided to throw that in!  we may do something tom though i dunno.  o well for now im off to bed! i will be back later! good night my friends!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      :D ! i feel a whole lot better and relieved now. Today went very well! school went good, football went ok, and the archie manning dinner was really good! the best thing was after when i got 2 talk 2 jes. we worked out all the stuff that had been goin on!  No arguments or anything we basically agreed on it all today!  we decided that we shouldnt be boyfriend girlfriend right now b/c espically with summer commin up that would just be do hard!  so we are dating for the time being.  that means alot more relaxed and a lot less serious.  also, just talk every few days, dont worry about having to do something all the time, more time for all my friends, and just simpler overall!  i think it will be alot better and easier!  im happy, good night!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhhhhhhhhh *breath in* ahhhhhh!  Are some things in life meant to be frustrating or what! ......... O well, rest of my life is going good. today i went out to my neighbors new pool and played with my neices and my neighbors kids (its scary, they are all growin up too fast for me, i feel old).  it was fun ohh and we had a really good mothers day lunch and my sisters early birthday.  i get to go visit her early this summer also:)! the rest of the day im about to head up to church and then have dinner probaly out somewhere and come home and get an early start of some sleep.  Well im gonna head out, im somewhat bored here! bye byes!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      2 parties in a row on the same weekend! thats fun lol.  tonight we went to what bryndan called "the ridgland party"  it was fun (down at the end of highland colony) there were prob about 150 ppl there at peak time!  i saw casey, sarah, and amanda there that was cool, they were excited ab takin my place at the beach lol.  i also saw tons of other ppl i knew from all over the place.  i drove myself out there tonight so i didnt drink anything again, i did take 2 little underagers home though lol.  the cops ended up driving up to this party at about 12 or so, not as early as last night.  Earlier today was a nice day though.  i woke up way to early and helped Jose with his eagle project most of the day.  i was hammering rebar and cuttin wood from 9 to 4.  After that i headed home and sat around a bit and decided to run, i ran about 3 miles (and damn it was hot/humid!) and then i had a really really relaxing jacuzzie tub bath!! omg i hadnt had one of those in a long long time i loved it i was all home alone and everything.  once relaxed we had a nice big family dinner and family time (both of which included laurnes b/f chris) and then i went out and i already told that story.  oh and jes comes home tom (at far as i know, i mean i havent talked to her since she left :p)  i really wish i could make these things more interesting i just realized most of you probally get really bored just reading the things i do in a list, i will try and make it better next time!  peace out and goodnight! everybody stay safe!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That was a fun/interesting/entertaining night!  today was a really long day (in a good way though) also, it has seemed like at least 2 or 3 days instead of just one.  First this morn, i went and took the AP US History exam, it wasnt too bad at all! then i checked out of school and went to wash my car and get gas.  that took way to long and then bry came over and we tried to go swimmin lol.  after that i said bye to jes at MC (shes headed to ole miss 4 graduation) and erin and katie tried to get their picture thing for art to work overhere but it wouldnt so they left.  then i got rdy for the sport banquet.  at that thing i got best defensive player for football and the coaches award for tennis (which i renamed the ms nichols likes michael award haha kinda scary though!)  poor bry though he didnt get a football one, i though he would this year.  after the banquet, i dropped my mom off and headed to the party at mikeys house.  Thats where the night was fun/interesting/entertaining.  i picked up a couple of ppl on the way there to be the DD (i was in no mood to drink right now b/c of all that has been going on with my dad latley) I had a really good time at mikeys though, i saw alot of ppl i hadnt seen in a long time there were TONS of ppl there :) at about 11 the cops came to mikeys house and so me and my drunk car load went around the back through the fence and drove away safley lol! then we congegrated on a street somewhere eles for about 45 min that was a lil more boring but still interesting.  humm then between about 12 and 12 15 i dropped everybody off and headed home.  and now im here!  it as a very full day! a good one though and school is comming quickly to a close! its great! hope everyone is doing good most parts of my life are just wonderful right now! im off to bed b/c i gotta help on an eagle project tomorrow early and get my sholder checked (it still makes funny noises when i move is hahaha) g'night everyone! love u!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gahh! *beep what was here lol* :) !  ne who it was a pretty good day, went by slow though.  i also cant raise my right arm, which really sucks.  hey pray 4 my dad please!  ok well i need to go study call matt and sleep.  bye bye now!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a wonderful day! it was very relaxing overall.  i woke up at about 645 and ate a nice breakfast, sat around, got dressed, and headed to take the AP english exam.  i think i bombed the multiple choice but did alright on the 3 essays.  the test was over at about 12 and that when i went checked out of school and went to macalisters for lunch.  after that i came to my house with kyle drei and bry till ab 3 when i headed to football practice, it felt soo good out today i could have ran forever but we didnt even run much.  we hit alot :) that was fun and then i came home.  then i ate and went to a john talbot concert (a christian singer guy).  it was really nice but i wasnt really into his meditative type of music although it did calm me alot.  then i came home and now im here.  tomorrow will hopefully be as easy as today.   love yall and peace out homies :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Uh oh! i think i made jessica mad tonight.  apparently i didnt pay enough attention to me so she got mad.  i dont even know what i did but i guess i feel bad for it.  the play went really well tonight though, a whole lot better than last night.  probaly because i knew what to do tonight.  i decided to help tomorrow with it also.  after the play was fun too.  we had a party after the play at my house with about 15 - 20 ppl (that when jes got mad at me) i dont remember exactly who all came.  i hope she doesnt stay mad at me.  well bryndan and hilton and nick are all spending the night and were watchin gladior since we couldnt stay outside any longer b c of the rain.  i will catch yall later today probaly lol. g'night and peace out.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes im still alive lol.  talk about busy though!! i used think i was busy but then prom time (which took up my life for about a week) came around, olympic day and campaiging for senior class pres and now this week football practice everyday and the play (which i somehow ended with the stage crew on lol) and tomorrow im getting confirmed.  its just been busy busy go go all these past two weeks.  i really wanna take a break u know... a second spring break would be nice! but hey!, its almost over for the year :) i actually got stressed out during prom week, it was scary! Everything is finally calming down though, prom ended up being really good, it looked nice and was fun. our grade won olympic day (whats new! :) and today is my last day with the play.  i won senior class pres election.  i did good on my act.  i got to miss a lot of school fri for the blessing of a habitat house. football team is lookin pretty good.  i finished my big art project.   AP english exam on monday and history on friday.  Its all lookin down hill from here :)  ohh and bry and nick are spending the night tonight yay! haha.   it looked like a couple of other ppl were slackin on the journal writing when i was too! :) at least i wasnt alone.  i sure hope that everyone else has been doing wonderful!  im off to go try and wake up my dad.  love and peace :)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hope everyone is having a wonderful day! i have sat around pretty much and been lazy, almost boring, i wish i had something pretty to look at like i did when i got bored in alaska! o well, i miss that place, i love nature! ok well im out buh byes enjoy the pics!    urlLink    I wish i could see this everyday!&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Mi Familia!&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Silly Chris!&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Just the Guys!&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Random big animal! with some big horns also&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    just a little creek runnin under the railroad tracks.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    One of the beautiful sunsets over the mountians.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    She, Emily, worked on the boat and OMG her british accent was GRRREAT!!! lol.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    After a couple of miles hiked u got a wonderful view!&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Its a big hunk of ice thingy! (glacier) there were tons of these&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Just enjoying the outside on my parents balcony.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Me and Chris leaving the bar, i dont really remember this one lol :)&nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm home.  wow the weather here sure does suck i wish it was nice, o well.  today was a long day, we started flying at about 8pm last night and got here, to jackson, at 11:30am or so.  a bunch of time changes in there also so my body is all confused!  i just went to the grocery store that was fun, NOT! lol well i did see courtney there, i hadnt seen her in 4 ever! i just unpacked and am not attempting to do nothing! lol.  i'll post some pics from my trip sometime soon.  im headed out for now.  call me if u know of something fun goin on, ive prob gotten out of the loop since i was out of town.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Its abnormally wonderful weather for alaska here, low 80's little humidity, and clear skies with fog at night!  everything is soooo beautiful, ive seen like 30 bald eagles just flyin around and today i hiked up a mountain and looked at a glacier.  wow i dont do that every day.  i really sometimes wish i lived in a place like this!  i miss everybody!  i have to go now though so im out! be home relativily soo!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was pretty good, did some normal everyday stuff and then went to david banner/ingram hill and got to take care of/watch over some "tipsy" folks.  they were absolutly halarious!! it was so funn!  the concerts were great too!  im off to my 3 plus a little hrs of sleep, and then my trip. love you guys!  buh byes!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Hey look!, its David Banner!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night was great! it was too hot but other than that, the concert was good, i saw quite a few ppl i knew, and i had a fun/funny caravan/carpool of ppl i took there (yall made me laugh alot, thank ya!) i didnt get in until ab 3 though with droppin ppl off and sayin bye and stuff so im a little worn, whew and i gotta do it again tonight 4 david banner, but i can just sleep on the plane tom.  ok well, im about to pack, eat, and get a haircut so i have to head out, this may be my last post b4 i leave town so yall have a wonderful time while im out!  i'll miss everybody (of course i will!) and i'll take lots of pics if u wanna c!  buh byes :D
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Switchfoot!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why hello to all! things are good here, last night was great fun, me and my mom and dad went to go see harry potter, yay! i liked it alot!! it was a bit different than the other 2 but still just as good! and today i went 2 best buy, installed/finished installing somebodys speakers, and now im about to head to jubliee jam to see switchfoot! yay again! it should be fun, just hope it isnt too hot out there.  hope you are doing great, yes you!  ~Migels
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight was fun! yay! i didnt just sit at home! ok well i thought i was just going to sit at home but at ab 7 i went to bops to get ice cream/ say hey to erin, katie, and hannah.  they were all to busy to talk though so i just got my shake.  i was sittin there drinkin it up and readin a book when all of a sudden i get invited to sara's bday party (by jes, thank ya) at buffalo wild wings so i decided sure why not.  there ended up being a bunch of stjoe ppls and a bunch of other ppl i knew.  it was great fun! near the end me joe and andrew karaoke style, sang "i believe in a thing called love, by The Darkness" u know that really high pitch song lol! it was great! i laughed for awhile and so did a bunch of other ppl!  oh and then after that i headed to a prep party but i didnt really stay long there, just long enough to say hey to everybody i knew (which was quite a few ppls) and then say bye to the few that i came there with, and i headed home at about 10 30.  i know its an early nght but i am still sick with a fever u know lol.  i prob shouldnt have gone out ne way but it was fun.  ok this went on forever, sorry!  im out to sleep. g'night my friends!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Point to ponder:   Are you truly happy?  What could u do to make yourself happier?  Good sunny afternoon!  im just glad im not workin.  its been a slow day, ive left the house once, that was 4 the doctor, they got me in and out quick. Good news, i dont have strep!, i did get some drugs and stuff though and i have to get a sholder MRI tom :(, o well.  ok well its time for my nap, what an exciting life, NOT! ok going to watch lilo and stitch and sleep.  bye byes.  PS. - PLEASE CALL ME I GET EXTREMELY BORED!!! (601-594-9172)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    See look im sick with bed hair aww.. lol&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Odd... this morning i felt fine and now i just woke up from a nap and i have a 100 fever. balls! this is no fun.  well i guess no work again tomorrow. i think im going back 2 sleep lol.  goodnight again :)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bryndan is gone, sniffle sniffle. lol. its all good though.  work was soo easy today, i actually got to feel worthless at work!! it was great (even though that sounds weird) to do next to nothing 4 a day finally, insdead of slaving away.  ohh and my dad is going on the cruise yay.  Just to let you know, Enya is some great music! ive downloaded a entire cd worth the songs. i suggest it to anyone who wants to relax.  ive listened to it all night.  im off to bed to finish this great day and then back to work tomorrow.  May god bless ya!  ~~Migels~~
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was a very good/ calm day.  i liked it a lot.  tomorrow is work though so im off to bed. goodnight
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      life is rough, good luck!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well then, i actually didnt really have a good day. i guess i was due 4 a not so good day. i feel bad tellin yall all my boring life but i guess if u read this thing u kinda wanted to know ne way.  today sucked b/c -i picked my dad up from airport and he just "slept" all the way home -it was really hot at work -i got stabbed by a nail at work (bleeding 4 20 min) -i was bored and didnt really do much tonight -i wish i was asleep -katie left 4 a long time (one of the few ppl i had left to talk to) -i got/get lonley (a lot!! ahh its crazy!) -i thought about the past way to much (depressing, very) -too many sad songs! they were everywhere today. -mom and dad prob wont go on our "family" vacation -i dont even think my dad is gonna go on our father son montana trip now. -my dad might leave for awhile tom (if u wanna explination ask me) -i have to go to a crazy doc tom -i havent even felt like eating much (crazy huh!) Things i should still be happy for (aka make myself feel better) -im living! -i got paid today -its a weekend now -i have a family -tomorrow is a new day  Ok well im off to go to sleep, goodnight my friends!   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pray 4 my dad if ya get a chance, hes what i guess u could call sick again.   Other than that work is kinda hard, but im definately not gettin bored, im busy all the time. i kinda miss some of the relaxation i used to have but it will be ok, i will get some back when we go on trips again.  Goodnight amigos!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I dont think me and jes are friends for awhile. i was kinda upset but i do hope she does good, in whatever she does though.  other than that!, it wasnt too bad of a drive back im just soo tired now.  I had a nice nap in the car and a fun stop though, those sure helped the trip.  when i got home i talked to ben and bry today, bryndan worries me sometimes, actually alot of times (just be careful and dont do stupid things if u read this).  i also went to my neice danielles swimmeet today, she lost poor thing, and she doesnt like loosing so she hypervenilated and cried.  no fun at all :(  lets see ohh and tonight i talked to matt. yay! ok ne way im gonna go get some early sleep, i have doctors and car checkups to galore for tomorrow.  good night my friends, i hope the summer is treating you well!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whew, this HAS been a REALLY fun trip, im finally headed home tomorrow.  its worn me out though i need a lil break of rest in relaxation.  In b-ham, on the way to atlanta, i got to meet a bunch more of katie mac's friends, espically at the bday/going away party.  it was great fun, they all make me laugh, very hyper ppl lol.  I just had a great time overall there, playing (even with her little brother), hangin out, seeing mountianbrook, riding 4wheelers!!, etc.   ATL was a blast too!, well besides the hard forced labor.  it did make me feel accomplished though, i painted a mailbox, and a table, and killed a tree full and hill full of cudzu, oh and helped move everything to the house. ahh and last night, that was fun, i went to laurens friends house (ritu) and she has a cookout/party haha. :) it was fun.  ok well im gonna go finish my blizzard and watch some more spiderman/ mib II.  Be back to reality/jackson tomorrow :/ but only for a week (plus a few days)! then off to da boat! ok good bye bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today/tonight was good!  i did a lot today it kinda seemed like 2 days.  i woke up in dallas, went to the airport, flew home, went to the denist, met my dads friends, went swimming, and met up with jessica.  Jessica and I finally got to talk, and shes no longer mad at me so thats good and now were good friends! yay! i have somebody that will go do something when im bored again. ok in other news, i have to pack to go to atlanta/B-ham(mountain brook) now, since i am leaving tomorrow and all.  i hope thats a fun trip! i think it will b e ok well im headed out. good night my friends!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hola Chicos y chicas! whats up?&nbsp; guess what i did today? well besides football practice, i was building something and i  severed  the end of my left middle finger!! with a electric saw!! it was crazy, i ran in  drippin&nbsp;blood &nbsp;and was like hey bryndan i need some stiches so yeah, i went to the doc and i got 8 stiches in the tip of my finger and they gave my some hardcore painkillers!! so umm yeah im kind of out of it right now but bry is gonna drive me around b/c im not suppose to do that so im sure i will have fun!&nbsp; ok well im out to do i dunno what! i liked that finger also :( o well i can use it again in a couple of weeks! love ya b happy!  ~MIGELS :~)  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i got back safley from tulsa yesterday and it was soo much fun overthere!&nbsp; even when we were pretty much doing nothing it was still fun.&nbsp; i really think that matt is my long lost brother, we are so much alike its crazy and he even kinda looks like me.&nbsp; ohh while i was up there we went jet skiing, tubing, out to eat a bunch, i met a lot of his friends (new ones like simone&nbsp;and ones i already met like biggie and tamias), went hitting golf balls, bowling, saw&nbsp;borne supremacy,&nbsp;and a bunch of other stuff!&nbsp; it was all soo much fun.&nbsp;&nbsp;im gonna have to go back to see him some time soon, posibly in colorado while he is in&nbsp;college!&nbsp;&nbsp;Well i'm now done with work for the rest of the summer! no more extra money :( but hey it wasnt fun while it lasted.&nbsp; Football started today, all that runnin was hard!! omg i felt like i was about to fall out, i couldnt see straight. but at least im gettin in shape again.&nbsp; football will probally start becoming a bigger and bigger part of my life up until about november.&nbsp; Ok well i have to get up early to head to a meeting with my daddy and then go to football right after so im out!&nbsp; hope everyone is doing and feeling marvelous! God bless! 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why hello all! i really want to write a long thingy but im kinda busy so yeah.&nbsp; tomorrow i head to tulsa OK to stay with matt and his buds!! yay! definatly excited.&nbsp; ive been workin these past 2 days and these past 2 days have been kickin my ass.&nbsp; im definatly not in a work mood, i just wanna leave jackson again its funner, lol, away from here and there are no worries. o well! bryndan makes me laugh!! i just though i would share.&nbsp; ok i have to go pack, go out to dinner, go out to ice cream, and then prayer group! probally i'll&nbsp;sleep after that b/c i gotta catch the early flight tomorrow, grr! o well good bye folks and i hope you have a great few days while im gone! be back tues night or wed morning!  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I would just like to say, life is one confusing little puppy!! i wish i could get a simplified outline of it and i wouldnt have to decide near as much stuff! ohh yeah and concequences are the devil, but i need to learn to not look back! still in atlanta love ya'll! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HELLO! whats up? nada mas aqui! im in Atlanta :) this vacation has been great so far (i'll prob wirte more ab it when i get home), ohh and im still in love with georgia tech so yeah thats where i wanna go to college.&nbsp; today is six flags!! that should be great and then tomorrow is a braves game.&nbsp; im gonna be soo worn out when i get home though, o well! birmingham was fun on the way over! Craziest thing was when bryndan almost killed himself on the four wheeler, he was going really fast when he nailed a tree and grabbed a branch on the way through the air that managed to keep him from landing head first, still some pretty rough injuries though.&nbsp; he was about due for an accident, it had been over 2 months lol.&nbsp; it was good to see everybody from overthere! they are all fun and really nice (even though bryndan and some of them had&nbsp;some skirmishes while we were there lol).&nbsp; it was still fun! they will all be heading off to college though, i kinda wish i was doing that too but o well only 1 more year! o hope everyone is doing great back in jackson and that everyone headed to junaluska has a great time there! hopefully i will get to see yall b4 i head out again to tulsa. bye 4 now, time to eat monkey bread, yummmm!  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HELLO! whats up? nada mas aqui! im in Atlanta :) this vacation has been great so far (i'll prob wirte more ab it when i get home), ohh and im still in love with georgia tech so yeah thats where i wanna go to college.&nbsp; today is six flags!! that should be great and then tomorrow is a braves game.&nbsp; im gonna be soo worn out when i get home though, o well! birmingham was fun on the way over! Craziest thing was when bryndan almost killed himself on the four wheeler, he was going really fast when he nailed a tree and grabbed a branch on the way through the air that managed to keep him from landing head first, still some pretty rough injuries though.&nbsp; he was about due for an accident, it had been over 2 months lol.&nbsp; it was good to see everybody from overthere! they are all fun and really nice (even though bryndan and some of them had&nbsp;some skirmishes while we were there lol).&nbsp; it was still fun! they will all be heading off to college though, i kinda wish i was doing that too but o well only 1 more year! o hope everyone is doing great back in jackson and that everyone headed to junaluska has a great time there! hopefully i will get to see yall b4 i head out again to tulsa. bye 4 now, time to eat monkey bread, yummmm!  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Party Days! Happy Birthday Hilton! yay big 17 haha you youngun These past 2 days have been major parties! its been fun! Last night was the best 4 me, bryndan drove me back to tripps house :) so i wouldnt die, that unlimited whoop juice finally got me, i actually got drunk like to where i would have done something crazy, but there was nothing crazy to do so i just had fun and tried to talk to ppl.  Then i worked outside for mr harkins this morn and went swimmin and 2 spider man 2 with hilton and then we went out to party again. i drove 2nght but it was still fun.  bry and hilton are laying on the floor behind hahaha, crazy guys. ok well im out to sleep or whatever, ohh if anybody wants to go swimmin, we can go at my neighbors house, im house sittin just give me a call! ok c yall later! be safe!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahh, friday, payday!  it was a pretty good day!  the past couple of days have been. i went to geyser falls yesterday with bry, nick, callie and mary, for callies bday, that was great fun! last nght i talked to jes and finally got out how i was feeling (an accomplishment 4 me), that was kinda dramatic but good however im still clueless on what gonna happen. humm on wed. ohh yeah and on that day i got senior pics that was fun to and then played around with katie and erin the rest of the day doing junior ambassador stuff and all that!  i think im gonna go out and party tonight, it should be a blast, probally spending the night at tripps, at least thats what im thinkin right now.  Ohh and guess what, katie mac got back in the country today yay!! starting next week, im gonna be gone almost the rest of the summer, birmingham (see katie with bry!), atlanta (see my sister and GA tech with bry!), tulsa (see matt!), and las vegas (my oldest sis is gettin married, :/ again) then school/football starts again.  its gonna be Krazy! ok well im out to work out get a quick shower go see a friend and then go out! whew.  hope everyone is great! u can call me if ur not lol! PS~ i think we may get a little kitten!!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All my friends that are out of town (espically those i havent seen in awhile or talked to for that matter!!!) need to come back in town now!!! You know who you are! i have felt extremely lonley latley and its not fun! well with that said, life has been goin fairly well latley.  Definately not as fun as cruise time but still pretty good! yesterday my day/night was consumed by a 9 hr poker game, i had a net profit of $4.50 yay! lol about 50 cents a hour.  at least i didnt loose it all or play for 16 hrs like some ppl.  so yeah i only got 2 hrs of sleep and then went and picked blueberries with my neices this morn! i was tired but the berries sure do taste good (5 gallons of them!, anybody want some just tell me) then i got a nice 3.5 hr nap. tried callin somebody but they wernt there :( and then i went to church.  i talked to bryndan and he is commin back in town tomorrow and we are gonna have a wonderful 4th of july!!! fireworks and drinks! haha should be fun/interesting/dangerous!! my kinda deal.  ok this turned out really long so im gonna go spend the night at my sisters and try to fix a friends computer!  peace
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good morning! wow that 11 hrs of sleep was absolutly WONDERFUL! i needed it.  i just wanted to ask everybody if you get a chance pray for my grandmother, she has cancer in a couple of places again we found out yesterday.  and also, my dad b/c he is starting his treatment (not 4 cancer thank goodness) and it will be 7 hrs a day 5 or 6 days a week for the next month or two.  Thank you guys! ~Migels
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Music- Counting Crows- she talks to angels  Today was good, i got 7 stiches out (i had already taken 1 out myself lol) and had 2 good football practices.  ohh whats not cool though is that my cut opened back up after they came out, o well just a little blood.  Well tomorrow im off to las vegas! i think it will be fun, i feel like a lil alone relaxing/God time though and i doubt i can get it there so thats not cool.  I have just been 2 busy and hangin out with too many people latley and i want a break b4 school starts back.  Ohh and if u didnt know, were going to my sisters wedding in las vegas, but I'm really worried that my sister rushed into her new marriage too quickly and the worst is danielle, she's my little neice and she old enough to know whats going on, she doesnt seem to like it.  i just wish i could do something.  ok yeah i just felt like saying that, hope everybody has a good last few days (or maybe weeks for some of you) of summer.  its my last year in st.joe and madison and maybe all of mississippi.   thats kinda sad, i'll come back sometime.  alright buh bye buds!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i have been Extremely busy latley! with friends and football etc. i sure hope everyone has been doing well though.  im out but just wanted to share some pics with ya! laturz   urlLink    This is my Wonderful friend Matt from Tulsa, OK that i went to visit. Hes great and i think im gonna go visit him at college in denver some time!  urlLink      urlLink    One of the bands from the 3 doors down, nickleback, puddle of mudd, and 12 stones concert. it was pretty fun!  urlLink      urlLink    My new kitten!  urlLink      urlLink    Me and bo! (i think that is how we are spelling it)  urlLink      urlLink    aww lol, more kitten  urlLink      urlLink    his innocent eyes can fool you, he will tear you and your shoe apart in a second!  urlLink      urlLink    My poor finger as of today, but hey, it looks a whole lot better than it did lol! hope y'all ar'nt too grossed out. :)  urlLink     
     

    
</post>


</Blog>