<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone. I am not too sure who all has signed up to be in motivation check, but I think its a great idea. As far as my vision to creat public servants for South Carolina, I am happy to say that the South Carolina State Student Association (SCSSA) is still continuing to build momentum, thanks largely impart to Katy Bayless! I personally have begun to reachout to students-- engagement is huge!! Anyone who wants to get invovled let me know! A few of you have emailed me, keep it up! :-) Thats all for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Explanation....Originally I planned for this blog to be a personal online journal.  I wanted people to be able to post comments and stuff to what I wrote, and I  thought  that meant they had to be "invited" to do so.  Well, I have now come to realize that the gozillion people I invited are all capable of "message posting", which is awesome.  So, I think now this blog will be turned into a forum for who ever wants to participate.  Since most of the new "members" are from Leadershape, it'd be cool to reserve it for L/S talk and updates.  (ie: delete the non L/S people...ouch)  That way, we can all quasi stay in touch and keep up with our visions.  Yes...I said the "V" word.  What do y'all think?  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What's up everybody! Just wanted to pre-invite you to a shag party that Mary and I are setting up for August/September time. So brush up on your steps! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Sid  Wanted to know if you are just sharing your blog or you want us to post our progress on our vision(MotivationCheck being the name of the blog) too?  Sunil
     

    
</post>


<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
           Was a very tiresome day. Did the condensation algorithm from 2 in the afternoon to 1 at night. I am hacking someones code to get a better understanding of it. I hope I  get it done tom. The code I am hacking is pretty badly organised and I spent 5 hrs putting it right so that I can understand it. Now my head's splitting....      I am such a loser . My palm was to arrive by UPS on friday and I slept through it. The mailman arrived at 11.15 and I got up at 11.25. Now I have to wait till monday as they dont work weekends. This was all because of debjani with whom I went pubbing on thursday night. We got home at 4 in the morning. She has a very bad funda of going to pubs at 1 am which is very irritating as pubs close at 2. Damn carolina and this bible belt.       I happen to have a lot of friends in CS here. Our talk mostly is on coding and I should say I have learnt a lot. I write pretty decent codes in C now. I think if I ever do a phd then it would be in CS. Robotics is a part of CS in many top schools so it wont be much of a problem. If I do Robotics in CS then I would be good in application level as well as system level programming which I think is pretty cool.       Another thing ... I am the organizational director in the clemson students council. I took up this post partly because it would help build my profile if I plan to do an MBA. It deals with me being a "middle man" between the council and various organizations in clemson.       have totally redone my site... Now its pretty hot.... You can visit it at http://sunilhere.tripod.com        Will write in later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
          The start of my day was a total disaster. I had to get up at 6.45 and mail Dr Mcneill my code before he checks his mail in the morning, then I had to study the condensation algorithm before meeting Dr Grimes at 1 pm. It all fell apart when I got up at 9. I did manage to do both but not how i wld have like it done.       I met Dr Mcneill at 2 as we were trying to figure out why the card cannot be synchronized using the synchronous counting function. We discovered that that function is not 6036 compatible so i have to use 6602 now. About Mcneill - Initially he was analysing me and appeared quite strict, asking me to get the results. Now that I have got them he's a lot cooler. We started discussing my career plans and he give me tips on how to apply to top colleges for a PhD. Hes hiring a post doc from India so I gave him tips on how to get someone good and what to look for in a Indian researcher. He treats me like  a friend now. Good for me.....       Then went to Walmart and picked up some grocery. Was home by 6. was so tired that i slept till 11. One of the very few days when I slept during the day.       I so want my palm to arrive   Till tom  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
            I just bought a brand new Palm top from amazon - Palm i705 for 100$. Its has wireless connectivity + all the classic features in a palm. Wireless connectivity wld cost me 20$/month which is optional and I dont think I'm gonna buy that, atleast not now. But once I have some money i'll do that. Its soo cool like a PC combined with your cell. I would be working in Barnes and Nobel for around 15-20 hrs/week in summer and wld be research for Mcneill for the remaining 20 hrs. So hope to earn some moolah. I am planning on two trips. One to florida with my undergrad friends and with my clemson friends somewhere else. I had gone to Charleston with my clemson friends during spring brk and I really enjoyed it. They are pretty cool. We all share the same funda in life- ENJOY.        I have had a lot of friends. Everyone have seriously affected the way I go about living my life. Friendship is something which I cherish dearly.       I hope I have them around all the while, as long as possible    will write in tom      
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
                     Its 2.25 in the dead of the night and I am waiting for the clock to show 2.45 so that I could go home by the last bus.I have been in front of my lab PC for last 4 hours first trying to automate the no of counts in my event counter and then use a synchronous mode. I feel so sorry for myself that I didnt achieve even one. Now I feel I should have stayed home and done some work on my thesis....      I did achieve something. I downloaded all my fav songs using kazaa and would be burning a CD. Today was like any other monday.. Boring.... I plan to go to florida in summer so I go about asking everyone what places are good to visit there... I have even asked some ppl the same question more than twice.... hahhaha Everyone around me is busy studying. Next week is exam week. I seem to be the only blessed soul in Clemson who has no finals. I took up just 2 courses this sem. One dosen't have a final and in other I have to do a paper review. Thats kid stuff.... Its 2.35 now 10 min to go....   So let me think what to type...........     Ya I read about this chic from my undergrad school who acted in a (Hot) music video. She wore thong and si shown to read a porn mag in the video. Now this chic goes to the media and tries to tell them that what she did was right and she wld do that even in real life. hahhaa thats some good stuff to be printed in the newspapers---- India has always had a problem in finding the threshold on vulgarity. I don't know why they care. Let ppl do what they want. They bring up this big shit on Indian culture and stuff. I don't know how can ppl be sooo foolish and waste time on such bullshit... C i would like if a girl wears less clothes but to be frank this chic I feel looks like a pig. Somethings wrong with her features. Feels like her face got hammered..... hahhahah  OKKK now its 2.44 and I can cut the bullshit   Cya then
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
          A very normal saturday. Work at Harcombe and then now its 12 at night and I'm in java city doing timepass. Work at harcombe was very light. All the student had gone home for easter and so the crowd was minimal. Good for us. Been to the easter mass in brooks center in the morning. I was to go there with Annie but she ditched me. She first woke me up from sleep at 8.55 asking me to accompany her for the 11.30 mass and when I went to pick her up at 11.15 she was sleeping. Was pretty bored to walk alone but didn't want to miss the mass. When I reached there I was happy because I had taken the right decision. I'm not a religious person but I like going for masses. I like the choir, the priest's sermon, the wierd ppl that come up and do the readings. I also like it because churches are beautiful, especially during easter and christmas when it is decorated. It was beautiful at brooks. Flowers of diff hues adorned the altar. Everyone there was well dressed and the mass was conducted very well. Everything was taken care of. Liked todays mass a lot.     After Harcombe went to Waffle House to have coffee. I went there with Vipul(Bulli) and Viraj. Bulli and myself go there often. I get this huge kick of paying for coffee once and having 4-5 refills.Hahaha.... Believe me thats the only reason I go there.     Had some fun at harcombe. Deep my roommate was using tongs and pretending to pinch Sawant nipples and sawant being short tempered started chasing him and then they started running over that part of the floor which Amos had just mopped. Amos was pretty pissed. To make things worse I started calling sawant stiff nipples and he started throwing ice cubes at me hahhaha and guess where all the ice cubes landed.... Amos's mopped floor. He then gave us a strict warning. hahhaha...     I have to get back to work now.   Till tom  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yest was the best pubbing night ever. Was rocked totally. Actually one of my friend Ankur had been pretty busy with his research work and could not party so he was totally in mood yest and it caught us tooo... We had 6 pitchers of Michelob + 3 cigarette pack among us. What got us was ankurs sick idea of back to back bottoms up. He himself had 10 while I had 7. TD's is the place where we hang out. Pretty nice place with live music. We used to go there initially to play pool but now its beer that takes us there. I wonder what ppl think when we catch the bus back home. We are like totally out. If they are ever asked to give a character evaluation we all will get a straight zero. hahhahah     I missed the Good friday passion so I can't afford to miss the Easter mass tomorrow. I always like Easter masses back home. Candles and stuff. Very nostalgic.... I was a brat back then. Always used to sit in the last row and make as much trouble as possible during masses. Had friends who were as bad so didnt feel as bad. There was also this hot chick   Neha who I had a big crush on who used to come for mass. I hated her dad for he thought I was a loafer. Now I don't disagree to it but I don't like to be remided of it again and again. hahhaha . She had a stupid BF. I am not in touch with her and I wonder what she is upto. The last I know of her is that she was studying medicine at Nair..    I have this thing with chicks at mass. I don't know why I fall for them.. Tomorrow will be on the lookout for Prof Schalkoff daughter whom I found to be pretty cool. I saw her on Palm sunday.   So till tomorrow....
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Just been to Lees defense... maaannnnn got freaked out. So much effort put in.... I don't think I can do a thesis.... Atleast not one like him... His thesis talked about drusen detection in retina using segmentation. His detection rate was pretty good - between 87 and 91%. I particularly like such work which wld put doctors out of business cause I don't like them one bit... They r ppl who take money from a sick person and ask him to respect him. I beleve Health is a humanitarian issue and shld be done free of cost. The govt shld pay for it... I dont like the fact that they ask someone who has broken his leg if he has enough money for a operation and threaten him that he won't be treated if he dosen't cough up the cash. I don't understand why ppl respect them. ppl think he did them a favor by treating them.. U dumbasses can't u get it ... HE DID IT FOR UR MONEY   I hope medicine wld be totally automated someday and we wld be free from these leaches.   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
                            Its a pleasant Friday afternoon at Clemson. Fridays have always been good for me. I wake up late. I do very less work and I spend the whole night partying. This week had been very hectic. My prob is that I work for two professors- Dr Hoover and Dr Mcneill. and research work demands that I think which considering my limited mental abilities is very taxing. Till last week I only used to work for Mcneill but then Hoover asked me to work on my thesis and since that day life has been HELLLLLL   Went out pubbing with Debbie(Parents named her Debjani) yesterday night.. Had fun... Jived .... I have been pubbing so often that these bouncer know me very well now and let me in without any ID.      My friend Lee Brandon would be defending his thesis today and have to be there. He did some work on observing retinal damages using machine vision. Pretty neat work.    Enough for now  Sunil 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      hi This is my 1st post. The reason I want to post my comments here is because newspapers around the world think my views are too idiotic so are not fit for their consumers. hahahhah. My argument is if Ozzy sells, if Bush (whom I think is the king of idiots) sells WHY NOT ME!!!!!!!!!!!!  Im a bit dazed now and my brins aint working so wld post my comments tom..  cya
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Finally got sampling running. Was a big problem getting motivated to work. I wasted a week on it and it took me 2 hours. Have to be more focussed. I have to write a small code and c if it works. Have a busy weekend scheduled. Hope to get a lot of stuff working..     For the past 1 month I have been wasting my time. It all starts at 10 when I wake up. Then am in coll by 12. Surfing till 3. Hungry at 4. Back home by 5 to eat. Too lazy to go back at night. kabooooom the whole day is gone. This has been my story for last 20 days. Have to get a timetable working....  Yest we partied. Was a lot of fun....  Last sat me and my roomies went to Atlanta. Viv and deep wanted to visit the temple. we ate some indian food at the temple. some puri and potato bhaji. They called it prasadam so we didnt have to pay. good for us....   On our way back we were searching for an Indian restuarant. Some bald Indian guy at the temple gave us the wrong directions so we ended up in the black ghettos of southern atlanta. It was miles and miles of absolute poverty. Really freaked us out. In all this confusion viv literally drove a cop off the road... He pulled us up and warned viv to drive carefully... Viv was sooo down by 2 back to back failures that we dropped or indian dinner plans and ate at subway.     I really do hate subway. They are such bastards. If u check out the photos of the subs they put up... So much meat ... looks soooo soooo tasty and the subs the dish out... Yuck. I am gonna give them a last chance ... Im gonna eat meatball sub and if I don't like it then I'm through. I've had it.... never gonna eat there again...   Talking about food has made me hungry..  catch ya later   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Been a really long time....     Was working on particle filter and the Nsom project. Got the particle filter algorithm done and now have to code it. Nsom has run into some problems as the computational ovehead is a bit too much... more than 400% on the execution time so have to look into it. Actually to tell you the truth I did very less work this week. Downloaded 20+ episoded of seinfeld and watched then. The 1st 15 were back to back. Imagine watching 15 episodes of seinfeld(20 min each) without a break.... cooooooolllllll. Karmok got the digicam and its turned out to be our fav toy. We click pics by the dozen. Have to admit it.. A grt piece..      My position in Graduate Student Government(GSG) demands that I arrange a get together for the presidents of all the organizations under GSG before june 30th. This is the first time I'll host a party inviting ppl I have never met.... pretty nervous...     Got the Charleston trip photos developed. Have turned out really well. sooo wanna put them up on my site.      We went to TD's the other day. Karmok puked again. I don't know why he has to do it all the time... Why the hell does he have to drink that much. His drinks have to be rationed.... Seriously.  Viv got his car. Its a pontiac. Has just 58000 miles on it. Pretty smooth. Our walmart problems have been solved. A car is such a convenience in the US. Especially during vacations.      I dont know what has got into me but I have started cooking pretty badly nowadays. Everything I cook ends up shitty. I hope its just a phase.   Nothing interesting on..... Hope next week will...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
           My library life is totally screwed up. I have not returned my locker keys. I have two books overdue, one of which is an interlibrary book(a big fine is on the cards). I find this very unusual but I always make friends who keep their stuff in my locker. From stinking gym shorts to free credit card Tshirts.... u name it, I have it.  Does it have something to do with my personality or something. I think i'll be a banker someday.....        My friend Karmok was on probation and he needed one A in a difficult course. I was a bit worried... but then he managed to get one. So we partied yesterday at Anups place. Karmok was planning to buy a digicam if he would get an A. By now he would have clicked on ADD TO CART. Good for him.       I went to waffle house 2 days back. I had 7 coffee refills. Thats my new record. All waitresses now know me well. I also take Karmok and Bulli along.... Sitting at waffle for 2 and half hours and talking about our past while drinking coffeee with my close friends .... I LOVE IT       I have still not started working for the bookstore..... So many things to do and so less time....       
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Just finished the mex files. Just have to polish it a bit. Finally... Have to start on Hoovers work. Our trip to Florida is being finalized. Will be gone from june 18 th to 25th. Would be grt fun especially as I would be with my undergrad friends. Meeting them after a yr. Practically stayed with them for 4 yrs of my engineering. Grt guys.   I tried connecting to the net with my palmtop using the free ISP wireless acct. The damn thing ain't connecting. So would have to buy a AT&T  wireless acct to get connected. It ain't a necessity so won't buy one now.       Have to get some order in my life. Have been sleeping at friends place for the past 3 days. hahhah have to stop that  neways bye
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
            Writing in after a long time. I'm enjoying my palm a lot. Its a i705 Palm. I have downloaded grt softwares on it. The most recent one is one that connects to my favorite sites and downloads info from them into my pda everytime I sync it with my pc. REALLY REALLY COOL. The software is called avantgo and can be downloaded from avantgo.com. So now I get the latest. I can search for restraunts nearby if I enter the pincode.... cool na.        Have to mex files done for Mcneill. Mex files are something that can be used to run C programs from Matlab. Really cool stuff. It creates a executable which converts matlab code and links it to the C compiler and runs the C code. I created a mex yesterday but I had some problem including the libs. The mbuild tool wasnt able to include the libs. Neway hav to solve that. A friend (Bryan) has developed such a wrapper which links compilers. He has been awarded a patent for it. Brilliant guy....        My summers started and plans to go to florida are still not finalized. United airlines is flying ppl from Atlanta to London and back for 350. Thats pretty cheap. Ankur has some friends in London. So if I add this to that then it results in a fabulously cheap trip. Hmmmm Uk for 600 is pretty good since I would be burning 300-350 in florida. Have to decide....       will write in later
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Been to the smokies.... camped, hiked... did white water rafting too... was grt fun...I have posted the pics on my site. Met nirup after a lonng time... he's still as stupid as ever. Trip cost me 120$. After returning suddenly i feel that I have not worked on my research for quite some time now.. Have to get GUI done by today. Plans are on to visit Boston this weekend. Matt and Vishal want to meet their friends, I'll just tag along... One more interesting thing that we all were planning was to take a trip to MIT robotics lab... Pretty cool stuff going on there.... I'll see if I can meet Dr Latombe.... He is considered the father of motion planning of robots. I do have a great deal of respect for this man...   This boston trip means another weekend of fun and no work... I'm testing Dr Mcneills patience to the hilt..   Have to get back to work  cya
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      someone has a blog but just dosent wanna to tell me about it... that someone reads my blog but dosent want me to read his.... this blogger is a close friend of mine... very very close... now who is this ??????????     Is it Nirup???????? nooooo        Is it Borya???  nooooo      ok ok just one clue...     Its this one big dickhead from univ of santa barbara who is doing his phd       NIRANJAN SHETTY      Bingo      here is his link  http://www.thinktomi.blogspot.com/      read his poem... was very impressed... his blogs reflects his intellect.... who do you think would read books on Zen... post quotes by bertrand russel.... do everything that I can only dream of doing.   Hats off to you Manu... You still are my idol  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      went for driving test today       Flunked the written test...This was the last hint I needed to confirm that I am a born loser.. So hereby..... I pronounce myself "THE LOSER" ......... I'm the Mayor Of Loserville.. I'm Sunil Loser Dsouza....       Felt bad ... hope the wound heals.     The organizational meeting for graduate student govt is coming up on thursday. Have booked the senate chambers and now have to send out the invitations..     something more interesting is coming up after that.... White Water Rafting. Myself, nirup and some of my clemson friends are going to the smokies for rafting. Would be fun. I did it I believe 3 yrs back on the ganges. That was one hell of a trip... We visited the taj and chisties dargha at fatehpur sikri , climbed Mt Chopta (aproxx 10000 feet) . Did white water rafting in the ganges..... did some canoeing on a lake... camped on mountain slopes... Had a first experiece of snow atop Chopta....      The last time we did it Nirup nearly lost his life as he fell off the raft... This time i'll makes sure he does by pushing him off the raft...       I hope to take one more trip with my undergrad friends.... hopefully in december....  Haven't submitted the code to Dr Mcneill as yet... have to get that done tonight.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Yesterday barman and I went to Waffle house. I love their cheese and eggs. Spent $8  but what the heck. Our conversation drifted to cars and then barman told me a very funny story of his friend in San Diego  here goes...     This desi friend of his got 7 tickets in a day. The were    1) Stealing a car   2) Driving without a license   3) Ramming the car against another car   4) Hit and run   5) Not stopping his vehicle after being pulled up by the cops   6) Lying to the cops   7) Murder attemp on the cop  Now listen to the real story(our desis version)    He had bought the car for his girlfriend sometime back. So all registration was in his GF's name. He didnt have a US license but he just decided to take the car for a ride. The car papers were unfortunately not in the car.  He decided to stop someplace and parked it for a while.  When he was reversing he accelerated a bit too much and his car rammed the car standing behind. He found that driver of the car behind didnt show any frustration - like in India, He didnt even make an atempt to beat him up. Our desi felt all was right and drove off. The driver of the other car thought our desi was drunk and wanted to avoid confrontation so he called up the cops. Now 4 cop cars started following our desi... our desi thought they were in an emergency and moved over to the left lane ... like we do in India. But the left lane here is the faster lane and the cops got alarmed that the desi was attempting to escape. The cornered the car and bought it to a stop. Our desi realised that he was in deep shit. The cops pointed their guns at him and told hin to come out of the car with his hands behind his head. Our desi was so worried that he forgot to put the car in neutral and the car moved forward and was about to ram into the cop who was standing in front of it when the cop jumped.....It was a murder attempt on the cop....   Our desi was taken into custody.... and had to appear in court with a "pretty good lawyer" as he was told to save his skin.    I was laughing my guts out after hearing this...  till later
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Been some time  Life is pretty cool. I am pretty focussed on work now. Got a lot of stuff done. Downloaded some more seinfeld episodes. Play cricket,basketball,tennis and do some swimming. My friend Barman has put up his profile on shaadi.com. Pretty funny site for ppl who arent desperate for marraige- like me. Myself and vicky have put up our profiles too. Amoung all the bullshit that I have put up here is how I describe my work     His Personality, Hobbies, Long-Term Goals, etc    I am presently working on calculating the survival time of ants after they have sustained 54% burns. I do this by taking a sample of 100 ants and burning 54 of them completely and then observing for how many days the remaining 46 survive. I have applied for reseaarch funding to National Science foundation. Hope to get results soon.   The 46 ants have survived for 14 days....    And here is my family background::      My family is buddhist... but I converted to jewism on my 12th bday. My father is a monk who lives in sri lanka. He is developing a new martial art called nikelash where the person has to try pluck the opponents eyelashes using his thumb and the small finger. The innovative part of his art is that the fighter has to wear nike shoes. My mom is a researcher too whos research is similar to mine but she experiments on humans. Her burn rate is more - 73 %.     Hope that I get some proposals soon...  Till then  bye
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Long time since I wrote.   I have to implement the particle filter in C using synthetic data. Planning to hack some codes.... but I know how to go about it... so its fine. Chatted with my sis yest. Shes doing good. She bought a digi camcorder for 500$. Piyush likes such gizmos and has money to indulge... Went for a movie yest at astro... 2 fast 2 furious.... Was such a fucked up movie.... now that I think of it, I haven't watched even one decent movie at astro.... except pulp fiction ofcourse. but then what more can one expect for a dollar. Havent been to a lotta parties lately. Anup and guys are shifting to village green in a couple of days..... so things r gonna be a lot better.   Manu called up yest night..... He is still the same.... with his high levels of commitment and his fuckall sense of humor. Hes doing good. He gave a business proposal for a startup in a competition that was held in UCSB. Was in news for a while... Manu on Californian newspapers...now thats news..Managed to reach the finals. Manu is doing his PhD ...earning 2000$/month and he still dosen't buy a cell.... I dont get it. It all fits in actually... during our engineering days he never gave us a birthday treat..... now do I smell stingy here? hahhah  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Planning on Appalachian trail on 3 rd week of aug. Viv,myself and nirup fixed as yet. Anup wants me to come to ohio with him during the last week of Aug if I want hime to come trekking.. Very bad idea this ohio. will lose 200$... My credit history is already screwed. 600$ deficit.   This appalachian trail is a 2200 mile trek which in one go takes 200+ days. But we r just trekking a section of it. Clingmans dome in Tennessee which is the highest peak on the trail. Borkar was interested in coming but he still has to finalize his plans with nirup. My fall assistantship is assured. My SIS got updated. I have to give Hoover updates every alt thursdays so I better get back to work.  cya
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      We r going trekking this weekend... viv is the god of adventure sports and mountaineering... Its sucha shame that i came to know of it after being his roomate for a yr.. chked out his pics... phenomenal... he even held training camps for his juniors...   we wld be taking his car... feels grt to have someone who is as int in such stuff...  next yr i hope we take a lot of trekking trips... long live viv
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      we went boating today on the koewee lake with jim and joyce(vivs foster parents) and ruth and ron. it was rons boat. It was simply grt. Ron is into candy business. ruth is a nurse. jim is a doctor while joyce is a housewife. They are really nice ppl. ron used to teach robotics at a coll nearby and he was discussing some aspects of it with me. we had lunch by a waterfall. it rained on our way back so for some time we had to dock our boat. Myself ruth and viv took up the job of anchoring it and we got totally drenched. rons place was beautiful. He built his house by himself. he showed us pics of his ancestors. one of them had fought napoleon.. his granddad fought the civil war. ron carves on wood...grt stuff.  I plan to buy ron et all some gifts when I'm in India. least I can do for giving me a ride in his 15000$ + boat
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      we r partying at Tiger Town Tavern today(karmoks bday bash). After that We r gonna jam. anup and arvind on guitar me on vocals.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
                    I think finally particle filtering algo is done. Unless Dr Hoover suggests any changes which I overlooked. I am happy that this literature review is finally over. Its the most painful part in anyones research. Its like putting one in a desert and telling him to build a city. He has no help of a town planner, no architect to help him with the design. Then after studying town planning and architecture and getting a rough idea of whats to be done one feels releaved. At least he knows whats to be done.                 Now comes the interesting phase for me.... programming.... playing around with cameras.... for the 1st time in my life I hope to work with a state of the art computer vision system. The particle filtering is to be used by the staubli puma to track the ball moving in a random manner. Dr Hoover is one of the few researcher(mebbe 2-3 more exist) in the world who believe in gods view robot vision. Everything is setting up well. Dr Mcneills work is more or less done and I have to tweak the gui to look good now... after that I work in configuring the linux kernel on his PC and just administrative work.           This means less work this fall(comparatively). I am planning to work for some prof in the finance dept and learn how to manage portfolios and a bit of investment banking. After all MBA in finance is the ultimate goal. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      met hoover and mcneill. dont know why but they thought that the work i have done was grt.. i'm like  duhhhh I've hardly done anything.  but feels good that ppl appreciate u even when u do nothing. So thats my new motto.... DO NOTHING   I'd rather play yahoo pool..  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
            Im hopelessly stuck on both research projects I work on. On particle filters I cant get the goddamn ideal particle sampling size... This thing is so new... 1998... hardly any papers on it ... forget books... And I believe that ppl working on this try to make this as complicated as possible. I had such trouble understanding it.... fortunately now i know it well ... I have to meet Dr Hoover tom and discuss this stuff with him... hopefully he would be able to motivate me.       On Mcneills front I cant interrupt the mex and reset the inputs.... I sent him the gui without the interrupt... I have no clue how I'm gonna do it.    Last night when I was trying to sleep... I just started thinking about my research achievements during past 3 week....absolutely zilch. I totally freaked out. I got up and started reading a paper on stochastic sampling.. I've read so much on particle filtering that now im sic of it... just then viv entered... I asked him if his research was going on well... hes like ... "you know what ....I just watched dewangee... it really good .... I have stopped working on mine since a long time ". I went back to sleep... but before that I made a promise to myself that I set targets daily and try to achieve them.  next 2 hours I'll work on sampling size... if I dont get it... im take ni's M/C vision classes
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      been to boston.... was one of the best trips i have made in the US. Stayed in one hell of a posh skyscapers in Boston downtown. Visited Harvard and MIT. Visited NYC on the way back again.... life never been better... havent worked for quite sometime and have lotta backlogs... have to set that right..   we were in harvard square on sat night... like any other sat night there ....there was live musin with ppl dacning on the square... one thing that was the most interesting was , among the ppl dancing there were MIT, Harvard profs and so were the beggers... ppl from all levels of the social strata... and regions of the world... was like utopia... never seen anything like this... also on the square was a cafe where anyone cld play chess with a international master by paying 2$.   have taken 2 trips along the east coast.... have to visit the west...  have to spend american independance at alicias place...   have to work my ass off this weekend to cover up for 2 weeks of pleasure..  I also have to set up a linux box and learn some new prog languages.... take up NI's machine vision classes. read some decent books - biography of E= mc square ...   have to stop playing monopoly in the evenings... though i have been having a lotta luck and been winning.... but would like to make my life a bit more productive..     
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      very tempted to buy a laptop. Love these gizmos.... Presently there are a lotta good deals.  I want something that could withstand a lotta computation since the kind of image processing work I do needs that.  Am a very impulsive buyer. so anyday now I could click 'buy now'.  If you want to donate some money so that I could buy myself a laptop mail me at sunild@clemson.edu.    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My habit of keeping file handling in C programming courses in my undergrad for option is causing a lotta heartburns now. Poor fundas in that and pointers too. I would give anything to go back 5 yrs in time and rectify the mistakes that I commited.   Went to greenville yest for singing practice for Indian Association of Greater Greenville fest on sat. Was put up with a gujju family. Mrs Shah treated us with idlis and vadas....been a long time since I was treated with decent food. I am now a part of "Tiger Chords".... thats the name of the indian music troupe at Clemson... Mr Shah had a couple of atrocious singers from Missouri rolla fly down for the fest. They sing soo horribly that I now feel sorry for Mr Shah since he paid for their air tickets... hahhahah now that I think about it even nirup sings better than them.... atleast I could have met up with him again.  till later  sunil  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Chk her out:  http://www.alexthegirl.com/  I spent 2 hours reading her stuff. Shes a damn good writer. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      We had a GSG meeting today. The graduate orientation is on sunday and GSG has been given the work of setting things up for it. I have been assigned the work of geeting orgs to set up stalls during the event. I still have problem generating pseudo random nos for my code. Have to give hoover a report by tomorrow.     Stacey Thompson is the new PR officer for GSG. She is the coolest chick I have ever met. She is intelligent, smart...very very beautiful.... she treked the appalachian trail... 2000 miles... she kayaks in level 3 level 4 rapids. Moreover she is soo sweet. But ............shes MARRIED... I have always fallen for girls who already have BF's or r married. Tough Luck. I'll tell her to find someone for me just like her....     have to get back to work  later  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I am the worlds biggest dumbass. There was this chick whom I used to like 4 yrs back... just a crush. Since I didn't feel like coding today I started hunting for her name on the web.... I got her hotmail id and I wanted to chk her hotmail profile. I usually chk my friends yahoo profiles and doing that is very simple ... but hotmail was a diff ball game altogether. When I under take such task I spend a considerable amt of time on it.... I am really really good at hunting stuff on the net (I hack codes for my assignments) and if I cant do something this simple then I wld consider it as a grt insult. I logged onto my msn and searched for her contact... then a couple of stupid clicks later I added her to my chat list. ... We have totally lost contact since 4 yrs and now she might get a feeling that I'm stalking her ... initiating forced contach or something. ....whereas my intention was just to c what she is upto....  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Past one week has been a roller coaster ride for me. I was offered a job in Cali at the start of the week. Didnt accept it as he wanted me to be permanent. On wed Mcneill mailed me saying that since the project is over he cant fund me for fall. I asked Hoover for an assitantship. Hoover assures me that he will try his best. I spend the next 5 days trying to find a way out of this mess. I even considered transferring to Simon Fraser in Canada.... I get a RA from Hoover on tuesday. This experience has taught me a lot about ppl. Mcneill always used to say that he would fund me for fall but when his work got done he suddenlyy backed out. I worked my ass off for his project .... always meeting his deadlines... I saved him 40 grand but still he would not spend 1600 on me. I usually trust ppl but such things change you as a person. I am sorry this thing happened not because it scared me to death but because I am not the same old self again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      one of the worst coding day ever.  Nothing seems to work.  The fucking segmentation fault. 341 lines of matrix code. totally confusing.  plan to go home now ... then comeback after 2 hours and work on it again..  hopefully eating something more wld remove this 10 hours of frustration  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Am in the linux lab. presently working on the Dislk on chip lab for embedded computing course. We have to install a linux kernel on our harddrive. patch it and the load the kernel on a M Syatem chip and boot the chip. seemed straight forward when Dr Hoover explained it to us and gave us the manual.... Maan this is killing me.very wierd errors that I get. The manual is as Hoover designed it to be - a typical shitty embedded comuting manual that one gets in the market. I just made an error due to the manual and I have to start the whole thing again. The ideal time for this lab is like 20-25 hrs but due to this manual it easily goes upto 75- 90 hours..... A real life embedded computing headache.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      watched japanese gp at a friends place yest. schumi won the championship... was a great race. he started 14th... then he has a small accident which forced him to change the cars' nose... so he was last but he fought back to end the race on 8th position. raikonnen had to win this race to claim the championship but thankfully barrichello held him. feels great to see ferrari win it 5 times in a row.   I came to school at 11 pm yest night with a one point agenga of working on my thesis... met vipul and krishna who convinced me that watching the gp at 1.30 made more sense... and that I can get up early the next morn and work(this never works)... bought their argument. ... we were to watch it in lemans but the ppl there were watching a movie... so we drove to VG. there my friend had not paid his cable fees so his connection was disconnected. at 1.20 we were stranded in VG, desperate to watch the race. so we hurried back to lemans. sandeep had taken the car so we had to walk... we reached there at 1.35 so missed the start... neway every driver was cautious and 1st turn was not that exciting... so didnt feel bad   just visited kharghosh's(jardoshs) site. was very impressed with his resume.. i always felt that going to a good school makes a hell of a difference... u have a lot more opportunities...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      its been such a long time since I have been here that... I even forgot my login to blogger.... tch tch tch... such a shame. I percieve blogging as a means to reflect on ones past. ask yourself " Am I living my life as I want to?... what mistakes have I commited and what measures are to be taken so that I don't commit them again. " Its very important for everyone to have this private moment everyday else we end up as machines.... doing things we are forced to do.... basically like a soulless robot.  past one month I have basically tortured myself by taking on too many responsibilities... Embedded computing course is killing me...(day before yest I sat 26 hours coding non stop without food,water or sleep. I have to do 2 nighouts before every research meeting .... GSG work is still there to be done ... need to sit down with sailesh.... Bee robot .... I need to give that sufficient time. I have a 693 test coming up ... A 668 presentation too....   I think i have to use my palmtop more to get more organised....  I promise that ill write in more often.    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      today in Yahoo Fantasy Basketball someone offer me Reggie Evans for Rasheed Wallace... I'm like.... Do u think im the dumbest ass in the world to trade wallace fr evans.... hahahhaha   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I get these stupid mails from someone who want me to help him with money laundering....  Im posting one of these.... There is neven a shortage of foolish ppl in this world  Subject: BUSINESS LETTER OF $22.3M U.S.D  Mail:  FROM MR ABUHA ABDUL THE MANAGER OF AUDIT AND ACCOUNTIN DEPT, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK(ADB) OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO.   Dear Friend,  How are you doing with your family?I presume that all is well with you.I wish to inform you that i am the manager of audit and accounting department of our bank.I got your contact from international directory search when i was looking for a foreigner who will assist me to achieve a great success business that will yeild us life success. Before i wrote you,i prayed that you will be a honest and reliable person whom i can work with to achieve this deal of our life.In my section in the bank, I discovered an abandoned sum of TWENTY TWO MILLION THREE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($22.3) when i was going through the old files for annual audit in an account that belongs to one of our customer who died along with his entire family on 1999 in a plane crash disaster.Since the bank got information about his death, the bank have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because the bank cannot release the fund unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately i learnt through investigations that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you so that the bank will release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent sharing since nobody is coming for it and i dont want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund.  Following our Banking law and guideline,it was obviously indicated that if such money remained unclaimed after four years without somebody apply as the next of kin , the money will be transfered into our Bank treasury as an unclaimed fund.The request of a foreigner as next of kin in this business is needed in the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner by claiming this fund.  PERCENTAGE RATIO:-- I agree that 35% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign bank account, 5 % will be set aside for expenses that may occur during the business and 55% would be for me as the pioneer or one who disclovered the business while 5% will be shared to the helpless peoples around us in the world such as ,motherless babies,charity homes,disable peoples and so on. Thereafter I will visit your country for sharing money according to the percentages ratio indicated above.So for the immediate transfer of this fund into your bank account as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as next of kin only to the deceased customer by indicating your bank name, bank account number,private telephone and fax numbers for easy and effective communication and location wherein the money will be remitted into.  Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email an application form of claim which you will fill and send to the bank as the next of kin. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is 100% riskfree and that you should fear for anythingr as all the needed arrangements have been made for the transfer .You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter,only if you are ready to assist me.Also i want you to understand that this is not a child's play.As a mere civil servant, i know that you are matured enough to understand every bit of this business because i would want to anything that will bring stagnation of this business as you know that all my hope is in it.As soon as you receive this mail,contact me through my private telephone number above.I expect your urgent response.  Yours faithfully, Mr Abuha Abdul  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A very funny article in slashdot.org  I would not purchase meat labeled with:  A) A listing that said "Animals contained within this package: ". For example, ground beef would be labeled as "Animals contained within this package: Cows". Assume a one half inch tall font.  B) A cartoon rendition of all the animals contained within the package.  C) Stock photography of all the animals contained within the package.  D) A specific picture of the exact individual animals contained within the package. Assume a 1 inch black and white photo.  E) A specific picture of the exact individual animals as they are being killed.  F) A specific picture of the exact individual animals as they looked as babies.   Got me laughing my guts out  Sunil
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My motivation towards my research is at an all time low. Got to get things rolling.  For the first time in my life I could actually remember my dream. Ppl(roomates and parents) have told me that I talk when I'm sleeping(which implies that I dream) but when I wake up I can never remember it. It was a very wierd dream. It was a medley of my undergrad years and my life at clemson. Like it was about me hunting for a job at Clemson but then I always used to go to my dept to check for interview calls that wld be posted on the notice board like at SPCE. In my dream I also made significant strides towards forming a trekking club and a OCW(Org for Childrens Welfare) at Clemson. I wish I could take some time off and do this in real life.  Was down with fever yest. Feel a little better today.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its 3 am. I am surfing orkut(for the uninitiated - it is a networking site to keep track of friends). One can make and join communities on this site.... I am so amazed to see that there are so many trivial communities within this site... Ppl want to categorise... ...say that they belong somewhere/someplace.... Its so closed an attitude. There are communities like "i like so and so actress community"... or "a particular school of thought community"... We have created borders that divide us... built walls around us...we like to live within this comfort zone... we want to "label" a person based on his/her race/religion... WHY?  Why cant there be a world without walls.... A world of brotherhood.... irrespective of the color of one's skin or of social,economic status.   I have always felt very deeply about this....Past 50 years a lot has been achieved... This dream of Uthopia is not unachievable... I hope in my lifetime ppl change their inner mindset....I hope that someday I act as a catalyst to bring about this change.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Friday evening is a good time to write my blog  Worked today. Was at the Botanical garden. Was a party of 40 odd. Thing most unusual abt it was the avg age of ppl there were 65+. Just a couple of good looking early 20's chicks got it so low. Without them the avg age would be beyond 70. ha ha.. Observed that there is a pattern in the way ppl drink wine.... Ppl who run to the bar early usually drink chardonnay....(these are usually heavy wine drinkers) ... ppl who take their time drink merlot...ppl who just want to try a bit of wine drink white zinfandel(these kind feel very ashamed of the fact that they want to drink wine).. They always tell me "I hope this wont get me drunk". observed one more thing.. couples(married) usually drink the same kind.  Havent worked on my research this week. Next week would really push it..  Am teaching ankur and vipul how to swim past. They have managed to float till now. Have realised that I am a very bad teacher. I make simple things too complex. I thought them breast stroke, free style and and butterfly stroke all in 15 mins flat and told them to practice. Now they seem a bit confused...lolz... Deep then helped them with the basics....    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Nowadays things are a bit different from the past two years. I actually make a serious effort to learn something new about my field. I do get up late in the morning.. 10.30 but I do work till 12.00 at night. I am reading stuff on image captiring so that I can implement my algos on them.  Vipul told me today that I need to learn Linux device driver programming and that it would help. I did download the first 3 chapters of the most used book on the topic. I need to actually sit and read them :)  I am planning to graduate by october cause I have been here for quite sometime now.  I met sabrina (friend from leadershape) after nearly 2 months. She had been to her parents place for summer.  Hope to see her around this fall.  Will write in soon  Sunil 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday I worked for a wedding reception with Mellisa. The host had asked us to butler pass the cucumber canopies, spinach kish and finger sandwitches. Now I was supposed to do that. I butler passed for 4 hours and I believe me it ranks no 1 on my list of most boring jobs I have done.  Its so stupid.... One walks around with a tray of goddies atleast hundred times around the hall with a smile planted on ones face. I was so bored that I was like "Somebody please shoot me"! If one has something interesting on ones plate then it is great cause it gets over fast but I was unlucky to have the done the spinach kish. After having coaxed everyone to try it,  Mellisa was like "Sunil make sure that they get it the second time". Now when I approached them the second time they had that disgusted look on their faces as if to say  "Go away maan.. you fooled us once into eating this yucky stuff, we are not going to fall for it again" Then there were some people who would look at the food on the tray when I walk by but when I offer them some they say NO. Duhhhh  Walking around that small hall again and again is really tiresome. To make things interesting I started offering anf flirting with the pretty girls at the party. :)  I think one should design a robot which would do this job. Real time path planning.... computer vision should also be done to notice which guest is looking at the tray(if he/she wants some). As far as I know.. Gecko Systems has come up with great bots for such tasks... room navigation... Aramark please talk to them 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We had the AID(Association for India's Development) welcome party tonight. I acted in a small skit. Acting in a skit is always fun. The bloopers... one gets to meet new people and get to know them really well. Viv's acting skill was a revelation. Viv has really improved a lot in the past 2 yrears. He is an active member of AID.. does his research work well... and also is so gung ho abt going for a trek always.    Am planning to sing for the CISA(Clemson Indian Student's Association) welcome  party. Lets see    till later 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>