<Blog>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I messed up.  Technically, this is now my first ever blog, and is subesquently senseless to those who don't know about stuff, or shit. Oh well.  OH NOES!!  I've got my posts back. I'll just have to repost them to make things more normal. Yeah, basically, ignore this post.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've spent an overly large part of the last twenty-four hours editing and making changes to my blog template. Most of them unsuccesful, which is why it looks exactly the same. I couldn't even get comments to work.   The point is, blogspots are addictive. I can imagine alot more time being taken up by this thing. I'm also currently pondering whether to change from .tk already, as the constraints of free domains are already starting to piss me off.  I saw Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban today. It's certainly the best of the three, and I like it even more due to my love of time-travel paradox, but it's still not all that good. Both Daniel Radcliffe (Harry Potter) and Emma Watson (Hermione Grainger) have improved massively as actors since The Philosopher's Stone, which is possibly the most overrated film ever. That ginger-haired guy is still crappy, though.  Positives: Lenny Henry, Dawn French, Gary Oldman, Jim Tavaré and Robbie Coltrane. Negatives: That ginger-haired guy.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My first blog in six months. Over a year since I started my original blog. Back in my youth, when half-terms and holidays were a time for getting drunk, staying up late and blogging about the most meaningless of things. And angsting because Lee from Blue is better looking than you are. Okay, nothing's actually changed in that time, and I still hate Lee from Blue.  This is a place where I will post things that happen in my life, and some things that don't.  Actually, I've just realised that that last sentence makes no sense. I feel strange tonight, like I'm drunk a bit. But I haven't had any alcohol since last night, and today have drunk eight cans of coke and two mugs of coffee. I'm gonna level with you: I think it was the coke.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Old enough to bleed, old enough to breed," says a 30 year old friend about a 15 year old friend. He's clearly a paedo.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My disease has now spread to my chest, filling my lungs with flem and causing a chest infection. FUCKING GAY, if you ask me. Which means I haven't been into work again, which means I'll probably get sack0rised. Which is truly fucking gay, and gay is homosexual.  So just when I was getting ready to go back to school, I get something else. Low resistance is gay. If things don't pick up soon, I may even not be in school for monday. Being ill is so depressing.  I'm gonna go to the bathroom and cough. BUY.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After my last blog, it probably looks as though my missing of the last two days of school is truancy, but it actually isn't. This time. I have possibly the worst cold I've ever had, combined with hayfever, and my whole head is over-loaded with flem and snot and smeg. It's also spread to my ears, and I've gone half deaf. Guns N' Roses never sounded worse.  So, I may be back at school tomorrow. Maybe not. If I am, keep away. It's probably contagious.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I need some time off. I need a break. My life is so 'go-go-go' at the moment that I barely get chance to blog, read, write, draw, sleep, or anything that I used to enjoy. I end up staying up über-late so that I can do stuff, and then being knackered and deaded the next day. I fell asleep / passed out in graphics today, which would have been quite embarrassing, had anyone noticed before I came round. They didn't, obviously. I'm now on my 6th can of Coke today, I'm hoping the caffeine and sugar will be enough to keep me going 'till midnight, then I'll lie in the dark with my eyes shut and listen to my nice new album by the Walkmen, on my Walkman. IRONEH!!!  I would comment on Euro "Z00"-thousand and four (Worst. Pun. Ever.), but I dont't think I can contribute anything extra, other than that I thought the England performance was class, bar the two stupid mistakes.  So, buy.  urlLink This album.  L.O.L., see what I did there?  So, bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ...then let me never grow up. This has been, without doubt, one of the worst school weeks of all time, ever. So much work not done, I have literally piles of stuff to get through. It's times like these I wish I was "a bit of a thicky" and able to ride by on the minimum amount of work possible.  Another reason: I've had three detentions this week, all from the same guy. Incidently, he's the only teacher to ever give me any real detentions: eight in year eight, and four this year. Not sure who that says more about, really. Still, Duncan was in everyday. LOSE!!  Third reason: sleep loss is really catching up with me. I've had around 16 hours sleep all week, and I haven't got into school on time since before half-term through over-sleeping or being too tired to move.  I should probably be doing some sort of homework now, but I can't be bothered. So nyah.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, back to school. I don't know why, but it's even more painful than usual. These holidays have been great, because I've done more-or-less what I want to do, and when I want to do it. With my parents being out of the house alot, and my brother sitting in his room putting on weight, things have been good. I've been going to bed late, and getting up late, and I still can't remember the last time I slept over the passing of a day. However, I think I've completely fucked my sleeping pattern, and it seems now I've somehow brought on the old insomnia. I didn't get a wink of sleep last night, and because there is no curtains or window cover in any form in the attic room at my dad's house, I saw the rising of the sun at about half-past four. Which is just irritating, to be honest.  I digress. The point is, these holidays have been good, and I can't go back. I'm not prepared at all, not least in that I have tonnes of unfinished / undone / unstarted  homework. Chances are I'll get very little sleep tonight, and I'll be in the worst of moods when some up-her-own-arse student teacher asks for my RE coursework first thing in the morning. That I have to face another 6-7 weeks until the summer holidays is an awful thought, and I just feel like crying.  FUCK.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This should be a blog via-email. Not quite sure  how it works, but if it does, woo.&nbsp;And if Lewis Denby can do it, I might be  able to.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Or works experience, or work sexperience.  Whatever, it's crappy poo. They get free labour, I do pointless work for nothing. "Good morning / afternoon, WTI training group, Adam speaking, how can I help?" It's hammered into me, I'm probably going to start answering real phones with it soon. Not that the phones at work aren't real, but they're not really real, if you see what I mean. Like when someone says "what use will pi be in real life?" to Mr. Easterbrook in maths.  So far, in my three days of being there, I've answered loads of phones and put together a crappy looking desk to replace a really nice solid oak one. You've gotta laugh when you're trading an antique piece of furniture for a flat-packed Ikea MFI MDF DIY Chipboard crap thing.  Recently I've been spending all my money on CDs, which is both a good and a bad thing. It means I'm no longer downloading music that often and stealing for pleasure, but it also means I have no money.  And in the end, HELLO CH-EYE.  Bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I let blogging get out of hand again, I think.  I don't honestly know when the last time was, but I think it may have been beginning of last month sometime. So to James Willock, I am sorry.    A year ago I blogged regularly at my old site. It's unbelievable how fast year ten went, and how much better, but at the same time worse, my life is now. Back then, I was angsty and depressed and stuff. I had a girlfriend, but I never saw her. Now I have a real social life and friends whom I actually like rather than just tollerate. I mean, I'm still friends with the others, but they aren't the winners, and stuff, y'know. I'm still friends with Ben, but I'm working on shaking him off. Somehow, though, in retrospect, last year was just so good. I was more laid back, life was so easy. The fact that I had a girlfriend, no matter how little I saw of her, was a good enough excuse to stop putting myself down over that fact that I didn't  really  have one. I had, on the whole, very little to worry about. It's strange, because although I my life is much better now, and I'm probably much happier, I can shake off the feeling that last year felt so much better. Hind sight is crap.
</post>


</Blog>