<Blog>


<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I wore a suit to school, and I think that overall, the response was good.  Because of this, i'm thinking about making the last day of every week "suit day".  Tell me what you think about that, cause if everyone would think that it's stupid, and that I'm an idiot, I really wouldn't want to do it.  My American Studies Portfolio is occupying almost all of my thinking, even though it's one of the most beautiful days I've seen in a long time.  Actually, depending on how much stuff I get done today, and early tomorrow, I would be quite willing to do something with people, as a break.  I wish that we had our pool open, today, cause that would be the coolest thing.  Not much else to say, actually.
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      When you were here before,  couldn't look you in the eye.  You're just like an angel, your skin makes me cry.  You float like a feather, in a beautiful world  I wish I was special,  you're so fucking special.  But I'm a creep, I'm a weirdo. What the hell am I doing here? I don't belong here.   I don't care if it hurts,  I want to have control.  I want a perfect body, I want a perfect soul. I want you to notice, when I'm not around.  You're so fucking special, I wish I was special.  But I'm a creep, I'm a weirdo. What the hell am I doing here?. I don't belong here  She's running out the door,  she's running,  she run, run, run, run, run.  Whatever makes you happy, whatever you want.  You're so fucking special, I wish I was special,  but I'm a creep, I'm a weirdo. What the hell am I doing here? I don't belong here, I don't belong here.                     -"Creep", by Radiohead  dude, why is it that i can't sort any of this shit out?
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      In the chilling words of a senior official close to the Bush administration, "Anyone can go to Baghdad. Real men go to Tehran." This, plus the fact that we didn't deal with N. Korea all the while they were developing a nuke proves to me that Bush is an idiot.  I really don't have anything else to say, as of now, so cya.
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy shit....  If any of you watched the game last night, you know what I'm talking about.  That was the singly most exciting game of hockey that I have ever watched, made all the more special by Manny Fernandez's incredible performance.  Oh well, enough about hockey, although it is the easily the best sport invented.  Today, we had our school talent show, and it was ok.  Some people were good, and other's were having bad nights, and some just sucked.  It really pisses me off how people act towards people that aren't good.  They act like they like them, and mock them.  If you dislike someone, then don't outright say that you hate them, but don't mock them by making them think they are good, because people are reasonably smart, and will figure it out eventually, and then get really hurt.  Some people were really good though, namily Colin's band, Alec Tackman (spelling?), the two slam poems, and the two acoustic guitars at the end, and I applaude everyone with the guts to do that.  Wow, as time goes on, I have less and less to say.  Cya later.
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, my cheering must have worked, because the Wild kicked ass last night.  That's last night's news though.  Everyone should watch their game today, it's game 7, and if we win, it'll be the biggest upset in the playoffs so far (9:00, ESPN).  In today's news, nothing much happened.  I sat and listened to asinine arguements against Mrs. Milburn today, rather than against vasquez, so not much changed in that.  I'm starting to feel overwhelmed by the portfolio, but looking over the one on Emil made me feel much better, because all of the analysis' (analysi?) were a page or less, some much less, and it obviously got a good grade.  I'm still not nearly far enough though, so I'd better do some before the game tonight.  I also have three math assignments, and an outline, so I really should work tonight, but I'll end up doing the minimum possible.  Oh well, it's my GPA.  We played ultimate frisbee today in gym, and I must bow to Wes' superior skill.  He really is a great player.  I really need to get together with people and go to Silver Lake, after this whole portfolio thing blows over, just to work on my throw, and chemistry among my team.  We are in the school intramural Ultimate league, but we are pretty much on the bottom of the totem pole, in terms of skill.  There are 4 teams better than us, and we are at about the same skill level as the freshman team.  Oh well, maybe next year, when the three senior teams leave, we'll be good.  That's actually pretty much all I have to say right now, so cya later.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've realized that I normally start off things by saying that nothing is happening, and then go on for a long time talking about all the things that I did.  I guess this isn't bad, because it is a whole lot more interesting then saying "Nothing's happening" and then leaving.  Well, to continue the tradition, nothing really happened today.  I sat in my desk, and listened to people make idiotic arguements with our American Studies student teacher for no other reason then that she is a student teacher.  I know that she's really a bitch and that the arguements are a good source of cheap amusement, but if you're beaten in an arguement, or if she's right (for once) then you really don't have a leg to stand on, and should give up.  Of course, all of this is in retrospect, and given the circumstances, I would probably do the same thing, so don't listen to me.  In band, the ritualistic girly-fication of me continued, although slightly toned down from the height of it.  For those of you who don't know, I threw Danika's Koosh Ball up onto the top of a light, and then she started slathering me with a foul-smelling concoction that they call 'lotion' (although not in the way that I'm sure some of you are thinking).  Today I only got marked with pink marker a couple times, so you can see how it's been toned down.  Last night, I saw Cutthroat Island, and although most of the fight scenes are pretty accurate, it is a pretty corny movie, and meant to be that way.  However, it is a reasonable movie, and if you're bored, and have already seen Amelie, and have no other movies to watch, it really isn't too bad.  The couches that we got downstairs are really growing on me, especially if you get the spots right between two of the back cushions.  Very yummy.  Well, that's about all I have to say, especially since I really should do my outline, and some work on my portfolio before the hockey game tonight. GO WILD!!
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sauna's are yummy.
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, nothing is really happening.  I'm sitting on a chair, typing, being bored, and dreading dreaded American Studies portfolio's.  I probably should be working on them, but I'm a huge procrastinator.  In recent news, we finally got couches downstairs, so I anticipate spending more time down there.  Unfortunetely, this pushed the treadmill next to the pool table, so some shots will be really really awkward.  We may rearrange it, but for now that's as much as will happen.  If any of you can tell me why people go on treadmills, I'd love to hear, cause it seems really really stupid to me.  If you're going to run, why not go somewhere, rather than sit like a gerbil.  Oh well, it's pretty impossible to make people stop doing anything, so I won't try.  Also, I got several nice 3 piece suits from my dad, which he got 15 years ago, and actually fit me almost perfectly.  It's actually really amazing, bacause the shoulder's are exactly the right width, and the pants are the perfect length.  Last night, I saw Amelie, a great french movie.  I recommend it to all of you, if for no other reason then that the cinematography and sound engineering is incredible.  They really set the tone of the movie, which is the best part about it.  As all french movies (at least the two that I have seen) it really doesn't end, it just stops, so expect that.  I'm gonna go and see Cutthroat Island, and maybe sit in the sauna with my dad, so I'm going to end on that note.  Catch you later.
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.  It's been a while, just 'cause i had no time to do this, and i just didn't feel like it for a while.  I finished my Portfolio the day before it was due, like most people, and, I wore a suit to school again.  The whole suit thing really bothers me, because i'm getting such mixed results.  Some people think it's great, or at least somewhat cool, while other people make comments about how i'm wearing a carpet or a rug, one or the other.  I'll have to figure it out later.  I went to Big 9 this morning, and it was pretty cool, but between doing morning stage crew, playing ultimate frisbee, and walking around like a crazed chicken trying to find my sister, i'm pretty tired.  Not to mention that it's 12 o'clock for the second night in a row, and the wild lost.... Damn, just keeps piling on, doesn't it.  i'm worried with women, knowing that if i do something, it'll either make me seem like a jerk, or make me feel like a bastard, and, if i don't do anything, i'll feel pathetic about my lack of social skills.  Reality tv shows are starting to get on my nerves, especially american idol.  It seems like american's are picking people at random to get kicked off. Rueben was actually in the bottom two, and he's easily on of the top two singers.  Our pool is open, but until it gets heated, and cleaned, and stuff like that, it'll probably be the middle of next week till i can swim.  Wow, i'm tired, so i'm gonna go to bed now.  Cya people later.
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm..... Not to much is happening now.  I have an outline to do tonight, ONLY 4 LEFT!!! I don't think she's checking them anymore, cause on the ones that I saw, there weren't any pen marks at all, and there normally are. 
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I saw Holes.  It was pretty good, and definetely worth seeing, even if it isn't the best movie i've ever seen, or even the best one in theaters right now.  I have nothing else to say, as of now, because i am deep in thought....
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I fear that my life may become a soap opera, or at least a little one, which would suck.  I already know nothing that is going on around me, so hopefully any complex things involving other people will pass me by.
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm feeling like a jackass, because i'm pissed off at probably not making drum major, and i shouldn't be....
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually, it really doesn't matter, because my typical reaction to things i don't completely understand is to ignore them, which will probably lose me many an opportunity.  In fact, it's possible that i've already missed some (and like a song i know, i am whistling happily in the dark). If anyone ever reads this, I have a question.  If there's an opportunity to go out with someone, or hook up, and it gets passed up, will it ever come again?  Is liking someone like that a one time thing, that has to be snatched then?  I hope not, because i don't act til i'm completely sure, which is probably to late.  God, i don't understand anything. Especially women. Like my mom... She figures out that i'm watching porn, so she tells me, (exact words) "If you want pornogrophy, save up 5 dollars, and go down to kwik trip to buy a magazine".  Aren't women supposed to think of porn as demeaning?  Maybe that's just the ideals of books that i've read shining through, but my sister thinks of it that way... I'm really really confused about almost everything in life, even though people think i'm smart, and have stuff figured out. Or maybe they don't, and i've built myself up in my mind, thinking that it's other people that are building me up... Wouldn't it be great if at the beginning of every conversation the people said EXACTLY what they thought about the other person?  Unfortunetely, people practice to decieve, and get tangled in the web they weave, and then they say "Oh well, i guess i'm stuck like this, and can't get out, so might as well live like this", so they end up disliking people they don't mind, or liking people they don't, or finding friends boring...you know, people say the worlds problems can be solved by communication, but what happens if two guys come up to each other, and say "I hate your guts", they're still gonna fight, right?  Telling the other person that they hate them didn't solve anything at all... So, maybe it wouldn't be that great, unless people decided that they wouldn't feel hurt by what the other person said.  I'd sure like to know what people thought of me, and if i'm right, or if i'm wrong (much more likely) or if i'm partially right, and partially wrong.  maybe, it'd be better if everyone just sent me a letter saying what they thought, rather then tell me in person. It'd be easier on the person, and it'd be less hard on me, but, i don't expect anyone to do that.  Also, there wouldn't be any talking about what the person said, so you couldn't say "WHAT!?!?! YOU THINK I'M (Insert random adjective)?!?!"  basically, what this boild down to, is that i would really like certain people to tell me what they think about me, mainly women, cause i pretty much know what guys think of me, and with a guy, it's just if you like them or not, not if you only like as friends, or if you want to go out, or if you can barely stand, or all that jazz that you have to deal with women (Unless you're gay, and then you only have to worry about likes and dislikes with women, and all the other stuff with guys).  Hmmm, that's about all i can say right now, cause i need my sleep, and i've pretty much exhausted this topic...
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How does a rift grow from nothing?  The sad thing is that I almosted wanted it, for a long long time, and now that I have it it's just causing pain, and confusion.  I guess I think I somewhat understand the reasons, and I understand them, but, then everyone else can't understand the reasons I give.  The worst part is that I don't feel like I've done ANYTHING, which may be the problem, but all of a sudden it's uncomfortable for her too, not only me.  Basically, it all comes down to "What did I do?!?" There's not much else to say.  You know, looking back at this I can't imagine how unbelievably stupid this it is.  I had no cause to say this, or feel it.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever had the feeling that you wish certain lyrics applied to you, but they don't?  It's very annoying.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello. I am tired.  Well, enough on that subject.  Today was pretty boring, although it did have one upbeat part of it.  I guess seeing a movie like The Pianist couldn't really be considered "upbeat" but i guess it'll have to work.  Unfortunetely, it got cut in half by a raging heathen (Craig's mom evidently does not appreciate great artwork, and made me stop watching for dinner) which royally pissed me off.  All in all though, it was a pretty good movie, though i think that I will not be able to truly feel the emotions that are trying to be conveyed until i have felt them in my own life (although the part where the old man get thrown out the window shook me up pretty well).  It actually really makes me feel like a callused bastard when i can watch a movie like that and come out of it feeling exactly like i did before the movie.  Hopefully that will pass with time, and a greater understanding of human pain.  As of now, i'm pretty cynical and ruthless with people I haven't known.  Well, after we got cut off in the middle of the movie we went to the great tourist trap known as....dun dun DUN  The Boardwalk!!!  This allowed us to meet JD and his girlfriend, and spend money on overpriced food, while staring at idiot tourists doing the YMCA on a boat. Aside from meeting JD, the only good thing was the band, which included a trumpet and a tenor sax, which was pretty cool.  I wish that I could do stuff like that, which basically means that i should practice a couple hours a day.  I guess this wouldn't be bad, and i'd get a pretty stong mouth out of the deal, but as of now, i get tired after half an hour.  Anyway, JD seems happy with his new girlfriend, and she seems happy with him, so I wish them the best of luck.  
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from The White Stripes concert, which completely kicked ass. Bought a concert shirt, for the first time ever, but they only had mediums and smalls, so it's slightly tight on me, but oh well. I'm gonna turn in now, so cya later.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm, I haven't been on in a while.  Listening to Ben Folds for the first time right now.  It's really nice to hear someone use such an "archiac" instrument as the piano.  It's also pretty upbeat, which my music collection sadly lacks (quite litarally).  Life in general is looking up.  I'm in texas right now, and aside from a really really bad case of sunburn, i'm doing really really well.  It keeps life new and interesting, as well as having some of the comforts of home (such as the computer which i am now blogging on).  In the past two weeks i've gone to the beach for the first time in several years, gone to laser tag for the first time, met a bunch of new people, got asked for drugs, went to a swamp, went crabbing, and saw both "Requiem for a Dream" and "Finding Nemo" (two more different movies could not be found in all the world).  I got asked out for a date, and am confused as hell about the motives.  Every time I've ever asked her about our status, we're "friends", and she has a boyfriend already, and she really likes him.  Granted, he's going off to college, but normally the reaction to that is to try and make it work, and if you grow apart, THEN you start looking at other people.  You could say that it isn't a date, but what else would you call going out for dinner?  I guess, in the end, it really doesn't matter, cause i'm not gonna complain about going anywhere with suzy.  I wish I was omniscient.  It would solve a lot of problems.  In other news, I think I've figured out my plans after high school.  I'm gonna go to germany, for a foreign exchange student thing, then do either peace corps. or go to Russia somehow (i still have to figure that one out). Then I'll go to college, and then to grad school, and then live life.  Now that I have found someone I'm feeling more alone Than I ever have before                    -Ben Folds (no particular meaning, but quite scary if it ever happens to me)
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I really don't know what's up with my family...  My little sister has discovered the idea that she can evade punishment, and that I really don't have that much power in the family, and has taken to needling me, and my older sister has gotten really haughty at times.  Oh well, i guess people grow up, and I'm not the greatest person either, so I shouldn't complain.  I'm kind of excited about my birthday, but not really.  It's just kinda there, and I doubt many people know about it.  Heck, I didn't even remember about it till a couple days ago.  It'd be nice if people knew, cause then I wouldn't feel like so much of a nobody.  I am becoming a recluse, or at least I feel like it at this moment in time.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We hung out at his house for a little, and then we went to Kemah Boardwalk again, for dinner, and hanging around.  Met JD's girlfriend, and Rena (sp?) which was pretty cool.  Got to talk with Rena for a good amount of time when i was trying to find JD, and she seemed pretty cool.  To bad that I don't live in Texas, or I might have tried to get something going, but oh well.  Then, we went to Pappadeaux, and I had fish, and a shrimp sandwich, both of which were very good.  After dinner, The other people "surprised" me by buying me an oreo mousse type thing, which was really good, even though I couldn't finish it. After that, I discovered the joys of coffee, and promptly stayed up til 3 a.m. This wasn't a bad thing though, because i pulled an all nighter playing Halo that night.  That was pretty much it, for staying in Texas.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm home from texas, and as evident by this blogging, I am back to my old habits of too much computer time way to soon.  The flights were pretty good, although i couldn't tell you what happened on two of the three, cause i was zonked out as soon as I got on, which is a pretty good way to pass a flight, in my opinion.  The last day in texas was pretty cool, cause I met zach for the first time, and he's pretty cool. TO BE CONTINUED... (errand time)
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hand Springs  I took my girl to go bowling downtown at the red door after and argument I started cause I thought she didnt like me anymore I cant help it sometimes i feel pitiful and of course shes so young and beautiful bought us two glasses of coke thats her favorite and I wanted to make up for earlier But I dropped her glass and it broke so I just gave my glass to her She laughed and so did I in our lane then she went to the vending machine to buy a candy cane but next to that was a boy I knew with a spring in his hand playing a country pinball machine called "stand by your man" I saw him talk to her but I stayed in my lane and played my game steady and was thinking of a day when Id be too old to throw a ball this heavy But I guess Im young now so Its easier to knock em all down Then I look and saw her say to him "youre really Hittin that ball around" And hes lookin at her the way i did when I first met her I can see in his face white Flowers, Cups of Coffee , and love letters. I was sorry to interrupt their game but I went and did it anyway. I dropped my red bowling ball through the glass of his machine and I said "are you quick enough to hit this ball Mr. Clean?" I was scared to lose her so I couldnt help being mean. And that ended both our games I said I was sorry but my girl left with him just the same I thought how much I hate when love makes me act this way I was bent over a broken pinball machine in a bowling alley and I threw it all away. Isnt it all just a big game   -The White Stripes   Isn't it all just a big game.... 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I got back from england, but I'm not really feeling like blogging right now.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I think that blogging for a long time needs to be caused by a need to complain about something (unless you're a girl, in which case you can talk for hours about the days events (not to be sexist, but it seems to be that way)).  The main problem with this is that (at least for me) when you begin complaining, you think, "Hey, this is really fucking stupid" and then you can't write anything else, because whatever you start writing is bad, so you just get pissed at yourself.  Anyway, It's really just hit me that this year, I will be a junior, and that I'm halfway done with high school, which kinda scares me, because I'm nowhere near ready to be responsible, or anything. I'm sorry, I just can't seem to write much.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have realized tonight that the most important part of a woman's body is her eyes.  Granted, I say that for all the old, stupid cliched reasons, but it is still as true as when the poets of old declared it.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well then, I had an all-night 'lockin' type thing last night, basically screwed around playing video games all night.  Got home around 6, went to bed, woke up around 11:30, and then went to NASA, and got to look around inside the actual Mission Control Centers.  I dunno, it was pretty cool, and it's pretty amazing how few people deal with the flying of these billion dollar pieces of equipment around.  I guess my previous assumption, that it was mainly just the astronauts themselves, was even worse.  I also realized that the people in NASA really aren't scientists, beyond the little projects.  The ISS, and the Shuttle are primarily astronaut and engineer run, which for all their plusses, really deal with the workings of the 'ships' rather then the scientific aspects of Space.  People have come, so I must go  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really wish that cryptic infos or away messages, or just cryptic ways that people do things would be explained, or at least someone would explain who they are to.  On a better note, I visited Rice University yesterday, and had one of those chance experiances that could mean something, if you go through with them.  There was this girl there, that originally I thought, hmmm, she looks cute, maybe I should talk with her, and then, when we had to say where we were from, she said "Azerbaijan".  So, I'm sitting across from the girl, that is good-looking, and is obviously at least somewhat of a smart, world-traveling type person.  And, I didn't do anything...  I dunno, I guess in the end, even if I had said "Hi", nothing would have happened, but it's one of those things that you wonder about.  Anyway, the rest of the trip was pretty good, Rice seems like a good school, even though I couldn't go there even if I wanted to.  It's pretty big, at least by my standards, and I would have to take a couple SAT II's to even apply, and I dunno if I could get in, but besides that, it seems like it is one of the better secular schools around.  I've been having some fights with Evelyn, Craig's mom (for those of you who don't know, I've been in Texas the past week or so), and I've ended up losing.  Basically, I did get her to let me hang out with Ancel, who she hates with a passion, but now I've created a situation were she doesn't want to let Craig hang out with Ancel.  So, in the end, I lose.  Oh well, at least I fought.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God, I can see this party being a complete failure, but then, I've done it with people I didn't even know, and it turned out ok.  For anyone who doesn't know, and is looking at this Blog, It's my birthday party, it's on the 11th, at my house, at about 4.  It'll wrap up about midnight.  Don't worry about bringing anything but a swimsuit (I really don't know why I'm writing this, because I don't think anyone actually reads this shit).  Man, I dunno how the mix of groups will go, especially since the one is so much bigger then the other. God, I hope it works.  
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      People are fucking assholes....
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tired, so tired of all this shit.  Not even an angry tired, just a "let's curl up and forget life" tired.  So, that is what I will do.  Goodbye for now, oh many splendored, yet somehow terrible, life.  I shall see you sometime far into the future, when the sun is bright, and somewhere, a bird will be singing sweet songs to wake me, and I will be restored.  -A very tired Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm, it's been a couple days.  I stayed over at Ancel's a couple days ago, and basically spent a night becoming comfortable with talking with him, and got to know him a lot better.  I duno, it's pretty cool when you reach a certain comfort level with people, and you can walk along, and just laugh, because you realize that you're with friends, you feel secure, and life just seems altogether well.  I realized how grateful I am that that type of environment has grown up in Minnesota, quite unexpectantly.  God, I love Death Cab.  They're one of the few bands that I can honestly say I become happy when I listen to.  Other bands have individual songs that you can listen to when you're down, but few bands are quite so great a Death Cab.  I've decided that to really become what I want, I have to start working now.  I mean, if I honestly want to know, feel, discover everything in the world, I have to begin now.  I have to read EVERYTHING, and do anything, and have the guts to do it.  So, I think that I must make a concerted effort to, at the very least, get back to my reading habits of old, to have a book every day, to actually be reading it, to actually care, and not lose interest.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't understand the owners of my workplace.  I mean yeah, to some extent I procrastinated hugely, but I'm going to get someone to work for me in time, and it will work out.  I was just trying to try another way, and yeah, I should have gotten back-up, but for god sakes, I'm trying.  I DO care about the job, and how the business does, and theres no way in hell I would ever do anything on purpose that would fuck them over.  I dunno, it just doesn't make sense to me why they constantly feel that I'm not taking the job seriously, or trying to fuck them over, or other shit.  Anyway, life in Texas continues as normal.  I kind of felt like the benign mediator for a couple days.  It seemed as if I had an answer for everyone's problems, and now I realize that things are more complicated than I had thought.  I dunno, in the end, people, however charismatic they are, must deal with their own issues.  I can only deal with the way I react to them.  I am not a psychologist.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, since I'm back, I've decided to try and make this a regular thing.  Unfortunetely, I have problems figuring out things to write about.  Ok, i just took an IQ test, and it has to be bullshit.  It's billing itself as a real IQ test, with timing, and about 32 questions, and it claims that it can give a full intellegence evaluation, but it says that my IQ is 166, which is above that of people considered Genius.  Hmmm.  I just took another one, which seemed more professional, and got 138.  You know, this is really worthless.  I mean really, quantifying intellegence levels only creates a feeling of inferiority or superiority which in both cases is paralyzing, making you either to afraid to do things because you're "stupid" or making you not do things because you have the hubris to think that you can get through life with no work.  In fact, judging by me and Ancel's situations, it is worse to know that you are above average, because you feel an enormous sense of failure when you don't achieve what you 'should'.  Well, I did take another one, and I thought that I didn't get the results, but that one said 159, so I dunno.  Of course, I want to believe them when they say they are high, but then, i must think that they are phony,  because I did when they said I was low, and I believed that fully.  I dunno, I guess I will leave you to judge how phony or not they are.  Results  The Detailed IQ Test : 166 The IQ Test : 159 "Emode" IQ Test : 138
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm.  I forgot that this ever existed, but looking back on what I had written I thought, wow, that looks like fun.  So, I am back from a long hiatus. It is interesting that both times I have tried this have begun in Texas, where I am again.  It is very sunny, and very hot, and with less movies then I would like.  I did get to see Magnolia last night, and honestly, I have never seen such a poignant series of vignettes.  I guess it is very difficult to create films like that and keep peoples interest, but when you think about it, it is difficult to imagine why more of these types of movies don't get made.  Just for anyone who has ever seen the movie, I enjoyed the cop story, many because I'm a sucker for a) relationships, and b) happy endings, and that one contains both.  I dunno, there is much to talk about, but my attention span is small, so it will have to happen another time, maybe after I finish reading "Heart of Darkness".  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, there's this new chick at work, who evidently has been the Mayo Varsity Girls Hockey goalie the past couple of years.  Not only this, but she's one of the best looking girls that's been at work.  I dunno, I feel like I got to be reasonable friends with her, but I overexaggerate everything involving women.  Man, right now, I'm feeling pretty annoyed at blogging, so I am going to be done.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I guess it's only been a day since my last post, though it feels longer.  At some point, I'm going to tire of this, and I'm going to stop, but not quite yet.  I saw Fahrenheit 9/11 last night, and I must say that it's rather compelling.  It actually brought me quite close to tears at some points, which is saying something, because I have never cried at a movie.  Even so, it made me realize at some points what a callused, jaded individual I am, though I like to think of myself as one of the least jaded in my time period.  For example, the scene where an Iraqi was apprehended on Christmas day, without the family ever being told the crime brought little empathy from me.  I dunno, it could just be that some sections were more compassionately wrapped, and some were just not as well done, or it could be that I'm an asshole.  I finished  Brave New World  today, and I think that I am in some ways like the Savage as he becomes towards the end of the novel.  He sees a society as evil, and forces himself to deny everything within it (and forces himself to expect perfection from himself), and beats himself physically whenever he falls from this ideal.  I think that the last paragraph is a perfect example.  I look at it, much like the Savage did, and analyze it for perfection, and in doing so allow myself no pleasure for what I consider good (feeling emotional at sections), considering that normal, while I take the sections that I did not like (feeling jaded and callused), and see that as a mortal sin, which is almost unforgivable and needs to be worked on.  There are three possibilities to this behavior.  One, it becomes exhausting, and one gives up.  Two, one has the strength of charecter to not only continue it, but also uses it to become a better person as time goes on, and three, one can never satisfy oneself and ends up, like the Savage, hanging from the rafters, slowly turning around in circles.  We shall see how I end up.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a leaf, floating down a river, laughing at the nymphs and satyrs frolicking on the banks while I pass, praying that the end of the river will bring good, not ill.  Maybe I should learn to swim.  Or maybe not.  Are the satyr's really any happier, so engrossed in their own actions that they fail to notice me as I float by?  Do they really contain the secret to happiness, or is it I, the leaf, who has the truth locked within my grasp?  Can they laugh at their frolicking as I do, or do they forget how funny, ironic, beautiful life is?  And to quote  Don Juan DeMarco , "Sure, why not?"  Because in the end, it doesn't matter.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, It is 3 in the morning, and I am still on the fucking computer, fucking around, listening to music, doing random shit...  Why do I do this?  Is there any possible point to this?  I get to celebrate my birthday today, I get to actually bask in my specialness, for one day in the year, and I'm going to spend it half-unconscious, and tired as fuck.  I guess it doesn't matter, because the people that I would actually want to do shit with aren't here.    Man, I haven't even listened to the words of Elliott Smith, and I already fucking love his music.  His voice just utterly kicks ass, and it's a nice switch from the excessiveness of so much modern music.  What is growing up?  It has to mean something, because people change as they do it.  Is it just a loss of innocence, of naivete?  Or is it a gaining of an understanding of the world?  I guess I've always looked at it as a loss, a problem, something to fight, at least emotionally.  As the late Marlon Brando said in  Don Juan DeMarco  "Where has all the fire from our youth gone?", and then later "Without fire, there is no warmth, and without warmth, there is no life".  I hope that a) I can gain much more of that fire, because I don't crave life, experience as much as I should, and b) that I never lose what I have.  To quote  Bladerunner , "I want more life, fucker."
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today is my birthday, which means I should have some amazing new pearl of wisdom to dispose to everyone, to enlighten them in their quest for life, the universe, and everything.  Unfortunetely, I don't possess this pearl of wisdom.  Sorry.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God, I hate it when you try to publish this shit (those two words have the same letters, have you ever noticed that?), and it dies, and you lose what you typed.  Absolutely sucks.  Anyway, I don't feel like writing all that shit out, especially since the art of composition, at least for me, has to be spontaneous, it can't be repeated, so I'm not going to.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am back in Minnesota, and much of the anger/sadness of leaving another place is at least numbed, forgotten, almost not there anymore.  So, this is what "Lost in Translation" is about.  Those few times in our lives where we go, we live, and we realize another form of life, a form that enchants us with it's possibilities.  (God, why is it that I can send that shit out, and feel like it's mine, and then look at it and say, "That's high-minded bullshit"?, Why can't I accept myself as being anything other then normal?, Why do I fight 'superiority'?) Why is it that I'm still living in Texas, even though I've come back?  I've spent the past hour dealing with my 'people', the Minnesotans, those that I've spent most of my life with, and I still feel as if I'm in Texas, as if the people there are more alive, more real, as if their problems are more real, and are meant to be solved, or at least helped to that end by me.  I have lived in Texas for a total of about a month, and I have heard the deepest, darkest secrets of two people, things that I would have never heard from anyone here, and I have lived here for several years.  Is it just because I'm new there?  Do people automatically trust someone new and interesting?  Or am I a different person there, somehow more interesting, more alive, more real?  I guess this feeling will eventually pass, like them all, and I will be left back in my world of "funny french comedies and amusing little sisters", as I called it in one of my poems.  God, I don't want to lose that group of people.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck life...  This whole thing fucking sucks.  I come down here long enough to learn to love it here, I get to become friends with everyone, I get to stay here long enough to even want to date people that live here, and I have to fucking leave.  Well, to everyone in Texas in general, thank you for existing, for brightening my life while I was down here.  I am sorry that I must leave you. Individually,  Craig: Thank you for allowing me to come, for calling me up and asking me to come when I had all but forgotten that it could happen.  Ancel: Thank you for trusting me, everytime I come downi seem to become good friends with someone else.  I still need the list. (Too bad fireworks didn't work out).  Jeff: You kick ass.  Truly, you are the coolest cracker I have ever met.  JD: I really hope shit works out.  Still didn't get to check out your crystal stuff, much to my sorrow.  I enjoyed the time we did get to spend together.  Zach: Another time down, another time with not enough time spent screwing around with you.  Keep working, I really enjoyed the shop.  Brett: I wish that we had blown shit up... God, it would have been so much fun.  Even so, that night was one of the better ones of the trip.  Emma: You're one of the coolest people I've ever met... Good luck in life, and don't let it get to convoluted.  Man, I didn't do justice to some people, but what I would say other then what's here is probably stuff that people wouldn't want here, for all to read.  Anyway, you all kick ass, and I honestly wish that I could stay, at least for another while.  -Dylan Zehr
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has come to my attention that people have about as much understanding of my inner workings as I have of their's.&nbsp; I feel that I must enlighten (as much for my sake as for other peoples).   Subject:&nbsp; Dylan's Crushes/Likings of Members of the Opposite Gender   Ok, basically, I have never dated, I have never really flirted, I have never really had someone that I have known about that would be willing to date/flirt/whatever with me.&nbsp; Because of this, I guess I'm somewhat desperate.&nbsp; Instead of allowing myself the opportunity to see women as merely people, I'm constantly, and I mean constantly, aware of their actions (especially those possibly related to someone liking me), and the possibility of getting to be "more than friends" (if sometimes it's only entertaining a wayward thought of the mind).&nbsp; This creates a world of mine in which everyone is a crush, everyone is a possibility, and I have no monogamy (right word? I dunno, but I think it gets my point across) in my likings.&nbsp; I could be feeling completely into one girl, and then the next minute talk to another and think "Hey, there might be something here".&nbsp; I dunno, I guess it makes me harder to read, if I'm constantly acting as if I like everyone, or at least multiple people at a time.&nbsp; I doubt this has really helped anyone, but it helps to get it out.   -Dylan Zehr   P.S.&nbsp; I am trying to get over the thinking of people as possibilities, though I'm not doing it very well.&nbsp; I think that the best thing I could ever do right now would be to purely abandon the idea of dating, of romance, of anything, and just worry about getting to know people.&nbsp; We'll see how that works for me  
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, that last post was bullshit, at least the first couple sentences.&nbsp; There's no way in hell that I can handle the ambiguity of life. &nbsp; And I shall leave it at that. &nbsp; -Dylan Zehr 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Emotions are over much too quickly.  &nbsp;  You know, my problem is not in the ambiguity of life, I can handle that.&nbsp; My problem is in my solutions to it.&nbsp; Whenever I create ideas, plans, images to somehow release the fog surrounding my world, they always end up skewed.&nbsp; I think this girl likes me, or that person dislikes me, or that I am smart, clever, or intelligent, or dumb, or an asshole, or amazing, or all of them at once, and then I act on these assumptions, that change daily, or even hourly.&nbsp; I guess it's better to act on them rather then to not act at all, but they fuck up my life immensely.  &nbsp;  I dunno...&nbsp; &nbsp; -Dylan Zehr 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        People say friends don't destroy one another, What do they know about friends. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; -Mountain Goats  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it hasn't been as long as I would like to think it's been, but I'm back for another post.&nbsp; It's interesting, I always do this stuff while I'm away from home, but while I'm home the habit stops and dies.   I wonder if I'm doing the right thing.&nbsp; I seem to act based on "what are people telling me not to do?", and I don't know if that's because I just feel strongly enough about what I'm doing or if it's just that other people don't want me doing it.   I've been struggling with myself over the basic principles of liking people.&nbsp; Basically I've realized that a lot of my likings that have been strong and prolonged (almost a rhyme there) have been based off of first impressions and very sketchy information, and I can't figure out if that's normal, if it's right, if it's wrong, or anything along those lines (the problem with long sentences like that one is that I sometimes lose track of what I was saying, and then the sentence doesn't flow).&nbsp; I dunno, I guess in the end the likings are there whether you want them to be or not, and the best thing to do is to temper them with reason (which I'm not doing, purely based on the action of articulating these feelings in a 'public' forum).&nbsp; Oh well, most times I make to much of things, both my emotions, and the fallout that I cause by my actions.&nbsp; It is entirely possible that neither exist.   -Dylan Zehr   P.S. And, like most entries that I think are perfectly clear in their message, this is probably going to come out as a bunch of ambiguous garbage that no one can understand.   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's been a little while, but I'm sure most people, at least some, if not most, know that I've been at family reunions the past while.&nbsp; New York (my dad's side) was pretty cool, I got to meet a whole new side of the family that I don't think I've ever met (the only guys about my age in the family), and they ended up being reasonable people.  The Shenk side I've always known, but I guess as the kids grow there are more 'new' people to meet.&nbsp; I've seen two of my cousins for the first time in at least two years, and they're pretty cute.&nbsp; There's a new baby boy in one of the families, and he's really little, and tiny, and fragile.  Hmmm.&nbsp; I don't even know what to talk about anymore, so I will stop.&nbsp; Just felt like I should update.  -A (for the first time ever) homesick Dylan Zehr 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, almost everything that I write about here can be boiled down to the phrase "I don't understand everything, and it annoys the shit out of me"...  Man, after saying one thing on the mantra of "It feels good to do what you want to do", I feel like I should say so many others, but how, when, is it a good idea, why would I? I want to say so much, and every bit of it would fuck up my life, or make it the best thing in the world.  -Dylan Zehr (who is now hoping that you aren't going to throw shit at him for this ambiguous, self-serving, somewhat worthless post)  Edit:  One of the things I want to say is that I just want people to be happy, though my problem is that I assume that I know what will make them happy 
    
</post>


</Blog>