<Blog>





<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        "Mike! Show me your balls!"- Josh.....but then again, hasnt everyone said that at one point or another?     "My boobs are too big for my bra to handle"- bet you thought i said that....nope! It was our own Miss Hillary!    "Show me your tits now, BITCH!" - even i busted up at that one......that would be from the mouth of Joe     "Why dont you go outside and play hide and go fuck yourself!" - Jason let this wonder fly!       
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         (17:37:36) MissStressed says to Lawmanis1: *throws a runt at you*  (17:37:51) Lawmanis1 says to MissStressed: stealin my words!  (17:38:04) MissStressed says to Lawmanis1: he he...so! its my candy!  (17:38:43) Lawmanis1 says to MissStressed: i'm copyrighting it!  (17:38:59) MissStressed says to Lawmanis1: thats going on the quote page     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        "Ok....we've been in the car less then 20 mins, and you have managed to say Crotch 5 times." Hillary said that to our lil miss jenn!   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       See what happens when i get bored?  (11:48:42) missShorty : soooo...your place or mine? i know..lets flip for it....Head at mine....Tail at yours.....  (11:49:31) missShorty : whats the name of your perfume? "catch of the day?"  (11:50:16) missShorty : If you were a tear in my eye...i would not cry for fear of losing you  (11:50:26) EvilAppetite : it's called Come to Me..does it smell like Come to you?  (11:50:51) missShorty : *L* thats a good one....  (11:51:47) missShorty : This is your lucky day...i just happen to be single  (11:53:50) missShorty : Do you have a name, or can i call you mine?  (11:54:58) missShorty : *LMAO* girl your so fine, i wish i could plant you and grow a whole field of you  (11:56:01) missShorty : baby..your so sweet, you put hersheys out of business     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So this funny thing happend when we (Me, Erik, Jason, and Hillary) went to Chi Chi's..........  "OMG!! My ice cream is FROZEN!!!" ummmmm dont remember who said that one.... "Oh spoon, I wish you had something good on it"*LMAO* that was either me or jason...we were waiting for our oh so yummy S'mor icecream.   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i heard this song on the radio last night driving home from work. Its been awhile since i heard it, so i really listened to it. Man......is this line supposed to make us want him or something? Cause honestly...when im thinking sex...i sure the hell dont want my mother involved.....*L*   Joe-All the Things Your Man
</post>


<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well I saw you with your hands above your head
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So much for my happy ending
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Girl, understand why See it's burning me to hold onto this I know this is something I gotta do But that don't mean I want to What I'm trying to say is that I-love-you I justI feel like this is coming to an end And its better for me to let it go now than hold on and hurt you I gotta let it burn  It's gonna burn for me to say this But it's comin from my heart It's been a long time coming But we done been fell apart Really wanna work this out But I don't think ya gonna change ya I do but you don't Think it's best we go our separate ways Tell me why I should stay in this relationship When I'm hurting baby, I ain't happy baby Plus theres so many other things I gotta deal with I think that you should let it burn  [Chorus] When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn, Let it burn, Gotta let it burn Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over You know that it was through Let it burn, Let it burn, Gotta let it burn  [Verse 2] Sendin' pages I ain't supposed to Got somebody here but I want you Cause the feelin ain't the same find myself Callin' her your name Ladies tell me do you understand? Now all my fellas do you feel my pain? It's the way I feel I know I made a mistake Now it's too lateI know she ain't comin back What I gotta do now To get my shorty back Ooo ooo ooo ooooh Man I don't know what I'm gonna do Without my booo You've been gone for too long It's been fifty-eleven days, um-teen hours Imma be burnin' till you return (let it burn)  [Chorus] your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn (let it burn, let it burn, you gon'learn) Let it burn (gotta let it burn) Gotta let it burn Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over you know that it was through Let it burn Let it burnGotta let it burn  [Bridge] I'm twisted cuz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (ooooh) I'm twisted cuz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (yeah)  [Breakdown] Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooohOoh ooh oooh (can ya feel me burnin'?) Ooh ooh ooh oooh ooh oooh So many days, so many hours I'm still burnin' till you return  [Chorus]When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn, Let it burn, Gotta let it burn Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over You know that it was through Let it burn, Let it burn, Gotta let it burn 
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I wanted to know, I love the way you laugh I want to hold you high, and steal your pain away I keep your photograph, and I know it serves me well I want to hold you high, and steal your pain.  'Coz I'm broken, when I'm lonesome And I don't feel right when you're gone away.  You gotta win, you don't feel me anymore.  The worst is over now, and we can breathe again I wanna hold you high, and steal my pain away There is so much left to learn, and no one left to fight I wanna hold you high, and steal your pain.  'Coz Im broken, when I'm open And I feel like that I'm strong enough 'Coz I'm broken, when I'm lonesome And I don't feel right when you're gone away.  'Coz I'm broken, when I'm open And I don't feel like that I'm strong enough 'Coz I'm broken, when I'm lonesome And I don't feel right when you're gone away.  'Coz I'm broken, when I'm lonesome And I don't feel right when you're gone away.' Coz I'm broken, when I'm lonesome And I don't feel right when you're gone.  You gotta win, you don't feel me anymore. 
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       On a Monday, I am waitingTuesday, I am fading And by Wednesday, I can't sleep Then the phone rings, I hear you And the darkness is a clear view Cuz you've come to rescue meFall... With you, I fall so fastI can hardly catch my breath, I hope it lasts [Chorus:]OhhhhhIt seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels OhhhhhIt's as if you know me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me I am moody, messyI get restless, and it's senseless How you never seem to careWhen I'm angry, you listen Make me happy it's a mission And you won't stop til I'm there Fall... Sometimes I fall so fast Well, I hit that bottom Crash, you're all I have [Chorus:]OhhhhhIt seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels OhhhhhIt's as if you known me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me How do you know everything I'm about to say? Am I that obvious? And if it's written on my face... I hope it never goes away... yeah On a Monday, I am waiting And by Tuesday, I am fading into your arms...So I can breathe [Chorus:]OhhhhhIt seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels. Ohhhhh. It's as if you've know me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell. Ohhhhh. I love how you can tell OhhhhhI love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me... 
</post>



</Blog>