<Blog>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dreamed I was back at work.  I was working in the Livonia store tho.  I had alot to do.  I continued working for what seemed to be quite awhile.  Then a coworker, Scott, came up to me & said they were discussing what they were going to get for lunch, & wondered if I wanted "in".  I looked at my watch, & it was only 10:30 in the morning.  I told him lunch wasn't for another couple hours.  He said he knew it, but they had to decide in case it got busy later, & he would just leave as soon as he could & get it.  Then he told me that actually one of the bosses was supposed to show later, but they were thinking of getting lunch from a Coney Island, but that they were not actually allowed to go there for lunch anymore.  I told him I'd have to think about it b/c I didn't have much money.  Suddenly, it was later & everyone else had gotten lunch already.  I thought they hadn't bothered to remember me, but they said that I had told them earlier that I didn't have much money & couldn't afford where they were going.  I couldn't remember that, but it was true.  I kept working & I felt I had so much to do, I'd never get done.  So I decided I'd work thru my lunch break.  I'd talk to Irene every so often while I worked, but I still felt overwhelmed.  Then I thought it was going on the end of the work day, & I noticed I was polishing some silver(plated) things, & wondering why I was spending time on that when there were more important things to do.  Then I took a good look around & realized I'd gotten everything else done, there was still several hours left, & I was just keeping busy til the end of the day.  So I walked over to a nearby gas station, except all I got was a bottle of Diet Coke & something I don't remember now.  As I left, I realized it wasn't much, but I didn't bother getting anything else.  Then I went back to polishing silver.  I decided the dream had become boring so I woke myself up.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was doing laundry.  I had everything clean in a laundry basket.  My cat jumped in it.  She'd been trying to bite me, I don't know why.  She just sat in the basket.  I thought about taking a swat at her.  I lover her, but she was turning mean.  I finally swatted at her.  She literally fell apart.  Her paws were still in the basket, but her body flew into another direction & she was still alive.  I felt bad.  I told her, I didn't want to do it, but I was angry b/c she kept biting me.  Then I glued her body back onto her paws.  She had magic powers & could turn into a human.  After she was glued back together, I picked her up & got onto a bus.  We rode for just a few minutes.  The bus stopped, & she turned into a human.  We were standing on the steps of the bus & she was looking at someone in the distance who was in some kind of trouble.  She got off the bus, but had trouble walking b/c I hadn't glued her back together just right, so her feet kind of swiveled at the ankles.  I felt really horrible.  I thought she'd put a curse on me or something, but she said she wasn't mad at me, but I had to help people who were in trouble.  I knew I had no time for something like that, but I felt I had to do whatever was needed of me.  I can't remember the rest just now.
     
    
</post>


<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I had a strange dream a few nights ago: I went to blockbuster and rented 3 DVDs.  When I got home I either called someone or he/she called me.  I told him/her about the videos I rented, looking at each one. The third I discovered was the empty case DVDs usually come in.  I told the person I'd have to go back and hung up.  When I got back to the store I explained what happened. I looked on my receipt and noticed I was charged for the purchase of the empty case for $4.99. Not sure how I missed all that when the DVDs were rung up.  Anyway I was about to exchange it for the movie when I woke up.  Never did know what movie it was supposed to be.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        My life is not really that interesting.  I do however have a weird coworker who tells the craziest stories.  For instance, recently she told us that she was in the hospital for a year and a half under quarantine with mononucleosis.  Says she got it from eating bad meat--ribs from a pizza place.  Anyway, she had 7 specialists watching over her the whole time.  She couldn't eat solid food, so she was fed intraveniously thru her nose. (ouch)   Another one is that her sister has the thyroid disease, but her eyeballs sometimes pop out of the sockets.  The whole family had to take a class to learn how to shove them back in. And yes, she can still see when it happens.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know, it's been awhile since I've posted last, but I've been busy. I've taken up geocaching. I never thought I would even buy a GPS unit because I didn't really like the thought of being tracked by sattellites, but then I can turn it off anytime I want to. At least I would get lost less frequently. Right now the weather is back to being cold & dreary. It's usually in the 70s this time of year, but it's been in the 60s lately. Today, it only got to 59 degrees & the normal high temp is 75. It's been raining off & on for a few days now. At least my allergies haven't been as bad as they could be. I've also discovered a new "character" I may begin collecting named Ruby Gloom and her cat Doom. Everything is a bit expensive tho. I also rediscovered Emily the Strange.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is cold and windy here in Michigan. Today had cold, wet gusts of wind most of the day. Other days it's cold and raining. Once in a while we get a nice warm, sunny day. We've had quite a few thunderstorms too. Now Kimba has to be on my lap all the time. It is a bit annoying when I'm trying to sew or knit.    Last night I had a strange dream. I was riding on a bike with two other people. We were riding on the sidewalk of a strip mall when I passed by a police officer. Then one of the guys I was riding with, who was on my right said we were approaching a stop sign that was on our far right. I stopped at the last minute. Then the police officer approached me and asked hadn't I seen the stop sign. I told him I saw it at the last minute because it is so far over to the right. He said he was going to give me a ticket, but I didn't know for what, but then I woke up.   Real early Sunday morning I had a dream that Ron & Scott got shot several times. Ron was sitting on top of a building sign & Scott was standing several yards away with a bunch of trees between them, and they were talking to each other on the phone. Suddenly a man with a rifle walked up to where Ron was, aimed the rifle up at him and shot him about 4 or 5 times. Scott ran over to see what happened and the man shot him 2 or 3 times. I got a phone and called 911. Once the EMS got there, I asked how they were & they told me they would be ok.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last Tuesday night, I turned off my living room lamp to go to bed.  The switch is on the floor, so I bent over to turn it off.  When I got back up again, I lost my balance. As I tried to regain my balance, I ended up stumbling across the living room and hit my TV.  It's a 32 inch that sits on a stand. I knew it was heavy enough to support me with minimal damage to the TV. When I fell against it, I did push it back a little, but also hit my thigh against the corner of the stand. Wouldn't you know it, I was taking a shower last night and for the first time noticed a huge bruise on my thigh.  The center of it is yellow & the outer "ring" is a nice shade of purple.  Of course my leg didn't hurt that much until I saw the bruise. Now that I know it's there it hurts much more.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I took a nice nap today. Didn't really know I'd fall asleep, but I laid my head down on the couch & next thing I knew I was asleep. Felt good tho. I didn't sleep real well last night because my sinuses closed up & I couldn't breathe. I woke up a little a few times trying to inhale. Then the cats woke me up 15 minutes early for their breakfast. I was mad at them, but I had to go to the bathroom real bad anyway. So I went, then fed them, then went back to bed for another 4 + hours.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why are people so interested in my life?  My life is so boring tho, that they have to make stuff up.  I have had more rumors spread about me than Hollywood celebrities.  More rumors than Michael Jackson, I think.  I just can't go on Jay Leno or make my own special and publically announce that most of the rumors you have told about me are false.  And never mind the ones that may be true.  Even if they are, they are NONE of your business. If they were any of your business, I'd tell them to you.  This is as public as I can get telling you to leave my boring life to me & try living your own a little better.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm glad tomorrow is Sunday. I feel so tired. I just may be going to bed early.  My upper back still hurts a little. Wasn't too bad most of the day.  I still haven't paid rent. Hopefully I will remember to drop it off tomorrow.  Anyway I have another computer desk now & it is easier to watch TV while I am on the computer.  I still have to finish rearranging the living some more.  I got some stuff thrown out, but I know I still need to throw out more.  But of course I am too tired to do it now.  Otherwise, nothing particularly noteworthy happened today.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, my neck doesn't hurt quite so bad now, it has crept down a little between my shoulder blades.  I know I shouldn't complain about people driving real slow during rush hour.  I can't help it, it is so aggravating. Do they realize they are backing up traffic?  If they know, do they just not care or are they doing it because that is there source of amusement?  Are they looking at all the cars behind them and laughing?  Ha ha & all.   Oh yeah, I heard on the radio that "bling bling" is being added to the oxford dictionary.  I wonder what the definitions will be. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        The weather is kinda crappy. There was a thunderstorm last night. Sometime during the wee hours the thunder was right outside my bedroom doorwall, but I was so drowsy I was mostly asleep thru it.  Even with my eyes closed I could still sence the lightning. I did the counting thing between the lightning & thunder, but it was too quick. The counting made me fall back into deep sleep. One of my cats is terrified of noises, but I was so drowsy I couldn't get up to check on him.  My neck hurts real bad. Part of it is out of joint, but I can't afford to go to a doctor & get it taken care of. (sigh) I'm tired now & going to bed.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It looks like I have to move. After several years in the same place I have collected far too much stuff. It is too overwhelming trying to get rid of it all. My rent keeps going up, along with the rest of my bills, but my income stays the same, actually decreases every year. Geez, Michigan is in a bad way. Ok, I know it isn't just Michigan. I wish I could find a better job. It would help if I could get out from under the high, old debt I have haunting me. I'm trying, but when they just keep adding services charges & I work part time in the winter, what am I supposed to do? If I'd had a crystal ball & could see what was going to happen September 11 that year, that the economy would take a turn for the worse, I would have been more careful. How was I supposed to know? I'm trying to get my first degree so I can get a higher paying job, but even that seems so far off that I feel ready to give up. But I won't--not yet.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Wouldn't you know it, my July 4th holiday got off to a bad start. On my way home from work Thursday afternoon I end up in a car accident. I got to the intersection of Warren and Beech Daly as the light turns red. I needed to turn left, so I get in the left turn lane and a woman in front of me got into the lane just as I was passing her. Don't look to see if anyone might be coming up behind you or anything. I just hope you weren't talking on your cell phone.     Fortunately the damage was minimal and no injuries. Except now, I can't open my front passenger door. Her car hit mine on the front quarter panel directly in front of the door and sideswiped most of the rest of it. Bother! Now I have to go thru the trouble of calling the insurance company, taking the car in to be fixed, etc., etc.    Well, fortunately the rest of my weekend went quite well. Even did some geocaching, some relaxing, some swimming. My eye feels better, too although, there's still a little blood at my cornea. I REALLY don't want to go back to work tomorrow, but, what can ya do.  sigh.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, it's been quite a while, again. Once again, busy.  On June 27 I was sitting reading a book (I decided to join the Harry Potter craze) when I felt my left eye burning and itching real bad.I didn't pay much attention to it, but Saturday at work, Juan was talking to me & he asked me if my eye was bleeding. I figured they were just more bloodshot than usual. A few minutes later, I went to the bathroom & looked in the mirror & noticed a blood vessel had broken. It burned real bad for a while, but it is beginning to feel better now. During the Memorial Day weekend I'd gone up north to Grayling. My mother & I went geocaching. We searched for 4 or 5, but only found 2, I think or 3. I have found quite a few more since I got back here to Westland. While up north, I used a Magellan Sportrak GPS, but when I got down here I traded for a Sportrak Map, because it has more detailed street level maps. Unfortunately, it seems to be somewhat less accurate than the other. Ah well. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, I knew it had been awhile since I last posted, but I didn't realize it had been this long. I survived the blackout of 2003. Fortunately, I didn't have anything in my freezer or refrigerator that was worth saving. Don't really go grocery shopping too often. It was miserably hot & humid tho. Ah well, I'll tell my adventures as soon as I have a bit more time.   Oh yeah, I never did move. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to see Lord of the Rings: Return of the Kings on December 18.  On the 20th I woke up for work with my right shoulder sooo stiff & sore.  I dreamed I was battling Orcs & Urak-hai with Aragorn, Legolas, Gimli & all the rest. I couldn't move my arm. Ouch.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah, I know, but I've been so tired lately. Besides working 40 hours a week, I've been juggling 4 classes (14 credit hours). Until last week that is. Finals. I'll check my grades in a couple more days.  First I have to get thru the Christmas shopping ordeal. I got Uncle Kenny's gift already. I hope to get everyone else's Wednesday after work. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Does anyone other than me think the "Snuggle Bear" looks a bit evil?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been laid off work for just over a week now. It feels good to be getting enough sleep. I'd been feeling awfully tired & drowsy all the time for quite a while. I feel quite well rested now. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I've been laid off work since Friday. I stopped by work yesterday for my paycheck & W2 form. Someone there told me that Linda M talked about me for 2-1/2 days straight about how she misses me. She hates me, yet she wouldn't stop talking about me until yesterday afternoon. Jealous maybe?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, I knew Juan is not the brightest bulb in the house, but Tim is not the sharpest knife in the drawer.  Last month, a cow with mad cow disease was discovered here in the United States.  We tried scaring Juan over it (didn't work that well, he's still eating hamburgers--oh well). This past Friday, at work, I mentioned to another coworker in Juan's presence of a news report I had heard the day before.  A reporter discussed about how some candles are made with cow remnants. The reporter went on to say that if you light such a candle & inhale it's scent, if the cow had mad cow disease, there is a very slight chance you could develop symptoms of mad cow disease. Tim, who was listening nearby, said that is B.S.  I told him that was what I heard. So Tim says to me, " So what you're saying is that if a house burns down that had a person with AIDS, and that person burns to death, then all firefighters and any neighbors nearby who inhale will get AIDS."  I asked him what AIDS has to do with mad cow disease, to which he replied, "It's the same thing." Ok, HUH???  I laughed at him and told him that was one of the stupidest things I've heard in a long time.  As I walked away, he insisted that the two diseases ARE the same thing.  If you say so Tim. (eyes rolling now)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I Never Did Well on Tests...  I managed to pull a 3.06 grade point average last semester, pretty good for me for having 14 credit hours (full time student status) while working full time (40 hours in MI books).  That is just above a B average. Maybe sometime I can make the Dean's List. That would be a personal accomplishment. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The people at unemployment were not, in fact, finished with the games. Saturday I got in the mail a piece of paper with a whole bunch of stupid questions:  1. Can you work full time at all the hours, days, and shifts of your of your customary job?    Never said I couldn't 2. Is there anything that would prevent you from immediately accepting an offer of work (for example: being out of town, a family death, being in jail, etc.)?     If yes to any of these...YOU LOSE 3. Are you willing to accept work at the wages you earned with your most recent work?     Does DUH mean anything? 4. Are you or have you been willing to accept work in the same location as you previously worked?     Why do you think I was laid off in the first place? BECAUSE THERE ISN'T ANY WORK THERE 5. What were the dates that your were not fully available for work?      What did I say that sounded like I wasn't? 6. On what date did you begin your school or training?      Several years ago, but that shouldn't matter to you 7.  On what date do you expect your school or training to end?       When I graduate, but for your benefit I QUIT GOING 8. Are you attending school or training full time?     Just for your benefit--NO 9. Does your class schedule allow you time to seek work and accept job interviews?      DUH 10. Are you participating in an on the job training program? The income you are receiving for this on the job training is considered earnings (means it will be deducted from unemployment, should you actually receive any).       tsk, NO 11. Is your school training part of an apprenticeship program paid by your employer or union?        How about asking me questions that apply to ME 12. Does your class schedule conflict with the work hours of your usual occupation?        Sometimes, but they didn't care. 13. If you were offered full time suitable work that interfered with your school or training schedule would you be willing to drop your classes in order to accept work?        Yeah, like I'm gonna find "suitable work" with no real skills & like I'm just gonna throw thousands of dollars away to please you people, but for your benefit I ALREADY QUIT. 14. If you were offered full time suitable work that interfered with your school or training schedule, could you have your classes rearranged in order to accept the work? You are required to provided documentation from your school that you can rearrange your classes.       Yeah, right, specialty classes at a university? and again, like I'm gonna find "suitable work" with no skills. If it's that damn important to you, I dare you to find for me a job at the same wages, that I could do. Otherwise just SEND ME THE STUPID UNEMPLOYMENT CHECKS.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried filing for unemployment (here in Michigan) online on January 19. I received the date & time of February 2 from noon to 1:00 to call for my first check. I did that, but was told my application never actually went thru & that I needed my confirmation number to collect. I couldn't find it anywhere. I searched for a week & I could not remember where I put it. This morning, I finally called a phone number so I could begin collecting starting the week after my lay-off. She tells me that I have to go to an office because I stated that I am enrolled in school. To them, that means I am not officially available to work whenever a company needs me. Except I am scheduled to go back to my job May 1. Doesn't matter. She gives me another number to call to find a location to file. I go there. Except that location is only for a MI Works place for filing a resume online. I find that out *after* I post a resume. They say they have nothing to do with actually filing for unemployment. So I come back home & call again. I explain the ordeal I'm going thru. She gives me the address to a location. I head out there. Wouldn't you know it, on the way, I'm stopped for speeding. He claims I was going 18 mph over the speed limit. I was only going 12mph over (ok, big deal, I was still speeding). He writes me up for 5 mph over. The thing is, it's $  100!!!  I get to the unemployment office &, naturally, I have to wait for about 100 other people who got there before me. At least it only took about an hour +. Then it's finally my turn. She pulls up my name in the computer. Says my information is right there. It was posted today. !*^@*#??!! Then she hands me a couple forms to fill out so I can receive checks for the last couple weeks. Now it's a wait & see what happens. Have I jumped thru enough hoops yet!!?? Where am I going to come up with $100 for a lousy friggin' speeding ticket. Yeah, I know, "That's what you get for speeding, stupid." Doesn't help any. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried to donate blood at the University today, except they have some kind of minimum hematocrit requirement thingy of 38% and mine is 34%. That means my red blood cell count isn't quite high enough, which means I'm a bit anemic. Bummer. On the bright side, I assume that is why I have been feeling so tired all the time. I'm sure it's bad nutrition based.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Fortunately, nothing out of the ordinary happened at school today.  Went to Psych class.  Got back my test results.  I did worse than I thought, but I still got a B which I won't complain about.   This morning I went to the Oakland Community College Highland Lakes Campus in Waterford to see a Hearing Impaired performer.  He translates songs into a Sign Language performance.  That was really cool.  His website is http://www.bertramweston.com and it was an hour performance.  He wears hearing aids and he said can hear the music, but he also feels the vibrations for his performances.  He said he had to search the internet for the lyrics to the songs to make sure he got them right.  Some of the songs he performed to was: God Bless America, "Truly, Madly, Deeply" by Savage Garden (I love that song), the Titanic theme song by Celine Dion, "In the Arms of the Angel" by Sarah MacLaughlin & some others I can't remember the names of or by whom.  I *think* one song is called "Steps One Thru Four" and I *think* it's by Usher.  I could look it up, but I don't feel like it just now.  One of his first songs ever, he said and performed for us, was "I Believe I Can Fly" by Usher.   Very emotional, almost made me want to cry--but come to think of it, almost everything makes me want to cry.   While watching "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King"  about every 5 minutes I had to keep from crying. Now, it's time to study for a quiz in tomorrow's "Juvenile Justice" class. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonite was History class.  We have a quiz every week on assigned reading.  This time it was on the European Union.  The question was "What 3 countries do not use the Euro as their currency?"  I had no clue.  If I'd read it I had no recollection.  My heart sank.  I figured there's my next 'zero' point.  Then at least half the class said a collective "HUH???"  "Did we read that?"  So the instructor took pity on us & said if we don't know we could opt to answer the question "In what area are the countries considered to be that are to rejoin the Europe this year?"  I knew that one was in my notes (the quizzes are open notes, thank heaven).  Answer: former Soviet-bloc countries.  Again *whew*  Geez, what next? And, OK, maybe I should already know the answer to the first question, but hey, I am historically challenged, I've never been to Europe, and I have enough trouble trying to keep track of my own happenings, much less everything constantly going on all over Earth. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Maintenance has been fixing up at least one of the apartments across the sidewalk from me on the first floor. That apartment has been empty for at least year, maybe more. See the March 21 entry for more on that. I hope it isn't someone(s) who feel the need to make everyone listen to their music. I hate that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I knew there was a quiz in ASL class last night, for which I studied for (kinda, as much as a person can study for sign language alone), and I knew we had to bring a historical event article/story for the instructor's approval for a presentation to give next week, but when I got to class the 3 video cameras were waiting. Backing up, for all six levels of ASL classes, after every quiz and midterms & finals first the instructor signs 10 signs & we write down the English equivallant. Then is 10 sentences signed in ASL & we write the English translations. Then we take turns at the 3 cameras & sign whatever we were told the previous week. For the quizzes we have to bring in our own tapes. For the midterms & finals the instructor provides 3 tapes & the cameras are assigned 3 specific things. All the signing we do is written in English & we translate it to ASL on the tape. Anyway, last week she didn't say anything about what we were to sign. So last night I get to class & see the cameras, and it being quiz night, I realize I don't have my tape. I panicked a little. I just figured I'll have to set up a time when I can meet with her & sign whatever. Only one other person had gotten to class, but she wasn't there, just her books. Then a few minutes later a couple more people walk in & also panic. They ask me what are we supposed to sign? I tell them I have no idea. Then another person comes in-and panics. We finally decided that the instructor puts in a request for the cameras well in advance & maybe she forgot to tell the person who sets them up that she wouldn't need them this week. As more people walk in (there's actually about 14 or 15 people who can enroll at one time), & get the panic look, we decided we should have had our own camera to take a picture of THE LOOK as they walk in. But we tell everyone in turn we don't think there's any signing this time. Sure enough, when the instructor walks in, she sees the cameras, & tells us she forgot to let them know she doesn't need them this week. *whew*  FYI, the historical event I chose is the Space Shuttle Challenger that exploded shortly after lift-off in January 1986. That was the one that had the first teacher who was supposed to go into space. I didn't really have much to show last night, so the instructor wants me to get more information on the people & their families, which is easy enough. That just involves lots of fingerspelling of names & many people (including myself) still have problems with reading fingerspelling. Ah well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After being away from home anywhere from a couple days to a week or more, most people declare, "it's good to sleep in my own bed." which is great and all, except they probably don't have a large flock of noisy, #^**@@!! birds hovering around their bedroom doorwall at daybreak. While I was away, I got to wake up when I'd had enough sleep.  It pretty much started when the oh, so considerate woman who lived below me felt the need to bring as many birds to the windows as possible with bird feeders. On both sides of the building. The woman moved out a month ago, but, naturally, THE BIRDS are still hanging around. She made sure of it by dumping one upright-standing thing over onto the front lawn. There's still bird seed all over the grass. In the back, directly under my doorwall, is a piece of wood that warped upward. THE BIRDS are using it for a shelter. I can't get to it bc maintenence nailed my screen shut. Unfortunately, they did it without fixing the hole in the bottom of the screen the cat made back when there used to be a balcony for her to try & get out onto. Anyway, getting to the point, I was rudely awakened by the screen constantly rattling like crazy. I jumped up to look, knowing what I'd see. In the back of my mind, I hoped it couldn't happen, and never got around to doing anything about it. Sure enough, a bird had gotten into the hole & was caught between the screen & window. I had to try & get the window open just enough to widen the hole for the bird & direct it's attention to it while not getting pecked or it having fly thru the crack into the bedroom. It didn't take long for it to make it's way out, thank goodness. But I obviously have to get the screen taken care of. Right now there's a couple Oreo cookie tin lids blocking the hole.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It took me about 5 hours to get home. At one point I thought for sure I was going to get a speeding ticket. I was back in Michigan at the time & saw the state police car on the left side of the road. He was facing Eastbound. He looked right at me going 80 miles an hour, except I had several people following close behind & I was passing other vehicles. He never did start after us, so after that I slowed down to 70ish for a while, but I eventually ended up going faster again. Overall, traffic wasn't too bad except, naturally, getting thru Chicago.  Oh yeah, somewhere north of the Michigan border I noticed a sign for Macaroni Grill. So obviously, they are here. I just don't know where around the Metro Detroit area. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We went to Chuck E. Cheese for Doug's birthday. Naturally, the kids had fun, which is the point.  Later, for dinner, we went to Macaroni Grill.  I don't know if we have one in metro Detroit. I haven't seen any--yet. But as with any good restaurant, we had to wait a bit for a table, but one cool thing was we watched the chefs making everyone's meals. I ordered a veggie ravioli.  We didn't get the baked ravioli dessert because they were all out. Bummer. I'll be starting my trip home sometime today.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am in Illinois now. I got here yesterday. It only took me about 5 hours to get here, I think. I am somewhere west of Chicago. The drive was not all bad. There was the occasional person who felt the need to drive slow in the passing lane. I hate that. But many of them feel they own the road & start road raging if you make them think otherwise. Then I just wait until I can pass on the right, even tho you're not supposed to. I know, it's more dangerous. If I have no opportunity to pass, I just wait it out. Eventually they'll get over on the right.  Anyway, in a little while we'll be going to Chuck E. Cheese for Doug's (my nephew's) birthday party.  His birthday is actually in a couple weeks. He'll be 8 years old.  But his birthday happens to be on Good Friday this year, so this was the best opportunity for his party.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm pretty sure I did fairly well on the Psych test today. It was multiple guess. There were some I questions I wasn't sure about. Ironically, they were about memory. Then she talked about sleeping, the stages, & when approximately they occur. Then she talked about sleep disorders. It would seem I have about 5 of them, one on a regular basis, one somewhat often, the other three not real frequently. Good thing, because then I'd start to worry. Although one that is not real frequently could be a disorder or not. The one I'm not sure of could either be night terrors, or they could just be me waking up from terrible nightmares, & I just don't rememeber I've just had a nightmare. If they are night terrors, which usually happen during stage 4 of sleep, I usually wake up with the symptoms during stage 1. More frequently, I do know they are following a real bad dream. Although, she said that having bad dreams frequently could be a disorder, which brings me to 6.  I completely forgot to ask about the explosion-in-the-head thing. Would that be #7? Yay, me..NOT!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, about 4 hours before my History class I'd suddenly remembered we have a quiz I'd completely forgotten about. I have no idea how I forgot seeing as we have a quiz every week at the beginning of class. I hadn't read the article the quiz was on at all. It's a good thing it's open notes, but there was about 6 - 8 pages to read, & no way I could get it all written down. I figured I'd just blow this test like I did the last one & I could still hope for enough cumulative overall points to at least get a grade C for the class. Turns out tho, the quiz question was fairly easy, & I'm pretty sure I'd written enough stuff to answer it to get the full 5 points. I never did get my 5 articles, in fact, I'd completely forgotten my news journal at home & didn't realize that until I was approaching the school. No big thing tho. I'll just try & get that caught up another time. I have lots to do over the next couple days, so I guess I better get to them. Like studying for tomorrow's test. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not much to report today. I went up to work to get my windshield wiper fixed. I ended up buying a new blade. That sucker cost me $14.00. It's supposed to be the best, but yet it's the same as the one that got messed up. It could be the way my wipers work.  Also, this morning I just happened to remember about my Psych test that's on Wednesday. I'd forgotten to study for it this weekend. Fortunately, I haven't got too much else to do between now & Wednesday, other than get 5 newspaper articles into my journal for tomorrow night's History class. I'll start the test studying thing now tho. Do the articles tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I woke up kind of early this morning bc I thought I heard knocking on my door. That happens once in a while. I keep my bedroom door closed so my cat and her dander that I'm allergic too can't get in (even tho she is a short hair & doesn't shed too much). Other times it sounds like a door slamming, but I can never be sure. One time I read in the newspaper all about people who are asleep & suddenly "hear" an explosion in their head. I'm always dreaming about something at the time, so the sound comes out as either knocking or door slamming. I can never be sure which it is bc the few people left living in the apartment complex are in the same building & some of them are door slammers. Although, one of them moved out the end of last month. The complex is becoming somewhat of a ghost town. The apartment rents here are high and the buildings beginning to deteriorate. It figures some of the people left are in the same building as I. Not real surprising tho. This building faces a parking lot & most people like to be able to see their cars from their windows. The building that's mostly empty has their kitchen/bedroom windows facing the pool, which can be noisy in the summer. Also, that building has regular bedroom windows, but this building has bedroom doorwalls. There used to be balconies, but they took them all off bc they were "unstable." I didn't think so, but after the stories I'd seen on the news about some balconies elsewhere across the country/world collapsing from too many people on them, I guess I can't blame them.  Strangely, they left the front balconies on. Anywho, even tho I got up early, I still didn't get much done. I'd been feeling a bit lethargic lately & suddenly realized I haven't taken my iron supplement for a few days. I took it & after it took effect, I felt more like getting my errands done. That wasn't until late afternoon/early evening, tho. Strange, tho, feeling lethargic, yet not being able to sleep at night. I'm too used to knowing I can sleep in every day. Going back to work is going to be brutal.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found out it was a good thing I didn't go to the class I thought about going to last week (see dates 3/14 & 3/15). The instructor of my Thursday night Juvinile Justice class teaches the one I planned to sit in, but this past Thursday, he said the guest speaker just pretty much droned on for 2 hours. The instructor said he didn't know if maybe the guy was just real nervous, (I know, although some of you like speaking in public, many of us don't), but many students started nodding off. The only part that got people's attention was when the guy showed slides of the 2 year old who died. She was badly beaten & he showed slides of her on the autopsy table. My instructor said there was one of her with her eyes open, and her mouth slightly open,  but you could tell there was no life behind her eyes. He did also say the actual cause of death was drowning. The mother put her under the running bathtub faucet so she could wash the blood off. Sick people in this world.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate when I can't sleep in the middle of the night.   Thuderstorms=Spring?  Spring officially started at 2:00 AM & sometime after that so did a severe thunderstorm. I can usually sleep through those, & I was finally asleep at the time, except wouldn't you know it, the thunder was so loud that someone's car alarm went off. I figured it wasn't mine, but I just had to jump up & look anyway. Nope, not mine. But it didn't surprise me that it was the Mustang. Fortunately, the guy lives in the same building that faces the parking lot & turned it off.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had several errands to run, and I got kind of a late start, and it wasn't raining or snowing, so I figured I'd check my windshield wiper after I got my important, before everything closes stuff done. I figured it would take time to reattach it, bc it happened once before, but then it needed replacing anyway, & someone at work did it that time. Huge mistake, waiting. When I finally looked at it, I saw the whole top half of the wiper somehow got bent out of shape. I'm not sure how that happened. It was fine all the way to school, & when I first started out of the school parking lot. Then it just suddenly went screwy. My wipers are not the "regular" kind that go in the same direction.  I bent it back the best I could, but now I'm going to have to wait until Monday when I can take it up to work & have someone look at it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried going to bed early, but that didn't work out very well. I can't sleep. Mostly bc I'm having trouble breathing thru my nose. It's stuffed up, 'cept I don't have a cold. I hate that. Now that I think about it tho, I haven't had a cold for many months now. In fact I don't even remember when the last time I had a cold *knock on wood*, & I didn't get the flu this year. I think I managed to avoid it last year too *knock wood again*.  I probably avoided all that by not touching anything any time I could avoid it. Some might say I bordered on ocb by pulling my sleeves over my hands or putting my gloves/mittens on to touch doorknobs & stuff, and washing my hands anytime I did touch something someone else may have touched. I also carry hand sanitizer around with me too and use it. Whatever works, I 'spose, cuz I always do that & have been doing it for the longest time now. Go, me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It started snowing again this afternoon, then sometime while I was in class, it turned to drizzle. I didn't get to De & Jerry's until after class & wouldn't you know it, on the way there one of my windshield wiper rubber thingys started to come off the wiper. Fortunately, it was the one on the passenger side. As long as I stayed from behind a vehicle, I didn't need to use my wipers. It was already late & dark out, so stopping to check it wouldn't have been convenient.  I didn't have their gate pass yet, so I stopped at the security guard's window. There's a directory a couple feet back that you're actually supposed to go to, except that's only if the residents have a home phone, which they don't. So I passed it by & drove up to the guard. She says "May I help you?" a bit snappishly, I think bc I interrupted whatever tv program she was watching. I told her who I was there to visit, then threw in that they don't have a (home) phone. She was cool after that, did her thing & let me pass. Everything there was ok. Hopefully I'll remember to look at the wiper tomorrow when it's lite out. Although I doubt I'll remember until I'm in the car driving & it'll probably be raining or snowing or something. *sigh* 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Snow blew around all day today. A few days ago I said I hate getting up late. Getting up early isn't very advantageous either. I woke up around 8 in the morning, laid in bed & watched the news for an hour, then got up. Then I made the mistake of watching a DVD movie I'd rented Saturday called "Russian Ark." I thought it would be interesting bc it's supposed to be somewhat historical set over 300 hundred years in Russia, and all done in one single camera take. It turns out it was set in a Russian Palace/Museum.  It WAS all done by 1 camera in a single 90 - 100 minute take, I didn't learn much history from it, but it made me so drowsy I had to take a nap. Today is my early class (Psych, 4:00 actually), so I still got nothing accomplished. I only got in 1 cup of Mate tea & it was kinda weak & not very hot bc I ended up having to drink it fast. I have a test next week. Fortunately, it's my only test. And no papers due next week.  De called me too. She & Jerry should be well on their way to Georgia. Their plane was supposed to have left at 8:00 tonite. I don't know how long it takes to fly there. Shouldn't be very long. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It snowed pretty much all day, but it wasn't a blizzard really. The streets were clear & class was still in session. I didn't think to wear my boots tho, & it was a bit slippy, especially for old tennis shoes with very little traction. I got my paper done at the last minute, right before I had to leave for class. I totally failed the quiz tho. The question was what was the second decision made by the President's Ex Comm when they found out Russia was assembling missiles in Cuba. I knew it was a blockade, but I for the life of me couldn't think of that word--"blockade." I was trying to think of "quarantine" also, but I suddenly couldn't get that word to the front of my brain either. That's only five points I lost, but still... I've come to terms with the fact that I'm definitely not going to make a 3.0 GPA this term, but oh well. It's just a good thing I'm not working now bc, it could be worse. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't go to that class I thought I would. I went to bed kind of early, & I woke up early enough, & thought about getting up, but then I decided I'd rather sleep, then start getting stuff done, bc I never started on the paper that's due tomorrow night. I also started watching a bonus feature on the "Thirteen Days" DVD called "Roots of the Cuban Missle Crisis," it's interesting, but it's kinda hard to follow, when your attention span is as short as mine. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's much windier today than it was yesterday, but was warmer today. I finally finished watching the movie. I kinda followed it with the book. I haven't written the paper yet. I'll get started on that in a few. I don't feel like doing it now. I hate that. I get writer's block until I haven't much time to write something. I hate when that happens. I have to go to bed early tonite bc I'm planning to sit in on a "Child Abuse & Domestic Violence" class tomorrow morning. There's a guest speaker who's going to be there who wrote a lengthy article about a little girl, the youngest of 5, who was beaten to death by her parents. Then they tried to make an older sibling take the fall, by saying he did it & it was an accident. It happened a couple years ago. There are too many sicko people in the world. And I'm gonna get started on my schoolwork. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really have to start getting to bed earlier. I hate getting up so late. It takes me forever to get motivated to get moving.  The cat hasn't thrown up...yet. I've probably been giving her too much tuna fish. I've been eating it alot because it's cheap. Every time I open a can, I give her a little, cuz she's right there smelling it. But tuna fish has lots of Mercury. Women who are thinking of getting pregnant or are nursing are only supposed to eat it once, maybe twice a week, but I've been eating it more than that bc I'm in neither category (not by choice). Anyway, even tho the cat only gets a little, it adds up.  Now I have to finish my Mate tea and finish watching/reading "Thirteen Days" so I can get my paper for History class done. That's due Tuesday. Plus I have errands to run later, and I have to study for an ASL quiz tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't do much of anything today. Went out for a little while. It was cold today, but not as cold as it's been all week--only because the wind wasn't blowing as hard today as it was all week.  Last week was excessively windy too, but it was so much warmer & nice. Yesterday, I found some really nice scented candles at "Bed, Bath, & Beyond." Except, sometimes they almost smell kinda cigarry.  I also found what I thought, at first, were floating candles, & I bought 'em thinking they would only cost maybe 99 cents, (they didn't have any prices posted anywhere). Turns out they cost $1.20. Wow! Then I got 'em home, unwrapped 'em & discovered no wick. huhh?. Then I looked at the label, & discovered they are wax air fresheners. Pretty cool I guess. Makes 'em a little more worth the money. I'd bought 3 of those, but all different scents.   On a more serious note, my cat has thrown up 2 mornings in a row, and the 3rd or 4th time this week. I'm not sure what's wrong bc I didn't see any hairbally things in her vomit. This morning after she threw up, she wanted to eat again, so I gave her some canned food, usually I give her dry--the same stuff for a few months now. She kept that down ok. I'd only given her a little, & she was hungry again later, so I gave her some more & she still kept it down.  She is real close to 10 years old, & otherwise still going strong. She is quite overweight tho. She still gets around good too. Once in a while I have her chase a red laser for exercise, she loves that. But also lately, I think she's been having weird dreams. She lays next to me on the couch & suddenly starts making weird noises & kind of twitches. Then she wakes up with a start & a high pitched rrrrrr & looks around for a second. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WOO HOO!!!  I GOT IT!!!  Actually I got 2 checks. And they are for 7 weeks. I also got a "Notice of Determination" that says,  "You attend night classes on a part time basis. You have done this while working full time and state you are available for work at any time. No ineligibility is imposed as the availability requirements of the M.E.S. act are found to be in order. You are eligible for benefits under MES Act, Sec. 28(1)(C), for the period shown. It is found that you were available for suitable full-time work." Yay, me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I called them a few minutes ago. I was told a check for the last 7 weeks was mailed out on March 10. Now I just have to wait for the mail for the next couple days.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't call today. Definitely tomorrow. I usually have been doing my laundry on Fridays, but I decided to do it today, so I wouldn't have to think about it tomorrow. De (my sister, for anyone who doesn't know me & is actually reading this blog) called me this morning to say her father-in-law is in the hospital down in Georgia. He has had heart problems for the longest time. I never asked, but it could be as a result of his mother having German Measles when she was pregnant with him. That is a side effect along with deafness, which he has. Anyway, he had a triple bypass a few years ago, but this morning, she said he has one functioning artery. They may have to fly down to Georgia, so I told her I'd check in on their cat & apartment if they do have to go.  It's a good thing I'm not working now b.c. this would be the third time now, I've had to come to someone's aid. Go, me.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I called them this morning. Naturally, the ph # they told me to call if I hadn't received any unemployment checks was just a recording saying they are having a really high volume of calls and can't answer any of them just then. Whatever. So I called another ph #. After the usual voice mail crap, I got a live person. I told her I filed for unemployment back in January & was inquiring as to whether or not I would actually receive any checks eventually. She checked my file & whatnot, and as usual the hold up is still the friggin @@#**# school thing. She asked me was I still going, I told her NO, I quit a month ago, so what's the holdup. She asks me if I have transportation to find a job or get to job interviews. I told for now I do, but if I don't get any checks, I won't have transportation. She looks & asks me if I received a questionnaire about my schooling. I told her not only did I receive it, I mailed it back a month ago. They don't have it. That's funny, cuz my employers received a copy a couple days after I mailed it. So WHERE DID YOU IDIOTIC PEOPLE PUT THE ORIGINAL??? She says she'll have to find it & review it.  Whatever. Expect another call from me tomorrow. And everyday until I get some dynamite up someone's ass.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made my biweekly call to MARVIN for another unemployment check. I think that's 5 they now owe me. If I ever actually get them, I'm gonna feel almost like I've hit the lottery or something. Trouble is it's already spent. With my luck, and their stupidity, I'll be back to work, then they'll decide since I'm working, I'm not entitled to them or something. Guess I'll start calling them everyday starting tomorrow. I'll call them until I actually receive the checks.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I went to Deaf Coffee Hour in Ann Arbor at Easter Accents. Dr. Philip Zazove was there. He's deaf & he's running for the House of Representatives. I had a brief conversation with him. For details on that click on the link to (my) Kim's webpage on the right near the top & go to the "Essays" page. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No unemployment checks yet. Still waiting.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been blogging for a year now.  Yes I realize I've been more regular since I started.  Alot happens at times.  At first it felt strange publishing my life on the web, but as I read other people's, I thought maybe someone somewhere would happen to read mine & be at least mildly interested....   Anyhoo, I slept 11 hours.  Woke up at noon.  By the time I'd thought about maybe going out to get stuff done, I'd decided it wasn't such a good idea.  Friday afternoons suck traffic-wise.  Too many fools out there behind the wheel.  I almost went to the park for a walk, but it was windy & a bit cool. So in the end I stayed home & read & mostly watched TV.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes today was nice out.  It got up to 81 degrees F.  I went to the park in Canton again & walked. According to the GPSr I walked 2 miles.  Then I got my backpack & found a place on the grass, & laid down & read for awhile.  I'd gone to the library in Westland & borrowed the first 3  I, Robot  books by  Isaac Asimov .  The movie is currently scheduled for release in theaters July 16.  I know I never got far in the books, so I figured I'd try to get as far as I could.  The movie is supposed to be based on all 9 books.  I know I'm not going to get that far.  Before I went to the library, I went to the school to pay for the class I signed up for that starts next week.  On my way I remembered I had a receipt from the last time I went to the bank.  It said I had less money than I thought.  I did some figuring & realized I never deducted from my Money program a check I wrote a week or so ago.  I don't know why, but I thought I had.  Which meant I don't have as much money as I thought.  I went ahead & paid for the class anyway, but it's going to be a tighter squeeze than I thought.  Hmmph.  On top of all that, I couldn't sleep last night.  I'd had some baked beans yesterday, earlier in the afternoon, & they were still with me.  At 3:00 this morning, I finally got up & took my last Pepcid AC.  The burning finally lessened.  It had occured to me that happened the last few times I had baked beans.  I'm never eating them again if I can help it.  The pain was unbearable.  I sat up & watched a previously recorded C-Span session that took place earlier yesterday in either the Senate or the House of Representatives on a discussion of the "new, improved rules of who no longer gets overtime pay beyond 40 hours/week."  Police, firefighters, & all first response emergency personnel will get paid.  Everyone else who is non-union making between $26,xxx (I forget the exact amount) to 100,000 is screwed.  They are "trying to strengthen the 40 hour work week."  Except some businesses depend on being open for many more hours than that each week.  And can't afford to hire people to cover the extra time.  Like where I work.  They even gave some examples.  A daycare worker who has to take care of even 1 child beyond the 40th hour is not entitled to overtime pay--unless he/she spends the time teaching the child something.  If he/she is only caring for the child for the parent/guardian--no overtime pay.  If you're a Manager & spend at least 20% of each week doing managerial stuff, your salary better compensate for the overtime your excluded from getting.  If your job is a specialty one, such as fixing things, computer installer, electrition, etc. ditto.  They even demonstrated by pure accident.  Each member had 5 minutes to ask/discuss whatever they wanted concerning the "new rules v. old rules," or clarify something. At the start of one's session, his microphone wouldn't work.  He moved to another, meanwhile another fixed the microphone.  Afterwards, the one who fixed it said "the good news is I fixed the microphone, the bad news is I won't be getting paid any overtime because it was a specialty job."  Ok, maybe to an extent they are trying to get people to do they're jobs within a reasonable amount of time.  Here's more.  They also said Funeral directors & specialty chefs who have 4 years of post high school education are excluded from overtime pay.  Someone said it sounded like they are trying to penalize people for wanting a higher education.  The secretary of Economics said all this stuff has been in the  rule book  all along, just not as specific.    That's about all I remember at this point.  I sorta quit listening, b/c it wasn't helping me get to sleep.  The  new rules  are slated to begin in August.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I looked out the window this morning & saw large, white things floating all over. I thought, " wait that can't be...SNOW???!!?"  No way, maybe it's flowery things from a tree blowing all over..a rather large area...  I had to run a couple errands & I checked the weather on the weather channel.  Considering it was in the mid-40's, I figured it had to be snow.  I'm not surprised at how cold it is.  Seems to me, it's been cold well into May in the past.  Blech.    This morning I considered dropping the class I registered for this next semester.  I could certainly use that money to pay my bills now, but there's the nonrefundable registration fee.  As it stands now, I can pay rent, & the car payment, & make half the tuition, but I'll have to wait until next week to pay the rest of the bills, except they are already overdue.  Hopefully, 1 week won't matter too much, but I still have a few days to work it all out & make a decision.  The registration fee is nothing to sneeze at.  It's too much to just give it up.  Next month won't be tight even if I'm not back to work.  It's just right now.  I'm glad I've been living otherwise simply, tho.  I'm still considering moving to somewhere cheaper & the less I have to move the better.  I'm just not sure about moving tho.  Moving to a cheaper place pretty much means moving to a place about half the size of where I live now.  Or, if I can manage to save enough cash by next August, I can consider moving to a manufatured home park.  But the only 1 I really like is further away from work & school.  And some of the drive would be a 2 lane (busy) road.  *sigh*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to see "Connie and Carla" at the Emagine Theater in Novi.  I went to the first showing of the day.  I and an older couple were the only ones to see it.  I didn't mind.  They sat further back, so I got to sit closer to the front in the middle & not be in their way at all, even tho it is stadium seating.  I hadn't eaten yet, & I'd gotten there about 5 mins b/4 the movie was to start, so I got a cream cheese stuffed pretzel (one of the cheaper things on the menu).  I'd never had one before, it was pretty good.  Anyhoo, the movie stars Nia Vardalos, Toni Collette, & David Duchovny.  It was a few other movies rolled in one. Similar to  Sister Act , they witness a murder & go into hiding. Except instead of impersonating nuns, they become drag queens. There's a brief reference to   Thelma & Louise  towards the beginning.  There was a couple parts I thought dragged a little too long, but overall I thought it was funny.  I also thought Nia Vardalos & David Duchovny worked quite well together. I'd been wanting to check out the Emagine Theater, that's why I went there.  I can't swear to it, but I *think* the screens at AMC in Livonia are still bigger.  It's been a few months since I was there.  After that I went to the school bookstore.  On Friday I was there & gave back many textbooks for some money.  One of them was my Psych book, but there was also a workbook, a couple reference books, & a CD-Rom that came with it that I never used & had forgotten, so I gave those back today.  Then I checked to see if the book I'd need for the next class was in.  It was--$70.  I didn't buy it yet.  I still have to figure out my overall financial situation.  Too bad the book wasn't in Friday, I could have paid for it with the money I'd gotten for the other books, but naturally, I've spent most of it already.  Plus I'm going to have to get to Target soon, & get daily stuff.  I'm not sure how much that's going to cost.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Because I'm a blogger I got an invite to sign up with Google's GMail.  I figured what the hey, even tho I already have an email address thru AIM's Netscape as well as another one.  Last I heard, Google & Blogger are both owned by the Pyra Labs; or Google owns Blogger & Pyra Labs.  Or whatever. Let's see how much spam I get.    I'm finally feeling the financial pinch of paying off a rather large past debt.  I registered for a class for the Spring/Summer semester & I need to come up with at least half the tuition by next Friday.  That wouldn't be too difficult except rent & the car payment is also due at the same time.  Hopefully, I'll figure something out.  I'm also waiting for my grades.  I've been checking online, I got my Juvenile Justice grade (an A), but he said he'd have everyone's posted within a day or two anyway.  It's the Psych one I'm worried about.  I wasn't feeling well & didn't study very well & ended up guessing at many answers.  I'm disappointed in myself for that, but it's obviously too late too do anything about it.  I am also worried about the ASL grade too. I didn't do all that well in the class.  But she didn't tell me I'd have to take the class again.  I heard later that someone else was told she would have to take it again.  Meh.  Now I'll have to wait another few days.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The semester is over.  I mentioned Tuesday night's cheater to the Juvenile Justice instructor tonite. Turns out his son was in the same class & had told him about it already.  Thru-out the semester, the instructor has mentioned his sons, I just didn't know one of them was in the same History class.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Normally, thunderstorms don't bother me. Listening to the rain is soothing & makes me drowsy. I prefer them at night so I can fall asleep. Yes even through the thunder & lightning. Unfortunately, they make my sinuses hurt real bad. There was a severe thunderstorm last night & this morning I woke up groggy & stuffed up.  I should have taken a Sudafed when I got up, but nnnoooo. Naturally, by this afternoon my sinuses hurt so bad I felt sick.  Had to take a couple Extra Strength Excederin to first get rid of the pain. I fell asleep on the couch for a couple hours, then took the Sudafed. I'm mostly better now.  This past Monday I was supposed to make my biweekly call to MARVIN. I'd remembered about 10 - 15 mins b/4 my 1 hour block. But I got to doing other things (like blogging) and forgot until 4 hours later.  So I have to wait until tomorrow.  Sux.  I would already have my paycheck by now.  Not that big a deal tho, bc it doesn't matter too much now. Bills don't have to be paid until next week.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went, I conquered, I came back alive to tell the story.  Some moron tried to cheat on the final exam tonite.  To an extent I can understand it.  There's so much memorization involved.  I thought I was going to go krackers. The rest is a breeze compared to tonite's class--all semester.  But I know I made it thru pretty good.  Probably other students over the years have tried to cheat. The instructor had told us what to study. Naturally, he gives us a couple more things than what's really on the test.  This guy had everything written down on note cards.  We had to have only either an obviously blank "blue book" or 3 sheets of obviously blank paper on the desk.  Those using paper would have to ask to use more sheets.  It was a pretend the reader of our papers knew nothing of what's being said essay.  Ok, now imo, if your going to take the trouble to write everything down on the cards, why not write them asap after being given what to study, then study them throughout the week.  I mean, many of us DO have busy lives, but if you're taking the classes in the first place, isn't that some sort of commitment to take the time & see it thru until the end? Anyhoo, about 5 or 10 minutes into the test, the instructor walked back to the guy & took his notes.  He then walked to the door & waited.  The guy gathered his things & walked out. On his way out the instructor told him he is done.  The guy tried to talk to the instructor, but I think even he didn't have anything to say. The instructor came back in & closed the door for a while.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I believe I did pretty good on the ASL final exam.  She signed first a long story, then a shorter one.  I know I missed some details in both, but I just couldn't remember it all at once.  She made us put our pencils down while she signed each one the first time.  Here's how it went. She signed the first story in it's entirety.  After she finished, we wrote as much as we possible could. Then she signed the whole story again. Then we wrote down whatever we thought we missed.  Next she signed the second story in it's entirety. This one was shorter than the first. Then we wrote everything down. Then she signed it again, & we wrote whatever we missed.  I don't have time to give any other details now.  Now I'll be happy to make it thru today/tonite.  All aboard the crazy train.  I'll be SO glad when I finish this one crappy, freakin class. It totally sux. I hate it real bad. Time to get back to it.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'll get back to my studying in a minute.  I went to the park again yesterday.  I took my GPS on my walk this time & I walked the same route as Saturday.  According to the GPS I walked about 1.30 miles.  Then I got my backpack out of my car & headed to the same picnic table.  Except, wouldn't ya know it, I could tell a walker was headed for the same one from my left.  He got to it a few steps ahead of me.  I looked around for another suitable one, but there were none I liked.  That was the only one far enough away from all the rest, was near a pond, and set away from the walk/bike/roller blade path.  So why would he pick that one?  Anyhoo, I just walked a few feet away & sat on the grass bc I knew he wasn't going to stay there very long.  Even after he left, I thought about staying on the grass, but it was so darn windy out.  So I got up & went to the picnic table.  In fact, it was too windy to get much studying done.  I had my notebook out, but I had to use my tape recorder, GPS, & Palm III as paper weights.  The wind kept blowing directly into my eyes too bc I didn't have sunglasses, & it's a bit bothersome when wearing contact lenses.  And I was facing the sun (I know, "what, you want macular degeneration or something?!?).  So I spent much of my time sitting there with my eyes closed leaning on my notebook.  But I did get some studying done.    Today there's a wind advisory.  At John Daly & Michigan Ave. a traffic signal came down.  That's around 10 miles SE of me +/- a couple miles.  I won't have time to get to the park today (bummer) bc I have a report I should be finishing now, & then I'll get back to studying.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back again.  I figured I'd fall right to sleep, but no.  I laid in bed for a couple hours, then finally gave up.  Now here I am.  Been awake since 10:00 yesterday morning.  Of course it didn't occur to me I could have just picked up one of my history books & started reading.  I probably would have been asleep ages ago.  Oh well.  Now I'm gonna end up wasting the whole afternoon b/c eventually I will fall asleep, then sleep all afternoon.  meh.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I went to Hines park & found a mostly quiet place to sit & study.  Today I went to Heritage park in Canton.  Not a whole lot of people there, fortunately.  First I went for a nice brisk walk around it.  I didn't think to have my GPS with the mileage counter with me, but I think, according to some posted guides, I walked about a mile.  I listened to the history lectures while I walked.  We were allowed to audio record them, thank goodness, otherwise I would have missed quite a bit.  Then I found a nice quiet (metal) picnic bench right near a pond and & I sat there & studied.  Sort of.  Every so often, some ducks would "dive" into the pond.  It made me want to take a dip, 'cept there's no swimming--for humans anyway.  I hope to go there often, as I've gained a whole lot of weight sitting around, eating too much, and being generally lazy for the last few months.  That walk felt good, except when I first sat down.  Even tho I stretched my leg muscles, I got that pincushiony feeling in both thighs.  That's from restless leg syndrome.  I get that every so often.  Anyhoo, it was nice & quiet other than the ducks playing.  It's only about 8ish miles from where I live.  I have to get in some kind of shape (other than what I'm in now) before work, otherwise I'm going to be miserable.  I'm still not sure when I'm going back (hopefully not real soon), but I'm giving myself about 2 weeks to get into a halfway decent shape.  Not much time, but that's what I get.    I slept quite well last night, no bad dreams, and I should sleep really well tonite.  I'm a bit drowsy already, probably from the walk.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was so freaked out this morning by the nightmare I'd had that I'd forgotten to mention what I saw yesterday.  Actually I guess I could have mentioned it in the blog I wrote last night, but I forgot then too, so here it is.  I ended up going to the 24 hour post office yesterday afternoon bc I couldn't find my stamps, so I figured I'd buy a couple for my taxes.  Silly me drove right past the post office 1/2 mile from where I live w/o giving it any thought.  Anyhoo, on my way to the other post office, I drove past a house with that big, huge inflatable pink bunny holding the easter egg, the one that's almost as big as the front of the house it's sitting in front of.  I can understand not taking down one's Christmas lights until 6 months later (if at all).  But really folks, that bunny needs to be gone the day after easter (imho), especially one that darn big.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's nice out & I know I should grab my textbooks & stuff & go to a park & study, but I just can't make myself presentable to the public.  I had a real bad dream that I woke up from at 6 this morning.  About 10 seconds after I woke up, my bedroom doorknob rattled, & it scared the mess out of me.  I told myself "it's only the cat, it's only the cat" & sure enough, the cat then made her meow/cry.  I jumped up, changed into sweats, went out, wrapped a blanket around me (bc I still had chills from what happened), laid on the couch with the news on tv & fell back to sleep at 8:00 & slept until 11:30.  I can't get the dream out of my head.  I'm writing it here so maybe I can forget about it.  Eventually this post will be archived, in the meantime, anytime I review my blog, which I do on occasion to check for spelling errors & such, I will skip over this one.  I don't care about misspellings & stuff here.  If you have a queasy stomach, I'll tell you when to stop reading.  And I will never mention it in another blog.  I may even change the archive settings so it's not on the current page for very long.  For all I know, once it's in writing in this blog, maybe it won't seem as bad as it is in my mind.  I wanted to get a Deadjournal account to put the dream there, but it costs money, which I don't care to spend.  Anyhoo, I think I know why I had the dream.  It took me the 2 hours I was awake to figure out where it came from.  Probably bc I was channel surfing for a few minutes before I went to bed last night instead of doing the smart thing & looking at the TV guide.  I came across some movie & watched a few minutes to figure out what it was.  There was a man walking down some stairs in a house.  He was talking to a bunch of people gathered together.  I could see him talking, but his mouth wasn't exactly moving.  He had on a mask.  The movie was "House of a 1000 Corpses."  I changed the channel, but ended up with a couple minutes of Sci-Fi & "Mad, Mad, House."  I changed it again & watched something else, which, I believe I flipped back & forth between Jay Leno & David Letterman.  I figured I completely left the shows behind.  If you know the movie & actually liked it keep reading.  Otherwise   STOP READING HERE .  The first movie, they then showed a dead man who had been skinned from the chest up.  I realized the talking man was wearing the dead man's skin.  I changed the channel immediately, but made the mistake of turning Sci-Fi & "Mad, Mad, House" where the vampire was going to make some people drink blood.    Now here's your  LAST CHANCE  to turn away.    The Dream: (Really it's disgusting, nauseating, it involves cannibalism so stop here)  I dreamed I was on a bus or train going on a trip.  I was sitting on a small bed watching a small television & eating a sandwich.  Possibly honeybaked ham & cheese.  Anyway, the TV program showed a guy mutilating himself.  I wanted to change the channel, but I noticed other people watching it, so I just turned away until that part was over with.  Suddenly it was no longer a TV, but a window, and the man's severed head was on a large stick.  The head looked into the window at me & spoke, he'd said something about not being able to die & he could just sew his own head back onto his body.  Then the trip was over, I'd gotten off whatever vehicle it was.  Then I was walking thru woods with about 3 or 4 other people.  We were on a path.  We came across dozens of garbage bags full of something, & nearby was a mattress and a makeshift camp.  There was a terrible smell.  We looked inside a couple bags which held body remains & clothing.  We kept walking & eventually came across more of the same.  We had heard that people were disappearing.  We figured out this same man was kidnapping people & eating them, but mostly their skin.  We kept walking, & finally came out of the woods.  All of a sudden we were inside the house where I really grew up & again, there was a really horrible stench of decomposition.  The man was sitting on the couch in the living room munching on the fingers of his own left hand.  He'd eaten them down to his bones.  He felt no pain & he could regenerate so it didn't matter.  One of the girls I'd journied with turned away & threw up.  We then got out of the house fast.  We started back thru the woods, but I told the others we had to kill this guy or he would keep doing it.  We were whispering as softly as we could.  The others told me there was nothing we could do bc the guy couldn't die.  He would just keep regenerating.  I kept telling them there must be someway, we couldn't let it go on.  I suggested maybe shooting him in the heart.  Everyone had stopped walking, they knew I was right, we had to do something.  Then I started thinking what if this guy was following us.  I started looking around.  That's when I woke up.  Time to go out & clear my head.  And fill it with history & psychological disorders.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This month is officially half over.  My lockdown begins.  Four exams next week.  I got a spot of good news tonite.  Next week's Juvenile Justice class final is open book.  The midterm was as well, & although I got a couple wrong, I got full credit for an extra credit essay, so I still got more points than I needed overall.    Tired now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished my taxes.  I actually had done the Federal about a month ago using H&R Block's computer software program, I just never printed it or anything.  The State taxes I did myself this morning, but it only took a few minutes.  Not much changed since the year before.  Now I just have to drag my sorry butt out to the post office to mail 'em.  Have to go out anyway for class, but normally that wouldn't be until later after most post offices close.  There's a 24-hour post office not too far away in Redford, but I'm not about to risk standing in some long line bc I was too lazy otherwise.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm finally starting to wind down.  Just have one more task to finish.  Taxes. No I haven't finished all that yet.  Been so busy.  I got my 2 Psych papers done.  Actually, an hour before class (right when I was supposed to be leaving for school).  I just put an ending on the second paper, grabbed my things & took off.  I got there with 15 minutes to spare.  Actually, I have one more paper for ASL class, but I kinda did it over the weekend to hand in this past Monday, but I decided to work on it some more.  One more class tomorrow, then I go into isolation for studying for all the exams next week.  Blech.  I do still have to get caught up on my current events journal & hand that in Tuesday, so I'll work on it Friday.     I haven't been sleeping much, so I'm real drowsy now.  Have been all day.  Glad I could record today's lecture on tape bc I missed some of it, kept thinking of how tired I am.  I also kept getting distracted by other people not wanting to be in class.  Meh.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got to class yesterday & once again there were the 3 video recorders & I hadn't bothered to bring my videotape.  The original class syllabus said we were supposed to have another quiz, but I knew there were more scheduled events presentations.  I asked everyone there who agreed that it was probably just another mistake.  Which it was.  Afterward, the instructor told us that for our final next week, she's going to sign 2 stories, each 1 twice & we have to translate them.  But she didn't say how long the stories would be.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got my errand done yesterday.  I was starting to get a headache when I left & it was starting to get worse when I got home, so I laid down on the couch & fell asleep for about an hour.  When I woke up it had gotten much worse.  The whole right side of my head hurt real bad, so I took extra strength Excederin.  It's the only thing that works.  I've tried everything else on the market for the pain to no avail.  I fell asleep for another hour.  It had mostly gone away, so I got up & worked on my Psych report.  Then my teeth started hurting.  At first I thought it was bc I didn't wear my bite guard while I napped (I clench so hard, I managed to crack 1 bite guard & some mornings I have to snap my jaw back to where it's supposed to be, ouch).  Anyhoo, I finally realized it's my sinuses acting up again.  That hasn't happened for several months, but now that it's getting warm again... So I took a 12 hour Sudafed.  Too late.  The pain just kept getting worse.  I went to bed, but I didn't sleep much bc I could feel my right eardrum & middle ear & the sinuses on that side burning like crazy.   At 7:00 this morning it felt like my eardrum was going to burst & my eyeball explode out of it's socket.  How I hate that. I finally took more aspirin & wrapped an ice pack around that side of my head & fell asleep for 4 hours.  Then I got up & took another Sudafed.  Feel better now, but the lack of sleep has me feeling crappy, but I still have to get these reports done.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing terribly interesting to post really.  I've (sort of) been working on 1 of my Psych papers.  This one is on stress & what the body goes thru & how damaging it can ultimately be on the body when it becomes constant.  I personally am not under too much stress, really.  I would be if I had to work while trying to juggle the classes I currently have.  It's strange how things sometimes work out.  Being given the opportunity to be laid off was a blessing & I didn't know at the time how much of 1 it would be.  For at least the last year or so I'd been able to manage 4 classes & work with no problem.  With the exception of ASL class, I still have basic classes, but this semester they still require alot.  Even tho I am quickly running out of extra cash & now have to stick to a very tight budget, but I'm not even thinking of that too much.  Sometime today I intend to go out & get a newspaper (The Detroit News & Free Press) & a 2-litre Diet Coke (with caffeine-gotta have that caffeine).   Anyhoo, back to the stress thing.  Researchers are working on a drug that will suppress type 1 CRH suppressors-the chemical released in the body when under stress & that they believe is responsible for eventually damaging the organs when it's in the body for too long.  Yep, someday we'll be in Aldous Huxley's Brave New World, where you can take a pill every day & live a drug-induced, happy, carefree life.  (Some people are already there, more power to 'em I s'pose).  http://www.huxley.net/  (sorry, you'll have to copy it into you're url bc I don't know how create the link here & don't care to figure it out just now).  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My sister tried talking me into going up north this weekend, but I just simply didn't feel like it.  I'm back to feeling tired alot again.  Maybe bc I have on my mind all the things I have to get done in the next couple days.  I haven't even finished my taxes yet.  Add it to the list.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So much to do, no desire to do it.  I did however, change my 2-way pager number this morning.  I had to. Was still getting random pages.  2 every morning.  I'd turn it off at night, & turn it back on in the morning, but there's no telling how long this is going to go on.  I asked her to take my pager address out of her computer address book.  I don't know if she did, or if that even matters anymore.  Anyhoo, I still have several things to do, so here I go.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing overly exciting happened today.  I don't have a class tomorrow bc of Easter break, so I can say 2 more weeks left of the semester.  I have 2 papers due next Wednesday.  I have another paper due on a Monday, but I don't know if it's next Monday, or the last Monday of the semester.  The instructor's syllabus had an extra week on it.  She didn't say anything about the paper this past Monday, but on the syllabus, she wanted it handed in the week before finals, which technically is next week.  I'll decide in the next couple days what to do about that.  I did decide to sign up for a CJ class for Spring/Summer.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got done most of what I had to.  I got my report done which consisted of printing out the correspondence I'd written to Governor Granholm telling her how filing for unemployment sucks when you tell the truth & admit your going to school.  I never got a response which was disappointing, but not surprising.  Which is also what I wrote for my report.  I'm sure I'm getting points off for not getting a response, but there's only such much a mere Michigan resident (I) can do.  I didn't get all the current events into my "journal", but I got some articles to discuss.  I'll put them in soon, as I'm actually falling behind on that.  The quiz, on the other hand, didn't go so well.  I think I didn't even give the answer I was supposed to.  Obviously, I didn't read the material as closely as I should have.  But today the instructor said that including last week's quiz, we are now only going for extra credit points.  Granted, I could use all the extra points I can get, but there's still one more quiz next week.  In a sense, last week's canceled out the one 0 pointer I got earlier in the semester.  At least we got out of class early tonight.  I'm glad I'm not working now.  Especially during the lost hour change.  The last few days I'd had a constant feeling like I needed more sleep, but haven't had time for a nap.  Today, when I got up, I felt well rested.  Tonight I'm going to bed right after Law & Order.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I gave my ASL presentation tonite, & boy did I suck at it.  I hate giving presentations in any class.  It was about the space shuttle Challenger that exploded after liftoff in 1986.  After I got to school I realized there was more I should have included, but it was way too late.  I also somehow didn't catch that last week the instructor had said the presentation had to be ten minutes.  I only knew that the initial things I showed her, she had said was only a few minutes worth, but I had told her I planned to get more info.  I do know, tonite's presentation wasn't worth 10 minutes.  I also had more trouble than I thought I would with technical stuff.  Also, I was so nervous I started fingerspelling dates & names wrong & would have to keep starting over.  I think I prefer videotaping?  Actually I prefer neither.  *sigh*  It's over & done with.  Time to move on.    For tomorrow night, I have to write a paper on a correspondence I'd sent to Governor Granholm 2 months back that I never got a reply to (no surprise), make notes for a quiz, & write brief summaries for some current events.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I almost forgot to call MARVIN today.  That stands for Michigan's Automated Responce Voice Interactive Network.  That's Michigan's system for getting one's unemployment checks.  The day & time one calls is based on the last 2 digits of one's social security number.  There's only a 1 hour block one can call at the the day & time designated.  The calls are made every other week.  Then there are some automated questions one answers & the answers are given by pressing the #1 for yes & #9 for no.  I remembered within the last 15 mins, & then it took me a few minutes to remember what I'd done with the booklet.  Anyway, I got my call in with a few minutes to spare.  Otherwise one can call any time that Thursday or Friday.   Yesterday I remembered I'd have to make the call, but this morning, I'd gotten caught up in something else.    Someone's computer is infected with a worm.  She was relying on the virus scan program to find it & get rid of it, except, she says every time she runs it, it says no viruses are found.  From the info I'm getting, some worms somehow alter virus programs on the victim's computer.  I've tried telling her that.  Now she thinks it could be a version of the Netsky virus.  My 2-way pager keeps getting random emails when the suspect computer is started up.  If it happens again tomorrow morning, I just may get my pager # changed and tell her to NOT put it in her computer address book.    Another reason I almost forgot about MARVIN is, this morning, I noticed someone else moving out of the apartment complex.  Same building, one entrance over.  Last week, I saw other people moving some furniture into an apartment right across the sidewalk, but, strangely, I couldn't tell which apartment. It wasn't much furniture.  The same 3 still look empty.  I wonder if one of them will be for show.  Which doesn't make much sense considering there are probably empty apts. much closer to the manager's office.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Every single year at this time, I forget to change my clock.  I don't know why I have trouble remembering that, I always remember to change them in October before I go to bed that night.  I've been up for a couple hours, and finally crawled to my computer and it had the message that it readjusted the clock.  That was my reminder.  I think it was the last couple years or so too.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to Deaf coffee hour in Ann Arbor again this month.  There were people there who went/are going to Madonna University (where I'm going to school).  One girl was in a couple previous classes the same time as I, and someone else who is now enrolled in the first Sign Language Studies class, which isn't actually a sign class, but more a history of sign language class.  She still signed very well.  She actually commutes from Saline, where she lives, to Livonia for the class.  That's a long drive.   Speaking of ASL class, I really should be working on the assignment due Monday night.  I still have to gather the info, then translate it into ASL, then practice it.  Time is just going by way too fast. It also occured to me this morning that the stores where I work are back to being open 6 days a week.  Even tho everyone still works 5 days.  They just have a prechosen day off, possible for another month or 2.  Then everyone works 6 days.  I'm not really looking forward to going back to work.  I still feel tired alot.  Maybe b.c. frequently I forget to take my iron?    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Only a little over a month left of unemployment, they didn't know when exactly they'll need me to come back.  The countdown begins.  It's actually kind of a bummer.  Also there's only 3 weeks left until the end of the school semester, which is cool, but there's so much to do.  I've been trying to stick to a more normal sleep schedule.  But it takes me forever between the time I wake up & the time I can "join the living."  I had to do laundry yesterday, but I'd completely forgotten I was almost out of fabric softener.  I use liquid Downy in the Downy balls, as the machines are in the basement & I'm on the second floor.  I had enough for 1 ball, 1/2 the other.  I had to fill it with some water.  I've been doing it in the afternoons well before I have to leave for school.  And I was not yet "among the living" enough to want to make a quick dash to the store.  I also didn't want to wait another day to do the wash.  Going back to work is going to be brutal.  Financially, I'm ready to go back, but that's because I had the opportunity to pay off a debt that's been haunting me for several years & the deadline was the end of March.  I just hope they hold to their end of the bargain & call it received in time & paid off.  I need to run errands today, but I'm not ready to go out yet.  Must*get*motivated....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got a letter in the mail from Secretary of State.  Generated by the most recent speeding ticket I got last month.  It says there are 6,922,000 drivers in Michigan who have 0-3 points on their records, which is 93% of drivers.  9 out of 10 are drivers without crashes.  There are 412,000 drivers or 6% have 4-7 points (me included, I have 4) of which 6 out of 10 are without crashes.  107,000, 1% of drivers, have 8 or more points, & 5 out of 10 are drivers without crashes.  There are a total of 7,441,000 drivers in Michigan.  I really wanted to know this.  I was starting to lose sleep wondering about it. Ok, no I wasn't.  But they were kind enough to remind me when I got a ticket before last month.  In case you're wondering, it was in June of 2002.  For speeding.  I was late for work.  Ok, I'm a speed demon.  I'm beginning to learn to slow down, even before the SoS's gentle reminder.  They also wanted me to know how important wearing my seatbelt is.  I know.  There were 10 true/false questions on the "Juvenile Justice" quiz & I got 1 wrong.  I'm not the only one who got that 1 wrong either.  It was in a video we watched in the last couple weeks, I don't even remember which video bc we've seen a few.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It rained some this morning, but then it cleared up for the most part & was nice & warm pretty much all afternoon.  I went to the park & walked 2 miles.  Then I flopped on the grass & laid there.  'Cept I always forget to bring a towel or blanket, so the grass is always itchy/tickly/prickly.  There were some clouds tho, & I finally left when a big one covered the sun & the wind got chilly.  I really don't want to go back to work tomorrow  urlLink   .  I know, I haven't been back very long, & really, it isn't  that  bad...yet.  It's just the getting up in the morning thing, & the occasional rude, obnoxious customers, who seem to be increasing in number every year.  Anyhoo, I rented the  Gothika  DVD.  I thought the movie was pretty good.  A supernatural murder mystery.  I was kinda disappointed that there were no good extras such as deleted scenes.  I'm not sure I believe she could slip into the pool without disturbing the water like that, but, then I'm not an expert.  I'd try it at the pool here at the complex, 'cept the water is too cold.  I have to jump in.  Otherwise I liked the movie.  & it didn't even give me nightmares, which I almost expected.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...and, as usual, spent alot more money than I intended.  I was only going there for a few things, but naturally, as I walked around I saw stuff I knew I already intended to buy.  Like another Brita water pitcher; I bought the cheapest 1 they had, & I had a $3 off coupon.  I have 1 already, but I make lots of sun tea and drink lots of water & those pitchers are kinda small.  Plus on the off chance we have another blackout like the one last year, I'm more prepared now.  I also realized I needed more filters b/c the last 1 in the pitcher I already have is going to need replacing soon. Those suckers are expensive.     I also found the  urlLink Biosilk Silk Therapy  leave in conditioner I really like.  My hair is so dry & brittle it falls out too easily.  I've tried most everything else, but this is about the only stuff that leaves my hair silky soft & keeps the curls.  It smells really good too.  But it too is expensive, & I ran out of the stuff awhile ago, but hadn't been able to afford it.  I couldn't really afford it now, but it was there & my hair is like straw now, I couldn't resist.  Going in I figured I'd spend about $50 - 60.  I walked out having spent $91.     While I was in Target, I heard a real loud rumble of thunder.  I was contemplating whether or not to buy something.  Some guy near me commenting on the thunder. Said something like "here it comes."  I said that I'd just been wondering if it begun raining yet.  I'd been in the store about an hour & a half or so already, & I had actually wondered if it had begun raining yet.  When I got to the checkout, I saw that yep, it was raining.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...because you pay the price.  I'd been procrastinating about calling around to price my prescription med.  I had an idea the pharmacy may have to order it, 'cept I didn't think about it being so close to Memorial Day weekend.  Until today.  I called 3 places--1 of them  not  being CVS.   Click  urlLink here  for that.  It figures, the one that has it in stock is the highest priced--only by $9.00, tho.  One of them that didn't have it, the lowest priced place, he told me he couldn't order it til Tuesday.  There was no telling how long it would take to get there, but I knew by then I'd be completely out of what I have.  It had also occured to me that I'd left the script on the end table next to the door at home, & I was at work.  And the pharmacy is closer to work.  I had to get to the bank first, then home, then backtrack to the pharmacy.  No problems getting the script, thank goodness.  Now 3 days off!!! Woo hoo!!   urlLink     Me:  urlLink     tomorrow, anyway, cuz it's supposed to rain Sunday & Monday, but oh well
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...but I'm still gonna mention how much I hate mornings...again  urlLink   .  I don't have a very bad commute--I live only about 7 or 8 miles from work.  I don't have to get on any freeways.  It's still frustrating.  Rule of thumb: if your going to pull out of your apartment complex right in front of someone (me) forcing me to slam on my brakes, you should think twice when you have a license plate that's easy to remember, such as  1WOODY3 .  What you don't realize is that I live in the complex right next to you.  I could creep over & find your car and...  But I really don't feel like wasting my time.  Suffice it to say you're a  urlLink   .  Some roadrager will get you eventually.    Anyhoo, 1 more day to go b/4 a 3-day weekend.  WooHoo!!!  After that is a 6 day work week every week.  Suck.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Way too tired to blog. I have a 3 day weekend coming up.  I'll play catch-up then.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...We were excessively busy today.  By the time I got home, my feet & back hurt so bad I had to lay down on the couch.  I got up about a half hour later & could hardly walk.  My lower back, hips, & feet hurt real bad.  I am ssooo tired I need a nap urlLink   .  I'd forgotten to set my alarm clock when I went to bed last night, but fortunately I just happened to wake up 20 minutes b/4 I had to get up.  I looked at my clock & knew the radio should have gone on 10 minutes earlier.  That's when I realized I'd forgotten to turn it on.  I set it to come on in another 10 mins & rolled over & dozed until it did.    Before I woke up I was having a strange dream that I was living in the 1800s & I had a sister (who was not either of mine in real life) who had discovered her long lost daughter who had been kidnapped as an infant about 10 years earlier was living with an older couple in the same town.  The sister had gotten a complete medical check up for the girl by the local doctor & it turned out the people were physically & sexually abusing her.  She came back to live with us.  We were all preparing supper, the sister was in the kitchen, me, the girl & Orlando Bloom were setting the table.  I think he was somehow related.  He was telling her she'd won a scholarship to a good school, except she would have to travel away.  She was very happy.  She wanted to go to a good school to learn.  I told them both not to say anything to the sister right away; she would not allow the girl to go b/c she had just found her & wouldn't be willing to give her up very easily.  I told them to let me handle it.  Then he started making passes at me.  I told him to cool it b/c I thought we were related & he was way too young for me anyway.  He said he didn't care, he was in love with me.  That's when I woke up.  I have no idea why he was even in my dream.  I haven't seen any movies recently with him in it.  I have the first 2  The Lord of the Rings  and  Pirates of the Carribean  on DVD, but I haven't watched any of them in several months.   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally got back to the park today & walked 3 miles.  I wore my Birkenstock sandals this time, & now have blisters on the top of my feet & on the bottom of my left big toe  urlLink   . Ouch.  I get my first working person paycheck on Wednesday, so I can more actively start looking for a good, yet cheap pair of shoes.  I hope, b/c usually those 2 don't go together.  Halfway thru the day my feet hurt alot.  Mostly my heels.  Suggestions anyone?    Anyhoo, it's raining...again.  And I so do not want to go back to work tomorrow.  But I have to.  Time to shower & go to bed.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thank God it's Saturday.  Who cares about whether or not it's a Friday.  I have to work Saturdays.  I made it through my first week back to work.  Today was sort of an easy day.  There was another thunderstorm early this morning.  I woke up for a second, b/c as usual someone's car alarm went off urlLink   . I fell back to sleep, then ended up oversleeping 15 minutes.  And my sinuses & for that matter, my head, was stuffed up.  I still managed to make it to work on time, tho.  Not sure how.  In a couple weeks I'll be working longer hours consistantly.  Not looking forward to it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had severe thunderboomers last night.  urlLink    It didn't bother me too much except the thunder was close by & naturally following ever crack of thunder was the random car alarm going off.  None of them mine.  I think some people were ready, b/c only one went off for more than a few seconds.  This afternoon the sky got black, then it lightened just enough to look green.  Then we had a severe hail storm for a couple minutes.    I loathe mornings.   urlLink    That's one reason I took the lay-off.  I'd been losing the struggle of getting up every morning.  Now that I'm back to work, nothing about that has changed.  Sometime during last nights thunderstorm, it got quite cold.  I'd left my bedroom doorwall open slightly b/c it felt good.  This morning it made me so  not  want to get out of bed.    urlLink    After stumbling around trying desperately to rush to get ready & not be late, I had to give up--on the not being late part.  I was 10 minutes late getting to work.  I'd been doing that consistantly b/4 my lay-off.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's 76 degrees (F) out & the humidity is 85%.  I should have turned the air conditioner on earlier, but nnoooo.  I just turned on a fan figuring it would cool off eventually.  I feel crappy.  Fortunately, I only worked until noon again today.  That's probably only going to last another week, bummer.  There is also Memorial Day weekend.    Anyhoo, I wanted to go to the park & sit & study for a quiz I have next Wednesday, but I had to get laundry done & I didn't get started on it til kinda late.  I have to go into the basement to do it.  There's 2 washers & 2 dryers, & I only had 2 loads to do.  Living in an apartment & having to pay $1.00 in quarters for each machine, I only separate my stuff into darks & whites/lights.  You do what you gotta do.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was an easier day at work.  Unfortunately, I got a bit of bad news.  I asked when the insurance would take effect.  I was told not for a few months.  This is bad.  I need to have a prescription filled next week.  I would have had it filled if it weren't for the idiotic people at CVS.  I'd been having trouble with them, & I knew I was making a mistake taking my prescription there back in January.  It was the day before my insurance ran out.  The pharmacist told me they didn't have any in stock.  They'd have to order it, except they wouldn't until Monday.  I told him my insurance would run out the next day so I asked if he could call around to other CVS stores.  He asked me what my co-pays were & I told him.  The cheapest was generics for $10.00.  The moron looks in his computer & said it didn't matter, because my prescription would only cost $9+ even without it.  So I figured no problem.  Then they call me Monday to ask if I have other insurance.  I told whoever, no, & what I was told that Thursday night.  He told me he didn't know who told me that because it wasn't true.  The prescription cost over $100.  I repeated that cost was why I'd asked him to call around to see if another store had it in stock b/4 my insurance ran out.  The guy on the phone just said I was given wrong information.  The end.  I told him I wished I'd known before.  So he tells me if I want the prescription paper back, I'm welcome to come & get it.  Gee thanks.  That infuriates me. What I've had is what the doctor gave me as a sample which runs out this week.   Sure enough--huge mistake going to CVS.  Their pharmacy is the worst.  In the past, it would take no less than 10 hours to get a prescription filled no matter what it was.  Everytime I went, there would be at least half a dozen angry people being told their scripts weren't ready yet.  Afterwards I heard on the news CVS charges over 150% above original cost for scripts anyway.  I heard Costco is one of the cheapest, but it appears I have to call around anyway. The problem is coming up with the money for it.  *sigh* 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was very busy today at the Livonia store.  My job requires me to work 8 hours on my feet each day.  Throw in another half hour at some point for lunch--that's my whole day.  I busted my butt again today.  There was ssooo much to do, I still didn't get it all done.  When I got home, I had to lay on the couch for a while b/4 my legs & feet quit hurting.  My back didn't feel that great either.  But after my shower I felt better, so I tried adding my profile to my original blog template & it just wouldn't work no matter what.  So I decided to just change the whole template.  I like this one for now.  Kinda girly-girl, but, what the hey.  I desperately need sleep, but I have to finish winding down.  My mornings aren't going well, but they hadn't for quite some time before my lay-off.  Fortunately, I only work 4 hours tomorrow, b/c I just remembered I never finished my homework for tomorrow night's class.  Big oops.  I copied & pasted my sidebar add-ons into the notepad, so I'll add those when I have time.  And tweak the rest of my page.  In the meantime my brain is about to crash, so....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went back to work today.  Along with 2 of the other 3 coworkers who were laid-off.    Thus ends a 4-month "adventure."  As broke as I'm getting, I'm still sorry to leave behind the "life of leisure." [I searched for jobs the whole time, I swear.] One of the guys went out on the road with the others in the morning.  The other stayed back.  2 hours into work, he comes over to where I am & looks at the clock & shakes his head.  We both laughed & he said, "Man, it feels like I've been here aaalllll day."  I said "Yeah right there with you, I was thinking the same thing."  He said, "I'll bet you normally I'd still be asleep."  I said, "I know for a fact I'd still be asleep."  We compared notes on what TV programs we watched.  Turns out we both pretty much saw quite a few of the same programs.  Not  that  surprising, really.   I was busy all day today.  Tomorrow I work at the Livonia store.  I already know I'm going to be busy all day again.  Meh, it's better than being bored.  I hope I stay awake long enough to catch "CSI: Miami in New York".  I'm already yawning like crazy.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, I had to get cat food.  I also wanted to get a  Detroit News and Free Press , which costs $1.35.  I got into my car & started out to a nearby  7-Eleven  for that.  When I started my car, the  low fuel  light came on.  Bummer.  So after getting the newspaper, I went to the bank & got some I couldn't really spare.  But I had little choice.  Then I went to a gas station.  I got $20 worth @ $2.01/gal.  The cheapest I'd seen of non-ethanol gas.  The ethanol kind burns too fast.  Anyhoo, that got me 3/4 of a tank.  Then I went to the grocery store b/c I needed some other things besides the cat food. I took a bag full of dimes, nickels, & pennies to put in a  urlLink coinstar .  I get there & someone else is using it.  Then suddenly it quits working.  She's got about half her change in there.  After some screen changes & stuff, the computer reboots & the Windows NT startup screen shows.  Then it's a "machine not available" screen.  Then an 800 number comes up on the screen.  So the woman whips out her cell phone & calls it.  She's told a store manager will have to service it.  She didn't get a receipt for the change she'd put in, so she can't go anywhere.  So I decided to at least begin my shopping.  I got most of what I needed, but I started to panic b/c I only had $20 left & I didn't want to spend it all.  I kept wandering back to the machine, but the woman is still waiting.  I was standing near the manager's office & employee counter, when I heard an employee mention about the machine to another.  Then 1 got on the intercom & paged the manager to the machine.  So I look around for more stuff.  I figured if the machine doesn't get fixed I'd have to put stuff back.  About 5 minutes later I wander over & still the woman is by herself.  I went back to the counter & asked if there was someone who could help with the machine.  I told them the woman had been standing there for quite sometime & was probably getting impatient.  I heard 1 more page for the manager & sure enough someone came & fixed the machine.  Turned out a couple sticker things had gotten caught in the coin sorter.  *Whew*  Finally I got to put my coins in.  It was my first time.  Not too difficult.  I had just $29+ worth of coins, but after their "processing fee" (which the screens warns you about before you decide to continue) I ended with $27+.  Still not bad. I had roughly $25 worth of stuff.  I have more change at home but much of it is rolled pennies I'll someday take to the bank.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love finding money I didn't know I had.  Who doesn't.  I went to the  Wizard of Oz  at Lahser High School in Bloomfield Hills tonite.  The whole thing was done in American Sign Language by the students, with 3 people offstage doing the voice interpretations.  I think it probably would have been better w/o the voices, but it was mostly for the benefit of hearing people who didn't understand sign language.  I enjoyed it very much.  They'd been working on it since February, and they did quite well.  I knew Karen would be there, & sure enough I found her shortly before the play started so I sat with her.  I also saw Fox News (my local channel 2) there.  I rushed home afterward & caught it on the 10:00 PM news.  Anyhoo, while I was getting dressed, I found a $5 bill in my pants pocket.  Pretty cool seein' as admission was $5 (which I'd already known) & I had pretty much just that much in my wallet already.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There's just the rest of today and then tomorrow left of my extended vacation.  I am ssoooo not looking forward to going back to work.  Getting up several hours earlier than I have been is going to be a killer.  It takes me a full hour to get rid of the grogginess every morning.  I learned in Psych class that it has to do with the chemical that's released when we first fall asleep.  In most people, the chemical is gone by the time they wake up.  It is all going to suk.  On the not so bad side, I'll still get Wednesday & Thursday afternoon off next week & probably the week after that.  But in June I'll be working 6 days.  But this should make the transition easier.  Plus I've been so broke lately.  I need to buy cat food & a couple other things, but then I won't have enough money to pay my car/renter's insurance.  That's due on Monday, but I have a 5-day grace period & unless I discover on Monday my unemployment ran out, I'll get my check Wednesday.  Otherwise, I have no idea what I'm gonna do.  I'm done thinking about for now.  Later tonight I plan to go to a play given by Deaf & Hard-of-Hearing High School students in Bloomfield Hills.  It's The Wizard of Oz.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I ended up not getting out til much later & maintenence never showed up.   But I had to mail Uncle Kenny's birthday card.  So I walked the approximately half mile to the post office.  Once there, I discover that mail pick-up from that box wouldn't be until 5:00 on tomorrow.  Bummer, his birthday is Sunday, so obviously his card will be late.  Then I walked around the track at Garden City park right next to the post office.  Seems to me I heard that once around is a mile or something.  I didn't take my GPSr with me.  This time I wore a pair of Keds I've had.  This time I ended up making the blister on the back of my right heel worse & got one on my left heel.  I started out sometime after a brief rainshower, & it was threatening to rain again.  It started raining just as I got back to the complex.  I probably would have been at my apartment, but I'd stopped a couple times to re-adjust my shoes--to no avail.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm going back to work Monday.  I ended up sitting at home most of yesterday waiting to see if maintenance would show up.  Well, actually I didn't call them until the afternoon, so I didn't really expect them to show.  I asked for a new air conditioner, but the manager said she didn't have them in yet, so I'm wondering if they are just going to wait to fix everything.  I was hoping they would at least have gotten the other stuff done before I have to go back, and I don't want to spend my last free days just sitting here waiting for them.  The air conditioner I have has been here since I moved in 10 years ago.  It still works, but only on high & the thermostat no longer works.  It was miserably humid yesterday which sucked.  It's not so bad today.   I'd like to go to the park & walk a couple miles.  Granted the last couple times ended up being a bit painful.  First I wore my only daily old, ratty sneakers & ended up with a blister on the back of my right heal.  I can't afford a new pair right now.  So I went again Wednesday & wore my aerobic shoes.  Those shoes I don't wear very often, they are narrower at the toes and I ended up with blisters where two of my toes rubbed together and I aggravated the one on the back of my heal.  Three blisters on the same foot, & I'd forgotten to take bandages with me.  I still managed to get in 2 miles each time tho.  Go me.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm trying out Blogger's new comment template, so here goes.....  My apologies to all who have left me comments in the past.  I was using Haloscan's tag, but I had to delete the whole thing from my template in order to use Blogger's.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got  the call  tonite.  I may be going back to work on Monday.  One of my laid-off coworkers had called in to say his benefits ran out.  I won't know about mine until Monday b/c that's when I make my call to MARVIN.  This means I have less than a week to lose lots of weight, and get my apartment in complete order so I can call to have maintenance come & fix a bunch of stuff.  I knew it would all come to a halt soon.  At least I got a good advanced heads up. I know, I've had plenty of time to get the place straightened out, but I've been incredibly lazy.  I just could never get the energy to do what needs to be done.  It's not real bad.  If I had lots more closet space to put all these boxes of stuff in...but I don't.  Even the corners are taken up.  But that's what I get for living in an apartment.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't felt like blogging lately.  Too tired.  Anyhoo, I've gotten stuff done.  I got my check Wednesday just in time to make it to the bank before they closed.  I dropped my rent check off.  The manager asked if I'm back to work yet, I told her no, & I told her why I had to wait to pay the rent.  She told me I didn't have to worry about it, bless her sweet heart.  Yesterday I went to Wal-Mart & got most of the stuff I needed.  As usual I neglected to make out a list, so I only remembered what I'd forgotten long after I got home.  At least it's all stuff I don't need right away anyway.  Today I went to the fruit/veggie market & got lettuce, 3 large tomatoes & 5 big Golden Delicious apples (which all cost under $5.00), then went to the school, dropped off some papers at the financial aid desk, bought the textbook I should have had Wednesday night, then went to visit a couple co-workers.  Then I came home & fell asleep for a couple hours.  I'm still tired, but I figured I'd get this blog entry done.  I still have to get the rest of my bills paid.  Probably tomorrow for that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just posted to my blog an hour ago, but it didn't show up.  Unfortunately, I just don't feel like rewriting the whole thing.  That makes me mad, I don't know where it went.  Here's the really condensed version.  I'm running out of things but can't afford to buy them b/c I still don't have my check.  If it comes in the mail tomorrow it won't be til late afternoon, & if it doesn't, I'm screwed & will have to find someone to lend me some $$ tomorrow, or I will have to ask the manager if she'll wait another day for the rent w/o charging me an extra $25.    There was more, but the heck with it.   A few minutes later         I found it posted under April 30.  I have no idea why.  But I'll try this again, so here it is:    I hate being broke   Ok, I'm not exactly broke, I just don't have quite enough money to pay my rent. I pray my check comes tomorrow b/c that's the last day of the grace period. Unfortunately, the mail doesn't usually make it until anytime past 3:00. If my check doesn't arrive tomorrow, I'll have to scramble to try & bum some money from someone until it does which I hate doing, or try begging the manager to give me 1 more day. I've been here 10 years & never did it before so maybe I have a chance. It's my fault for paying for that class when I realized I would be cutting it too close. Good thing I have enough food, it's just other things I'm pretty much out of.   Geoffery Fieger has his own imitation contest copying Donald Trump's, called  The Intern. He's making them do stupid things. I don't mean to watch it, it just happens to be on the channel's news I happen to be watching. I didn't even watch Trump's program. First Fieger made them go thru an abstacle course. After they completed it, he told them they didn't strategize their way through enough. Then he made them sell Calgary Flames memorabilia--around Detroit. I guess 1 or 2 of them succeeded, which is saying alot. One of them suggested buying the stuff so they could have fun destroying it. (In case you don't see any big deal, Red Wings fans are very loyal & spend pretty much the most money on Wings memorabilia than any other team). And, yes, I know the Wings lost last night & are officially out of the running for the Cup. I guarantee everyone is well wishing Stevie a speedy recovery, but now he can relax & mend at his own pace.   I also saw on the news that there is a gas station in Pittsfield that had a computer glitch. People started using their driver licenses in order to turn on the pump. They thought they were getting free gas. They didn't stop & think that the black strip on the back of our licenses holds some kind of readable info. Such as...oh, I don't know...our license #, which can maybe be traced back to one's name & address perhaps? It turned out it was mostly college students--go figure. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Spring/Summer semester has started.  The class I enrolled in- Criminal Justice Organization & Administration -starts Wednesday night.  The instructor is also one of the department advisors, so I plan to set up an appointment with him to find out what GE classes I still need to take.  Not including the class I'm now signed up for, I will need 6 more CJ classes.    I got word that I'll be going back to work soon, possibly in the next week or 2.  I'm not ready.  There's so many things I want to do yet.  Although alot of them, I just got too lazy & didn't bother to do.  My bad.  I had a headache & my sinuses hurt Saturday & today.  Yesterday, was cold & rainy & nap day.  Also some stuff I was supposed to do today involves spending money, & I want to wait until I get my check, which should be about Wednesday.  Hopefully, b/c 1 thing is I have to get the book for class.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm very tired and my back hurts.  Lots of heavy lifting & bending.  Time for bed.    urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On the way home from work.  I was on Cherry Hill traveling west approaching Middle Belt.  I was still about a 1/4 mile away in the right traveling lane, when I saw a car pull from a parking lot on the south side of Cherry Hill into the same lane as me, but he was way up ahead.  East & West bound cars were sitting at the red light.  Suddenly the car started swerving way out of control.  It pulled up onto the curb & onto the grass, clipped the truck it was trying to pull behind, & flew into the gas station right on the corner, still swerving all over the place.  It just missed hitting some gas pumps &, thank goodness, there were no cars on 1 side of the pumps, or they would have gotten hit.  He finally managed to stop his car & I saw him jump out like he was trying to get away from the car.  It was an older model, I figure from the way the car was jerking the accelerator must have gotten stuck & the brakes wouldn't stop the car properly, & the guy had freaked (as I would have).  The truck he hit was an older model too.  The bumper of 1 of the vehicles had come clean off.  Admittedly, I continued on my way home.  I figured they didn't need me taking up space.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      C.'s truck had a wrong tent on it, so I had to take the correct one out.  My boss printed out a map for me.  My destination was in Detroit near Evergreen between 6 & 7 Mile Roads.  I get to the street, but there are no houses facing the street I was on.   urlLink   ?!?  The addresses were not even close to what I was looking for.  Fortunately, I'd remembered to borrow TC's cellphone (I don't have one b/c I don't talk on any phone nearly enough to justify paying the high price of monthly service).  I was about to call back to work when C. called me & asked where I was.  I told him & that's when he told me I was about a 1 & 1/2 miles north of where he was waiting.  I found my way to the right house, & once I got back to work E. checked the program on a different computer, & that 1 was correct.  The map I got was from a software program loaded on the computer b/c it isn't hooked up to the internet.  It's strictly for everyone to print maps.  And face the possibility of of being where they don't intend to be.    A few hours later I had to run to the store for more cases of  urlLink sterno  b/c we were fast running out & had people buying it like crazy with the chafing dishes they were renting.  As soon as I drove into the parking lot, I saw S. loading more chafers into someone's car & knew he was waiting for me to get back.  Whew.    Now I'm tired & really need a nap.  7 more hours of it all tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I figured I'd stop by the bank on the way to work this morning & deposit some money in my account.  I went to the branch 3 miles from the Livonia store.  Wouldn't you know it, the ATM was offline.  I couldn't go until later in the day.  Once I got there & deposited some money, I discovered there was still enough, but I had no clue how.  So I had to wait until after I got home from school to try to figure it out.  I finally registered to get the info online.  Lo & behold, my state income tax refund saved the day.     urlLink      Whew.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I work in Livonia tomorrow.  And it's possible I have a bunch of checks bouncing all over the U.S.  Long story I'm too tired & worried about to go into now.  Suffice it to say, I didn't pay attention like I should have.  I'll have to go the bank ATM b/4 work & deposit money in the morning.  I'll find out what my balance is then.  In the meantime I'm starting to get a headache over it, but there isn't much more I can do about it.   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw  urlLink  Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban   at the  urlLink Imax  theatre in Dearborn today.  Wow, that was ssooo cool.  Yeah, more expensive, but well worth it.  Except I ended up in the 3rd row from the front, which may have been a bit too close.  But I was right in the center of the screen, & the back had filled up, so I was afraid if I moved back, all the prime seats would be taken & I'd end up on 1 side or the other.  Considering how big the screen is, maybe it doesn't matter, but I stayed put.  It was still really cool.  Before the movie starts someone on a loudspeaker explains all about Imax, & says you can see all about it after the movie.  I probably should have, but after the movie, I couldn't remember where to go for that.  He also said that if you experience any dizziness from the movie, to just close your eyes for a few minutes & the feeling will go away, because you are not moving.  You remain stationary at all times.  Fortunately, I didn't have any problems.  The last time I saw an Imax type movie was ages ago for a class field trip.  I couldn't even tell you what I saw, or what grade for that matter.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Only had a small fight with one customer.  Everytime they come in to reserve something for a future date, as soon as we add everything, which is the rental, the sales tax,   plus   the deposit, they totally freak out.  We require that they pay the deposit   and   the rental.  How else do you think we can be assured that we  will  get our equipment back?  Duh.  It even says on the reservation form we fill out.  At the very bottom deposits are  in addition  to the rental.  I tried pointing this out to the woman, but she was so busy ranting, she wouldn't shut up long enough to read it all.  Many of them do that tho.  As soon as they learn they will get there deposit back (as long as we get all our equipment back in the same shape they received it) they calm down.  Sheesh.  I also had 1 person who thought he was being a smart ass.  We  always  require a valid Michigan driver license to rent anything.  So, as usual, someone wanting some chafing dishes and tables came in, & I asked for his driver license.  Thinking he's being smart, he asks me what would have happened if he had walked there & didn't own a driver license.  I told him he probably wouldn't be there for several chafers & 4 tables (2-6' & 2-8'), b/c how would he get all that home?  His answer was that he would be making a whole lot of trips.  Riiiiiight.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I spent some of the day in the back.  At one point, I wandered up front to see if there were alot of customers up front.  There wasn't, but I noticed a contract sitting there for a lawn edger that had been rented an hour earlier to be returned in another hour by a name & address I recognized, her house is kittycorner to the one next to ours.  I made sure I was up front when I knew she'd be returning it.  I recognized her as soon as she walked in the door.  I'd mentioned to I. that I knew her when I saw the bill.  So when J.R. came in, I. said out loud for her to hear "There's your neighbor back with the lawn edger.  Your former neighbor anyway."  J.R. glanced at me, but was trying to figure out what I. was talking about.  I knew she didn't recognize me at that point.  I had to tell her I'm one of G.'s daughters, the middle one.  That her daughter used to come over all the time.  Then she asked me was I C.'s or her younger son's age.  I told her "my younger sister L. is C's age"  I'm the middle daughter.  She finally started to remember.  I. told her I'd seen her name & address on the contract & recognized her.  J.R. said that yes she still lives in the same house.  I wasn't sure if she knew about why mother sold the house, so I told her that she had after Grampa died & moved to the place up north.  She asked me where was it & I told her Grayling.  She said that was quite a ways up.  I told her not really that far & that C had gone with us one year.  I could tell she vaguely remembered that, then she said "Oh yeah, I do remember that."  She asked me how long I've been working there, I told her 17 years, but normally I'm at the Dearborn Heights store.  She said "WOW 17 years? Wow that's a long time."  (yeah, tell me).  Then she told me that C is married, has a 4 year old daughter & lives in Oxford.  I didn't get any info on S, I got the impression she had to get going, plus we were starting to get busy again (as was happening all day).  We did our great seeing you & I'll tell the others I saw you thing, then she left.  She was quite energetic, almost jumpy.  That also reminded me of yesterday, I was at Dbn & when one of the guys got back from their deliveries, he told me they were in my old neighborhood (they delivered some stuff to a house on Fox).  (He knew because in the past, stuff in that area came up, like what stores used to be called & stuff, that's a whole other story).  Anyway, he was surprised that there are still some dirt roads over there.  I told him, yeah like Norfolk.  He said yes they were on Norfolk.  They drove up to Fox from Beech Daly.  He mimicked bouncing around from potholes.  I laughed.  I told him I think they left it a dirt road because many of the cross streets are the 2-way stops & the potholes act as speed bumps otherwise people go zooming thru there too fast.  (Ok, I don't know how true it is).  I also told him I remember the busses went up Norfolk & every one used to crowd the back of the bus cuz it was fun being bounced all over the place (I do remember kids used to do that for that reason).  I'm in the Livonia store again tomorrow. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There started out 3 of us, 'cept I.'s son called her this morning while he was on the road for his job.  He said his chest on his right side felt like it was going numb, so he was on his way back to his job & asked her to meet him there & take him to the hospital.  She got back to work about 2:00 or 3:00.  She said his whole right arm & leg had also gone numb.  The doctors did a EKG or EEG (I always forget which is which & I could have looked it up b/4 this post, but I didn't feel like it), but it didn't show anything.  But they still think something happened like a real mild heart attack or he may have a clogged artery or something.  He opted to go home & go back tomorrow for all the tests they want to do.  So they sent him with a prescription of Nitroglycerin & told him to take some aspirin as well.  Even tho it was just R. & I most of the day, I still got quite a bit done.  I even got to take my lunch break at a reasonable time-1:15.  I sat & read the Detroit News.  They had an article in the  Health & Fitness  section about iron deficient anemia.  From what I read, it definitely explains why I feel so fatigued, & is the probable explanation of why I find it hard to concentrate & remember stuff, & of why I'd experience painful heartburn so much.  I try to remember to take my iron every day, but once in a while I'd forget.  I did notice that after taking it for awhile, even sporadically, my heartburn & indigestion lessened a great deal.  There was alot of nights I couldn't sleep at all or I'd have to sleep sitting up b/c my esophagus felt like I had swallowed a gallon of lighter fluid & followed it with a couple books of lit matches & drank some sulfuric acid to wash it all down.  Since I started taking iron supplements, my stomach & esophagus has calmed way down, but I didn't realize the connection until I'd read the article.  'Course, I've also cut way back on diet coke, so I know the decreased intake of carbonation has helped too.  Besides water, I drink more sun tea made with a combo of  urlLink mate  &  urlLink rooibos  teas.  I put 7 bags of mate & 2 bags of rooibos (pronounced  roy-boss ) into a glass jar of filtered water & put it out on the balcony for the whole day.  With a little lemon juice & some artificial sweetener it tastes sssoooo good.  'Cept it makes me have to urinate alot.  Fortunately, there are bathrooms nearby.  I didn't used to like tea until I discovered mate.  It is very mild.  I wish I had a gourd & bombilla for it tho.  Rooibos is much stronger, being a red tea, but I've developed a taste for it.      Anyhoo the iron deficiency article also listed quite a few foods that contain iron, so next time I go grocery shopping I can pick some of them up.     YAY PISTONS!!!!!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My legs & feet hurt real bad & I felt a bit nauseated.  So I went for a bike ride.  Strangely after my ride, my feet didn't hurt nearly as much as they did b/4.  'Cept the seat makes my arse hurt.  Oh well.    I'm working at the Livonia store tomorrow.  I know I'm gonna be real busy.  This morning wasn't too bad, but it was busy this afternoon.  Yesterday was really busy.  Yesterday I didn't get to take a lunch break until 3:00.  Today it was 2:30.  Not that I mind too much.  It seems to make the rest of the day go faster.    3rd period & the Pistons are up by 11 points.   WOOOO HOOOO!!!!!!  YAH PISTONS!!!!!       urlLink        FEAR THE 'FRO!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, they wouldn't be quite so bad if I would get together everything I need for work the night b/4.  But nnnoooooo.  I'm always too tired Sunday night.  I always figure there isn't that much to do, it won't take but a minute.  Hah!  Silly me.  I end up running around the apartment grabbing things: water bottle--drat needs refilling, prepare my ice tea in a travel cup, toss everything back into the purse, grab the contact lens stuff from the bathroom, etc.  I always end up leaving at least 10 mins. later than I should.  Thank goodness alot of kids are out of school for the summer, so traffic is much lighter.  Finding a place to park once I get to work is becoming a major hassle.  There are more people working & the female who lives in the house right behind the office/showroom is a freakin' weirdo.  She has several people living with her, & feels she's entitled to the whole side street.  My coworkers & I have been parking there for like a million years.  She just moved there a couple years ago or so, & figures she can take over.  Last summer, anytime someone parked in front of the alley directly behind URA's building, she started leaving notes on the windshield telling them they cannot park there.  She'd sign it "The Mayburn neighborhood" or something like that.  One of my coworkers beat on her door & told her she was a stupid bitch & to never go near her car again.  It eventually became my turn for the note receiving.  Then she started laying in wait for me to get to my car & she'd chase me down.  Once she called the police.  I was still at work at the time.  They left as I got out there so I didn't think much of it.  That was the second time she chased after me.  By that time TC had already talked to the police.  They said the street is public property & she has no business telling people (us) we can't park there.  So, she tells me she had the police out.  I asked her what did they say.  She said "Never mind what they said."  I told her I already knew what they told her--the same thing they told us.  She asked what that was.  I told her that it's a public street, not exclusively belonging to her & we have every right to park there.  She tells me that by her living in a house, that gives her more "power" to park there.  I told her only in her dreams.  We've been there a whole lot longer than her.  I then suggested she go to city hall & find out exactly where her property line is.  She went back into her house.  Anyhoo, I had no choice but to park on the street next to her driveway one day last week.  After work, there was a note on my windshield telling me she must have all those parking spaces for everyone living at her house.  She puts in the note that I should park in front of the house across the street from her (which doesn't happen to have a driveway, so where are those people supposed to park?).  The next day, again, no where else to park.  So I left a big note on my own dashboard saying "If you come anywhere near this car, I will call the police & report you vandalizing this car and for you stalking me."  What do you know, no notes from she-whacko on my windshield.  'course I'm not sure if she even looked, but oh well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...because I am incredibly tired.  Only having 1 day off a week kinda sucks.  I end up sleeping most of the day away.  I went for a bike ride this evening.  My first "real" bike ride in a very, very, very long time.  Yep, I finally got the bike fixed.  My bum hurts from the seat & my hands kept going numb from me gripping the handlebars real hard.  The bike is a tad taller than is actually comfortable for me (no the seat won't lower anymore than it is).  Anyhoo, I rode to Merriman, then turned around & rode to Venoy.  On the way to Venoy a large portion is in front of a Landscaping place that has all rocks going to Cherry Hill. I actually managed to ride the whole thing w/o losing my balance or control of the bike.  Then I rode back to Merriman again, & also rode around a couple of the apartment complexes a few times each.  All pretty cool for me. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ronald Regan died Saturday 6/5 @ age 93. Ray Charles died today @ age 73.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was starting to feel resentment at the beginning of the week b/c it seems every time I have a test coming up in class we are also super busy at work.  I crawl home exhausted & in lots of pain & can't concentrate enough to retain all the information I need to for the tests.  My midterm was yesterday: 10 essay questions.  I kept getting brain farts & couldn't remember everything.  The information was in my brain, but for some of the questions I couldn't for the life of me get it out, but I think I still did pretty well.  I answered all the questions, but I couldn't elaborate the way I wanted to for some.  Oh well, I'll find out for sure how I did next week.  The godawful heat & humidity didn't help matters at all.  We don't have any air conditioning where I work.  But we do have a couple fans strategically placed to circulate the hot air.  That almost helps.  The cold actually felt good today.  'Cept the rainy weather made it dreary.    I got to take a quick drive out to Plymouth this morning b/c S. & J. were missing something for one of their orders, & they couldn't finish w/o it.    Being so busy at work also caused me to keep forgetting to buy a birthday card for my older sister.  She just turned 40 (oop, I probably shouldn't have said that) & the only time I'd think about getting a card is at night when I'm already home & too tired & achy to get the motivation to go out & buy a card.  Or I'd think about it while at work when I can't exactly go anywhere.  After work today I went to the grocery store b/c I had a strange want for a salad with Feta cheese, salami, & Ranch dressing.  I bought a premade salad & the rest of the stuff & added it in.  I also got a belated b-day card.  As I was leaving, as usual, I realized I'd forgotten something I meant to buy.  Arrrgh.  But there was just no way I was going back.  Some other time.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       WOOO HOOO!!!!!!   Fear the 'Fro!!!!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometime late last year, someone threw out a 12-speed bike.  I figured it was meant to be thrown out b/c it was sitting next to the dumpster.  It sat there for a couple days.  I'd been thinking of buying a bike, but they are expensive & I wasn't sure how much I'd actually ride it.  So there was my opportunity to have a second-hand one.  Considering my financial situation, I don't mind getting second-hand stuff.  I now have 2 pair of good, comfortable "hand-me-down" (ok, hand-me-up b/c they're from my  younger  sister), shoes; thanx again, Lyn  urlLink   .  Anyhoo, about the bike.  Both tires were fairly flat, so I figured it had to be a cast-off.  I called TC who lives on the other side of the complex to swing around & toss the bike in the back of his truck, & take it up to work.  It was already getting cold out, so I didn't do anything about it then.  As it started getting warmer out, I started thinking about it.  I meant to start "working" on it b/4 Memorial Day weekend, 'cept I forgot when I left that Friday (it's still at work).  I finally remembered about it this week.  So I got the tire size a few days ago, but didn't get to a store b/c I was way too tired.    The first "always something" was yesterday.  I went to Sports Authority for the inner tubes.  They only had 1 of the 2 in the size I needed--at least the size was right, but I wasn't sure about the width, but I bought it anyway.  Then I went to another bike shop & got 2 that I still wasn't sure of the width.  Oh well.  Then I had to backtrack to the health food store not far from SA for a couple other things I wanted.  All this w/o much gas in the car.  I got home & figured I'd fill up the tank on the way to work.  Just b/4 going to bed, I realized I hadn't paid rent.  And I had 1 more grace period day.  I figured I drop the check off on the way to work, 'cept I hadn't even written it yet.  In the morning.  I got up a little late, & on my way into the kitchen to make a cup of mate tea, I saw the DVDs I had to drop off (due back b/4 noon, I work til 3:00).  So I did my morning routine a bit faster.  Not fast enough.  As I was getting my purse together, I'd realized  darnit!!  the rent.  No time.  I got in the car & realized   drat!!  no gas in the car.  Still have to drop off the DVDs.  The latter is first, I pass it first, next is gas.  I passed up 4 gas stations b/c they were a bit steep in price.  I got to a BP & it was the cheapest.  Got 3/4 of a tank.  Ended up 10 mins late to work.  *meh*  Secondly:  After work, I figured I'd get the tire tubes changed & take the bike for a ride.  Hah.  I got the tire tubes changed (the back one had a gash in it, hence why it was flat)--except the back tire is frayed in 1 spot.  No way the tube will stay in with the correct pressure in it.  FUBAR.  Need a new tire.  So I went to a bike shop on the way home today & got a new one.  But I have to wait at least until Monday, now.  It was a real good day to go for a ride too.  It's always something.  urlLink     The back brake cable needs reattaching too, plus it could use new handlebar grips, but those are a cinch.  Oh yeah, I dropped my rent check off b/4 coming home.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I got home from work & fell asleep on the couch.  Woke up just after 9:00 & watched CSI.  After that I took a shower & went to bed.  Tonite I did laundry.  B/c I had to.  I so did not feel like it.  But I also had rented the  Finding Nemo  DVD last weekend & it's due back tomorrow morning.  So I had to watch it.  I'll drop it off on the way to work.  It wasn't too bad, I guess.  It dragged in places.  I liked the Ellen Degeneres fish, Dory.  If it wasn't for her, I would have started bawling & turned the movie off.  IMO.  Now it's late, I'm really tired, & I still have to make my bed & take a shower b/4 hitting the sack. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was at the Livonia store today.  As usual I couldn't make myself get up in the morning & dawdled too much, so I ended up late.  It was pretty much as busy as I thought it would be.  Trying to get my work done, answer phones, wait on customers, etc.  I still managed to get quite a bit done. But I didn't get time for a lunch break.  I'd gone to Burger King for R. & myself, so in between phone calls & stuff I munched on my fish sandwich which was at about 2:00.  R. was busy helping one of the guys who came from the Dbn Hts store to pick up lots of equipment for their orders; so it wouldn't fail, every time I took a bite & had a mouthful of food, the phone would ring.  People asking all sorts of questions.  There was so much stuff to do, I still didn't get it all done.  Even the stuff I'd left 2 weeks ago.  All that was pushed to the back & more piled in front.  I did get a little of the stuff that's been there done.  But, oh well.  I'm back at the Dbn Hts store tomorrow.  Anyhoo then I had to rush home, take a fast shower & get to class.  Fortunately, class was an easy session.  But midterm next week  urlLink    yuck.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh yeah, several times.  I don't know why, but I feel strangely sick & lethargic when I have to get up early.  It eventually passes, but it makes me run late for work.  I've been like that for quite awhile now.  I wonder if it has something to do with my low blood pressure, now that I think of it.  Once I'm up getting the ole juices flowin' for a bit, I get to feelin' better.  I work at the Livonia store tomorrow.  I know there's going to be a ton of work.  And only 1 other person there.  Bummer.  It's probably going to be real busy customer & phone call wise too.  I hope I can get enough done.  Best to not think about it now, otherwise I won't be able to sleep.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't normally get much time to rent DVD movies, but I rented 3 last week:   Haunted Mansion  which was kind of amusing.   50 First Dates  which was mostly funny, but I didn't agree with how the family handled her short-term memory loss. That was a dumb. Other parts were more sad than expected in the movie.   Mystic River  which I thought was a good movie. I didn't like what happened at the end, but I liked the end in that it was very unexpected. There was a moral to the story.  Sometimes, you think you have the facts you need, fill in the rest of the blanks on your own & jump to your own conclusions. Unfortunately, you end up completely wrong.  Several people I know do this time & time again at my expense.   At least the end result is nothing like that of the movie. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I took my car to the dealership before work. I'll need the back bumper &amp; the whole exhaust pipe/tailpipe and muffler replaced. The guy told me that the exhaust system is a depreciating part. In $$ terms that means if they can find an aftermarket one, I pay nothing. If they have to put on a new one, I pay a percentage of the cost based on how many miles are on my car. I have just over 25,000 miles, so I'd pay 25%.  Because I had to be up abnormally early, I was excessively tired by midafternoon. So I decided to try a  lightly carbonated, sugar free Red Bull  for the first (and last) time. Yuck The only description I could think of is that it tasted like a glucose flavored jolly rancher.  urlLink    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was at the Westland Police Department to file an accident report this evening & Fox 2 News was sitting in the parking lot.&nbsp; I asked at the desk why they were out there.&nbsp; The officer told me a body was found buried in the yard at a house.&nbsp; The body had been there for 7 years.&nbsp; I wanted to ask more questions, but he probably didn't know much more, & even if he did, he probably couldn't tell it anyway.&nbsp; Oh well, I'll just watch the 10:00 news for more.   &nbsp;  On a very different note, I got an A- in my  Criminal Justice Organization and Administration  class.&nbsp; Go, me.  urlLink        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Some jerkoff keeps driving back & forth thru the apartment complex with his car stereo at top volume with the base cranked up to the max.&nbsp; It sounds really bad.&nbsp; He'll be deaf before he grows up.&nbsp;   Anyhoo, I got back the paper I wrote for class & got a 100% A.&nbsp; I also got the remarks: "You did your usual excellent work.&nbsp; Nice presentation & paper."&nbsp;  urlLink   &nbsp; Go me.&nbsp; I think I may actually get a grade  B  for the class tho.&nbsp; Everything on the final exam was too much information for my brain to retain all the details of, so I just wrote down as much as I could remember.&nbsp; Ah well. I'm not gonna worry about it.     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been trying to study for my final exam tomorrow night, but it's hard.&nbsp; It's been kind of hot & real humid.&nbsp; It's&nbsp;79 degrees out now & the humidity is about 69%, which I suppose is not really that bad right now.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'll get back to studying in a minute.&nbsp; I can't wait for this exam to be overwith.&nbsp; I feel so tired all the time because I haven't been getting enough sleep.&nbsp; I wake up every morning feeling real tired & lethargic &amp; sick.&nbsp; By 3:00 every afternoon I have a desperate desire to take a nice 15 hour nap--but, obviously can't b/c I have to work til 5:00.&nbsp; Several times I've taken a nap as soon as I got home.  &nbsp;  Ok,  urlLink   &nbsp; back to it.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Not sure if it's good or bad...    As mentioned in a  urlLink previous  post, I did a presentation in class that included the Sex offender registry.&nbsp; Last night in class there were more presentations.&nbsp; One guy, before beginning his, said, "Someone last week did one on the pervert list." (It took me a minute to realize what he was referring to.)&nbsp; He then said, "Yeah, I looked at it &amp; discovered my Aunt Betty was on the list, so I called her, &amp; we had a nice long chat, &amp; I just want to say thanks for that."&nbsp; Wow.&nbsp; He didn't sound mad or anything, the way he said it made everyone in the class laugh.    Next week is&nbsp;the final exam.&nbsp; WOOOHOOO.&nbsp; Last night I registered for 2 more classes for the Fall term, so I have 4 classes.&nbsp; 'Cept from my calculations I will only need a total of 11 more classes &amp; I would love to graduate in May, so I may actually take 7 classes for the Winter term if I (hopefully) have no scheduling conflicts.&nbsp; And yes, I plan to take a lay-off from work for that.&nbsp; I may even try signing up for 1 more class in the Fall.&nbsp; Then, I figure once I get the syllibi (plural for syllibus?) for all the classes I could then determine if I will have enough time for all the homework &amp; stuff.&nbsp; If not I can drop a class immediately without losing any money.&nbsp; But I have plenty time to decide as the class I have in mind still has plenty of available seats &amp; classes don't start til September.     I have no idea how this post is going to look upon publishing as it appears the people at blogger have once again been busy.&nbsp; Now the composition is set up just like  Word  'cept not nearly as many font choices.            
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night, I went back to the  urlLink Imax theatre  in Dearborn to see Harry Potter & the Prisoner of Azkaban. The first time, I sat in the 3rd row (read  urlLink here ). So last night I sat much further back. Way better. The movie started shortly after 7:00 PM. I'd made the mistake of getting some popcorn. I knew it would be around 9:30 when the movie let out &amp; I'd be kinda hungry b/4 then. That's all the food Imax has other than candy. As soon as I tasted the popcorn, I knew it was too salty & I'd get an "allergic" reaction. Anytime I eat stuff with too much sodium, I get a bad "too much sodium" headache. My head feels like what happened to Aunt Marge (if you haven't already, you'll have to read the book, or see the movie for more on that). I ate slowly, so I didn't start getting the headache until the end of the movie. I didn't want to drink too much pop during the movie, b/c I didn't want to get up anytime during the movie to go to the bathroom. I hate that. I had to take a couple Excederin on the way home, but by the time I got home I was feeling sick. Fortunately, it was time to shower &amp; go to bed anyway.   I still enjoyed the movie--more so b/c I didn't have to strain my neck to see everything like last time.   Thus this,  urlLink this , &amp;  urlLink this , ends my busy week.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As soon as I got home from Up North (we were west of Escanaba, btw), I just got my stuff in the door, discovered the cat had thrown up near the front door, cleaned it up, & I went straight to my computer & started on my paper.  I'd gotten some stuff written down already, I just had to get it into  Word .  I still made sure I got to bed at a decent hour b/c I had to work the next day.  Right after work Tuesday, I settled in front of the computer & got cracking.  It had to be at least 4 pages, otherwise it was 10% off the grade.  I only had about 2 pages.  But then, around 10:00 PM, I started brainstorming.  I did my paper on  urlLink the Sex Offender Registry  & the  urlLink Offender Tracking Information System .  That led into the fact that, in Michigan, all convicted offenders must submit a DNA sample to police authorities.  Unfortunately, there is a huge backlog of samples needing to be entered into the national DNA database.  This led to 2 more pages all about  urlLink CODIS .  I finally finished my paper and the Powerpoint slides for the presentation I had to give in class about 1:30 Wednesday morning.  Still had to get up at 7:00 for work.  Then, during my lunch break, I was reading the Detroit News paper & saw an article pertaining to the sex offender registry, about a bill the House of Reps & the Senate had both passed & was on Governor Granholm's desk for review & her possible signing stating that juveniles who are convicted of having sex with minors within 3 years of their own age not being put on the registry.  I kept thinking of my paper, & had already decided I wanted to rewrite some of it, plus I had forgotten to create some Powerpoint slides for my presentation, such as the title slide, and decided I also wanted to add the stuff about the article.  So I'd asked my boss if I could leave work early (he said yes), I left 1 & 1/2 hours early came home & added all the things I wanted.  Class starts at 7:00 PM, & I knew I had to leave home by 6:15 at the latest to make sure I got there in plenty of time.  There's a computer in the classroom with internet access, so I could show all about each of the internet sites.  The presentation went quite well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know, it's been awhile since my last blog.  I have lots to tell, so get as comfortable as you can.  Last week I was surprised to find the place where I work would be closed July 3, 4, & 5.  That meant I could to L. & J.'s reception party.  That also meant lots to do before going.  I also knew I had a 4-page report due for class on July 7.  So in between making the arrangements for the trip, I also had to find as much information for my paper as I could & print it up to take with me.    Anyhoo, on the 3rd is when I left for Up North.  And, apparently Murphy was a bit bored & decided to have fun at my expense: more things went wrong than I cared for.  First I got off to a late start.  Then I went to get D at her apartment.  Those stupid, lame, dolts who run the complex decided to not have anyone assigned to work the gatehouse, but they left the gates down.  They have an ultra lame teleprompter thingy that is hooked up to people's land line phones.  For those who actually have a land line phone.  If the resident doesn't  too bad.   I got out & tried shoving the gate up, hoping to break the motor or something, but I couldn't.  I don't normally have a cell phone, because I never made enough calls to justify paying the hundreds of dollars each month.  Fortunately, I'd borrowed one from work for my road trip in case of emergency.  And luckily, D has a cell phone.  So I called her. She was going to come down & swipe her gate pass for me, but I got tired of waiting & when another resident swiped his/hers & went thru, I hit the gas pedal & zoomed thru behind 'em.  Anyhoo, I finally got there, we packed her things into the car, & then her husband asks if she has the phone # of where we're staying.  No. She hasn't a clue.  I tell her it was on the invitation.  She has no clue where the invitation is.  I finally go to my car for mine.  I'm rooting thru my purse & realize that for the 5th or 6th time, I'd forgotten to drop off my rent check.  AArgh.  So she gets the ph# written down, we leave, go back to my complex, I drop the rent check off.  Then, b/c my GPS had sounded the low-battery warning, I stop off at CVS for more batteries.  I decide to get a new pair of sunglasses.  I get in line.  There's 5 people ahead of me & no cashier.  The photo cashier is open.  An old woman gets in line ahead of me.  She puts something up on the counter, the cashier rings it up.  The woman drags out her checkbook, doesn't know the date.  Asks anyone including me if we know the date.  No I just know the days of the week (mostly).  I see a bunch of other things in her cart.  Oh geez, she's gonna pay for stuff separately.  The other cashier is back & ringing people up.  I move there.  The next one in line hands her a card the register won't read.  She keeps swiping it, but the register does not recognize it.  Cashier has to call the manager.  Finally, the customer pays for something.  Next. Eventually, I hear in the photo line, the woman paying with a check that she has more stuff in her cart & it would help if she paid for them.  Duh.  I finally pay for my batteries & sunglasses, & get to the car.  I search my backpack for my swiss army knife, find it & cut the price tag off the glasses.  I peel the sticker off the lens, that's when I notice it's missing a nose pad.   urlLink   !!!  So I go back in & there's no less than 6 or so people in each line.  So I grab another pair just like the ones I bought,  make sure there's nothing wrong with 'em  & get in line for the cashier I got b/4.  Finally someone else opens a register, but I still got the same 1 as b/4.  I explain about the glasses, she checks & makes sure the new ones are the same, they are, she enters it into the register & I'm on my way.  I get back to the car, retrieve the knife & hand it to D to cut the tag off, while I changed the GPS batteries.  Done!!  We're  finally  on our way.  Much later than I would have liked, but no more major crises after that.  Several hours later we cross the Mackinac bridge.  Right after that is when I remembered I should check the driving directions.  Ok, the exit we take is.....the one I'm passing up.  AAHHH.  So I take the next one & we end up in St. Ignace.  I need a gas station anyway.  I finally find one, & I also learn I'm making my way back to the road I need anyway.  It would take another 4 hours to get to our destination, so we decided we should get some food.  No fast food joints in St. Ignace.  Didn't surprise me really.  So we stopped at  urlLink Bessie's Original Homemade Pasties  & got vegetable pasties to go.  On the way back, naturally there were traffic jams on I-75, everyone else also driving back from Up North.  A couple times when we were crawling along, I could hear a strange creaking, flapping noise coming from the front driver side wheel/tire.  After awhile, after I'd driven over orange strips placed at construction points, the noise stopped.  Once I got D. home, we looked at the tire & discovered a nail in it.  So on Tuesday I ran it over to the Shell gas station across Telegraph & had the nail taken out & the tire patched.  Whew.  The rest of the weekend went quite well.  There was so much excellent food at the reception, I probably packed on another 20 pounds.  I certainly feel like it, everything was  so good urlLink          urlLink     I'm glad I was able to go, I had fun.  It's a shame our mother was unable to go.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I met a friend from Sign Language class who is a sign language interpreter at the Golden Corral Buffet last night. The food was good. It was quite busy, so people ended up doing pretty much an assembly line type of thing where we start at the salad making section, then work our way up to the entrees.  Anyhoo, we hadn't gotten very far when the line seemed to be almost at a standstill so we decided to sit & eat what we'd gotten &amp; wait for the line to decrease.  I needed lots of signing practice, so we signed our conversations.  We'd been sitting for an hour when K. wanted some water & we realized no waiters had come to ask us how we were doing.  Everyone around us were being waited on.  I told K. that maybe they all thought we were both deaf & were afraid to come up to us.  She laughed & decided that if we could flag down a waiter we'd pretend she was deaf &amp; I was her interpreter.  Waiters were all around us but they were busy seating new people so we waited some more.  I wanted some macaroni & cheese b/c I hadn't gotten that far the 1st time, so she told me to go ahead.  On my way there I noticed around me that other people were being waited on.  1 waiter was even asking someone if she wanted a  refill  on her coffee.  I was making my way back & was almost to the table when I saw K. had finally gotten a waiter's attention.  She was signing to him, but naturally he didn't understand.  He kept asking her did she want some rolls.  I made it to the table & interpreted to him that she wanted some water.  He asked if we wanted anything else & I told him coffee for myself.  He looked at K. & asked if there was anything else, she signed no.  He didn't know so he asked again if we wanted rolls.  I said no, nothing else thank you.   5 mins later the waiter came back, but he was carrying a few bakets of--rolls.  He laid a couple on the tables of some people who had just sat down.  He had an extra so he put it on our table.  Finally he came back with our water & coffee &amp; put both in front of K.  We just laughed.  After that the waiter did come back & check on us a couple times.  I only screwed up once being K.'s interpreter.  I forgot she was supposed to be deaf, &, when the waiter checked on us around 9:00 (the place closes at 9:30) he said we could stay another hour.  She had to ask me what he'd said b/c she wasn't supposed to have heard him.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's a good thing I took a nap yesterday.  We had more thunderstorms around 1:00 AM.   urlLink      Normally they don't bother me, 'cept these were real loud.  One sounded like a massive explosion right outside my bedroom doorwall.  I got up early & took my car to the dealership & got it fixed.  They had it finished this afternoon, so I picked it up after work.    I meant to go vote, but I forgot.  Oh well.  It was miserably hot & humid again.  Yuck.  It's 79 degrees right now & the humidity is 82%. Today's high was 87 degrees  urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I never did catch on the radio what the temperature & humidity got up to today, but it was miserable, & I see the weatherpixie is down right now.  I don't work where there is air conditioning, just some fans blowing the hot air around, but it's something anyway.  Right now it's 84 degrees & the humidity is 63%.  When I got home, I turned my air conditioner on & took a nap.  The dealership called me this afternoon to tell me the parts for my car are in, so I'm taking it in first thing in the morning b/4 work.  It's supposed to only take them the 1 day, so hopefully I can pick it back up after work.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to the park & walked about 3 miles. It was hot tho, &amp; I was tired. I'm always tired. It's been a couple weeks since I've been able to get to the park & walk. I want to go walking every day, but it's all I can do to crawl home after work. Anyhoo, after my walk, I grabbed a mat &amp; towel from my car & laid on the grass for a couple hours &amp; took a cat nap. I'm still tired. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>