<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay! Finally it's my district's turn to take part in a massive island wide blackout. Cheers to the electricity company.   29 June. 10:10pm   I was about to reach out to on the fan and embark on my math homework when I suddenly found myself engulfed in total darkness. It took me a while before I figured it was a blackout because I was still recovering from the shock. My brother became very excited all of a sudden and ran around the house searching for candles. I wonder how he sees in the dark. There was still no reaction whatsoever coming from my parents. Outside was pitch black too and the only source of light was coming from my neighbours' windows. Apparently they found it very amusing to flash their torches at the opposite block and wait for a response. Which was returned to them, by the way. I happen to live in the middle block so I got the opportunity to watch 'the battle of the blocks', as my neighbours took turns to flash coded signals to each other. Amusingly enough, this was accompanied by various un-human like screams/shouts/hollers/shrieks/bawls. Our blocks must have been acoustically designed because these noises continued to ring through the air without a break for the next ten minutes. I didn't stay around for the whole show though; I was busy finding the coolest spot to sleep on in case the electricity didn't come back on for the rest of the night. And my brother was still trying to find the candles. Ha! I knew he couldn't see in the dark!   29 June. 10:45pm   The lights just flickered back on while I was trying to sleep. After all the trouble of carrying my mattress out to the hall, I have to move back to my room to continue my sweet slumber. Well, at least now the fan is working.  cxy says I'm talking to myself in my daily entries. So to keep me from the brink of insanity, I've decided to put in a daily poll: DO YOU THINK I'M TALKING TO MYSELF?? HUH! DO YOU?! DO YOU?! ANSWER ME!!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a miracle! I'm actually still alive and kicking after two consecutive days of school. The past two days have been dreamy ones. When you're not fully awake, the seconds seem to drag on like hours. But when you're sleeping, you're told it's already morning right after you hit the pillows. School makes you miss the comfort of your bed more than usual. I'm still trying to get used to getting up at 5:30am in the morning instead of 12pm in the afternoon.  Did you know if you pick the low E string on the guitar and let the open note ring out before bending the whammy bar repeatedly, you'll get a sound like that of the motorcycle. The exact same one you hear when they're starting the engine. Cool eh? I believe there're still many other funny sounds you can produce with a whammy bar, but I have yet to discover them yet. I don't play with my whammy bar much. It makes my whole guitar go out of tune within a matter of seconds. Yucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally! Some colour to my posts...   urlLink    Life Lesson #1: Always remain optimistic, even in times of adversity.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm turning nocturnal from all the late nights watching soccer. I can hardly keep my eyes open in the morning without feeling it sting. Horrible thing is school reopens tomorrow and the only thing I'm looking forward to is Bridge. I wonder if I can wake up on time or stay awake throughout lessons.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm not a perfect person There's many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you  And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away  And be the one who catches all your tears That’s why i need you to hear  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You  I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      france just lost.  a tragic defeat.  can you feel my anguish?  france is crying.  greece is partying.  ...and i'm here blogging my depression away.  dawn made me do this.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hell Yeah~ Now this is MY type of Quiz! I like my warning label, but it doesn't look nice here because it blends in with the black background.      PARENTAL    	  ADVISORY    		  JOYCE CONTAINS EXPLICIT LYRICS      Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the first time in months, I can safely say out loud: I need a haircut. My fringe is so long now it keeps irritating my eyes and the rest of my head looks like an overgrown bush. Everyone seems to be going for haircuts recently. Maybe because of the fact that school reopens in exactly TWO days. *runs amok* It's back to Horror Camp and I'm still so unprepared. Guess who will be welcoming us back on the first day? Cheah! *horrified scream* Lit with Cheah on the first period. Talk about Monday blues, this really brings it to the extreme.  It's been three days since the arrival of our new fridge but I still can't get over it. The elation and excitement of filling up the empty spaces on the cold shelves, deciding what goes where. I've been making more trips to the kitchen, just so that I can look at it's glossy white surface, grip the handle, yank open the door and breathe in cold air as it blows onto my face. Ah, but I'll probably grow out of this phase when my parents go marketing sometime later and dump in all the fish and meat, stinking up everything else.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       THE SONG OF THE OLD MOTHER    I rise in the dawn, and I kneel and blow Till the seed of the fire flicker and glow; And then I must scrub and bake and sweep Till stars are beginning to blink and peep; And the young lie long and dream in their bed Of the matching of ribbons for bosom and head, And their day goes over in idleness, And they sigh if the wind but lift a tress: While I must work because I am old, And the seed of the fire gets feeble and cold.    -- William Butler Yeats (1865 - 1939) 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After playing too much on my guitar, I begin to fantasize about my own weird noises. And here is one of them:   urlLink My First Remix   It's nothing much, only 8 seconds worth of my fantasies, and some have already heard it before. A little short, but do enjoy and give comments. I think the remix factor injects a little more rock to this recording. It's not quite perfect yet, but I hope to improve my skills as I go along. And as if you don't find this jarring to your ears, more works will be up when I finally get my new acoustic (which will be a few months later), while others are still in the making. Sorry, no electric guitar clips until I figure out how to get a nice, clean sound amidst all the distortion.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the right you'll see the addition of a new feature. (The sidebar looks so long now) In case anyone gets bored from reading one of my posts, feel free to play it. I got a 43 on my first try. Quite slow if you ask me, it's all the darn mouse fault. Anyway, let me know when you get bored with this game too and I'll try getting another one.  My new fridge is coming today! New fridge = bigger space = more food! Woot! This equation, I like! My parents aren't around, so the onus is on me to make sure that this huge ice box makes it safely to our kitchen. Unscathed, unharmed, sparkling clean. They gave me a briefing last night on what to look out for. Scratches, accessories, receipts, delivery orders and what-nots. But the point is...I have a thick wad of notes in my pocket right now! *evil cackle and furtive eyes* Umm...*straightens up*...the money is for the fridge, yes, I'll make sure it gets into the correct hands...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A few days back, at my cousins' house, I noticed a big difference between the speech of a 4 year old and that of a 7 year old.  My 4 year old cousin initiated a conversation with me - on potties. In case you didn't know, a potty is the toddlers' version of a toilet bowl.  "It's pink. Pink is my favourite colour." (Very innocent)  The conversation was mainly one sided while I just nodded my head.  With my 7 year old cousin, the conversation was mainly one sided too. Only, it was very much made up of four lettered expletives.  "You ugly butt! You idiot! You ass!" (I have omitted the more offensive ones)  And I just sat there and watched him exhaust his vocabulary of profanities before he'd start all over again. I couldn't get in a word edgewise.  Isn't it amazing how fast we mature in terms of speech? Okay, maybe this big difference is also owing to their difference in gender. What will I be hearing next?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw this link on both Sharon's and Yanyun's blogs, so out of curiousity I decided to find out what makes a 'joyce'. I wonder how they get this stuff anyway.      How to make a joyce        Ingredients:   5 parts intelligence  1 part ambition  5 parts joy        Method:  Combine in a tall glass half filled with crushed ice. Add a little sadness if desired!       Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     I was playing with the new Hello programme. Free uploading! Cool. And this was what I got out of it: A really old Calvin and Hobbes comic strip from the year 1993 (above). It's a little small here, can't go any bigger. So to be able to read it, you'll probably have to click on it to see the blown-up version.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Denmark VS Italy 0-0 Sweden VS Bulgaria 5-0 HAHAHA! oops, did I say (type) that out loud?  Okay, enough of soccer. I shall go to bed early tonight. And if I can, wake up for the match between Germany and Netherlands at 2:35am, though I don't see much of a fight. I need to conserve my energy for the quater-finals coming up.  Which reminds me, two full pages have been dedicated in today's paper to report the match between England and France. Boy, does Beckham look vengeful on the front page. But no one can deny the power of Zidane and Barthez!  The posts are getting longer and longer. So much for the short and sweet.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Within the past 2 hours, I have witnessed the most remarkable change of events. Frank Lampard scored the first goal within the game and within Group B itself (Switzerland VS Croatia: 0-0). He headed David Beckham's free kick into the top right corner of the goal. The first ball that managed to get past Barthez in 12 games. While the England supporters went wild and started singing the national anthem, my heart sank. France had so many opportunities at the goal but they were simply off tonight. Or rather, this morning. David James (England's Goalkeeper) thus had plenty of footage showing him throwing in the ball over and over again. England had scored in the 33rd minute, just before half time, and the score remained 1-0 all the way into the second half. By the 80th minute I was starting to lose hope and told myself 'this doesn't look good'. The game became stagnant as the players merely passed the ball from one side of the field to the other.   I must commend the England players for their effort though. You could see that they were really trying. Beckham played a great game and Neville got a bloody head while trying to head the ball but still bravely stayed on in the game. Rooney, however, hogged the screen most of the time especially in the first half where he displayed his use of brute force against the French players. He makes use of his big body mass to ram into or block off French players so that he can clumsily dribble the ball along the sidelines, and kick it out. This clumsy goofball should be playing rugby instead of giving England a bad name. Deciding to put this 17 year old on forward must have been a great challenge for Coach Eriksson who finally took him out in the second half. Hot favourite, Owen, on the other hand barely had contact with the ball, and even lesser footage. He too, was taken out of the game in the second half. Barthez could be seen strolling around the goal line waiting for England to attack until Beckham, who took most of the shots, had a second free kick. This was swiftly blocked off by Barthez, France's life saver.  There was 3 minutes added time because of all the fouls and change of players. These 180 seconds proved to be the turning point as well as the conclusion of this game. Zidane took a free kick 20 seconds into added time. Not surprisingly, he scored. England had lost their lead and it became a draw. But the climax came when James rushed forward to tackle Henry, giving him a huge fall and France's second free kick in 2 minutes. All eyes were now on Zidane as he did a slow run towards the ball, carefully swiping it. The stadium went quiet as the tension and suspense kicked in. (pun intended) The ball took forever to fly through the air. I felt the anticipation and excitment. It curved exquisitely and shot past James' head into the net! ZIDANE SCORES AGAIN! France goes wild! This is the first time they have beaten England in an international competition. England was still in shock. And I can finally go to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Portugal VS Greece   Greece played a great game with Karagounis scoring the first goal in less than 7 minutes into the opening game. And the second goal when Basinas was given a penalty kick in the 51st minute. Everyone was waiting for Figo from Portugal to do something about the 2-0 situation they were in and he finally rose to the occasion late into the second half of the game when he took a corner kick. Ronaldo made use of this golden opportunity to do a beautiful header and scored the final goal. Although Greece bagged the majority of the penalties with 24 fouls, the game ended 2-1 in their favour.   Spain VS Russia   Russia totally paled in comparison to Spain. They were just freely dribbling the ball around without any specific aim. Sharonov of Russia was also the first player to get the red card. He wasn't even allowed to sit on the bench and was immediately sent off the playing area, after two yellow cards in a row. Radimov got sent off next for use of foul language. Spain on the other hand has obviously been put through the mill and displayed their co-ordination and excellent tactics when taking the indirect free kick. With a swift false move they carefully avoided the human wall and got the ball past the Russian players. Unfortunately, they missed. The highlight of the game was when Valeron of Spain stepped onto the field in the second half. Within mere seconds of his entrance, his first go at the ball scored Spain their first goal and Valeron's fourth international goal. Spain began playing rough too when David Albelda (yellow card) rammed himself head-on into a Russian player in an attempt to get the ball. Russia continued dribbling aimlessly until the game ended 1-0 to Spain's advantage. And the fouls committed: 21-12 to Russia's advantage. (or is it disadvantage?)   England VS France   7 hours to THE game. I wonder how the punters are reacting to this particular match. France (Defending Champion) definitely has the upper hand here with players (many of whom are from Arsenal) like Star Strikers Henry and Trezeguet , Zidane, Pires, Viera as midfielders and Barthez on the defense line. England has excellent teamwork but I'd like to see them get their balls past Barthez. He is the most flamboyant goalkeeper I've seen with elaborate actions while trying to block the shots. Agility is his strength. Although England has Beckham on midfield, Owen on forward, and Campbell on defense, I still think their chances of winning are slimmer. It'd be interesting to see how England reacts towards such a strong opponent. Many fans will be rooting for them tonight. But they'd be of more help praying for the team. With enough luck and effort, they can pull it off with a draw. It'd be a pleasant surprise for many if England wins. But hey, miracles do happen. My prediction: 2-1. France wins. I'll be utterly disappointed if they lose. This had better be an exciting game if I have to stay up into the wee hours of the morning waiting for it.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had the luck of laying my hands on a $2600 Artist Series Takamine acoustic guitar yesterday. It belonged to Nathaniel. I wonder when I'll have that kind of dough to get myself a decent acoustic. Since I had just sold my year-old Takamine, he kindly lent it to me to play for Sabbath School. He's selling it sometime this week though, so I'd probably have to go look for another guitar. The ones in church are currently in a very crappy state. It's like they were horribly bashed up, with missing strings and broken bodies.  Yesterday night was the opening match (Portugal VS Greece) of the Euro Cup 2004 which will last for the whole month. (WHOOP!) Greece won 2-1, with Portugal managing to score her first and last goal of the game in the last 20 minutes. I fell asleep around 11pm while waiting for the match to start at 11:50pm. This information was provided by my friend Dawn at 1:35am this morning, after managing to wake me up. I'll probably watch the highlights of last night's match later at 5pm on Euro Channel 21. I think the match everyone will be looking forward to will be tomorrow at 2:35am (what unearthly time) where two great sporting rivals - England and France are pitted against each other. But until then, I shall stick to my resolution for today. That is to clear the pile of homework stacking up on my table.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Until I post my next entry, here's something to keep you entertained.  Ever seen what a chicken looks like after getting run over while trying to escape from a chicken factory? Now's your chance. Click  urlLink here  to mourn Charlie the Chicken's death. Not one of the most pleasant pictures you'd see, but ironically funny. Recommended by a fellow blogger named  urlLink Rick . He sells cold beer.  Check it out.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because my writing skills aren't all that fantastic, my posts shall be short and sweet.  Like this one.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I've started a blog too. It's supposed to help me improve my essay writing skills in the long run (yeah right). Having a blog is fast becoming an 'in' thing with the crowd. And I'm here to join in the fad. To check out the rush. In exchange, my life is put on the display board.  My blog title is actually adapted from the Jim Dunlop motto - 'Live To Play Live'. Was just browsing through their website and was especially attracted to the picks section. Many famous stars use Dunlop picks for their style of playing too. Metallica, Hoobastank, Korn, Avril Lavigne, Linkin Park, Blink 182, DefTones, Sum 41, AudioSlave, Good Charlotte, just to name a few.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Are you all bored with the content of my posts recently since they have been mostly about Steve? Don't worry, this shall be the last. My excitement and jubilation will all die down after tonight. I hope Amabel manages to sneak in to  urlLink Bar None  tonight where they'll host the After Show Party at the Marriott Hotel. Then she can try and help me get his and Billy Sheehan's autographs or maybe one of their signature picks! Damn, I wish I were 6 years older now. I'll be going to town later to get the Passion and Warfare CD (It's Vai's  "magnum opus [and] a most excellent album"  according to Wai Quen.) that I've been saving up for too, at least I can accomplish more tasks in one day. So bye, I'm off to see Steve Vai, Billy Sheehan, Tony MacAlpine, Jeremy Colson and Dave Weiner. If you still don't know who they are after that much publicity on my blog, you can check out the  urlLink official online website  while I'm gone, or go read Page 3 of the Life! section today. 
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'll give you all a break from my constant ranting on how I&nbsp;live my life.        ...keZzz...         &nbsp;   urlLink     
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Saturday was Adventist Students' Fellowship Day so all the Adventist students from various parts of Singapore met up for dinner at Hotel Rendezvous. For just $10, I was treated to a buffet spread though I&nbsp;feasted mainly on the  spaghetti and  desert. The theme for this year is 'Climbing Mount Adversity' so basically the committee decorated the place to look like Base Camp; even the temperature was freezing. We were among the first to reach so I had to wait for quite a while before dinner was served. In the meantime I was entertained by a group doing forfeit with their butts. After eating our fill, there was the skit and video introducing the newly launched   urlLink  ASCO   &nbsp;(Adventist Students Care Organisation,&nbsp;founded by Uncle T.C.)&nbsp;website and it's functions. It helps students to search for tertiary institutions of higher learning. I was supposed to be acting as the innocent victim who got mugged but I asked Wanda to fill in for me. I hope I didn't disappoint Nathaniel because I backed out&nbsp;in the last minute. We all received a very stylish metallic pen as a door gift. It has four different ink types: black, red, a 0.5 mechanical pencil and a white tip (which I have yet to discover its purpose). To choose the ink-type you just have to look at the word printed on the side of the pen and click the top. No fussing, no turning. Just look, and press. How cool is that? I don't know how it works but it sure saves a lot of hassle. Uncle T.C. also graciously gave me his 'dog tag' with the words 'ASF Day 2004. We Stand Alone Together' inscribed on it (only committee members have it); just&nbsp;like the kind you wear in the army so that they'll&nbsp;know what to carve on your tombstone&nbsp;if you happen to die in battle. Louis ended up having to get his from Pastor because I took Uncle T.C.'s.   The trip home was a hilarious one, I laughed 'til my side muscles ached. Wayne and Louis were fooling around as usual.&nbsp;But Wanda looked so beat since she was out the whole day.&nbsp;We were sharing lame jokes and riddles from the MRT to the bus stop. I got to&nbsp;know a new friend too. I've seen Amos in our church many times but didn't really talk to him.&nbsp;Now I'm looking forward to more of his lameness this Saturday, though I think the bus ride home together with Louis and Barbara kinda scared him off a little. (Sean got off at Clementi, while Wayne and Wanda alighted at Chinese Garden for their mum to&nbsp;fetch them.)&nbsp;He says he'll need to bring two jackets to church in future. One to keep him warm from the air-conditioner in the sanctuary and the other to guard against my 'leng' jokes.    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        On my way home today I saw a teenage couple quarelling on the streets, and boy, did they get physical. I wouldn't mention which school they come from, but I'd tell you, it wasn't a very pretty sight especially with their school name printed in large font on the back of their PE shirt. The girl was giving her boyfriend some light punches and when that didn't seem to daunt him, she&nbsp;kicked him&nbsp;in his *censored*. (Ouchie!)&nbsp;That really got him fired up. He bent down to grab a book, rolled it up and retaliated with a good smack across the girl's&nbsp;face.&nbsp;Though I was quite a distance away, I could feel the full impact of that blow.&nbsp;Even as&nbsp;I think of it now, I'm still rather taken aback by what I witnessed --such brutality.&nbsp;My heart went out to the girl, why does she still choose to hang out with him?&nbsp;Then again,&nbsp;I wouldn't know whose fault it is to start with.&nbsp;I would've lingered around a little longer to see how this brawl would turn out; but&nbsp;the strain in my bladder muscles was getting unbearable. I hope they&nbsp;break up. But who am I to comment? Maybe that's just their way of showing affection.&nbsp;In&nbsp;any case, the conventional way is still much safer and accepted by&nbsp;most people. These fights are simply too violent. They might just kill each other without even knowing it, thinking they were just&nbsp;showering care and concern.&nbsp;Tsk, young people nowadays.  &nbsp;  I just learnt yesterday that JJ will be coming to our school to perform next Friday afternoon. This is the coolest thing that has ever happened to Nanyang in the past&nbsp;4 years of my Secondary school life, though I'm not a big fan.&nbsp;I hope it's not another one of those hour-long seminars on how to&nbsp;compose chinese&nbsp;songs, it isn't everyday that some pop star comes to your school. But, Steve Vai Live in Singapore will be the coolest thing to hit Singapore in the past 15 years of my life. It's still a week away! This is going to be the longest week I'll live through.  &nbsp;  Also, Bridge has officially been recognised in our school! Now we don't have to keep tabs on the school bells to avoid being caught by the teachers. They'll just have to stand aside and watch us play our cards with no ability to confiscate them! Haha to them! Gosh, am&nbsp;I mean. Million thanks to Sara who had the guts to send Mdm. Mak the email asking for permission to play with&nbsp;poker cards. Surprisingly, she approved and even sent out emails to all&nbsp;the staff to make sure that they don't hinder our card playing. Man, I like&nbsp;Mdm. Mak more and more now. (Is this abnormal?)      EDIT:  I just updated the entry 'Something off an email...'; please re-trace your steps back to it.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The winning essay for the Commonwealth Essay Competition was published on The Sunday Times two days ago, just thought I'd share it with you all. It was written by Amanda Chong, 15, from RGS. I marvelled at the way she managed to&nbsp;portray&nbsp;the individual characters through their thoughts and actions. I was&nbsp;especially&nbsp;moved by her conclusion when she described the mother's reaction&nbsp;after being&nbsp;told she'd be sent to a home. Yes, I know this post is a little late, but&nbsp;for the benefit of those who don't&nbsp;have the habit of&nbsp;flipping through the papers, click&nbsp; urlLink here    to read it.&nbsp;Maybe you can pick up a thing or two on writing compositions, like I did.  &nbsp;  Today was the second time in two weeks that the 157 bus engine sputtered and died on my way home. It took a while before the bus driver managed to re-ignite it and get on the&nbsp;move again. My orthodontist gave my brackets a new&nbsp;outlook today after the previous dull grey bands, explaining my colour scheme for this post -- orange.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It was my turn to go for the dialogue session with Mdm. Mak this morning. No sweat. I've been to her office before, about&nbsp;a few months back because I got caught skipping mass dance. Now I can look back at it and laugh at myself for being such a doofus brain. But thanks to that incident, she has agreed to make mass dance period a little slacker for Sec. 4s. After talking to her today, I realised that&nbsp;she is actually a rather friendly person to get along with, not at all like our stereotyped perception. She was sincerely putting in the effort to understand the problems we're facing. She even took time (half an hour into our Lit. lesson to be exact. --don't be mistaken, I'm thankful for that)&nbsp;explaining to us the rationale behind implementing things the way they are, and gave us the assurance that she'd rectify the problems that we've brought up, like&nbsp;Liz’s cca issue. I think she now knows more about us in that short half an hour session than what Mrs. See knows about us in 2 years. Way to go, they should organise more of such 'talk shows'.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Nice. Now I can blog with more variety. These colour and font options weren't here before.  &nbsp;  It's a drag waking up on Wednesday and Friday mornings, because something in the back of my head keeps prompting me about the long day ahead. I'll be spending the next 9 hours confined&nbsp;to the walls of my classroom, either because of the extra lessons or the endless mock tests week after week, only to make it home just in time to lay the dinner table.&nbsp;It's supposed to have&nbsp;become a routine already, but I still dread it. The monotonous droning of the teachers' voices puts me to sleep even quicker than&nbsp;general anesthesia.  &nbsp;  Mondays are equally bad because you can&nbsp;feel the whole week's activities&nbsp;waiting to jump at you and swallow you whole the moment you step out of your house door and board the bus which takes you on the slow ride&nbsp;to 2 Linden Drive. Kinda like the roller coaster&nbsp;cranking its way up to the highest peak and then releasing all brakes, plunging you into the depths of who-knows-where at a thousand miles per hour.  &nbsp;  It is relief getting out of bed on Tuesday mornings&nbsp;because you know there're no more long band practices&nbsp;to make sure that you're one of the last few to rush out of the school gates just before the security aunty slams it shut with a bolt and lock. &nbsp;  To top it all off, you don't know the sheer delight of waking up on Saturday mornings after sleeping for as long as you like and smiling to yourself because you can do the same thing the next morning, without worrying if you're going to run down in time to catch the school bus, or if you packed the wrong timetable.  &nbsp;  But this is not going to happen this week though. I have to be in school by 7:40am tomorrow for the Literature Symposium with TCHS, CHIJ and&nbsp;SCGS. Damn, I hope you have a good night's sleep.&nbsp;  
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey, Hotmail is not all about spam you know.    DORMITORY   When rearranged: DIRTY ROOM    PRESBYTERIAN   When rearranged: BEST IN PRAYER    DESPERATION   When rearranged: A ROPE ENDS IT    GEORGE BUSH   When rearranged: HE BUGS GORE    THE MORSE CODE   When rearranged: HERE COME DOTS    SLOT MACHINES   When rearranged: CASH LOST IN ME    ANIMOSITY   When rearranged: IS NO AMITY    MOTHER-IN-LAW   When rearranged: WOMAN HITLER    SNOOZE ALARMS   When rearranged: ALAS! NO MORE Zs!    A DECIMAL POINT   When rearranged: I'M A DOT IN PLACE    THE EARTHQUAKES   When rearranged: THAT QUEER SHAKE    ELEVEN PLUS TWO   When rearranged: TWELVE PLUS ONE    PRESIDENT CLINTON OF THE USA   When rearranged: TO COPULATE HE FINDS INTERNS   Boy, the person who figured out all these is one smart ass. A very free one at that too. I wonder if there're anymore from where these came from.     &nbsp;      UPDATE:  Jeremy just came up with these two new additions&nbsp;for my list. He's trying to find an anagram for my full name now.       &nbsp;    MARRIAGE     When rearranged: A GRIM ERA     &nbsp;   And the URL of my blog,     &nbsp;    TRASH BAG    When rearranged: BATH RAGS     &nbsp;   Okay, he just revealed to me the ' urlLink secret origin ' of these anagrams. Haha, I'm feeling dumb again.&nbsp;Now it's not so secret anymore.   
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After one solid month of intensive band practices, it finally paid off when the MC from MOE declared Nanyang the winner of the 'Grooviest Band in The Gardens' award. We cheered ourselves hoarse. I think the last time I felt this high was during our Lifeskills Camp Formal Dinner. But now that I'm home and everything has quietened down, I can't switch back to my mundane lifestyle. The worst thing is I have to wake up in about 7 hours' time to prepare for school, while I'm still having trouble getting over all the excitement today.  Today is also the last time I'll be going back for band practices, so I'll have no more excuse to procrastinate my revision. I wonder if I'm supposed to be happy or sad. Anyway, it's about 47 days to our first prelim paper. The problem with the future is that it keeps becoming the present. It seems like yesterday when we still had about 200 days to our finals. Sec. 4s! Do you feel the adrenaline pumping?? I better stop laming around and get cracking, so I won't be blogging as much now. Maybe only once or twice a week. Keep checking back for new updates though!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel obliged to make known the occurrence of Band Fiesta tomorrow evening, since everyone is doing their part in promoting it. It's held at the Botanical Gardens, 5:30pm. Do come and show us your support! This fiesta will be showcasing the Top 10 bands. 5 tomorrow and the other 5 next week. Besides NYCB, St. Patrick and River Valley will be performing too. I can't remember the other two bands.  I had a hell of a time at church today. I never knew church could be so much fun. Now I'm looking forward to it more than ever! I was still wondering what will I have to look forward to to get me through the school week after the Youth Day celebrations. I shall make it point not to be late for Sabbath next Saturday.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many people have heard this song on the radio but don't know the lyrics. Sozzled did this song for the opening of Youth Day yesterday too. In case you couldn't catch what Melanie was singing, here it is:   Do do do do do doo...  She's got a lip ring and 5 colours in her hair, Not into fashion but I love the clothes she wears, Her tattoo's always hidden by her underwear. She don't care.  Everybody wants to know her name, I threw a house party and she came Everyone asked me Who the hell is she? That weirdo with 5 colours in her hair.   She's just a loner with a sexy attitude, I'd like to phone her cos she puts me in the mood. The rumours spreading now that she cooks in the nude. But she don't care, she don't care.  Everybody wants to know her name, How does she cope with her new found fame? Everyone asks me, Who the hell is she? That weirdo with 5 colours in her hair.  She was all I thought about, The girl I couldn't live without. But then she went insane, She couldn't take the fame She said I was to blame She'd had enough And shaved five colours off And now she's just a weirdo with no name.  Everybody wants to know her name. How does she cope with her new found fame? Everyone asks me, Who the hell is she, That weirdo with 5 colours in her hair.  Do do do do do doo... 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My previous post might have invited some controversy, so this post shall end on a short and positive note.  Happy Youth Day, everyone.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great, after Euros comes Copa America. But I'm giving it a miss. TV Mobile was playing the match between Venezuela and Columbia just now. Because I live all the way at Jurong, I managed to watch all the way into half-time. It isn't nearly as exciting as Euro. Partially because the players are foreign to me and also because the speed of the game is so slow! I ended up looking outside the window most of the time, only to turn back and see them miss the goal three times in a row. And then we have our very own S.League, who are hoping to qualify for the World Cup in 2010, and who are ironically, even more foreign to me. I'm sorry for being so honest. But seriously, who bothers to keep up with the scores of Home United and Jurong Football Club. Even The Straits Times has very little news to do with our local sports scene.  Talking about media, I'm sure you have already noticed the striking similarities between our reality TV, and America's reality TV. AI(SI), The Bachelorette(Eye For A Guy), The Amazing Race(Are You Game Enough?). They might be coming up with the Singaporean version of Fear Factor and The Apprentice pretty soon, so look out for them! Survivor is difficult because of our limited land space. The only place where they can host the show would be in Pulau Ubin. (Yeah, I bet that would be challenging.) Where's the much talked about originality? Oh, I forgot. They're hiring foreign talent to do that aspect of the job too. Yes, I should try to look at things from their perspective. I understand that if they don't mimic America's shows, Mediacorp's ratings will plunge big time. Who denies the fact that reality TV is the reason why everyone is suddenly watching Channel 5? Even our SS teacher recognises the fact that Singapore copies what others do. Isn't that the reason why they put Switzerland and Venice into our syllabus? So that we can learn how they form their government, so we can form ours. So that we know how they lead their people, so they can lead us. The only thing they have yet to copied from the Westerners, and cut us some slack, is their education system. Can't they tell from the child suicide rates? That is why there're more and more cases of graduates going abroad for further studies and end up staying there permanently, resulting in us having to poach foreigners to drive our economy for us, even increase our birth rates for us. I see why we're dubbed a cosmopolitan state.  This has been a skeptical and critical post. I shouldn't have wrote it, and you shouldn't be reading it. We should always remember our roots and have unwavering faith and undying loyalty to our motherland. What was I thinking? I'm Singaporean.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm finally done reading 'My Story' by Dave Pelzer after two long months. How slow can I get. This book is a trilogy set which compiles his auto-biographies of three different segments of his life, namely his childhood, his teenage years, and his early adult life. The first two books were captivating. The last part was just a boring conclusion to everything. There were no more explicit descriptions of how his deranged mother abused him and how he fought to survive even when he was all alone. Unlike the first two, which was what kept me hooked onto them.  I've started on Mitch Albom's 'The Five People You Meet In Heaven' two days back. Inside, Eddie, the guy who dies and goes to Heaven, meets his first mentor -- The Blue Man. He said something so provoking, yet in a way, so true. 'Strangers are just family you've yet to meet.' This led me to think about a certain bogus theory which states that everyone is linked to everyone else in the world by six people. Which means, I know someone > who knows someone > who knows someone > who knows someone > who knows someone > who knows Brad Pitt! Or Saddam Hussein. Or Madonna. But why do I need to know them anyway. This theory sounds more amazing if we put it in another way. We're all descendants of Adam and Eve -- Doesn't this just directly make us all brothers and sisters by blood? Now who says I have a small social circle?  Anyway, less crapping. I hope I don't get stuck on this new book for too long. I want to read Dan Brown's Da Vinci Code. Everyone is talking about it. I'm sure it's going to be a good novel with an exciting plot.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There're a few CDs lying around on my table now. Steve Vai's The Ultra Zone, G3 Live In Concert, and Linkin Park Live In Texas. Thanks Sean and Andy respectively for lending them to me. I've listened and watched all three. The Ultra Zone shows a totally different side of Vai as compared to his previous songs that I've heard. Ultra Zone features a more melodious Vai, instead of his usual hyper-speed shredding style. But a few tracks in this album sound a little foreign. Vai has employed the use of some Pan-Arabian vocals and Indian-like tunes. I didn't like the singing, the female singer sounds all whinny and I don't understand Arab/Tamil or whatever the language she's singing in. Luckily most of the tracks are instrumentals.   G3 was a whole new experience for me. Satriani's anthems like Summer Song still sounds as refreshing as when I first heard it. Eric Johnson's fantastic use of chord voicings in his tunes never fails to leave me in awe. Although he looks and plays like anything, but a guitar rock idol. And Steve Vai's guitargod image in addition to his weird noises and the way he abuses his guitar totally rocked the stage off. I can't wait till his concert in three weeks' time.  I missed Linkin Park's Live In Texas Concert on Channel 5. Thank God for DVDs. Actually it was more or less the same as their MTVs. except for the frequent brawls among the audiences. Chester is still screaming his throat off. I could see his veins bulging out. I wonder how many lozenges he has to take just to get through one gig. Mr. Hahn was the only one who didn't sweat from all that jumping around because all he does is move his middle finger up and down the disc. Their second last song 'A Place In My Head' was the ultimatum when they smashed up that Ibanez. (They smashed up all the remaining gear after everything was over.) I think I'm going to watch everything all over again before returning them the CDs this Saturday. What to do, there's nothing else worth watching on TV nowadays.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This blockbuster is everywhere! On our television screens, on the radio, in the newspapers, smacked on the front cover of magazines, huge posters, even handphones are not spared. This movie is hitting box offices all time high rates, grossing about 40 million in pounds on its opening day. The trailer is capturing our attention, and so is Tobey Maguire. I'm going to watch it.  EDIT: Right after I posted the entry, my cousin rang me up to ask if I was free today to catch the movie. So I went with my brother to watch Spidey in action. This is the first time I see the whole cinema so packed. Finally, some competition for Harry Potter. All the shows from 1:00pm to 4:30pm were fully booked, except for some lonely seats here and there. Good thing for us we were able to snatch some seats by the side for the 2:00pm show. Nice action-packed movie, I enjoyed the part where he tried to stop the speeding train. But the only thing my brother remembers is the lady with her violin singing her out-of-tune Spider-Man song. Okay, I shouldn't reveal too much for those who have yet to see it. Go watch Spider-Man 2! You don't want to miss it. This might just be the last blockbuster to hit the screens this year after Harry Potter and Troy.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      31 matches, 25 days, 16 countries, 8 quarter-finalists, 4 semi-finalists, 2 finalists. But it all boils down to only... ...1 Champion tomorrow morning.  Who will it be?  I hope it's Portugal.   4 June. 5:00am   Greece takes it all.  But I'm not sad. For all their effort and skill they deserved to win every bit. Their defense unit was impenetrable, making scoring a hell lot tougher for Portugal. Ronaldo on the other hand, totally screwed up today's match. What captured my attention was when some crazy fellow dashed out into the field 10 minutes before full time. He looked like one of Portugal's supporters but I couldn't really see what was on the cloth he was waving. After throwing it at the players, he ran like a mad man on the lose head on into the goal where the officials caught him. Nuts, he was still waving and cheering when they carried him off.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow traffic on my blog practically tripled on Friday night because of the weekend, but now it's returning back to stagnant mode again.  Had Hazelnut Cheese Cake for breakfast. I didn't quite enjoy it because I tasted more raisins than hazelnuts. It still can't be compared to the Oreo Cheese Cake I ate four Sundays ago. Secret Recipe has the best Oreo Cheese Cake around. Absolutely heavenly. It's cheese is white and smooth and does not leave a thick aftertaste like normal cheese cakes do. And unlike normal cheese cakes that make you stop halfway because it is so filling, Secret Recipe leaves you yearning for more. It's cheese practically melts in your mouth and slides down your throat. Although I paid an exorbitant 5 bucks for such a puny slice, I think it's worth the experience.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw Mark Lee at IMM today promoting his newly launched CD -- Young Hero. I was drawn to the stage by the blaring sounds. He was shaking his head so violently to the music I thought it might get detached from his neck. Jack Neo explained that he had to write these type of songs for him because Lee couldn't sing any other genres. I didn't even know he sings. He even did a little dance which showed off his grey boxer shorts. Neo went on stage a little while later to show his support too, they sang a couple of songs together and talked a little about how a Changi Prison cell looked like. One of the scenes in Neo's new movie 'The Best Bet' was filmed there. I think 5 out of the 6 songs in his CD was sung within the short half an hour. I wonder why would the audience still bother to pay 16 bucks(they gave a special discount of $2 today) to hear them all over again.   I didn't hang around to see how many people actually bought the CD just to get their autographs. I went to grab a burger for dinner. Only to learn after that that the fries I ate contained 47% fats. I really do have a healthy diet.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was finding something to do online when I saw a completely pointless personality quiz, which was exactly what I was looking for! So I took it. And this was what it told me:       The Completely Pointless Personality Quiz     How completely pointless. I really wanted to find out that I'm a pocket watch. Well in that case, I hope it's a Swatch.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blah.  Since I can't entertain you today, I shall let Eric do the job. If you're having trouble expressing yourself, the person you should really turn to would be Eric. I would say that there's no better man for the job. But who's Eric you ask? Click  urlLink here  to see Eric convey an emotion. Or emotions, rather. I laughed at a few of them, others are quite dumb though and some are simply disgusting. Have fun anyway, this should keep you occupied for a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Happy 39th, Singapore. 
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Totally forgot about the dance practice in school this morning. (Sorry! =S)    I made it to church just in time for Sabbath School. Learnt about the three angels' message versus the three frogs' message in Revelations (Woo, big chapter!) from Auntie Pik Yee.    Had my first bible study lesson with Bee Guang after lunch.    Managed to go for band BBQ at yasi's house. The honeyed sausages and satays were tasty!    Met Pinhao on my way there. Been a while since I last saw him but couldn't stay to chit-chat because he was in the middle of a basketball game.    Saw Xiefen and some of her HCJC friends in the study room beside us. Holy hell, I never imagined that I would actually meet someone who was a more intensive bridge player than me and my classmates. But there they were sitted around a square table holding poker cards for more than four solid hours. They ate alot too, helped us to finish Ms. Chong's large birthday cake!    Made friends with Yingxu's brother, Xiao xiao/Edward/Juju. (I still don't know his real name.) Cute little Pri. 6 boy. We played a little catch and soccer with Zhuo Jing and Joanna, since everyone else were just busy barbequeing or eating.    Reached home at 11, couldn't do any homework.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I went to check my cca results after school yesterday, I got an A1 (Yay!), but so did everyone else. It was quite surprising actually, I don't even know if I did anything right in band for the past four years. Darn, if only it were my 'O' level result slip.    Today was a good, happy and fruitful day because I missed school. Played with the pedal some more in the morning because I've to pass it on to Nicholas tomorrow. I'm going to miss the amount of gain I managed to get out of it this past week although it did eat up a whole 9V battery.  Went down to Isetan with my mum and brother, got ourselves a mogu cushion each (Mine is bright orange! =)) and some new towels. Paid a hefty $36 for the nicely packaged 0.5mm in diameter polystyrene beads, but it's okay because this is more solid and it doesn't go out of shape easily like the cheaper $9.90 ones do. Now I'll have an additional thing to hug when I go to bed. The nice people there gave us a discount for a tower fan to thank us for patronising them and offered to deliver it to us free of charge so we didn't need to lug our shopping bags home. I'm enjoying the cool wind from the fan now, a break from the recent span of hot and humid weather.  Next, to Takashimaya's Sushi Tei for lunch. Saw MediaCorp artiste Cassandra Lee and two other actresses, my mum said she smiled at us but I was too occupied with heap of sushi in front of me  to notice. Then, to the departmental store to get myself some new clothes. (Yes, I finally got down to it.)  No more time for anything else, we caught a train back to Jurong East so I won't be late for cell group. Took the opportunity to go scouting for books at Popular again. Sadly enough, Tuesdays with Morrie was still out of stock so I left for MacDonald's empty handed. Met Shaun and Joel on the way there. Louis and Tricia joined us halfway, Nathaniel and Trudy joined the group at the traffic light, and Barbara, Nicholas and Wei Siang met us in Jurong Entertainment Center itself. It was past 7.30. So much for meeting in church at 7.00pm. This should tell you a lot about the punctuality of Jurong youths. It's an unspoken rule that the meeting times are always stated half an hour earlier than the actual meeting time for reasons we all know why.  We took quite some time settling down and actually getting down to ordering our food. Barbara treated me to popcorn chicken from KFC and I treated her to McFlurry from Macs. All this happened while Sergeoh and James waited alone in church for us to return. Cell was out in the open tonight and without bibles too, we just used the hour to catch up with each other. The breeze was cool; the porch lights were warm and cozy. Everything was perfect until Tricia, Trudy and Barbara all screamed in unison with the appearance of a little brown cat, just when Shaun was at the climax of his horror story. (He was the victim of attempted assault in school this week. He has a psycho maniac for a classmate, who tried back stabbing him, literally, with a penknife. Thank goodness his friends pushed him aside in time, or we'd have to have cell in NUH for the second consecutive week, after Victor's case of food poisoning and infected capillaries.) That has got to be the most frightening 5 seconds of my life, as far as I can recall.  We were too lazy to move after cell ended so we set up a little booth with baskets lined up at one wall, and us, standing at the opposite wall with an entire box of balls, all geared up to shoot. We got bored after a while because none of us managed to score, the balls simply bounced off the wall and we had to pick up the mess. So we decided to aim at Louis instead, after all, there was a larger chance of us actually hitting the target. Sergeoh didn't like the idea of just using one ball at a time, so he simply hurled the entire contents of the box at him. They all missed though, so we had to start picking up the mess again. But well, whoever knew the immense pleasure little inflated plastic coloured spheres could bring us.  Wayne decided sit through the full loop of the 334 bus ride to accompany me after everyone alighted seeing that I was all alone, but I think it's because he's too tired to walk after playing soccer. Haha, nevertheless, it was very nice of him to do so. Because of the delay during dinnertime, cell ended late, explaining why I only got round to blogging about the day's events at this time of the night. Say no more, my new cushion lies invitingly on my bed as I type.  Peace.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Back to the classic white colour. There aren't many colour choices when you have black as your background. I'm playing with the Ibanez TS7 Tubescreamer now. It's the first pedal that I really got to try out and it belongs to Sean. (Thanks for lending it to me and Nicholas!) Since no one else is at home, I can safely unleash the awesome power of the overdrive pedal! Muahaha! I hope the noisy construction work downstairs is loud enough so the neighbours won't trace the origin of the generated noise pollution to me alone. Initially I thought it was just to amplify the sound or something to that effect since it's named  'Tubescreamer' . I couldn't tell that the grey pedal was for overdrive effect when I first saw it until I received Sean's SMS. No wonder there was the tiny knob on the top labelled  'Drive' . How silly of me. I've also managed to lay my hands on Dan Brown's  Da Vinci Code  (Finally!) and  Angels and Demons  (The two bestsellers on Life! bestsellers list for the past few months) when I passed by MPH the day before. You won't be hearing from me for the next couple of days. 
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       No wonder I found this song so familiar when Dawn asked me to listen to it on Friday at Gramophone. I heard the punk rock version by New Found Glory somewhere last year when I first discovered them. These lyrics are adapted from the NFG version because Astraweb has yet to post the version by North. I don't think the lyrics should differ much (There's another version by B.B. King and Bette Milder). Nice ballad anyway, go listen.       Tonight it's very clear     As we're both lying here     There's so many things i want to say     I will always love you     I would never leave you alone          Sometimes i just forget     Say things i might regret     It breaks my heart to see you crying     I don't wanna lose you     I could never make it alone     I am a man who will fight for your honor     I'll be the hero you're dreaming of          We'll live forever     Knowing together that we     Did it all for the glory of love          You'll keep me standing tall     You'll help me through it all     I'm always strong when you're beside me     I have always needed you     I could never make it alone     I am a man who will fight for your honor   urlLink      I'll be the hero you've been dreaming of     We'll live forever     Knowing together that we     Did it all for the glory of love          Just like a knight in shining armor     From a long time ago     Just in time i will save the day     Take you to my castle far away     I am a man who will fight for your honor     I'll be the hero you're dreaming of          We're gonna live forever     Knowing together that we     Did it all for the glory of love     We'll live forever     Knowing together that we     Did it all for the glory of love          We did it all for love     We did it all for love     We did it all for love     We did it all for love   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>