<Blog>


<date>29,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						     Bad Weather, Bad Baseball   Yesterday Leah and i took a few Junior High youth to a Ft.Wayne Wizards baseball game. The weather was absolutely horrible. For late April, the weather should have been at least "jacket weather." But it was "witnercoat and beanie weather."  It was not that fun. But I'm not sure what was worse, the weather or the baseball.  God love the people that run the wizards, but do we really need 3 or 4 leagues of baseball in America? I love the game of baseball but i'm no good at it. Thus i don't play. Some of these Wizards shoud take my aproach and stop playing. Its almost painful to watch that kind of ball play. Maybe they haven't noticed that most profesional sports in America don't have 4 levels of "farm" teams. XFL didn't take, CBA shut down, so when is minor league baseball, at least the Low levels of the game, gonna shut down. Well...hopefully soon. I love the game of Baseball, and i want to see it get the press it deserves, but if you're not good at baseball, then don't play. No one wants to watch a game with  "average" baseball players. If i wanted that I'd go watch Church and Industrial league softball in a city park for free.  This has been a social comentary on the game of minor league baseball.    

						
</post>

<date>22,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, its official. I'm moving to California. I told  my church yesterday that I was leaving and i feel that a weight has been lifted off myshoulders. the kids in my youth groups took it well. I was sad afterwords, but i'm good. So here's the scoop.   I'm moving to Anaheim, CA and working as College Director/High School Assistant at the Crystal Cathedral in their Student Ministries department. That's the same place i interned for a few months at. I'm excited to be going out there. God has really blessed Leah and I's socks off with this move. If you are obedient to His Word and His call, He'll be FAITHFUL all the time! He has opened doors to So. Cal as i was going to manually close a door here in Indiana. So, its exciting to be getting out of Dodge so to speak. I'll be starting my position there, the last week in May.  Then i'll be flying back for my best bud's wedding in late June, then flying back to So. Cal for a  few weeks. Then flying back here for my other best friend's wedding in late July. Then going "home" for a few more weeks, only to come back to Ohio/Indiana and get married myself. so...its SUPER CRAZY now but...i wouldn't want it any other way!   Things that are super-cool to me right now:    urlLink amazon.com  coffee   urlLink Andrew W.K.  Chillout Sessions by  urlLink Ministry of Sound   urlLink Google  Leah the new Pedro the Lion record God's Faithfulness 

						
</post>

<date>10,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Wow! This is so much fun. I'm so excited to keep in touch with all of you via our new Web Log. There is so much to tell. Brian and I are both seemingly living life in the fast lane, but that's not all bad. Time is short now, but stay tuned for fun, gushy stories and info. I plan to update soon with wedding plans and details, new pictures and more. Blessing to you from us! 

						
</post>

<date>09,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						        The above pictures are from out trip to Southern California. The one on the left is from the airplane. That's the grand canyon. The one on the right is leah at Newport beach. It was sorta crummy weather, but we had a good time none the less. 

						
</post>

<date>09,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   this is cool.  urlLink email me.  

						
</post>

<date>09,April,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   This is the *brand new* web log for Brian Manley and Leah Pennington. (soon to be Mrs. Manley) Here is where you can find out what is going on in our lives between now and till we stop bloging.  

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi Again - sad day today b/c Brian left for Cali.  He arrived safely and all is well.  I can't believe he's gone already.  New on my end?- I've moved a load of things out of my apartment and will move the rest out the first week of June.  I'm ready to close the chapter here at HC. It's been a good run, but it's time to move on. I will be living with my great friends Angie and Larry White this summer in Ft. Wayne. So the best way to contact me is via my cell phone or my hotmail address.   Other things new on my end?- I'm completely addicted to talk radio. I never thought I would be, or if I was, would ever admit to it...but I am. I really like it!  Other joys in my life these days are simple things like great conversations with old friends, good books (She's Come Undone, Wally Lamb) and good coffee.    Hey B - do you think anyone reads these ramblings besides us?          Later Skaters- Leah 

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Oh how time flies when you're having fun!  The craziness continues, but so does God's amazing and perfect blessings. I got my top wisdom teeth out yesterday - OUCH!  Actually it went really well and they didn't have to use stitches or give me an ice pack for my face.  No chipmunk cheeks here, except for when i smile-but that's nothing apart from the normal. Brian took me in and pampered me all day-it was GREAT! Our wedding invitations are in and we'll be sending them out in mid-June. Watch your mailboxes for them-they're really different and we like them alot.  Also, on Monday the staff ladies and some students threw a shower for me, it was such a blessing a well needed break from the norm.   As the school year is ending and Brian getting ready to leave next week, reality is definitely setting in.  The ending of another chapter in life and the super exciting beginning new one about to begin - it's all surreal and bittersweet at the same time.  I'm faced daily with a miriad of emotions and things yet "to do."  Although it can be overwhelming at times, the blessings and newness of it all adds a new perspective that is all together refreshing and rejuvinating.   I think it was that silly Hope Floats movie then ended with the quote..."beginnings are always scary and ending are always hard, but it's the stuff in the middle that makes it all worth while."  Cheesy as it may be-i think that may sum up things for now.  And, tomorrow is a new day with new opportunities-seize them!   

						
</post>

<date>07,May,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey!  It's the long lost Leah.  Since my last blog, much has happened. Wedding plans are coming along and we're pretty well set for Aug. 24 - I can't wait to see you all there. Brian and I registered at Target and Bed, Bath and Beyond last weekend, which was fun for all involved.   Things at HC are going well, the year is ending quickly and graduation is right around the corner. (May 18) My position as RD ends effective June 1, so I'll be moving to Ft. Wayne for the summer. Brian leaves for Cali on May 25 and his first day is May 26.   I've sent my resume out for about 5-6 different jobs. I'm anxious to hear back from them especially since two of them were sent to Disneyland....YIPPEE!  Although, things seem to be a whirlwind right now around me and "us", it's been amazing to see God's faithfullness. Not only as a couple preparing for marriage and a move to the west coast but also individually. We are excited and know that the Lord has amazing things in store for us. He keeps confirming our decision to move time and time again and providing everything as we need it and most times even before we ask.  I think that's all for now.  Goodnight! 

						
</post>

<date>02,May,2002</date>
<post>

						
						        Does anyone read this blog anyway? are we writing this for any reason at all? just checking. Anyway, Arms and the Boy, my band, just released a 2 CD EP. One disc has 8 Arms and the Boy songs, the other disc has a 35 minute short film which the music was written for. The movie was really great for being a NO BUDGET film. Those who worked on it knocked the ball out of the park!  Its available through me or Josh Mackey, if you know him. Email me for info. Its only $5. where you gonna find that kinda bargan?  

						
</post>

<date>02,May,2002</date>
<post>

						
						        I got to see Damien Jurado and Pedro the Lion on tuesday night in Detroit. I was quite an awesome show. The new Pedro the Lion record is amazing and he played most of his songs from that record. Its a rather depresing record, and during the show he comented that the new album   urlLink Control   was his "empire strikes back."  You know, at the end of  Empire , Luke looses his hand, Han Solo is darn near dead, or so we think. So it looks as if Pedro the Lion will put out another record to finalize his past 2 records. He said that there may be "redemption" in the future record. that sounds cool to me. Also...Damien Jurado was awesome and tons of fun. Very weird to watch at first but then became amazing to watch. It was a blessing to watch 2 musical geniuses at work. The drive to Detroit sucked but the music made up for it. ROCK. 

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Howdy!  First and foremost Brian and I survived our road trip. We had a lot of fun and had absolutely no problems...Praise God!!  We left Sunday at about 10:30 a.m. and drove straight through until Monday at about 1:00 p.m. At that point neither one of us could go any further. We had made it to Gallup, New Mexico which is just on the border of Arizona. We took a nap, then got some dinner and then went back to bed for the night...needless to say, we were tired.  So on Tuesday morning we left at about 8:30 a.m. and arrived in sunny Anaheim, CA at about 6 p.m.    "News worthy road trip note"- when we entered Arizona, we were about 45 minutes north of Show Low where the 350,000+ acre fire is burning and they've evacuated the town. Anyway, the highway and desert around our road looked foggy, but it turns out it was smoke from the fire. It smelled awful and was really errie to drive through. It didn't clear up until we were passing through Flagstaff which is about half way through the state. Anyway, we were listening to talk radio (of course) and as we were driving, President Bush was flying over heading to Show Low to check it out and meet with fire fighters and victims.  It was so crazy for us to be in the heart of an area of national news.  Our hearts hurt for the people of Show Low and we prayed for a miracle to stop the blaze. It's only mere miles from the town and unless something changes it may wipe out the entire town and take everyone's homes.  We ARE so blessed, and take so much for granted!  Sidenote: We had a blast at Chad and Jenny's wedding, it was wonderful. The boys at Chad's wedding must have partied too much the night before because Brian was tired and out of it all Sunday. The evening was striaght out of a fairytale, complete with princess Jenny!   Also, it was the first time I had ever seen Brian in a tux...wow!...look out!  Current Update: So, last night was the Highschool kick off for youth group which went well and tomorrow we leave for Catalina Island for a highschool camping retreat. Next week we're celebrating the fourth at an Anaheim Angels baseball game.  I'll close for now and update more next week. Thanks for your prayers as we try to find some housing next week and also a job for me. The search continues.  talk to you later. How about this pledge of allegiance thing, huh?     

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi. Well, i'm all settled in at the Whites...my serrogate family FYI and having a blast. I've even started a new workout with Larry (dad), he's such a great motivator so I think I'll stick with it. I even ran yesterday, can you believe it?!?!  On the wedding front, the invitations are going out this week! And, speaking of weddings, one of Brian's best friends from home, Chad, is getting married this weekend which means that I'm picking Brian up from the airport on Thursday-YIPPEE!  I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HIM!   Then on Sunday we are starting out on our long awaited ROAD TRIP to Cali. We're taking Brian's car so he can have it out there with him. I'm making a mini-vaca out of it and staying until July 5. We hope to find an apartment and hopefully I wil be able to job interview. I'm also going on a highschool camping trip with him to Catalina Island for the weekend with his students. I'm so excited to meet them.  Until next time- "sing in the car. sing loud. sing long. sing bad."   

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello!  Well, today was the big moving day. Mom and Dad came down and helped me pack up and move all of my things out of the apartment. As exciting as it all was, it's seems a little surreal now that I'm sitting here alone in this big residence hall with an empty apartment. I'm moving my things to  Angie and Larry's house in Ft. Wayne tomorrow.  I'm anxious to see what the summer holds and thrilled to be living with them.  Sidenote:  Brian returns to Indiana for Chad and Jenny's wedding in exactly 12 days and counting. Can you tell I miss him or what?!?This long distance thing has been more difficult than I had originally imagined.  Anyway - wedding plans are coming along, I've potentially found some part-time work for the summer at an insurance office and I'm ready to relax and have a break. The last few weeks have been non-stop crazy.    Another Sidenote:  I got my feet tattoos redone on June 1 and they are healing up nicely this time. For those of you not in the know, the first time they didn't heal very well and the one even got infected...YUCK!  Not exactly a fabulous first time tattoo experience, but I'm glad I did it none the less. I will admit that it hurt A TON the second time...maybe I'm a wimp. Either way...it hurt.  I hope you are all doing well, I'd love to hear from you...God bless your socks off! - Leah       

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2002</date>
<post>

						
						       [My Office] I'm alive. don't anyone worry. [not that anyone would] i have made it to california!  i've been here 2 weeks now. i'm still liking the so cal lifestyle better than in the Mid West. its been fun. i really hit the ground running here. a few days after i arived here, the high school group had an all nighter. that was rough. being up for over 27 hours is tough. but i'm alive to tell about it. so...indiana/ohio people...feel free to email me and say hi. i'm not borred at all, but i want to hear from some familiar voices/faces. peace.  

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   I am officially an California resident. I've now got Cali plates and a Cali license. Sure, it took 4 hours to get it, but at leat i got em'.  DMV's are not fun to anyone, but California DMVs are the most hideous and nasty things you've ever seen. There were more people at the DMV  in line than i went to High School with. Hundreds of people, who all don't want to be there, and we're waiting in hard plastic chairs or in que lines. I bet that  hell  is a lot like a  California DMV. I think Dante talked about that in is book...oh...maybe not. Anyway...it was aweful, but i made it through it. later.  I did finally get to go to a concert on monday. There's this club about a couple miles down the road from where Leah and i will live and they get some great bands. I got to see a couple of bands that i've been listening to for years and never had the chance to see them. One of the bands  urlLink [Hey Mercedes]   is comprised mostly of a band from the early days of the Indie rock scene that really introduced to that style of music. Anyway...it was such a treat to see those guys. Also,  urlLink Piebald played. This was a band me and my buds from college always listened to,hung out to, drove to, and acted stupid to. So it was very cool to hear them play songs that brought back memories of hanging at college. Note- This is my first nostalgic-college-memory-thing. It was cool though. later  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   we finally landed an apartment! yeah...thats exciting news in our own little world. its a nice ol' 1 bedroom place in Anaheim just seconds away from Edison Field(Angels) and Anaheim Pond (Might Ducks). Not that we'll go to games there all that often. its a cool place to be. anyway. thats my 2 cents.   

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, here's the scoop for the week.  First, my mom came and visited this week. She came Thursday and so we were able to spend some much needed mother/daughter time together. With the summer being so crazy, it's been hard for us to connect and so we ran some errands, altered my dress...which is actually my mom's wedding gown. It's beautiful and I can't wait to wear it!  Then on Friday, Dona drove over to Ft. Wayne and my mom and I met her for lunch and then we went to the Rose Garden, The Chamber of Commerce and the Pfeiffer House (where the rehersal dinner is going to be held) We had a great time bonding and talking about all of the wedding details. Oh, I'm so excited. The wedding is going to be so wonderfully perfect!  And then today my "Aunt" Jan, Angie, my sister Sarah, my mom and I went to Bryan, OH today for a bridal shower. Some of Dona's friends from the neighborhood and church threw it for me and it was lovely! We had a great time and it was great to meet all of the friends of Brian's family. We had brunch, which was delicious, and then Dona gave a very sweet toast for Brian and I. Then I opened all of the gifts. Everyone was so thoughtful - I felt like a princess being pampered for the afternoon. What a great day!...What a great week.  God is so good! - to give us exactly what we need when we need it. 

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   The Samantha Runnion funeral was at the CC last night. it was crazy around here. There were over 5,000 people at our church last night and we had youth group at the same time. some of our kids had to park across the street to get to youth group. anyway..about every single news channel within 80 miles of here was in our parking lot yesterday. it was a busy place. I guess it went well. i didn't see it on TV but i heard it was a good funeral. It was a big deal for this area to put this somewhat behind them. Just keep praying for her family. later. 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello!  Well it's been another whirwind weekend, full of fun, travel and quality time with Brian. He came in late Thursday night (7\18) to Toledo and his mom and I picked him up and then went out to eat. It was so great to see Brian again, of course. Then our friends Andy and Meri got married on Saturday and we all had a good time. Two weddings down, one to go. For obvious reasons I'm partial and most excited for it!  Brian's flight was delayed and then canceled on Sunday night and then again on Monday night so he didn't fly out until early this morning. I can' t say I was disappointed in the least. It gave us some much needed time to spend with each other and chat. The cool thing was that his dad was leaving for business today too and they were on the same intial flight out of Toledo to Phili, PA. God is so faithful!  That's all for now. Buh, bye  :)  

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Here are some recent photos:::::::::::::::.........         

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello Again!  As I promised, I'm here to give you the scoop. First and foremost-Brian is coming home in four days-YIPPEE. Of course I'm excited for all of the obvious engaged, love struck reasons. But also, because our time in California was so great for us and our relationship. We grew so much and were challenged in so many ways that we've moved into a whole new realm...and it's fantastic!   I went with Larry and Angie to the Rose Gardens tonight and we looked around and planned out the ceremony and where we'll put everything and everybody. Oh, I'm so excited...it's going to perfect!  Things are coming together so well and stress free. By the way, the last few invitations are being sent out tomorrow, so if anyone doesn't have theirs by the end of the week, e-mail me so I can send out another one. Also, don't forget your  RSVP! Okay, enough of the task driven side and onto more emo-  Although the summer is only half complete, I can't believe the wedding is next month. It's been an amazing time for me and the stage I'm at in my life and I know now more than ever the true sovereignty, grace and faithfullness of the Christ. Although most of these new or reminder revelations have come through challenging and often difficult times, it's been so amazing and profitable. One of my dear friends sent me a card lately and she wrote inside several encouraging and uplifting things. One thing that will stay with me was this, "hang in Leah, although the stretching may be painful and unclear now the view from the other side will be perfectly complete and inspiring." Of course this, and a multitude of other reasons is why I'm blessed to call her 'friend.'  goodnight. 

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						          

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello!  First of all thank you for taking time to catch up with our lives. From what I hear, there are a lot of you who are checking in with us, which is GREAT! We love it, and now that most of the invitations are out, I promise to be better about updating so you have lots of new, fun things to read.  Like Brian said, my time in California was seemingly a whirlwind, but we had fun, grew and were blessed. Of course I'm so excited that he's heading back to the midwest in a matter of days.  To update you a bit: the Catalina trip was a blast and a gave me a wonderful opportunitity to get to know the kids and hang out with them. I had never been to Catalina and so it was as exciting for me as it was the kids. We camped just outside of a town called Avalon with cute little shops and restaurants. Brian spoke for the weekend and did a fabulous job. Of course I'm trying not to be biased, but the kids really responded to him and God used him in a mighty way.  And the fourth of July was super fun! The Angels didn't play so well, actually they were pretty bad, but we had fun and the fireworks following the game were beautiful. The turned all of the stadium lights off and played patriotic music in the background.   As for the apartment hunt...it was frustrating, disappointing and at some points almost painful, but God used it to bring us closer and that made it worth while. We found a two bedroom apartment that was exactly what we both wanted near downtown Orange, but God made it clear that it was not for us. So as disappointed as we were, we started looking again and found a one bedroom apartment in Anaheim that ended up being less expensive as well. God is faithful, it's usually us who are not or at least we get impatient in the process. So we are convinced that this is the place that God has for us.  The flight home was safe and went pretty quickly. Of course they usually do because I, as well as Brian, love to chat with people we sit next to. I flew in Tuesday night and then left this morning to come back to Ft. Wayne. I spent some extra time with the parents in Mich. and wanted to be home for my dads heart catherization which went really well.   So, I'm back and ready to get going on the wedding again. I had a nice break, but now it's time to get to work. You know it's kind of funny, I'm used to telling people the date of the wedding as "we're getting married in August"...and now I can say..."next month."  WOW!  This summer has really flown. Well, I'll update more later. Bye for now.  

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...after a long road trip, cross country, taking a youth group to Catalina Island, marriage counceling, trying to find an apartment, and trying to get in some "quality" time, Leah has left Southern Cal. I dropped her off at LAX this morning at 6 am. (i never knew what Southern Cal looked like that early in the morning) Anyway...i'm bummed she's leaving yet excited because i'll be home for Andy Sikora's wedding next week so....i'l see her. But the time out here was well spent. We looked and looked and looked for apartments, and i think after all the work, we landed a place in Anaheim. We have yet to sign the deal in to being, but i'll probably take care of that later this or next week. I'm sure leah will expound on the apartment and make it sound better than i could. But thats it for now i think. later.  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi!  Well I went this weekend to Chicago to visit my dear friends Liz and Gavin!  THEY ARE THE BEST! We had such a great visit and it was good to hang out with them one last time before the big move. It seemed really odd for Brian to not be with us however. And speaking of Brian...he's coming home TOMORROW. He flys in at midnight and then we are staying with my sister in her new house in Indy. Then we're headed up to Fort Wayne to finish up some last details. I know the week is going to fly by and that I won't be able to update as often as I'd like...so my apologies in advance. We'll be sure to update you when we get back from the honeymoon in September. Wow...so I guess that puts us officially today at 5 days and a wake up until the most beautiful and perfect wedding day ever!  YIPPEE!  goodnight. 

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello!  Time just keeps slipping by...we're officially at 9 days and a "wake up". Most exciting is the countdown to Brian coming home which is officially at 3 days and a "wake up."  Other exciting news...Brian moves into our apartment this Friday!  Fun-times :)   As for the wedding update...all of the big things are done...there' s just a few items left and after that it's all small details.  I'm so happy to have almost everything complete so that when Brian finally does get here, we can actually have some time together that is not "task-driven."   My dress is altered and cleaned and GORGEOUS!...if I may say so myself. Oh, I can't wait! Nothing much else is new...but if something does come up...I'll be sure to update the blog. Byefornow!   

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						        tee hee hee.  The coolest as of late: books:: The ragamuffin Gospel by Brendan Manning Survivor by Chuck Palahniuk The full Message Bible  music::  urlLink Aloha , sugar (indie rock with a vibraphone)  urlLink Sasha , airdrawndagger  urlLink Hey Mercedes  IZ (some killer hawaiian music)   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Holy cow. It seems as if i've spent my whole summer working on not working for the last 2 weeks of august. confused. yup, me too. let me explain.  my whole summer has been in So Cal and getting aclimated to the culture, kids, people, etc. so it takes a while to get in a groove, and i've finally gotten into that groove. And now i'm heading home to get married. which rules, but i've spent all summer being detached from friends, Leah, myself, but i got a ton of stuff done. I guess it's a small sacrifice to loose a whole summer working hard, to be rewarded with spending the rest of my life with the coolest chick around. good trade off i think.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   The countdown continues...only 14 days and a "wake up"...ohhh how exciting. As everything is getting finished...it's mind boggling to me how fast the summer has passed. August used to seem so far away and now it's mere weeks until the big day!    Angie and I finished the cake stand yesterday and it's beautiful. If you don't know about the cake stand, you'll see it at the reception, if you do...it looks great, just like I had imagined. I'm meeting again with the florist on Monday and the goal is to have everything finished by next Sunday before Brian flys into town!  I can't believe it's only a week from this Sunday.   Tomorrow I'm headed down to Indy again to see Sarah. We're having one last weekend of sister bonding time prior to the wedding. While I'm there, we are going to the Dave Matthews Band concert at the Verizon Music Center on Sunday night which should super fun.   That's all for now! Buh-bye ~ 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello, hello!  Today is officially 18 days and a "wake up" until the wedding.  I"M SO EXCITED! Words do not begin describe the happiness and anxiousness. Today was spent running errands and finalizing checks for the wedding. We're pretty well set and almost done.    As for me personally, things are super on the home front. Angie and Larry (and Stuart too) are so amazing and have just blessed my socks off this summer. God has been so faithful through them. However, the summer is getting long and I'm antsy to see Brian and to move to California. It's time.  I'm not sure what I will do with myself when Brian and I can hang out all of the time. And at the end of the day neither one of us has to drive home or fly across the country...we will both already be home. What a beautiful thing!  All in due time!    

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Before I begin...Brian, the web log looks great! I like the new design...You're the best!!!!  Ok, first and foremost I must draw attention to the fact that we're officially at 21 days and counting.  And now onto the important stuff!  I went to Indy yesterday and returned today to help my sis with the big move into her house and out of her apartment. All went very well. She had almost everything packed when I got there yesterday and then today she had quite a few friends all ready to help today. I'm so excited for her because the house is so nice and in such a great neighborhood.  On other fronts...as exciting as the countdown is, things are simultaneously becoming a little crazed ...so now, more than ever, your prayers are much appreciated!  Till next time... 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   It's officially August, YIPPEE! The countdown has begun, only 23 days and counting! Things are starting to pick up and I'm trying to finish all of the details and get everything done. It's fun, but there's a little more pressure now as time is winding down.   The other day, I went blueberry picking with Angie and her niece and her niece's kids...we had so much fun. Yesterday I finally got to hang out with my beautiful friend Rebecca over lunch and I've been able to spend some wonderful time with my other very dear friend Molly. What a great blessing to have such wonderful friends.  Tonight is a big night in Ft. Wayne, they are raising the roof on the coliseum. They are opening up the parking lot and allowing people to come in and watch. They are even bringing in large spot light to illuminate the extravaganza. I drove by today and some guy already had his junk food trailer all set up. I'm interested, but the only thing is that they are starting at 2 a.m and it will be up at 5 a.m. A lot of people are going as skeptics. Because of the age of the current roof there is a large possibility that it may cave in on itself or fall off the crane attachments. Either way, if I do go, it will be in my PJs.  Tomorrow I'm going down to Indianapolis to visit with my sister for the weekend and help her move into her new house from her current apartment. She is moving into a really neat subdivision with two of her friends from her Bible study at church. She's anxious to leave her old apartment behind. It was only blocks from the Indy Speedway which was super crazy on race weekends.   For those of you news buffs like me...Praise God the two abducted girls in California were found alive and unharmed today! What is the world coming to?  That's all for now. Thanks for checking in with us. 

						
</post>

<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   The below story took place just down the street from us at our new apartment. we could see the lights all night long. wacky stuff!  BOTCHED ROBBERY BECOMES STANDOFF Sunkist Car Wash in Anaheim is evacuated and assistant manager locks men inside.    ANAHEIM – A botched car-wash robbery turned into an all-day, armed standoff Sunday after employees of the Sunkist Car Wash locked three men inside the building and called police.   One man surrendered after an hour, but the others remained holed up inside for more than seven hours and were still inside the building in the 2500 block of Lincoln Avenue late Sunday.   About 8:30 p.m., police drove an armor-plated vehicle up to the building and tossed a cellular phone inside.   "When you hear the telephone ringing, pick it up and talk to us," police said over a loudspeaker. "No one's going to get hurt."   But the suspects refused to answer.   The attempted robbery started about 3 p.m. after employees noticed the men eyeing an office containing the car wash's safe.   First, they bought three Snapples and some cashews and hung around the waiting area, said cashier Jackie Contreras, 20. They played a golf video game and started watching her.   "One of them was looking at me, and every transaction he would look," Contreras said. "I think he didn't know if he would rob me or the safe."   Contreras said one of the suspects, described as a man with a shaved head in his early 20s, was standing near the door to the car wash office. She told him to move away from the office three times, but he didn't go anywhere. "He said, 'I understand,' but he didn't move," she said.   Contreras said she also saw him signaling to someone inside the office, and then she noticed that the other two men had disappeared.   She ran out of the car wash and got the attention of Assistant Manager Ramon Meza, who was standing in the detailing area.   "She was running scared and told me we were getting robbed," Meza said.   Meza, finding that the men had closed themselves into an office, quickly evacuated the business. Two employees and three customers were inside. Then he chained the outside door, normally a nighttime security precaution.   Customers, realizing what was go on, left their cars and ran away.   "I was getting out of my car and saw everyone running, so I just ran," said Luis Rubio. "I just wanted to take my baby and go." Rubio left his green Dodge Ram parked in the car-wash line and ran away with his 21/2-month-old son.   Police said they were glad Meza locked the men inside the building.   "It is unusual ," said Sgt. Rick Martinez. "And it was very fortunate for us."   Snipers, SWAT members and the police K-9 unit surrounded the building and the Jiffy Lube next door.   Duane Stout was about to finish paying for his oil change at the Jiffy Lube Station next door when he was told to leave by police. He left his blue Cadillac in the parking lot.   Later, he stood and watched as police hid behind his car with guns pointed at the building.   "They're using my car as a shield," he said. "I don't think I'm coming back here again."   Police said they believed the men inside had weapons.   The man who surrendered had a shaved head, a tattoo of teardrops near his eyes and a large tattoo on his back.   The Jiffy Lube manager, Andy Pahl, said there were two cars stuck inside his business.   "They had been drained (of oil) already, so I can't let them go," he said. "I've got to go back tonight to do those oil changes."   Police said at the scene they were in no rush to force the men from the building.   Martinez said that police would exhaust every tool before sending in officers - possibly sending in a robot with a camera to spot the men.   "Time is on our side," he said. "We could be here until morning."   HERE IS THE NEWEST REPORT ABOUT THE STORY: Standoff at Anaheim car wash ends, two suspects remain at large.  One suspect is custody for attempted robbery.  By ZAHEERA WAHID  The Orange County Register       Police came up empty after a nearly 12-hour standoff at an Anaheim car wash with two men suspected to be holed up inside. Anaheim police entered the barricaded Sunkist Car Wash at about 1:30 a.m. with SWAT members, cameras and canines, but found nothing.   "It's not unusual," said Anaheim Police Sgt. Rick Martinez. "As frustrating as it can be sometimes, it's just part of the job. ... Who knows, they probably got out before we even got here."   Police had been trying to coerce out the suspects they believed were locked inside the car wash building since about 3 p.m. Sunday. There were originally reported to be three suspects who were allegedly trying to rob the car wash safe, but one surrendered about an hour after police surrounded the place. The man, in his early 20s and identified only as   "Caspar," was arrested, and he told police there were two men still in the building. Witnesses also said there were two men still in the building. Martinez said "Caspar" and car wash employees would be questioned further as part of the investigation to figure out exactly what had happened.   "There's no explanation," Martinez said." All you can work on is what people tell you."     

						
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

						
						    WE MADE IT!  Leah and I are officially married, vacationed, moved in to our California home and back to work. My head is still spinning from all the craziness..but that's normal right? I'm sure that Leah will expound more on our little vacation-wedding thing...but i'll just say this.... Jamaica was rad. Being married is rad. moving into a new apartment right as you get off your plane sucks. Unpacking sucks. Leah is rad. Ikea is rad.   Right after we got back, on labor day Leah, her parents and myself went to Ikea (a really cool furniture store) and bought an awesome RED couch, a cool little chair, a couple of wooden chairs for our "dining room" and the coolest entertainment center for our tv and stereo (and my PS2).  It was such a long day of shopping and waiting and moving Leah's Dad's trailor (which can easily hold a car) up and down California freeways around the Ikea parking lot. it was fun though.  Anyway...thanks to everyone who was at our little party. I had fun. I hope you did too. I'm truly glad i'll only do that once, but i really did have fun seeing all of my old buds and some of Leah's friends. thanks. later. 

						
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   * 

						
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   How bout them ANGELS? i'ts so cool to be in the town where the best baseball team in the world resides. Anaheim folks are going nuts around here. i drove through the parade this morning to get to work. It took me twice as long to get to work. But boy were the car horns honking! anyway...its cool. But next week we'll all forget and look forward to the Mighty Ducks to win the Stanley cup and for the San Diego Chargers to win the superbowl....then...southern California will have dominiated in ALL sports for the 2002-2003 season. Wouldn't that be cool?      I'm thinking that an APPLE I-POD is like the coolest thing around right now. Just to think of a device where i could put ALL of my music and take it with me...that may be the coolest invention since the George Foreman Grill.  So..all of you who love me...should look in to getting me an I-POD for Christmas. It's just around the corner. :)  

						
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Here are some pictures from the past weekend. Dusty Abshire, our old college buddy, came out this weekend to see the "perfect world" of California.  While he was here... he/we had an extraordinary time. Dusty met Reggie Miller of the Pacers and got his autograph. We saw Tim Mann from the band FOCUSED at a used record store. (only old HxC guys would know of Tim) We were running out of gas on the way home from Hollywood so we HAD to stop at the next exit, and it just happened to be Compton, CA.  Which, all you old Gangta rap fans know, is VERY GHETTO! It was freaky for a few minutes. But hey...we needed gas! Like i said, we went to Hollywood, and it, as usual, sucked. Its such a dump. Anyway...yesterday we went to Disney Land. Leah, Dusty, my friend Chuck, and myself went. Chuck got us in cuz he works there.  California Adventure was cool. The actual Disney land was weak. Here are some pictures!      In front of California Adventure    Leah sitting on a bench made from giant pop-cicle sticks. This was in the "a bugs life" area.   Here's the WORLD SERIES from the freeway by our house. We were driving, thats why its blurry.   Dusty, Brian, Chuck   Here we all are infront of a well manicured Mickey Mouse flower arangement.  

						
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   I know leah said that life in So Cal is great, it is but.....its crazy at the same time. Like yesterday...i went to get my hair cut at a place called AMERICAN CUTS. I walk in...and...no one spoke English! It was all girls speaking Vietnamese and very poor broken English. So..needless to say...i had a hard time telling the gal cutting my hair HOW to cut it. well...She obviously didn't know what i said cuz she butched my hair pretty good. I think i told her about 2 inches on the top...well..its now about an inch. I look like i could join the Marines right away. I was bumed at first...but hair grows back. American Cuts....yeah right!   Angels are on today in the Series. So...the freeway by our house will probably be all jammed up. Its sorta cool though. Knowing that i can see the lights from the stadium from our house..then watch it on TV. GO ANGELS!!   THINGS I'M IN TO RIGHT NOW     urlLink Karate -some boots---amazing jazz-indie rock (Chris and Andy...i'm sending you a coppy)     urlLink Waxwing -Nobody can take what everybody owns --- Its good to listen to passionate/emotional music when all the stuff on the radio sucks and is void of emotion and creativity     urlLink Cave In -Tides of Tomorow--- Only the best band no one has ever heard of. (well...except for cool people)  Punch Drunk Love--Leah and i are gonna try to see this today. It looks awesome. By the guy who did Magnolia.   Anaheim Angels-- Its good to see my local team do well. Its something us Orange County folks can be proud of. Lot of bandwagoners though.  

						
</post>

<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Life in So. Cal. is great and we're having fun getting adjusted and settling in.  Last weekend we took the jr. high and high school students to Six Flags Magic Mountain for the day as part of a weekend event called CONVERGE. We spent Friday night at a nearby church with other youth groups and about 400+ youth. Then early Saturday we headed north to the "Mountain" as the kids call it.    On Tuesday we had a surprise visit from my friends from Jamaica. Jim, Penie and their three children are on furlough right now and they are visiting the west coast and several attractions. They called us from Mission Viejo, about an hour north from L.A. so they came and took us out to dinner and hung out. Then they spent the night at our apartment complex in their RV they are traveling in. On Wednesday they came to the church and I gave them a tour and then Brian and I took them out to lunch. Later that day they took off for their next destination. It was so great to see them and I was thrilled that they were able to meet Brian. Which, by the way, they loved him....I knew they would.   

						
</post>

<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						       

						
</post>

<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, it's been over a month since our last blog, so we hope that we still have a faithful few to check up on us. So much has happened and I'll try to fill you in as simply as possible. I'm officially a California resident as of today. The DMV was a crazy experience, but I made it through and it was well worth it because of the beautiful new driver's license I know posses.  Brian and I went to Newport Beach with the student leaders from the youth group and we had a great time and we stayed the weekend at a beach house.  Then last weekend we went to Sacramento for the Youth Specialties conference which is a weekend seminar for youth pastors. It was a great time and we learned a lot and were able to meet some really cool people.  This month at Youth Group we are having a big outreach each Wednesday called Outrageous October. We have theme nights which are fun, but they are a lot of work. I've been filling in temporarily at the student ministries office (where Brian works) to help them during this busy time and to give me something to do till I found a job. Which speaking of...I just got offered a position at the Children's Hospital here in Orange County in their PR department. It's such a blessing and answer to prayer. Ever since we moved here, I've had my eye on this job and so I'm thrilled to take the position.  This weekend we're off to a near by church where area youth groups are meeting to have fun, hang out, and do a climbing wall, etc. and then on Saturday we're going to Six Flags Magic Mountain. It should be a great time, but a long weekend. Then next weekend we have nothing planned and we couldn't be happier. Then the last weekend of the month our friend Dusty is coming to visit. So we have a busy month ahead of us, but it should fun. We're excited for November when things will slow down a little bit. We love you and miss you and thank you for all of your prayers, they are felt and appreciated. 

						
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Merry Christmas! Although the weather is not too convincing here in So. Cal (65), we are so excited to be celebrating our first Christmas together as husband and wife. We hear and see from our family and the news that the midwest has been pelted with snow. It's been an interesting few weeks, but nothing has been more adventurous than the past weekend. Where to start I'm not sure, other than to say that everything is ok.   It all started last Saturday night. Brian was cleaning the bathroom (to surprise me while I was out) and accidentially knocked the curling iron off the counter and it turned on. Needless to say, when the phone rang, he didn't realize it and stepped on the curling iron burning the underside of his toes...OUCH!  On the other end of the phone was none other than yours truly calling to say that I had been punched and mugged in the parking lot of a local WalMart. Yes, you read correctly. This guy came from between two cars, I looked up then he looked down and pretened to walk the other way. Suddenly he turned, punched me in the chest which knocked me off balance and then he grapped my purse off of my shoulder. This other guy drove up and he jumped in the "get away car" and were laughing histericially. I chased the car through the parking lot to get the license plate number. I was successful, except for one number. I stopped a car driving past and screamed for him to chase the car and get the plate # and direction they were headed. Luckily this guy was one of my guardian angels that night and did what I asked and returned. This young couple walked up to me b/c they heard me screaming for someone to call 911, they had and handed me their phone. I talked to the dispatcher and they the young woman walked me to my car. Praise God I had my keys in my hand, so the car was safe and sound. There was an awesome older hispanic man waiting by my car who saw me running and yelling. In the chaos of the moment I left my car door open and bags laying on the ground. So the police showed up and I talked to him, just as Brian showed up. We all went into the store and I went back and looked at the surveliance camera. It was really sickening watching my own demise on film, but the great part is that it is all on film!  It was all premeditated, the camera showed that they had been watching me, then drove around the aisle dropped the theft off and then waited to pick him up. The police officer said that it will be charged as a felony since it was a theft and an assult. So he might spend a few years in jail! YIPPEE! After we were finished, we came home and spent the next 2 hours on the phone canceling my phone, credit cards, bank account and trying to remember what all I had in my purse. The only things that I think they really got of any value were my clie' and $20. Then our circuit breaker freaked out in our apartment and we had no power until Sunday.   On Sunday afternoon Lori, my dear friend, stopped over to be a wonderful friend and give me a hug. While she was here we were in the kitchen where a candle was burning on the counter. She reached over it and suddenly her newly dry-cleaned sweater went up in flames. The chemicals from the dry-cleaning were burning and her sweater was ingulfed. We were screaming and hitting her with towels. After the flames were out we were amazed that her sweater wasn't even singed because the flame was burning on chemicals only and not her sweater.   So she left, unharmed, and we had lunch and thought we'd load the dishwasher and relax before the college kids came over for our Christmas Party. After we stared the dishwasher, water started spuuing out from the bottom like some sort of funky fountain and flooding our kitchen floor. At this point we looked at each other, laughed, grabbed some towels and called maintenance "again." The great news was three fold 1.) I didn't get hurt, stabbed or shot by the mugger, 2.) For the 4-5 "tramatic" things that happened, we have 400-500 things to be thankful for and ways that we are blessed by God and 3.) We know that our marriage is stronger and they we can survive just about anything :)    We are happy to report that our Christmas was less chaotic! We got up and had a Christmas breakfast of champions, cinnamon rolls! Then we open presents, the funny thing is that my sister got me a really cool purse for Christmas! Also, "santa" brought us NFL Blitz for our PS2...so Brian showed me how to play and I actually like it....a lot!  Then we had lunch...I made Brian a Christmas "steak"....we didn't want to do turkey or ham...so we improvised! I think I did okay with my first shot at Christmas dinner...I made some of Brian's favorites and so he was happy. Needless to say we are blessed and we had a great day!     

						
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey everyone. This is brian. I have a new Cell Phone number. you can now reach me, at my ever so cool phone @  714-396-4444 . thats right. 4444. i begged and got an easy to remember number. kewl huh. call me! 

						
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    I GOT TO MEET BIFF!!!!               That's right! I got to meet Back to The Future's Biff, aka, Tom Wilson at the men's ministry bible study on Monday. He was a rad guy with a great story. He signed my Back to the Future DVD set. It was fun talking to him and i was surprised he was willing to beat on my head for a picture. He made me bow to him first....he was funny. The other guy in the picture is Dan, a student in the College minstry. anyway....that made my night. Good start to a new year! 

						
</post>

<date>04,January,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      WAY TO GO BUCKS!   Who woulda thunk it? how are the OSU buckeyes the best college football team in the nation? That's so amazing to me. In my lifetime, i didn't think i'd ever see it. The bucks being good. Wouldn't you know it, as soon as i move out of the midwest, the Bucks win the biggest bowl game of the year.  Well...i cheered on the most i could from the left coast. ROCK ON! 

						
</post>

<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   HAPPY NEW YEAR! its the big OH THREE! yikes. how did that happen. Well...the year is off to a good start. My parents and brother and his buddy were out from Ohio from the 27th to the 1st. It was great having them here. It was like being home, but without the snow and junky weather. I was sad when they left. You know thats weird...in high school...i didn't want anything to do with my family. Now hanging out with them is such a blast. Maybe if they stayed for a month...then i'd be sick of them. I don't know.  Anyhoo...i think the start to a new year, and capping off a old one is cool. Every magazine and TV channell has their top of 2002 kinda thing. I want to do one here. And since you can't tell me no...i'm gonna.   BEST OF 2002    RECORDS  Isis-Oceanic Minus The Bear-Highly Refined Pirates Frou Frou-Details Dillinger Escape Plan-Irony is a dead scene Coheed and Cambria Hey Mercedes The Chemical Brothers- Come With Us Groove Armada- Another Late Night The Flaming Lips-Yoshimi battles the pink Robots Hot Water Music-Caution Jimmy Eat World-Bleed American Sense Field-Tonight and Forever Mastodon Bright Eyes-Lifted... Cave In- Tides of Tomorow      I think that will do   MOVIES  Lord of The Rings -2 Towers xXx Punch Drunk Love Adaptation Spider-Man Orange County   BEST THINGS ABOUT 2002  Getting Married!!!!! Watching my best friends get married Driving acrost the country to move to Cali Tony Hawk 4 Mp3 Players Seeing Spider-Man with Chad Cronin the day it came out Also...cutting in line to see Starwars with Chad and Vince at 12:00am in Goshen Having my Family out for Christmas  Watching the Anaheim Angels win the World Series just down the street from our house Realizing that the Beatles are the best and most amazing band of all time.  OUT...   

						
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   VEGAS BABY!  VEGAS!   As you may have guessed...Brian and I just got back from a whirlwind vacation to Vegas. My wonderful husband planned a surprise long weekend getaway for us. We took off on Friday Morning and started driving...I was oblivious to our final destination until we came around the bend in the road and the sing read LAS VEGAS...210 miles.  I can't tell you how excited I was. We've talked about going to visit since we're so close, compiled with the fact that I've never been...it was the perfect vacation spot. With President's day today, it made for an extra long weekend.   We had such a great weekend! We even walked the entire length of the strip....that's a lot of walking. It's a fun place, almost too much at times.....Sensory overload!  None-the-less, it was a great getaway weekend, restful, fun and exciting. We gambled a bit here and there, deciding that Black Jack was our favorite. We even came home, up $8. I know, I know...big rollers...but we had fun and lost no money....YIPPEE!  Thanks Bri for a fabuous weekend...I have the best husband ever!!!!!  Till next time...     go to  urlLink THIS SITE  to see some pictures from trip. (if the picture doesn't show up above) 

						
</post>

<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So...its raining here finally! i'm actually excited about that.  Its been fun to pull out "rainy day" music from my collection and just chill out. That's something i miss about the midwest, having rainy day music. Stuff you can't listen to when its super sunny and beautiful. One of those records is MASSIVE ATTACK's "100th Window" It is the best chill-out, trip-hop, rainy day record. Listen to it online.Their website is very cool as well.       Rain seems to make life slow down a bit doesn't it?  That's a nice change of pace for life out here. It's TOO NICE here at times that you loose site of the joy of crummy days.   

						
</post>

<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   YO! Well...after formating my hard drive TWICE, and reinstalling all my software TWICE, My comptuer is back on line and in full effect! It was a mess...if you really wanna know...just ask later. So..this is my first blog since the computer fiasco.    Here's the deal. The weather out here is crazy! They called for rain both friday and saturday...its saturday...Sunny and 80. so...the weather around here is rockin!  You have to check out the NEW  urlLink Johnny Cash Video   urlLink  for the song HURT. It is the most beautiful yet sad Johnny Cash memorial-type video. He's not dead yet...but he's very old. It seems as if he had a choice, this is how he'd go out. And actually its his first video in 15 or so years. It has immages of him in old movies, him in concert, clips from the Jesus video he helped produce. And it's a Nine Inch Nails cover. It makes me cry every time i see it. Let it move you.  check it out at  urlLink his website .      Another STAR sighting...I met Ben Stein yesterday. He was speaking at the Nixon Library about his new book and signed it for me nad we talked for like 2 seconds. I brought my camera for a picture...but it ran out of batteries right as i was getting the picture taken. it sucked. Oh well....at least i have the memories. Stein was really cool and really emotional when he talked about Nixon and also his parent. But I do advise you check out his new book. "How to ruin your life"  It's this satirical opposite approach to comedy. Its full of Ways to ruin your life. Like: "reaize that you're the center of the universe", "Hang out with the wrong crowd", Make other people feel small", and my favorite: "Know that the rules of reasoable, decent conduct don't apply to you." Its just funny. And when he signed my book...he told me to "STAY COOL!" Words from the man.  later skaters      

						
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      Leah::Molly::Minta 

						
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						        our friends molly and minta are visiting with us for the week. this is the crew at church this past sunday. its beautiful around here.  

						
</post>

<date>26,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm having the hardest time getting free web space and getting pictures up on line. so...leah and i might get a web site. i don't know why i'm sharing this on line...but i am. anway... if we a website we might dirrect you to that from the blog...along with the blog...but...it might have a message board, bigger pictures to print out...if you'd even want to...I also want a space where I can put up some of my digital art and stuff like that. PC wallpaper etc. if anyone cares...let me know what you think.   

						
</post>

<date>24,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   i got sick of the old blog's art,  and the armsandtheboy.com site...where i was squating some of our pictures and files got shut down...so new look...new art...cuz i'm bored and feeling sassy. i'm trying to figure out how to widen out the text part of the blog...oh well. any HTML guys out there that can help...kick me down an email. hotwaterbrian@hotmail.com  

						
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hey....here are some pictures from the snowy weekend last week.    urlLink www.geocities.com/musicismath78/index.html   

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   We felt like we were missing out on the snow and weather in the MidWest and so we decided to go play in it for a weekend. We took the HS Youth Group up to Big Bear (mountain) this past weekend and was it fun! About half of the kids that went had never seen "real" snow or has never seen snow fall and so it was so precious to watch and experience it from there perspective. We had snowball fights, attempted a snowman to no avail and some of them even went snowboarding or skiing.  We had a guest speaker, a worship team and cooked all of our own food, which is always an adventure. It definitely reminded us of "home" and what we were missing out on. I think that little taste of snow, cold and wet was enough to satiate us for now....as we were glad to return to the 70 degrees that awaited us at the bottom of the hill :)  It's rained in Anaheim on Saturday and usually following it's really clear and you can see the mountains really well. On my way to work this morning I could actually see all the way to the snow cap of the mountains where we were. Cool perspective and talk about beautiful...WOW!  Love to all.... 

						
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   all i see is famous people!!! today i was at starbucks getting some coffee, and the guitarist from The Offspring came in. it was weird. he just has this look...anyway....only i would notice that.....but some of my buds (andy, dusty, chad, etc...) might appreciate it. he was cool.....with some young chick...probably some arm candy....he's pushing 40...... the offspring suck though so i didn't care. This year i have seen more "famous" people than ever before. its weird. but....they are famous to me.....no one else would notice these guys....but i seem to have this nack for spotting famous dorks. 

						
</post>

<date>29,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Um...Just a heads up to anyone who would want to see us [and to evil villians who would want to break into our apartment] Leah and I are coming to Indiana/Ohio! We'll be HOME   June 12-16  . We fly out of OC at the crack of dawn, and get to Indy around 2:30 or so.  Then we'll leave around 5 pm-ish on Monday. We're coming home for my good ol' buddy's wedding. But the goal is to see as many people as we can while we're home, as well as take a break from Cali. We truly miss the Midwest and we're super excited to be home soon. So... urlLink email me  if you want to hang out. I'll expect you to cover the food and drinks. :)   

						
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   HI DUSTY! 

						
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...for some of you, you may not see the pictures on here any more. just those cute little red X things. yeah....we can't seem to nail down a place to store info. so...we're looking at buying a domain name and some other stuff to keep this site up and running. Also..if we do that....other friends can have their own little blog-ish sites for their hip friends and family.  urlLink let me know if this is stupid or cool.    I was thinking the other day. Music sounds amazing on a good set of headphones, over speakers. I say that because as much as i love music, i failed to realize this until the other day. so...my advice...listen to music on a good set of headphones...i recomend it. i use these......    Anyway...um....i feel as if people listen..so its cool to talk. but..um...music and culture is awesome this year. Me and a friend were talking the other day and we both decided we were just super huge students of culture. fashon, arts, music, movies...we just soaked up what what culturaly hip and fun. not that we are hip, but we loved studying culture and following trends and such.  Anyway..i suffice it to say....2003 is a good year so far for music, movies, videogames, fashon and such. so far so good.  the thing that cracks me up the most is the TRUCKER HAT thing going on. where did that come from? even at the NFL draft these soon to be millionares were wearing the trucker-80's style hat to their respective team. weird. anyway..   A MIGHTY WIND ...is so stinking funny and great. go see that movie. Anger management...sucked.   Splinter Cell  is the best PS2 game to come out in forever. get it as well.  MUSIC:::     The Postal Service - everyone needs this CD like i said everyone needs Frou Frou. Can't beat it. Its Chris from Death Cab for Cutie singing with Jimmy T from Dntel. Sacrine sweet pop that everyone should love.    The Black Keys ...great stuff. Led Zep meets Hendricks meets Muddy Waters...awesome, lo-fi blues rock. Jake Sikora will love this.    Cursive - the ugly organ. just good, artsy.    Boy Sets Fire - the new one is great. very emo in the right places but metal in the other right places.     A Static Lullaby - so cal kids that can bring the emo-metal thing. very good.     Damien Jurado - still great. back to his old sad, rainy day, roots rock.     CAVE IN  The best record to come out this year. SO FAR. Radiohead has a new one coming out in a few weeks. But until then...this is it.  thats it for now. um...i got a new Sony Clie. My old one busted. my new one rocks though. it has a camera on it. so....it takes great web pictures. anyway...only I care.     

						
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   well. it sounds like my [brian] folks are offically moved to North Carolina. its sorta sad...but its all good. its  a new place to visit. um....i really don't have anything new to say but its funny. its friday morning and i'm enjoying my day off and my next door neighbor [or someone near me] is BLASTING worship music out their windown. its great and all..but it's keeping me from playing my video games to my fullest potentential. :)  no...its cool...but come on.....its like their either doing morning arobics or all half deaf. but...praise God.   

						
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     Brian:::Robby:::Angels rock! 

						
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     

						
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     

						
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Tonight Brian and I are going to a wedding of a friend/coworker of mine. She's getting married in Newport Beach at this really cool place called the Turnip Rose. It looks kind of like a Spanish Palace. It should be great and it will be the first wedding that we are attending as a married couple so that makes it even more fun. Emily (my friend) and her fiance Lance only invited around 100 people and so we were honored to be included on the guest list. Emily's been sharing with us at work about all of the details of  the wedding, but mostly the reception. One of the things I'm most interesting food things I'm excited to try are champagne infused strawberries. I've never heard of them prior, but they sound really yummy. We'll let you know!   :0) 

						
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   As you've probably read, Dad Manley was here in So. Cal. and we were able to connect up and have some fun and dinner with him. Dad and I decided that this cool Japanese restaurant sounded great, it's at "The Block" and called Kogi's Shabu, Shabu. Brian wasn't sure and needed some convincing, but since it was 2 against 1, we ended up there. Shabu, Shabu is really fun to say and the food is even better. Shabu, Shabu means "swish, swish" in Japanese, or so the server told us. Basically you have a pot of boiling water in front of you and then they bring out meats and veggies and you cook them to your liking. You can add spices and such to be sassy. You even get to cook these really cool clear rice noodles too. We had a great time and once we were there Brian liked it too. Then we went to Starbucks and walked around. Dad bought this really cool Hawiian shirt from Hilo Hattie and some new swim trunks from Ron Jon's to wear when he's out on the lake in their new boat.  Then we took him to LAX and called it a night.     

						
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   can you smell that......it's my anger subsiding. due to large cups of coffee, the amazing grace of God, hanging out with teenagers, and a couple of nights sleep.......i feel better. Our God is good!  He is great at cleaning out our hearts, if we just let Him. [can i get an amen?]  but...on to more things. leah and i have't "talked" in like.....oh....a good day or so. (this is due to youth group going on last night...its not like we're 'not talking').....BUT WHEN in the world did she get time to write 3 blog entries! rock on! i'm glad she's taking a more active role in this NEW INTERNET THING. [get it....its a joke...the internet is not new.....geee...you guys are lame....]    anyway....Call up Nick Carter [back street boys] 813-787-9550 and ask him if he likes getting phone calls from strangers. [check out www.buddyhead.com they give out all sorts of phone numbers and email addresses of rock stars and famous people. they also hate everyone]    Everyone...check out  urlLink ANDY SIKORA'S BLOG .  It's all good, in the hood!  he says only 2 people check it. lets make it 6 !!!!!! :)  um....the one and only Paul Manley is in Southern California today. we're suposed to do dinner with him tonight. he's out here for business in COMPTON! yes...that's right...where N.W.A. and Dr. Dre hail from.  sweet eh?   Right now...everyone should go buy the new  Shai Hulud  record. its great. ok...not everyone. just probably andy and dusty. and they don't even like hardcore. its insane. check it bro.   Mr. Chadwich Cronin and his lovely bride, Jenny will be in So. Cal. next weekend. nothing like everyone i know coming out in a 2 week period.  

						
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, I guess today is my day to update the blog with info. Brian and I are visitng the midwest for our friends, Nick and Andrea's wedding in Ohio on June 14. So, we're flying in on the afternoon of June 12 to Indy and heading home to West Coast on Monday evening, June 16. We'll be passing through "The Fort" and definitely want to eat as Casa's, any takers?  It will be a short visit, but we're hoping to see as many familiar faces as possible.  We're also REALLY excited to be able to see both of our families, it's been too long!   

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, now for the current buzz. I'm sure some of you may now know through the grapevine that my sister, Sarah, is engaged to be married to a guy she met at a friend's wedding last May. His name is David Anderson, and he is a graduate of the Citadel and now in Officer/Ranger/Jump school (it's hard to keep track) with the Army. He proposed to her in the chapel on the Citadel campus and they are planning to be married there by the end of this year. Brian and I thank you in advance for your prayers surrounding this event. 

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, although this is old news, I do feel like I should get in my two cents worth of info about American Idol. CLAY was robbed!  He such a nice guy, works with special ed kids and it just a good guy. Whereas, you have Reuben, who has been sited in LA and said to have a potty mouth and a head that too big for his britches. Anyway, like I said, old news, and they both can sing. I just hope Clay makes it big on Broadway someday, or blesses kids with a song here and there. Emo, yes I know, oh well. 

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink      Well, after a less than best weekend, I will admit that it ended on a great note. My friends Lauren, Joanne, Katie and Deb (L to R in the photo) were in town. I met all of them while at Huntington College and it was such a breath of fresh air to chat and hang out with them. We ate at a restaurant I've been wanting to try, SoupPlantation, and then of course grabbed some java at "the 'bucks." It was so great to catch up on what was going on in their worlds and just laugh and share stories. Thanks ladies for a much needed evening of fun and memories. 

						
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   well. ever had one of those weekends where you feel like you've been in a car accident?  So brused and battered and hurt... but emotionally. yeah. that was the type of weekend Leah and I had this past memorial day weekend.  We would just like your prayers for just "stuff".  God knows what's going on...so just pray for us. Like I said...Leah and I are tired, hurt, and worn out.   Also...side note...not pertaining to anything...i heard the debut to the new Metallica song "st. Anger" this morning on the radio. It was the most rediculous sounding song I've heard in a long time. I consider myself a fan of Metallica...but this crap was horrible. for them to relases that song as the first single....it means that's the only airable crap on the record. i'd love to be proven wrong...but it was jacked. i bet you can listen to it online. i don't know why i just shared that. but.................................................... 

						
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   yeah. Ruben rocked it. word. i should have put some money on him. taht woulda been sweet.  hey..all 3 people that check this site...check the  urlLink Less Than Jake E-Card . word. 

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   RUBEN or CLAY? Clay is lame. Ruben all the way for American Idol. not that i really care. its just that leah really likes clay. so...i must dislike him. If Clay wins...i'm pulling the race card. racist america.  also. check out the new  urlLink deftones song 'minerva' . great song. heavy-beautiful-powerful. 

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    there is a new  urlLink Less Than Jake   record out today! yippeee!  get it. it will be on MTV soon enough. 

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   This past weekend, Leah and I spent Saturday morning with some High School kids, painting over Grafitti in Garden Grove. here are a few pictures.cool. Oh...Leah will proabably have some cool news but she wants to post it. anywy...enjoy the pictures. click on the picture and check out the hood of a neignbors car!     urlLink      

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   "Thanks to June's friends, fans and loved ones at this terrible time. I love you all." -Johnny Cash  In sad news today  urlLink June Carter Cash , wife of Johnny Cash passed away at 5:04 CST on May 15 at Baptist Hospital in Nashville, TN. following complications from heart surgery she underwent on May 7.  June was 73 years old.       

						
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi. I added another wallpaper for your lovely PC computer. if you want it that is. i've been working on this for a few weeks. now. for me some take minutes, others take a long time. it wasn't ready till this morning and a i tried this filter, i liked it so...her you are. its something to get that creative side of my brain a workout.     urlLink       by the way. don't you hate spam email?  it sickens me every stinking day when i go to my mailbox and i get just crap emails. i hope the person that invented the spam email can sleep well at night. jerk.  

						
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Andy and Meri Sikora have a blog.  urlLink CHECK IT OUT!   Also:Leah and I helped some friends of ours move into their new apartment today. And...it was a beautiful day to move stuff. But...My back is jacked up. I prettymuch pulled a fridge up a flight of stairs as a couple of guys pushed it. Well...it didn't seem that the pushing was too great...but the pulling on my part...that was a bit much. i should have stopped...but i just wanted to get it done. anyway...after we got the fridge into their apartment...i sorta lost my hearing. it was weird. everything went quiet...or muffled....and that ever so popular ring you get when you are at a concert right in front of the speaker. yeah. that was me. it was weird. like....no blood was going to my head. luckily a doctor was there...and she said i was fine.  it had something to do with my blood pressure form pulling a friggin' refridgerator up some stairs! Also...Leah helped. She thinks she's wonderwoman. :)  So....i'm gonna beg for a back rub.  later 

						
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Southern California is full of good sports. Can you believe that and team, spawned from a Disney movie, is working their way into the Stanly Cup finals.(maybe) The Might Ducks? What? Also...The Lakers Suck. I hope they bite it this weekend. I just can't stand them. So...Go Sacramento Kings!  Leah and I were going to go see Elliot [a band we like] in Anaheim, but I'm kinda sick. Dave Chow was in Mexico last week..and brought back something to the office. Lucky me...i'm sick. :(  oh well.  I get to rip all of my CDs while i'm home this weekend. I took in my MP3 player....the batteries were Nickel Metal (sufice it to say, they degrade over time, and i use it every day...so they were bad) so i took it back to best buy. thank goodness for service plans. they stoped making my old one...so they gave me an new one. [very nice]..but i had around 18 gigabites of musc (300-400 albums) and only 6 coppied over to my computer. so i'm trying to RE-imput all my music to my new player. Its worth it....but time consuming. anway....i'm blabing booring stuff....  Yippee! Andy and Dusty are coming out to Cali in July!!!   later   

						
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   In very exciting news...my good buddy Keith Goldfuss and his lovely fiance Mandy has set a date for their wedding. October 5th. Everyone should go and crash it! Just kidding...so...that means i'll be back in the mid-west again. But its not till October...so don't hold your breath. So...again...It looks like i'll be home June 12-16 and October 3-5 or 6th. Yippee!   X-Men 2 still rules. how bout that scene where Wolverine just looses his cool. yeah...that was stinkin' awesome.  I missed that about Wolvie's character in the first one. he was sort of a patsy...Its good to see im just see red!       

						
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Yup. X- Men 2 was amazing. and to boot...we sat behind Mark Solomon from Stavesacre. [dusty, i thought you'd appreciate this] everyone. go see x men 2. 

						
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   HEY YALL! I'm finally happy with the way the site looks. Now we have pictures, wallpaper, other junk. Also..we have a  urlLink guestbook  for you to leave a message and say HI. Sign in all the time. say hi. i hope this keeps us more up to date and entertaining. not that this site is amazingly entertainin or anything...but you know.  Go see X-Men 2.  

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hey. we're slowly making this site come back to life. um... urlLink sign our guestbook.   also..we're headed to an angels baseball game tonight. ROCK ON!   

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   ha! ha! HTML didn't win! we finally have decent looking blog. it'll be jacked for a few days..but its almost back up to speed. (ignore the weird links...i stole them from another site to make ours work) HTML is the most frustrating language ever.  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm so bummed, Brian and I, well mostly Brian was jazzing up our Blog and it was looking so rad....then dun, dun, duuuh..."it" happened. We're not exactly sure what, but "it" happened and the page and all of the pictures and guest book were no more. :0( So, pardon our mess while we try to update and fix what we've lost. Thanks so much to our tried and true visitors who keep us updated via the guestbook and keep up with us via the blog.  We really enjoy reading your messages and posting ours for you. Hope you like it!  On other fronts, life is good. We've had so many visitors and friends lately...we're so blessed. And this week has been good catch up time for us to sleep and get our bodies back on a quasi schedule again. And today, believe it or not, the sun is actually shinning.  I know I shouldn't complain, but it's been really gloomy the past few weeks and we were starting to go nuts. Our jobs are going well, although our trip back east made us realize how much we really miss our friends and family.  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   freakin blog-jerk thing. i'm overhauling the blog cuz it lost a ton of our script. so...new pictures and stuff and rants and raves will be next week. i don't even know where our free messageboard went. stupid jerk thing.  not only that...but i droped my mp3 player...and jacked itall up. so...i'm RE-RIPPING all my friggin records again. [andy and dusty..you got lucky]  

						
</post>

<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't know about the rest of you, but the weater here is starting to suck. We've got this..."JUNE GLOOM" thing going on. its where weird ocean moisture-clouds hover over the beach, and about 30 miles inland. So...its looks like its gonna rain all the time...but rarely sputters some drizzle. (fo shizzle)  Its getting depressing and thats why i write about it. cos i can. but...we still live in california...and that's worth...well...nothing. I really miss the midwest and all the beauty and simplicity of it all.  Plus...all my 'gangstas' live back there. hi.  Clara Sayer was kicking it in our home for the past few days. She is now back in Cleveland. :(  But...i want to share about the weirdness and power of Clara. I credit her for "hooking up" Leah and myself...but really sneakily and magically. it was wild and cool...yada, yada, yada... and now she's done it again.  Her friends Chad and Candy live in Huntington Beach, and she tried to do another match making...but with couples. its really cool. so...we might have new friends. which...sounds really silly...but its hard to find and make friends out here in so cal.  at least ones that we'd want to hang with. so we're kinda excited about hanging out wiht them. Leah and Clara hung out with them on wednesday..and they went to Ikea and Chad and Candy bought a couch and strapped it to their early 90's model honda. i guess it looked really funny.   In other cool...and only i would really like...news...i got to go to  urlLink The Militia Group's  headquarters and get tons of loot!  urlLink The Militia Group  is a really cool record label that Chad (from above) runs...and has tons of great bands and stuff. So...that was awesome. free music will always rock.   alright...pictures are coming soon. 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Holy crap we're tired.  We made it back to Cali only an hour after we were supposed to...so thats good. Its wednesday now...and i still feel like I've been hit in the face by Mike Tyson.  My body is mad at me...and rightly so. I've given it no chance to recharge or given it any good food.  But i digresss....Our trip back to Ohio/Indiana was great. We got to see our families (both Pennington and Manley crews) and our good friends. Thanks to those who bought us food or let us crash on their floor. We're very thankful. We'll write more and have some pictures to show in a few days.   Right now, Clara Sayer is at our home playing videogames. Its cool...its just that we're working...but we hung out last night and we'll hang out tomorow and later tonight.  We have seen virtually everyone we know in the past 3 weeks. Its a bit of sensory overload. I can't believe i'm saying this, but i can't wait till the next time i feel bored or like i have nothing to do.   ok...later. 

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Chad and Jenny Cronin visited us this past weekend. it was great. we'll post more stories and pictures later. 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      NEW RADIOHEAD!! NEW RADIOHEAD!! NEW RADIOHEAD!! NEW RADIOHEAD!! 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   i'm tired. anyone else tired. they need to create a national holliday centered around a giant nap.  The first wednesday should now be National Nap Day. You get the day off to sleep all day. i think that would rule. If only i were president......  Leah and i are working on our schedule for when we come home. if you want a piece of our time...you better get ahold of us...cos we're cutting it close and tight on time. and i say this not to sound arogant or self absorbed...but we really only have a few hours to meet with our crew....then we're flying back to, as some would say, the land of fruits and nuts. so...let us know.   check this stuff out....some high school kids somewhere dug up a dirt old time capsule from years ago. 1995. what a joke.  urlLink check it out.  

						
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   We'll the wedding was just wonderful. The setting was picturesc, the evening was warm, Emily was beautiful and the food was incredible. We had a great time and I was glad that Brian was able to get to know some of the husbands of that ladies I work with. And I was able to get to know them better. We had a great table of fun people. We'll post a picture soon. After that, Saturday and Sunday just kind of flew by and now the week has started and is almost finished again. We must be busier these days, because the days seem to be flying by really quickly. But, I love that we are into summer now and the days are extending longer. I love the fact that it's still light out at 8-8:30 pm.    More exciting news on our end is that our dear friends Chad and Jenny Cronin are coming for a visit Friday night. Brian will be in Palm Springs for a HS Youth Leader/Volunteer Retreat, so I'll get to hang with them on Friday. On Saturday Chad and Jenny are headed to the magical Disneyland and then upon their return Brian will be home and we're all going to grab some Mexican food and catch up on life. It will be so great to see them because they are so rad and we've really missed them. It's sad that we haven't seen them prior to this as they only live 5 hours away in Arizona, but, I'm sure you can all understand how that goes.  p.s. the strawberries were REALLY good  :0) 

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   i'm sitting here in my closet of an office tired from a long youth group night. i'm draggin' this morning. my friend starbucks is trying to get me back on track..but i'm still tired. i'm listening to this band called  urlLink THE FIRE THEFT ...they are the new incarnation of Sunny Day Real Estate.  It's beautiful music that is really deep well thought out. i really like it. (and i have the CD via a friend, but the record won't be out till October!)  But the thing is...there is this one line that just keeps haunting me.   "i buried my life away...can i dig it out again?"   as he says this in relation to the song...it's this feeling i have all the time of wanting to revert back to my old 'worldy' way of living.  That life I used to lead...on my own...by my self... NOW put in the hands of the Lord...who give NEW LIFE. And i wouldn't trade it for anything on the planet...but at times of stress, depression, and anger...i would want nothing more than to DIG UP my old life and take it for a spin again.    Oh how we're all like this at times. Where that life we died to comes back to remind us of the sinful joy we experienced without God.  And i think it's healthy. beleve it or not..i do.  It's GLORY to God for seeing where we once were and where He's picked us up out of the pit and yuck...to clean us off and love us and to say "go and sin no more."   At times I want to dig out my old self... but my new self...the Godly self, is reminded of the joy and salvation found in Jesus. 

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   this just goes to show you that the city of Chicago rules and will continue to be my favorite city.  urlLink click here.  

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      I'm back from Houston. Didn't get to see much of the city. it was humid as all-get-out.  the conference i was at was right next to the astro dome. i was kinda excited to see the astro dome...but they should change it's name to the ASTRO-DUMP.  it's such a hole. but the conference was in the reliant center...where the Houston Texans play. it was sorta neat.  on my flight from LAX to Memphis... Isaac Hayes was in first class! i also saw him at burger king eating breakfast when we were there.  and in memphis i saw some Pro Wrestler guys that i think i know (knew). that was a highlight.   The new THRICE record is amazing. everyone should own it. rock on. 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Andy and Dusty made it home safe yesterday...just without luggage. the lovely people at American Airlines though it would be a good 'character building' experience for andy and dusty if they left their luggage in Dallas. dorks.  hopefully they'll get their undies and tootbrushes soon.  also...i'm off to Houston tomorow for a youth conference...and the best part is that i'm not taking any kids!!! Dave and i are going cos he's speaking and so i can check out how this is done and just to chill with dave for a couple of days.  i've been 'chillin' with everyone lately...except my own wife. i'm a dork.  

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hey yall... Andy, Dusty and myself created a blog site that is open to anyone.  The blog is  urlLink Midwest Mindset.  This site is intended to be a place where we, as friends and other people we know, will dialogue about Life, theology and culture. Just a soundingboard to talk through stuff that troubles us and makes us laugh. email one of us to join the site and begin talking.  

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Dusty and Andy have arrived safely to the great state of CA. It's always so great to see familiar faces. Brian has off the rest of the week, so they'll get to hang out and have "boy time" like the good ole college days. I think they are headed to Disneyland tomorrow and the beach sometime soon after that.   New on my end, I may be headed to court tomorrow regarding this chic from Anaheim who was sold my credit card numbers, etc. from when my purse was stolen in December. I'm "on call" for a court date. I even received an official supeona in the mail...that was a little weird. It almost made me feel like I was the one that did something wrong. Since this is a prelimiary court date, the victim's assistance lady said that I may not have to go and that I'll be called in at a later time. Finally some closure to this crazy situation. So, I'll have to use some vacation time to go to court. But, if I don't have to go to court, my supervisor said that I could take Friday off so I'll be able to hang out with the boys. Ahh, I can't decide which sounds better, closure or vacation.  Keep praying for my sister and parents. They traveled south today to move some things into an apartment and prepare for the wedding. I know that Sarah is happy, and although this is what she wants, I'm sure it's overwhelming for her while at the same time exciting.   

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hi everyone. check out  urlLink www.friendster.com  .  become our friend. then you'll be cool like Leah and I. sweet. 

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...i'm back from DCLA-sacramento and i'm alive to tell about it.  I'm exhausted and beaten....but i wouldn't have it any other way.  Our crew had a great time. the drive up was a bit tiring: 8 hrs in a 15 passenger van. but we got a bit of rest....then the conference stared on tuesday and we were off and running. it was like the fastest 4 days i've had in a while. but one of the coolest things was...eating at this gritty soul food restraunt in Sacramento with Fred Lynch, Efrim Smith, and all the students. it was great. good ol' friend chicken and weird fried fish stuff. REAL SOUL FOOD. it was great.   When i came home i arrived to all sorts of drama. we're really struggling to get our wedding pictures and the photographer has been really flakey. i'm ticked. but...i just want our pictures..and i'll be happy. Also...in Jerry Springer like fashon..... Leah's sister's is getting married THIS WEEKEND! Her Fiance David, whom she was gonna marry in September, is now shipping off to Iraq for military duty and so they think that rushing into this wedding this is what's best. Believe me...its weird. just pray. it's funky and Leah is sad.  but...the bright side is this: Andy Sikora and Dusty Abshire are coming to the Left coast on Tuesday Night!!!! so...i'm very excited. it looks as if we'll be hitting up Disney Land....eating a lot...and maybe going to a show. anyhoo...later. 

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   So the week is going well...better than I thought. I"ve been hanging out with my friend/neighbor Bernadette. Monday we went to Home Depot to get goodies for our work projects. I needed paint to redo a dresser I had and Bern got plants and boxes to create a container garden for her patio.  I just redid mine and so I think I may have inspired her. I'll have to post a picture. Tuesday night we went to an Angel's Game, they lost, but we had fun. And tonight is project night.  Anyway, Brian is doing well and his trip is going great.  I'll be so glad when he's home. It's cool and time away is good I guess, but it's so quiet at night. The main part that I don't like, of course, is that he's gone.    Ok, I think the primer is dry, so it's time for a coat of paint.  later... 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   brian is off for a week in sacramento with the hs kiddies for a dcla youth conference starting today until saturday around midnight. this is exciting and happy....but right now i'm feeling super sad. i know it may sound cheesy, but it's the first time we've been apart since we moved here and i'm bumming out.   be sure to pray for him while he's away and also safety for driving...it's an eight hour trip and he's the only driver. i'm sure i'll be able to keep myself entertained and have little projects to complete...but i can't help but feel like part of me is missing.  sad.  

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hi. i'm leaving in about an hour. talk to you all later. leah...i love you.   

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm so excited that our web log is finally staring to take shape. It's so funny that when we have people visit us now and we take pictures, they say, "now I can be on your site right?"  Like it's a status thing now to be on our site. I love it, how cool that you all dig it so much.   Well as Brian alluded to, we went to an Angels game which was fun and we got to hang out with our friends Chad and Candy. Be sure to click on the link, they are so cute :0)  Then on the 4th we went to a barbeque at their friend's house, Faith and Brady. They are cool cats and we had fun munchin and listening to their neighbors shoot off about 5 hours worth of homemade fireworks. It was pretty intense, fun for the first few hours and then migrane inducing the last few. Fun with gun powder. Anyway, we had a blast and it was fun to hang out with some new people.   p.s.  By the way, Paul and Dona, does the picture at the top look like a blurred picture of something familiar?  Cool, huh.  

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   3rd...we went to an angels game with  urlLink chad and candy ...um...the 4th was good. like andrew w.k. said to do... we partied hard . well...we played 'barbie uno" for 2 hours. um...i'm sure leah will say more but it was fun. check out the new pictures.    "blue steel" 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   happy 4th! be safe. we're going to a bar-b-q in Costa Mesa at one of Chad and Candy's friends. i get to bring my M90s i bought 2 years ago in indiana. you can take the boy out of the PYRO, but you can't take the PYRO out of the boy. sweet. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   this blog is not working out either. crap. sorry for those who actually read and go to this site. it probably won't LOOK GOOD for a few more weeks. but...that's alright. I'm heading to DCLA, a student evangelism conference in Sacramento. it should be cool. but if anyone wants to hear from me or whatever...call my cell. [714.396.4444] Leah will still be around and stuff. so...pray for me and the students on this trip.   I'm stupid. Right after we get back from DCLA, Andy and Dusty are coming to the West Coast to chill for a week. cool...but i'll be in re-charge mode. they know it..its..all good.  then...a day after they leave...i'm heading to Dallas,TX for a youth conference. I'm jsut tagging along with Dave as he's speaking there.  so....i'm an idiot. but...you know what...i can rest when i'm dead.  oh..in cool news...i just discovered that Premonitions of War, a Toledo, OH band that  came to be when Chad and I left Acharityh... (Tim and Nick went with some other Toledo guys...and formed POW) POW just signed with VICTORY RECORDS. to anyone that knows music....is a big indie label that we all used to hate...and sorta put out bad records.  But..way to go POW...check out www.premonitionsofwar.com  Also...buy Militia Group Records stuff. They are cool people that could use your money. (come on dusty...you know you want to buy some....)  Listen to: The Mars Volta, Poison The Well and The Polyphonic Spree.  it will make you feel better. later 

						
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   For your viewing pleasure... i give to you  urlLink  OUR LIFE: YEAR ONE... IN PICTURES  . A video that I made for Leah covering the first day we were wed...our honeymoon, car accidents, trips to disneyland friends coming out to visit us...then at the end...August 24, 2003. (it made Leah cry)   Enjoy!   (to download it... right click on the above link and then click...'save target as'...then save.  it requires windows media player to play it.) 

						
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Thanks to all of our friends and family for the phone calls, cards and e-mails of congrats on the occasion of our one year anniversary. Where has the time gone? I wish we could all get together again and party!  But for now the only parting that will be done will be by Brian and I in Las Vegas this weekend!!!  We are so excited for our getaway (thanks mom & dad x2 - you rock), it's much anticipated after a crazy-busy summer.  Sunday we went to Disneyland and California Adventure and had so much fun. Brian will have to post pictures. The funny thing too is that Sunday is designated as "Bat Day" which is a day for all gothic people to come out in droves to Disney. I guess it's been going on for five years now, not sanctioned by Disney, but an unofficial gathering. Probably about half of the guests that day were adorned in all black including black parasols, stacked shoes and arrived in hearses, it was pretty wild and definitely an adventure.   

						
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     Well...good news is...i'm sorta done with my zany month of trips and such. the High School trip was great. I'll post some pictures later...but until then...you get me and spiderman driving a 'spider-mobile' at some shoping mall.   stinky news is...i had to cancel the college ministry work trip to arizona. i canceled it for a number of reasons...some beyond my controll...but i'm happy with it. i actually get to spend my 1 year aniversary with my wife instead of other stinky college students. :)  i was really bummed on wednesday but i'm over it.  i've just been so stressed and beat up and worn out lately. psychologically and physically. i'm counting down the days till we're heading to vegas.  but...as i was walking into church today... i overheard a couple of older guys running into each other on the sidewalk...and the one said...like everyone else does..."how ya doing?" and instead of saying the obvious "good" or "great" he said..."you know..fighting the good fight!"  I like that. That's how i feel lately. this whole sumer actually. just fighting the good fight...for what it's worth. just hanging on to fight to further and foster what God's doing in this world, with students and with myself. but it beats the crap out of you.  so...for dusty's sake...here's what i've been listening to lately...   Spitalfield : Remember Right Now   The New Amsterdams: Worse for the Wear   Guided by Voices: Earthquake Glue   B.T. : Emotional Technology    Damien Rice : 0   Me First and the Gimme Gimmes: Take a Break   The Polyphonic Spree : The Begining Stages of...                                            The Casket Lottery: Possibilites and Maybes                                             The Format: EP  Here's a cute picture of leah that i took with my phone. tee hee hee.   

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     Howdy yo. i'ts been a while since i've posted anything. i'm tired and buys as of late. pray for me. I'm heading to a high school camp this weekend and then next weekend leah and i are taking some college students to Arizona for a work trip on an indian reservation. it should be awesome..but hot as all get out.   BUT the light at the end of the tunnel is that the following weekend (labor day weekend) Leah and i are getting out of dodge...and going to the Paris hotel in Vegas.  we can't wait. i have day dreams of us being in vegas already....it's what keeps me going.  the good Lord has kept my sanity down and my hopes high. this summer has been tough but good.  thanx for your prayers.    the above picture is me and my friend Jesus...er..i mean Chris. Chris is one the collest guys you'll ever meet. he's an iron worker who only works to suport his surfing habbit.  Nothing get's this guy going like surfing, wakeboarding or anything that could possibly kill him. this picture is from last week when we went wakeboarding with Jeff (the jr. high pastor).   But bad news...this past weekend Chris was down in Mexico surfing (he goes everywhere to surf)  and was riding a motor cycle to get to the surf spot and fliped the bike and really mangled up his hand bad. and he just had surgery on it yesterday. (serious stuff...so serious it may never function right ever again kinda serious) so..pray for him. and the bummer is that he makes his $ with his hands being an iron worker. so..that stinks.    these gangastas are the mexican EMO-rockabilly mafia.  actually...they are guys in the latino ministry that always come hang with me. one dude is a total greaser- rockabilly bro. the other is a total emo kid. it's awesome. they are cool cats.  this picture is from the harvest crusade at edison field. it was outside on the blacktop and cool 98 degrees outside. so...it was stinkin' hot.  

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   go to :  urlLink http://pictures.sprintpcs.com   to see the pictuers that i take with my camera phone.  log in # is: 7143964444 and the secret password is: brian   you can leave comments to pictures and stuff. it's fun. 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   last night i got to see  urlLink THE ROCKET SUMMER  at the chain reaction in anaheim. The rocket summer is a really cool   band on  urlLink the militia group  label. the coolest thing is that in japan he's BEATLES  huge. yesterday when i had dinner with him he was just getting back from japan playing shows, opening up for Coldplay and Radiohead.  you know the old expression 'huge in japan' ...it's true!  he was telling me this story where he was leaving a record store over there, he had to sprint to his van and still got mobed by tons of screaming fans that once he got in the van, they jumped on the van! it's totally out of 'that thing you do'. crazy. everyone should buy his CD.   

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   last night i went to an angels game against the NY yankees. i hate the yankees. anyway...it was a good game but the yanks won in extra innings. darn it. but...here are some pictures from my new camera cell phone. word up.      

						
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   what the?a side of arnold you probably haven't seen. next CA govenor?  urlLink click and watch...    

						
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   check out the new  urlLink e-card for Anadivine . it's amazing!      

						
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   here's a picture from 2 weeks ago at a baby shower for one of Leah's friends.    

						
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      Leah and I got to see a sneek preview of School Of Rock tonight. It was so stinking good! It was clean, funny and all Jack Black. Everyone needs to see it when it comes out. It's especially great for all the rock refferences throughout the movie.  long live rock! 

						
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      urlLink click here  to vote for our friend John Sayre's hand and bass guitar to be on a jones soda bottle! how rockin'!  

						
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     It's a sad day. What an honorable man.  

						
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      hey everyone.  just a heads up. Lori Chow (wife of dave chow...the dude who did our wedding) is going into surgery tomorow on her brain tumor. It's really serious and pretty life-changing if not life-threatening.  Please pray for her as well as the doctors tomorow morning . It's a 3-4 hour surgery...so be a warrior!  

						
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   something happened to the blog. we lost some data and code. that's kinda important to this whole 'internet' thing. so...probably get to overhaul it tonight. how fun.  stupid sexy bloggger. arrrrrrrrrrggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhh........... 

						
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     Leah and i's trip to sin city was stinkin' great.  we got to do all sorts of stuff and not spend a ton of money (which rocks).  it was the most absoutely perfect way to end this "very hard" summer. this summer kicked our butts. so... sin city..er...Vegas was the best way to just get the heck out of town, spend a few bucks, stay in an awesome hotel, see some cool sites (as well as stupid drunk people) , and just RELAX.  we also got to see the BLUE MAN GROUP which i've been dying to see for the past 4 years. it was a trippy show, but worth every penny. it was great. thanx to our parents who hooked us up with the $ to get away. it was a true blessing.    So...school is in full swing and it's weird...i'm slowing down a bit. which is very nice. i was about to snap a few weeks ago...but now...i'm fine.   We've been having awesome youth group wednesdays and sundays. which... in youth ministry, you're not supposed to be all excited about 'numbers' and stuff..but when there's more students there- it's just a more fun environment.  Also...kid's are gettin really deep in worship and small groups which is something we've never seen before. Praise God!  I got paid today...that rocks.  I've also got a new obsession with getting a MAC. i've decided to give a 'stone cold stunner' to PCs- and make the switch. the only problem is... i don't have any money to make the switch.  anyone wanna buy a drum set?   Speaking of drums... you've gotta check out this band  urlLink THE AGONY SCENE.   They are absolutely great. years ago there was this band called ACME that had an ad in a ton of zines that said "more metal than an F'n scrap yard".  The agony scene would whip acme's bootay.  the agony scene is so stinking heavy black metal stuff with old hardcore breakdowns.  just brutal yet weirdly melodic. (ty and jake..you'd love this) think At the gates meets Zao when they were good. check it out.    Check out the new Chemical Brothers song  urlLink "the golden path"  with the Flaming Lips. great video too.     

						
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   yeah... i've been sick lately. that sucks....er...stinks. (sorry mom) um.... mumbling to myself a lot and aching. it stinks. um...the fires are almost over and done with. the wind shifted directions and isn't blowing junk into our air. and its cool...i started raining today. (better late than never) leah is cool...she bought me the hulk DVD. i'm gonna watch that now.    

						
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     This is a picture I took this morning at church. The cruddy camera-phone doesn't do it justice, but you coud stare at the sun and see the perfect circle of it.  It was wild. The smoke and debris is so thick in the sky that even at 8:30am  (but usually has tons of daylight)  This morning the whole sky was orange dusty. It's been raining ash all day and everything has a layer of soot on it.  It's quite surreal. Everything is dirty, you cough on the air outside, and it's as if it's slowly snowing- but it's pieces of timber and peoples homes. Outside it smells like someone is burning leaves in the fall time. Better yet- it smells like a bon fire for a party. very weird.  Well...just to let you know we live and work about 20 miles or so from the fire- we just feel/smell the effects of the real fire.  There's not danger for us...and I doubt there will be. The only harm to us is the air we breathe. so....we're safe. 

						
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     ROOOOYYYYYYYYY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  hey.  urlLink new pictures  added to our october pictures. they're from youth group last night. we had our room tricked out and all postered-black lighted-glowing-dance club ready. it was cool. check em out. also...pics of when leah's parents were out here.  urlLink click here  if you're cool.   {oh...read leah's posts below. she gets more done with words and posts than i do} 

						
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm so excited to brag on behalf of my dear friends and my serrogate parents Angie and Larry White. They have been trying to adopt the most beautiful little gal from Jamaica, SHANTEL. (the orphanage where I lived for a time) This process has been going now for 3+ years and finally the paperwork has cleared and she has a visa and all is well. Angie is heading down to Jamaica next week and they will return in early November. I can't believe she's finally "coming home" to the White House. And the best part is that we are going to be able to visit her over Christmas break while we are home visiting other friends and families. HOW WONDERFUL! And Brian is super excited to meet her. He's seen pictures and heard a million stories and she the same and so it will be a happy meeting and reunion. Be praying for them during this wonderful time of hugely anticipated transition in their lives. 

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I know this is long overdue, but wanted to give my two cents on the past month and a half and the events that have transpired. September: Well it's come and gone all too quickly. Work was really busy, but by the end of the month we were able to get away. Brian and I went to Pheonix to visit Chad and Jenny and attend the national YS convention. It was really great to see Chad and Jenny and visit their new world. However, it was really hard because the convention soldified a lot of things we'd been having issues with and made us realize that God is working in our lives and stretching us. The hard part of stretching is that SOMETIMES IT HURTS, but in the end it means that you've grown and it's such a blessing! So be praying for us and life has it's changes and we seek God leading in our lives.  On other fronts my parents were here for a 10-day jaunt and it was so wonderful to see them. It had been over a year, which was way too long. We were able to show them all of our favorite places including the beach, Watson's Pharmacy breakfast and the Orange Circle, our favorite restaurants and where we work. Also while they were here, Brian went home for Keith and Mandy's wedding. I didn't go, but my parents and I had fun here. We walked in the largest, annual fundraiser for my job, the CHOC Disneyland Resort Walk in the Park. It's a 5K walk that each walker raises money for and the path takes you through out Disneyland Park and Disney's California Adventure Park. A lot of the characters were out and on rides and such and so it was really fun to show my parents around. They also were able to meet a my friend's from work which is always nice to put a face with the name.  So now it's almost November, where has the time gone? It sure doesn't feel like fall here...it's been in the 80's and 90's all week so far and should be into the weekend. Now you may think I'm complaining, but be assured I am not. As a huge fan of the sun and heat, I never curse a beautiful day, but would definitely agree that some cooler weather/fall-like would be a nice change. By the way, thanks to my bro Stuart for sending pictures of the changing leaves in FTW from your digital camera on your cell phone....those Rock......YOU ROCK!  ~ TTFN ~  

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      urlLink this is just too darn bad . bums me out.  (sorry dusty) :( 

						
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   YOU'VE HAD TOO MUCH COFFEE WHEN,    You can type sixty words a minute with your feet.  Instant coffee takes too long.  You chew on other people's fingernails.  You answer the door, before people knock.  You sleep with your eyes open.  You go to sleep, just so you can wake up and smell the coffee.  You don't even wait for the water to boil anymore.  You're the employee of the month at Starbucks and you don't even work there.  (leah adds...tee hee he)  You lick your coffeepot clean.  You go to AA meetings just for the free coffee.  You're so wired you pick up FM radio.  You have a picture of your coffee mug, on your coffee mug! 

						
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   so...it's been a pretty wacky week. Not much happend...yet a lot seemed to happen. I can't put my finger on it...but I'd rather have not had last week..... i'm ok though. despite the cubbies and the bo-sox biting it, so much goes down in an adult life...and it can be taxing.  from monday--all i wanted to do this weekend was sit around and not do anything. lucky for me, i kinda did that. you'd think i'd feel good and relaxed...but no. (what the heck am i talking about?)  Leah and I did get to hang out with our friends chad and candy last night which was a breath of fresh air. We went to the chain reaction for a show. it was just nice to chill, talk about rock, and tell silly stories.  i'm sorry...i'm babbling.   Go Marlins.  

						
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     new pictures are up and to your right. see...there it is. click it. 

						
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     

						
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   oh my gosh!!!! Jeff and I were just at the Block (an outdoor mall in Orange) and I saw C.C. DeVille from Poision walking around. IT WAS AMAZING! (well...actually it was just ok and he looked and acted strung out on heroin ad was wearing a HBO-sopranos hockey jersey-other than that...very cool)  CC friggin' DEVILLE!!!!! oh yes...the guitar slinger from the famed glam metal outfit known as Poision.  i got a picture (below) but it's really bad (cos i didn't want to up set mr. DeVille...you know- it's for sure him-trust me.) ROCK ON.  remember   "Every Rose Has it's Thorns!"     

						
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   How in this great world of ours (with the growth of technology, information and so much data flying around it's hard to be mis-informed) did a bunch of yokels vote into office the friggin "running man" ? what the? it's almost surreal around here. i just can't believe it. i truly believe that he won because  Joe Averageman  thinks it's "cool" or "funny" to vote him in. I'm not the sharpest knife in the drawer, but from the word GO, Arnold seemed as if he was just doing it on a whim. Yeah...that's the kinda guy I want running my state. I hope he runs for some higher office. I'll move to Canada.  Dork.   In other stuff...Leah is now 27 years of age (yet still gets carded to taste wine at the stinkin' Olive Garden) go figure.  Keith Goldfuss (old college buddy) got hitched this weekend. I got the oppertunity to fly back to the midwest for the wedding in Michigan. It wasn't bad-It wasn't good. It was cold. I have evolved into a huge wuss. But....really..it was fun. got to see all my buds from Ft. Wayne and Huntington.  Got to go see a movie and just chill out and make fun of each other.   It was wild...Keith and Mandy's reception was at Adrian College, where good ol' buddy Chad Cronin went for 2 years. I used to go up there all the time and get in trouble and also play shows there at this one hall. Well...it was a flashback because the hall we used to play as a hardcore band....was where Keith's reception was held. it was great.   Also...the picture below shows what happens when you dance to "the luckiest" by Ben Folds at you wedding. Sweet emotion!    in closing: dusty and anyoneelse who buys records that i say are good: buy the new Coheed and Cambria record. It is fenominal. (especially the line at the end of  three evils .  sung in the most awesome melody "pull the trigger and the nightmare stops". YIKES! smells like Ozzy's "suicide solution")  BUT HONESTLY- It's amazing. also...yesterday the new Paul Van Dyk came out...AMAZING. get it. it will revolutionize the way you understand "emotional" music.       

						
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Sometimes, even thinking about yawning will make you yawn. And when the person next to you does it, forget about it -- you'll yawn, too. With all this talk about yawning, in fact, you've probably already yawned.    "A yawn is an instinctive behavior: You don't have to learn to do it, and yawns are even present before birth," says Robert Provine, a professor of psychology and neuroscience at the University of Maryland, Baltimore County.    Is the myth that yawns are actually contagious true?    "When one person in a group yawns, over half of the people in the group will yawn within five minutes, and the rest will at least be tempted to yawn," says Provine, who has been researching yawning for more than 20 years. "What is surprising is that virtually anything having to do with yawning triggers a contagious reaction."    Provine explains that while yawning is highly contagious, so are other human behaviors, like laughter, and this reaction is actually very normal -- and ancient.    "When you see someone else yawn, you don't think to yourself, 'Well, I'll yawn, too," says Provine. "It just happens -- it's instinctive, and it's a very primal aspect of human behavior that goes back to ancient herd mentality."   -stolen from msnbc 

						
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hey kids. we're in Fountain Hills, AZ with our friends Chad and Jenny. It's very nice out. 70's.....sunny....CLEAN AIR. Seriously...i can breathe so much better out here than in LA. Hey happy thanksgiving.   ...give thanks in all circumstances, for this is God's will for you in Christ Jesus. 1 Thessalonians 5:18 

						
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, after this weekend, it's official...Brian is old. Of course that's relative when you figure my age into, regardless. Happy 25th Buddy! I surprised him on Thursday night and we went up to Universal Studios City Walk in Hollywood. We ate at BB King's restaurant/bar and listened to this horrible cover band, but we had fun and it was entertaining to say the least. We walked around to all of the stores and little shops which was fun. VH1 was filming their "Best of '03" show so there were all these she-she made up girls prancing around half clothed and alot of "pretty men" sauntering around in their Ben Sherman shirts and perfectly quafed hair....the whole event seemed very metrosexual in deed.  Then on Friday, Brian's REAL birthday we went to see one of our favorite bands, Copeland, play at the Chain Reaction. The show had been sold out for weeks, but our dear sweet friend, Chad got us in so we hung out with him, Candy and our new friend Scott.  Afterwards, we did our due diligence and ate at Denny's with some scenesters and the band.  Saturday night we went out with Chad & Candy, Scott, Zack and Mark for Brian's b-day to BJ's Pizza. YUM!!!  It's a microbrewery, pizza joint with the best desert ever called a BaZookie! It's a fresh warm chocolate chip cookie, with vanilla bean ice cream on top with hot fudge. Brian got a free one and they put a candle on the top. There were a few table in the back with us full of young kids too so they were all singing and clapping and cheering when it came out. It was pretty cool and Brian was a good sport even though he usually shys away from that kind of thing.  We were going to play miniature golf -  (that's what it's called on the West Coast, if you say Putt-Putt people laugh out loud at you and think you're weird....I had to learn this the hard way  =(  I guess it could be worse....who knew?!?!) - anyway, we were going to play mini golf, but it was so cold last night...it got down to 35-40 degrees and was really windy.....BRRRRR!, so we decided to go to Chad & Candy's apt. and play cards. This of course was a much better option!   So, now it's Sunday and I can't believe that the week is going to start again tomorrow. It's been such a fun week that I hate to see it end. But thankfully it's going to be a short week! We are heading to Pheonix, AZ on Wednesday afternoon to spend Thanksgiving with Chad and Jenny. (not to be confused with Chad and Candy/...both very cool, just two different couples) So we are really looking forward to a break and then December's just right around the corner...I can't believe it.  WOW!    peace ~ 

						
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   ...to quote and agree with Brian...."actually is a good movie"....it really it!  I really think that anyone, of any age and any stage of love or lack there of would really enjoy this movie and walk away with something. It's funny, Brian and I were the youngest couple in the theatre. Interestingly enough there were a lot of singles there too, or at least people viewing it solo. I found this really ironic initially since it is a movie about love and being in love, right? Right, but wrong too. Granted the main preface of the film is love, but not the soley romantic, dating, sexual love. Given, that is the plot of a couple of the side story lines, but the main focus is about the different types of love. I.e. adult to adult, love of circumstances or chance, child to parent, ironic love, siblings, jealous love that is never actualized and sacrificial love.   It's really interesting and intriguing all at the same time and I found myself routing for characters and situations that I wouldn't normally advocate for in reality and shying away from others that are a normal soap box for me. It's amazing what Hollywood can do in just two short hours to wisk you away to an alternate reality.....then with the flick of a light switch you're zapped back into the life and reality you brought into the theatre. Either way, I left the movie feeling great and filled with thought.  enough of my diatribe....go see the movie, let me know what you think. The soundtrack really cheesy and good too if you're into that kind of thing.  p.s. Sun Kil Moon ROCKS!!!!!!!  check it out.  

						
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      Everyone needs to check out Sun Kil Moon. This is the new band from Mark Kozelek- one of Leah and I's favorite singer/songwriters. He was in Red House Painters, did the solo stuff of AC/DC covers and is the bass player in the move 'Almost Famous.' The record is just stinking beautiful and perfect for the winter. Very romantic too. Just stinking sweet.    *Lets take a trip down memory lane........One of the first records I bought Leah was either a Red House Painters or Mark Kozelek CD (I can't remember) but she loved it so i knew she was cool. THEN...one of Leah and I's first dates was to a Red House Painters show up in Ann Arbor, Michigan (she surprised me). While waiting for Leah outside the bathroom I met Mark Kozelek and was completely star struck. He was a really cool guy...but Leah was bummed she missed it.  But that show is one of my favorite memories with Leah. It was a cramped bar show...so there wasn't much personal space, and they played for about an hour and a half. I stood behind Leah for the whole time just hanging on to her...loving every minute of it...the music and just being with her.     Mark Kozelek holds a special place in our hearts.  

						
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   -Sports radio out here in Cali super upset over OSU climbing over USC for the BCS ranking. Every time i turn on the local sports show...they are stinking ticked! For anyone living east of the Missisippi- you're missing out on some of the funniest whiners go off. Boo Hoo...OSU had the 17th hardest schedule in the country, while USC had the 60th hardest schedule. Wussies. GO BUCKS!! MICHIGAN SUCKS!!!!  -The new full length from Chicago based PELICAN is amazing.  urlLink download track 1 from their site.  (it's 10 minutes long!)  - Are you Metrosexual? Find out  urlLink here.    -Check out the  urlLink video of really cool art . Different but cool. (you need windows media player)  - You wanna read a good engagement story?  urlLink Check out Chad and Candy's Blog.  tee hee hee.  -Check out  urlLink The Sincerity Guild.  They are a rocking band from Nashville- and I had breakfast  and dinner with Brett this past weekend. Very cool band...even nicer guy.  -Cnet.com bought out Mp3.com and is  urlLink ruining it . Set them on fire! Send them hate mail!  -Again  "GO BUCKS!!!!!!"  

						
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      The big game is this weekend....but can anyone tell me...is it on National TV. let me know asap.  Buckeyes..in the BCS again...just one more game!!! GO BUCKS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  

						
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Every once and a while...Leah and I will suck it up...and pay full friggin' price for a movie out here. We went and saw the Matrix Revolutions- that was a pretty big let down. Good ol waste of $20. Leah HATED IT! (I liken it to this...you ever been stuck on an airplane- trying to enjoy your flight...maybe trying to sleep: but it's just too loud, cramped, and anoying...you squirm to get a good position...but your body just is in pain and agony from just being on the plane...that was Leah in the movie theater for the Matrix 3)  SO.....I owed Leah a "Good" movie. She wanted to see LOVE ACTUALLY. I was sorta down....I had read it was a good film...plus i LOVE Christmas movies...so we went for it.   Leah will tell you more...but LOVE ACTUALY is "actually" really good! (they should put that on the movie poster) It was such a fun-creative movie with all of these stories coming together.  It's hard to explain...but it's stinking good. Again...Leah will expound at a later time.    Go see it.   Oh....Friday I turn a quater of a century. I know its dumb...but NOW I CAN DRIVE A RENTAL CAR!!!! Small victories!! 

						
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Check out...  urlLink THE DARKNESS .  stinking cool.  my frend chad showed them to me. stinking funny....yet good. go figure. You can't go wrong with a chorus like "get your hands off of my woman" (thanks chad) 

						
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      urlLink make your own sign!  

						
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     New Pictures for the fall. As well I added some of my digital art work for you to check out.  peace. 

						
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink this  is the coolest thing i've seen all day. urlLink  check it out.  

						
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Leah got sick the other day. she was out for a couple of days. But now we're all better!!!! :)  We're in the midst of spring cleaning ( i know... it's the fall) and tearing apart our whole apartment becuase we're convinced we can find more storage for all of our junk.   This should be fun.  Lets see... in true music junkie form...I was at the record store the other and they had this 'limited edition',Italian release, 1 of 300 made, LIVE Karate CD.  It's pretty awesome.  If you like the group karate.  I knew it had to be amazing since the guy at Bionic hates everything that ever comes out and he was raving about it.  I'm a nerd.  New top ten to the Left. yup...still a nerd.  We took the college group bowling last weekend...Leah whooped my butt. more on that later.    

						
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm happy to report that Angie, Larry and Shantel safe and sound back in Indiana. They arrived yesterday, and we missed their call which was a bummer! We went to bed really early, I think it was close to 8:30 pm...we both needed it. Anyway, their new adventure has begun and we're so excited for them. I can't wait to hear every detail of their trip to Jamaica. Of course I'm so jealous that they were there, but so happy all the same. I can't believe it's finally a reality. Thanks to all of you for your prayers on their behalf. It means to much. Be prayerful for a beautiful transition both here and in Jamaica. 

						
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Brian's been sick for almost two weeks now, battling a cough, sleepless nights and pain in his chest. I haven't caught it yet, I owe it all to my free little flu shot at work. Brian thinks it's silly, but I really believe in those little things. It hurt bad enough when I got it that it better work :)  Unfortunately with the weather change and all the ash and junk in the air I think I'm headed toward a sinus infection, yuck! I guess I'm more sensitive than I thought. Anyway, maybe I'll make doctors appointments for us both, I think we could both use some meds. 

						
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   We're at Angie & Larry's house right now, it's so wonderful to see them and hang out with Stuart and Shantel. I can't believe she's really here in the states. The trip from NC was really long, (14 hours) but worth it to be able to see all of our friends and family members in such a short time.  However, today Brian woke up with the stomach flu. He's been sick all day (you know, talking to ralph on the big white phone) and resting. I feel so bad for him and I know he's bummed that he hasn't been able to see all of the friends he/we'd like to. As they say, que sera sera, tomorrow is a new day.  We are hopeful that it is only the 24-hour flu. He seemed better tonight when I checked in on him and he did eat a few crackers with a shot of Nyquil....enticing combo I know. It has changed our original travel plan a bit, but we are excited to be spending New Year's at the White house in Fort Wayne and then traveling onto Chicago on Thursday.   For all of those who may be worried about Brian, no need he's in great hands. I've been pampering him to the hilt. Angie says it's good "mom" practice. 

						
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   it's saturday. we're still in North Carolina. Still driving alot.  We're currently at Leah's sister's house in some military town. We went and saw the military base and where all the action goes down.  I couldn't help but feel a bit angry and upset about Bush getting us in this "war" mess a while back- looking for "weapons of mass destruction." when you see the people affected by war and military duty- it takes on a different meaning. As if there could have been defnitive evidence before we started getting our troops killed.   the trip at my parents house was the best thing to happen to me in a while. i love my folks- the older i get the more i want to hang with them and just learn from them. they treated Leah and I to all that the Mooreseville area had to offer.  last night we went to the most killer gourmet mexican restraunt. "gormet mexican?- oxymoron? NO...it was so chill...killer margaritas and amazing presentation.  The food was off the hook. mmmmmmmm...i want it right now!  but right now...sitting on my sister-in law's computer- i'm ready to sleep. it's not been too eventful here. tireing though. my head hurts.  tomorow we head to the FORT!!! i'm so pumped!!!! MUNCHIE'S & CASA'S and friends. what more does a young couple need?  maybe some raspberry beer from muchies...but that's about it. 

						
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   merry christmas everyone.  we're in North Carolina with my brother and parents. it's really really really really good to be "home".  The drive down was great- got to hang with Chris for 90% of the trip and tell jokes and just be brothers.  The West Virginia mountains were super beautiful with all the snow.    Today is surreal.  In a new home that is now "home".  It's weirding me out...but i'm cool. It's the best to be with family. I wound't want to be anywhere but here right now-today.  Blessings. merry christmas. 

						
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   hey. we're in Detroit, actually...Dundee, MI- ouside of Detroit. We're cool. We didn't feel the heat from the security threat level stuff. But Leah's mom got stopped in thier van by a cop in the airport. Orange County was pretty chill. we talked to this girl who started out in LAX and said it took her 3 hrs from the point she was dropped off to the time she got to her terminal. so...we're cool. heading to Ohio tomorow to see my cousins and parents and brother and stuff.  rock on. 

						
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Here's our Trip info: Let's get together. Let's PARTY!  Brian's Cell: 714-396-4444 Leah's Cell: 714-469-7636 email: hotwaterbrian@hotmail.com -OR- leahmarie03@hotmail.com  CHRISTMAS SCHEDULE 2003  12/22 - Fly into Detroit on Monday - stay with Penningtons  12/23 - meet Manleys half way in Toledo with Penningtons and then ride back to Ohio with Manleys for the family party.  12/24 - ride back to North Carolina with Manleys  12/25 - Christmas day at Manleys new house - all day 12/26 - evening meet Penningtons and go to Sarah's apartment 12/27 - Sarah's house w/parents - Pennington's Christmas 12/28 - ride back to Michigan with Penningtons stay the night  12/29 - Penningtons taking us to Fort Wayne to Angie and Larry's  12/30 - hang out in Fort Wayne with friends 12/31 - late afternoon/evening - taking train to Chicago to see Gavin and Liz 1/1 - Chicago- party with Gavin & Liz 1/2 - blue line to airport - fly back to California  

						
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Saw Lord of the Rings- the return of the king tonight. It was stinking amazing. i wasn't super geeked on the first one. the second one was good...but this third one...better than all the good parts of the first 2 combined.  It was well worth the 3.5 hrs. Rumor has it that Peter Jackson said that there was supposed to be another  1.5 hrs of ending that they couldn't lawfully or "according to the rules" put on the 3.5 hr movie already. so...wait for that dvd!  if i ever get some free time- i'll post our schedule and numbers while we're gone so we can all party.  

						
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     New Spiderman 2 trailer  urlLink here !!!!!!!!!!!!! 

						
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink this  is cool.  urlLink click it.   

						
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   so...it's official. Leah and I are addicted to the TV show 24. We just started at the begining of this year...and we're hooked. After last night's episode...yeah...we're sold. It's off the hizzie.  We're stinkin' excited to come home in 2 weeks (or less now) so...ROCK ON! we'll have our schedule for our trip up on the site soon!  the militia group has a new E-card online for thier upcoming label comp.  urlLink check it out ...Brandtson covering "king of pain" by the Police!  um...i'm going bald. i've realized it. i think i'm gonna just shave my head...darn it.  I think it's just stinkin cool to know what others are listening to. Like  urlLink Ty  and  urlLink Brett ...both dudes like to list playlists. So...i will too....  Brian's Playist... as of late...  The Casket Lottery/Small Brown Bike Split EP Lovedrug- new full length Explosions in the Sky- the earth is not a cold dead place The Mercury Program- a data learn the language Converge- Petitioning the Empty Sky Pelican-Australasia M83- Dead Cities, Red Seas & Lost Ghosts  

						
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   well...i (brian) am sick again. this is no fun. but anyway....that was to make you feel bad for me. did it work? um....i spent my day off at the militia group office yesterday working on an zine advertisement for them. they're strugglin' since the coolest designer, brady, left to do  urlLink his own thing .  so anyway...i took me way too long to do their ad....it's cool...i made the deadline... a. it was on a mac and b. i didn't know where any of the files were....but it's ok.... it was fun.   um...i see that nick hale (old acharith guitarist) has just left  urlLink premonitions of war .  so...now there's no ex-acharityh members in POW.  at first ex-achariyth was half of POW...then anthony left, then tim, now nick. well....support them anyway when their  gust busting record comes out on victory in january. support the once electric music scene in Toledo. boy...those were the days!  um... in being sick i get highly emotional...it's nice....but weird.  check out  urlLink Lovedrug.  I got their new ep and they stinking rock. the sad thing... no one has signed them yet.  If I had a label...i'd have signed them by now! they'll be big. 

						
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						      urlLink          click above...an awesome 80's quiz...to test all you new wave hipsters!    

						
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						     to you right...click on the thingy that says "fall pictures"....yeah that one....we have new pictures there from our lovely trip to Arizona. rock on. 

						
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...Leah and I are back in OC and alive to tell about it. We went to Fountain Hills, AZ to visit our friends Chad and Jenny Cronin.  We left OC at 5:00am Thanksgiving day...arrived in Fountain Hills around 11ish.  So...about 5.5 hrs. Good trip. While there we had a wonderful time of eating like pigs and enjoying it.  The weather was amazing. in the 70's and not cloudy at all. We went for a hike one morning...STINKIN' AWESOME. The desert terain was really cool and beautiful. We'll post pictures later. um... It was just a good time to catch up and chill.    On Sunday Chad preaced at church...he rocked...and his friend Joel was to do worship. And on whim...Chad asked me to drum for the Sunday worship...so I did. Joel and I did worship...Chad brought the funk. It was great.  Chad even used a really silly joke I told him in his sermon. (i hope his pastor didn't get mad)   We left Fountain Hills around 12 noon Cali time....in hopes that traffic home would be as easy as going there. Well.... seeing 4 major accidents, a few traffic jams and 8 hrs later...we walked in the door around 8pm.  We got stuck outside of Palm friggin' Springs for about 2 hrs. Maybe moving 4 miles the entire time. We were going crazy. Hungry, tired, stressed...and music came to our rescue!!!!!!!!  Journey's Greatest Hits was a good sing along... along with some other chill stuff by Mineral and Red House Painters...WE WEATHERED THE STORM!!! I H8 California traiffic.   I'm sure Leah will say more later...but...that's my take on it. peace. 

						
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   howdy folks. sucks to be you on the east eh? yeah..it's sunny and in the 70's around here. sorry...had to say it.   urlLink     um....I created this really interesting art piece yesterday.... and I submitted it to deviantart.com - a site i check regularly to get ideas and stuff... and they posted it...so...  urlLink go check it out here.  (click on the smaller image to see the full-sized wallpaper)  Leah thinks it's twisted and weird...and she's probably right...but that's sometimes the point of art. anyway....if you go...leave a comment if you want. also... the more it's viewed the better ranking it gets. word up 

						
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   HEY! Premonitions of War's new record comes out today. go buy it. it's amazingly brutal!       for all you pitchforkmedia.com fans...  urlLink this is funny . 

						
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey. i'm back at sea level, which feels good on the old lungs and head. we stayed at 8000 feet which is the highest camp in all of california. cool eh...no....walking to your cabin wears you out. at that level...the air is so thin it took me about a day just to get used to having to breathe harder everywhere I went.  so....that's why Oscar De La Hoya trains up here before a fight...if you can be in rockin shape at 8000 feet...you can kick butt at sea level.   I also just added a 2nd video from camp.  urlLink check it.    download it and watch. it's cool cos half these kids have never been in snow. the kids in the video that are sledding....have never done that in their life....and were sledding for 4 hours before i had to drag them inside to thaw out. it was cool.     so.... we added some urlLink  pictures  from camp and from the past month. so...enjoy.  

						
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i'm heading off to camp with 50 high schoolers this weekend. yikes. but i made a video for our first night...and i'll be making videos up there for each of the days...recaping what went on...encouraging them....anyway... i made a small- web version of the video. if you want to see it... urlLink here it is.   you'll need  urlLink quicktime  to watch it. download it and watch. 

						
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey. sorry its been awhile since an update. not much to talk about. i'm gonna try to make the site look halfway cool tonight. um... i'm going to winter camp with 60 high schoolers this weekend. pray for me. :) um...and while i'm gone one of the coolest shows will be in my backyard. The Pale, Rocky Votolato and Limbeck. So...i'm sad. Leah's probably going.  Anyway...i stumbled across  urlLink this  really cool/good video show doing an interview with Rocky Votolato and him doing some live stuff.  urlLink check it out.  

						
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I am getting nothing done today at work. Which is evident by me writing this.   um...great news..my dream has come true. I finally got an  urlLink i pod !!!  With a best buy waranty on my old mp3 player- a few gift cards, a coupon, a nice best buy employee (who thinks i'm cool)- i walked out the door with the most rockin-sexy-piece of technology to come out since the Etch-a-Sketch. Rock on. I'm verry happy. 

						
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I must have been out of touch or just raised in the mid-west where you only show your toes less than two months a year, because last time I checked getting a pedicure, or lack there of, was not a big deal. Well, now that I reside on the left coast I've found this to be a totally different story all together. I had been wanting to try it and now living here has increased that.   So, I finally got a pedicure this weekend. And, now I know why it's a big deal. IT'S FABULOUS!! It was a spa pedicure with a massage chair and it was totally relaxing and fun. I went with my dear friend Kelly from work who talked me through the whole ordeal. I have to admit I was a big nervous. I didn't really know what to expect and now on the other end of the whole experience, I find myself addicted and excited for my next visit.  I never knew toes could look so cute. So for any of my friends or family out there who are curious, GO FOR IT! You'll love it, cross over to the she-she side of life....it's FUN!    I really wasn't raised in a cave or anything, promise. For those of you who know me well, you can appreciate my excitement for the little things. 

						
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   holy crap. i'm watching 'dumb and dumber-er' - and i can't quite understand why. it's one of the most aweful movies ever, yet I'm fully compelled to watch it. A student that used to come to our college group was supposed to be the 'dumb football player' guy who's friends with harry and lloyd- but he lost out cos he lived in so cal.  i think it's a good idea he didn't do it.  I'd rather not have a carrer than have this movie on my resume.   um...i proably should say that i technically didn't pay for the rental. it's through Netfilix.com  that's such a sweet deal. check it.  um...for all you "real men of genius" fans....  urlLink here they are!  my mp3 player is loaded with em. man...i'm a dork. 

						
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     It's been an OK week. I feel as if i'm an emotional rollercoaster all week. But all in all...I wish I was still at my parents home in NC and sitting on thier couch- sleeping all day. that would rule.  But instead I get to play catch-up on work. Suck.  The positive side of things: Ever since I saw the commercial for the movie Big Fish, I've been dying to listen to YES. The commercial has the YES song "see all good people" for all 30 seconds of it....and that got me totally obessed with YES again.  When i was in Achariyth, Nick Hale's dad was in this prog-rock bar band and he turned me on to Yes. Then when Leah and I started dating, I would drive from Warsaw,IN to Hunginton, IN to see her for a few hours- and the trip took about 45 minutes. The coolest part was that I could throw in "Close to the Edge" by Yes (3 songs- 45 minutes) when I was in her parking lot I'd throw it in- and the album would be closing up by the time i arived at my apartment. It was so cool.    So...It's all i listen to now.  Yes- sure they were my  urlLink dad's era of music - but they do stuff that no one will do for 20 more years. Long live prog-rock.         

						
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    i added the  urlLink final pictures  to our fotopages page. that was pretty much our trip. write a comment. it makes us feel special. 

						
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today- i was really into this song by Nora. Don't call the cops or anything...but i think i am crazy...but it for some morbid reason it helped me relax.  Funny eh?   THE CHAMPION-by NORA I got a bone to pick with you  and I'm gonna pull it out of your ribs  You're not all you're cracked up to be  and I'm not big enough to walk away  You be the bigger man  We won't stay down  because we're knocking down your door  We're burning down your house  I've got a gun to your head  and I'm asking do you wanna live?  Is this how you wanted it?  What's behind my eyes?  What's behind my skin?  Can you see in?  What's behind the barrel  I'm holding to your head?  I've got whatever it takes  and you came up wanting, get up  This is a love song, it's a sing-along  I wrote it just for you  How long is your list?  Mine's about to get shorter   

						
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey...to tide over the 3 people that visit this site... urlLink here are a few pictures  from our vacation. i'm just starting to load them so... check back to  urlLink this site  more often to see our new pictures.! word up. oh....new blog site soon. just a new look so...nothing fancy. 

						
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey, just a quick update to let everyone know that we're home safe. We had an interesting time trying to fly out of Chicago due to weather, but thankfully we talked to the right guy who put us on a direct flight with another airline which got us home at the same time even though we left much later. And since we switched airlines, we were "randomly selected" to go through all of the extra security precautions. Talk about fun, yippee! Anyway, we'd do it over again in a heart beat for a direct flight and to be home.   We added it all up and throughout our little adventure east we traveled and visited through 8 states; Michigan, Ohio, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, West Virginia, Virginia and North Carolina, I think that's it. And, we used at least 6 modes of transportation; bus, amtrack train, L-train, cab, car, van, plane. So it really was an adventure. The best part to report is that we were able to see so many of our friends and family and had a great time.  Thanks so much to all of you who housed us, fed us and provided a mode of transportation. We really appreciate all you did for us while we were there to make our trip possible and wonderful. You'll never know how much it meant to us. Thank you, thank you.   Pictures are coming, watch for an update or link to get to there.  Happy New Year! 

						
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   finally, we've arrived! It's so great to be in our favorite city and with our friends Liz and Gavin. Brian's feeling better and our train ride was really great too. We'll be headed home on Friday all too soon, but at the same time, all good things must come to an end.  

						
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We had an event at the hospital last Thursday and the Chuck Jones Foundation came in to present a concept for our lobby. The Chuck Jones Foundation works with warner brothers so there were displays of Donald Duck, Bugs Bunny and the like. So it was fun to see what they would concept for our lobby's new decor. They have displays and hands-on games, it's called distraction therapy for the kids.  It's interesting. So anyway as I was helping get media/photo concents for the patients and their families, I was circulating the room and who to my wondering eyes should appear?!?   NANCY CARTWRIGHT!!!  I couldn't believe it, I'm not sure what she was doing there or how's she's affiliated, but it was so cool. She's the woman who does the voice for Bart Simpson.  She is really big into children's issues and supporting the cause so it was neat to see here. Also the director of Finding Nemo was there too. How funny!   

						
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey ya. um..let's see...oh.... I would apreciate prayer for anyone who's into that...this weekend I am fasting for 30 hours for an event with our kids called  urlLink 30 Hour Famine.   I would appreciate prayer for this event cos dealing with grouch and hungry kids is not the most fun thing in the world.  And when I'm hungry i get grouchy (just ask Leah) so...pray all goes well.   thanks.  Ipod lounge for some reason tore apart an Ipod mini.  urlLink check this out.     

						
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       Mel, Bill, Jim i'm sitting in my office laughing to myself cos i ran  urlLink into this site  on accident...actually google searching for pictures of elvis...anyhoo....it's just funny. some of these pictures are people that think they are celbrity look-alikes. I hope no one makes money off this  urlLink junk.  

						
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So...we lived through "STORM WATCH 2004" out here. Everyone was talking about this huge pacific storm...and it was pretty gnarley, but it's over. It's like Christmas. All this build up..and then..poof....it's gone.  oh well. People drive stupidly though. it's pretty wild. To quote my Pittsburg-redneck neighbor.."everyone around he's a bunca F***n' P******!"  like that...yeah...real nice.  Um...for you music junkies that care or just want to be cool... Andy and Dusty...may remember me listening to a band called INSIDE. they were from NJ...and the singer had a really wild-cool voice. So...that INSIDE record is one of my fav's for all time....and just the other day i find out that the singer and half the band is in a new group on ONEDAYSAVIOR called DEARLY DEPARTED. urlLink Listen to it here   mmmmmm....can't wait! 

						
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It has been raining off and on since Friday and we love it. It has only rained like this one other time in the almost two years we've lived here. The only sad part it that a.) California's don't know how to drive in it or what to do if they hydroplane and 2.) there's no drainage so the water just piles up and left standing everywhere, including the freeways. Which make for a nasty combo.  We helped our friends Chad and Candy move on Sat. with a nice little drizzle. We had fun and made the most of it though. They only live six minutes away off of Lincoln now too. It's fun to have them so close.  After moving we went to Scott, their roommate, play a show. (The Lyndsey Diaries)  fun times.....and it's still raining.   

						
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     am I dreaming?  Jon Bunch (who Chad C. saw greasing up his chest at a show) of Sensefield and Further Seems Forever....in one SUPER GROUP....wow....  urlLink check it here.  

						
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Check it... DJ danger Mouse took the Jay-Z's "black album" and mixed it with the Beatles "white album" to create the "GREY ALBUM". It's amazing!! ....and I know it's illegeal... but cos  urlLink EMI banned the album  from sales....  urlLink pirate it here . word up. 

						
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Zao was a good band.  WAS...a good band.  urlLink read this junk . then chek out their new picture  urlLink here . just give it up. 

						
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      you know...when stuff seems to get frustrating.... urlLink this makes me happy.  there is so much fun stuff on this site. it may be my favorite site so far this year. the outkast remixes are da bomb. 

						
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        Last night we went to the Chain Reaction to see the bands Limbeck and The Format, and they are so great live! The whole place was rockin' because they sold out which meant there were about 500 kids there. That makes for a packed show! We took our friends from college group, Mary, Melissa and Robbie. Robbie decided to go last minute so he and Brian dropped us off at to go get him a ticket and then they went to park the car. We were lucky too, because we bought one of the last three tickets they had. I think they had a blast.  It was a great night.   UNTIL.......we went out to get the car and go home and the car was GONE!  Keep in mind it is now 11:30 pm  My heart sunk and started beating so fast. I couldn't believe it. Brian kept saying, "Where's the car, oh my gosh it's gone, it's gone." I'm trying to process what is happening before my eyes or as the case was, what was NOT before my eyes (i.e. the car!)    Now going on 12 midnight   It turns out after a few phone calls we discovered that, although the security guy for Chain directed Brian to park there, it was an "authorized only - tow zone." You'd think that if the guy is directing cars there and there are already 10+ cars there that 1.) maybe they had made arrangements for extra parking, 2.) it was ok to park there. Well both of these were wrong. And the whole lot of cars got towed to an impound yard. I personally think the security guy was in ca-hoots with Tows-R-Russ, the place that now owned our car.   So we are now stuck with two dilemas, no car and all of us stranded and how do we get back home. So Brian flagged down our friend Rory (to the rescue) who drives a mini cooper and he took me and the girls home to get our other car and drop them off to pick up their car to go home. Brian and Robbie got a ride from Rory's brother, which was a highly magical ride to say the least. (that's a whole different story) Anyway, finally all of our friends got their cars and were headed home.    Now 12:30 am   Now the second part of our adventure begins, we have to find this little tow place and plead and pay for the guy to let us have it back. We finally found it and the guy there was really scary. Almost like if you sneezed wrong he'd want to punch you. So after reviewing our options, we decided to purchase the $155 tow package. Included in this package is a towing fee of $90, plus vehicle storage @ $25 per day for two days and a $15 gate fee. (since it was towed at 10 pm and we picked it up at 12:30 am, that's two days - but I didn't want to chance arguing with this scary dude, if he says two days, well then it's two days) PLEASE NOTE MY SARCASIM!!!      Now 1:30 am  Bedtime. We finally get home and call it a day.   So, today is a new day and luckily payday none-the-less so all in all it could have been much worse. I guess $155 isn't so bad compared to it being stolen. And also, I'm so glad we carpooled and didn't have our friends drive, that would have been three more cars at $155 each and I would have felt so bad for them.  Ah, life's little treats. fun times. it makes for a good story, or so I hope.  

						
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     

						
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     

						
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    !!First read Brian's entry or this will leave you a bit confused!!   (see below)       So as you've read, Friday night bombed. The restaurant, although cute and enchanting from the outside with their little twinkly-light patio/cantina area, went down hill quickly. We both knew we should have left after waiting 15 minutes to be recognized, but still we stayed.  And it's in a REALLY ghetto part of Orange. We were a little afraid to leave our car parked on the street. The enchanting evening to be, based on a fun staff Christmas lunch complete with treats from the Panaderia (spanish for bakery) was a bomb. So we went home and watched "Under the Tuscan Sun", this was a redeeming part of the evening for me, but needless to say it didn't do much for the Bri-guy. So Friday was a wash, but luckily there were three more days of potential ahead of us.  Saturday ROCKED! Those little kids at the trailer park are soooooo cute! There little kool-aid stained faces and eyes so big and brown you could get lost in them. My favorite little guy from last time came up and nudged me on the shoulder. When I turned around, he looked up at me and said, "do you wememba me?" Oh, my heart just melted. So I responded, "oh Isaac of course I remember you." To which he responded, "cause I wememba you, you were here last time" this quickly followed by the best hug and then off he went to play a game with friends. That right there is exactly why I love going there. The saddest part is that the city has plans to tear all of that area down to build hotels and restaurants for conventions and business meetings. So, I'm not sure where these people are going to go, but it just kills me to think that they would be homeless.   Saturday night was fun and the boys were surprised with a yum dinner. Although, the smell of steak is repulsive to me, they all enjoyed it. And the show was fun. Copeland was great live again, and Mae has now been put on the list of bands that suck live. As for the Limbeck thing, the lead singer looks like Lex Luther on Smallville complete with a huge square jaw and all. Candy was the one to spot him and compare to Smallville, I just think he has a distinct look, almost scary, yet intriguing.   Sunday was good and we had fun with the college group as usual. Then Monday was so much fun. We had always wanted to drive on the PCH coast line, so we did. We went through Malibu and Santa Monica. There were surfers-a-plenty out and about and the homes were amazing, WOW. It still so funny to us because when you grow up in the midwest you think every aspect of SoCal is ritzy, beautiful and so glam. But Malibu is just a little surf town, kinda dirty, very compact homes along the coast and really quaint. Of course not forgetting the other side with Rodeo Drive. But even that is much cooler to see while watching pretty woman. We decided that it's fun and definitely great to experience live, but that everything looks so much more amazing under lights and by the eye of the Hollywood camera.  Monday we headed to our favorite little Mexican restaurant. We felt we need to be redeemed in the Mexican food department. So our fajitas rocked and at Alcupulco, Monday is known to the locals as Margarita Monday, cheap margaritas are always a good idea.  And now I find myself behind my desk and computer facing the beginning of the week. Excited by the fact that tomorrow is already Wednesday and payday none-the-less, but with a lot to do and one less day to do it. In the end, I think it all evens out and you'll never catch me complaining about a day off!  ta ta! 

						
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so...i've not really wanted to write on the blog lately...but i guess we had a pretty eventful weekend. Lets see.... On friday..we hung out and went to this mexican restraunt that Leah swore was good. She had been there for a work meeting...so... we went.  Once we got seated at the restraunt, we had waited for...oh....about 15 minutes before anyone talked to us.  Then....once the food had been ordered... we waited another 20 minutes. The food, once we got it, was not too good.  I'm not sure if my steak fajitas were really beef....or horse. they just tasted funky.  Then they forgot half my food... then in order to appease us....they gave us " flaky delight" desert.  it was crap. so...we split...feeling ripped off.  Saturday redeemed itself.  We started out our valentines day hanging with some pretty poor kids and families in this Garden Grove trailer/rv park.   It's a ministry an elederly lady at our church started 3 years ago....just hanging out with these kids at this central location.  After 3 years...every child within ear shot of the meeting place shows up. These kids just needed love.  it's a pretty ghetto area.  Kids are dealing drugs and prostituting and causing all sorts of trouble. Not to mention that in a trailer...there could be up to 12 people living in one 500 sq. ft. area.  It was bad. But...we had so much fun hanging and being Jesus to these kids and mothers.  I had some of them teach me some spanish...it was awesome.  Then on Saturday night... Leah and Candy supprised Chad and I with a steak dinner!!!  So...we munched on some good eats... hung out for a bit...then headed to the Chain Reaction to check out the Mae/ Copeland tour.  It was fun hanging at the show cos we got to hang with some cool friends we usually only run into at the chain.  Copeland was AMAZING. The last time they were in town was the best band i'd seen live in a long time.  This time...there were 10 times better.  It was nice and lovey-dovey in there. they played some lovey songs... all couples embraced... good stuff. Mae was horrrible.  They opened their set with some free-jazz crap that was slow and lifeless.  their record is good...live they are not good.  So...then today.. Monday... Leah and I headed north of Santa Monica to cruise down PCH through Malibu and Santa Monica. It was a beautiful little trip.  We got some cool pictures....which I'll post later.   Tomorrow we're excited.  We're headed back to the chain reaction to check out Limbeck and The Format. (2 of leah's fav bands and she has a crush on Limbeck's singer)  The running joke is that Leah and Candy have a thing for Limbeck's singer.    I wouldn't know...she got to see them when i was away at camp. hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm  

						
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i know it's already played out and anoying...but this is the last mention of it.  urlLink Take the new METROSEXUAL QUIZ .  "Mextrosexual was so 2003." 

						
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i don't know what the heck happened...but it seems as if all our code for the blog just disapeared. oh well. so...enjoy booring old blog. 

						
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Over the past 6 or 7 months, even before his death, I've been reading CASH by Jonny Cash - his biography.  Reading just a few pages every night before going to bed, and finally last night I finished it.  What a great book.  So full of wisdom, great stories, and passion for music and the Lord that only Johnny Cash could have. What a cool guy.    Leah and I FINALLY watched  Lost in Translation  last night.  That was a stinkin' good movie. It was slow, pretty dry, not that funny, but somehow it was a beautiful piece of art.  I really liked it. I don't know how it got a golden globe for best comedy.  I regret not seing it in the theater when i wanted to back in November. Oh well...it's worth the watch.   

						
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     if you happened to miss Coheed and Cambria on Jimmy Kimmel Live (like I did), someone was nice enough to put it online  urlLink here.  check it. 

						
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...the Super Bowl was a great game. I'm not sure the ads were all too spectacular but...hey...they only spent 16 million on each 30 sec ad.  Our college ministry part was cool.    OH!...today at lunch, I was at Rubio's eating my fish tacos, and siting in front of me was Jason Lee! The actor from all those Kevin Smith movies. It was cool. I just noticed it was him...but some kids in our restraunt, as soon as Lee got up to leave, these kids bum-rushed him for an autograph.  It was weird, but cool.  

						
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so..i never finished the story about the power going out. well...let's see. the power went out at 5:50ish in the AM.  I came home Monday around 1pm cos i was tired and the power was still out.  I hung out... listing to a cruddy radio... then decided to wash my car and give it the wax job it needed.  3 hours later i was done with that....and the power was still out.  Leah came home around 4:30.... and we ran some erands.... and the power came on while we were at home around 7pm. so.... all i wanted to do was play MLB 2004 on my PS2 and drink some cold water.   Nothing in our fridge got jacked up..so that was good.   OH....and i couldn't make coffee...that sucked.  -THE END-    Also...if you have  urlLink I-tunes  (which you should all have), William Hung has released a teaser-EP for his new record coming out. You can listen to 30 seconds of each song (which is more than enough time to "smell what he's cookin'") don't buy it... just listen to each 30sec clip over and over and over again.  "I believe I can fly" will make you pee your pants.  

						
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So...at 5:50 this morning...our power went out.  So did the juice for the entire block.  The silence was creepy...i couldn't sleep... so was in the office today at 7:30am....that's a first on a Monday. I just have this gut feeling that today is gonna really suck.  But the bright side is that I got to go to Starbucks at 6:50ish... suck down a few cups of coffee and read the very liberal, and lovely OC register. One main article I read was about this guy who tried to convince Orange County to build a mono-rail all over the county in the 90's.  They shut him down, so he went to Vegas to try the same thing....and they're opening a new mono-rail on the strip this summer! It was about as stupid as it gets.   Oh...for those of you who live in or near Goshen, IN- check this out -- I just got this from Ana Stustman the other day... "Steve Bucemi is currently filiming a movie in goode ol' G*town along with Liv Tyler y Casey Afflec... or so my Mom tells me... Steve hangs out w/ my sis @ the Electric Brew!!!"  Just when I leave the hood... Bucemi rolls into town.   Leah and I hung out with some folks (the Davis family) from Bryan,OH!  They were neighbors of mine back in my neighborhood. They came to church with us and we showed them aroud the Block of Orange. It was fun and the kids want to move to CA. I tried to encourage them to stay back east with their feet nailed to the ground.  I don't think it worked. 

						
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hellogoodbye- a band from OC... released their  urlLink EP  on the net...for FREE!.  It's alright. ( i think Dusty would like it) We saw them in concert a few weeks back...they kinda sucked....so... waddya want for free.  urlLink get it here.  

						
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Happy St. Paties day! I know it's over by the time you'll read this...but... whatever. Um... Some kid gave me some Irish-punk music to listen to all day. It was quite addictive.   I wish i was Irish.  HEY...I added some NEW PICTURES from last weekend. check em. 

						
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         there  are a lot of ways i'm gettin' old. And i'm realizing it now... I know...i'm only 25..but...old in relation to where i was a few years ago.  Anyhoo...one of those ways... and i hate to admit it.... my slow growing love of CCM music.  I've been anti-CCM music for years...at least the stuff that's all popular and expensive. But as I've been in ministry for a few years and CCM stuff just comes across your desk...I'm starting to kinda like it.  I think it's the quality of production mixed with the power of the music, which has lately been worship-focused. (and I'm a sucker for worship) So... I'm almost ashamed to admit it...but I dig it. (note: i still don't like Michael W. Smith, even his worship stuff) Anyhoo... I don't know why I shared that.   So....the new Jars of Clay and  CITY ON A HILL -The Gathering CDs are really good. (beautiful scandalous night is my fav) (and Delirious is always good: the new one is great)  Um...also...visiting folks:  urlLink please sign our guestbook ...no one has signed it yet. I'm getting sad. :(   

						
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     It's a real trip. Summer has started early this year out here in CA. On Sunday it started. And Sunday so happened to be the Youth Auction, which had consumed my life for the past few weeks. Anyhoo...the weather...yeah...it got realy warm really quickly. On Sunday for the auction... it was around 85 or so outside. Thus...inside..it was just stinkin' hot.  All in all...the auction was a success. I'm glad it's done...well almost. I've got some paperwork to do on it.    So yeah...It's hot lately. Well...HOT for March. I'm not complaining...i promise...I like it...it's just wierding me out.   Also...the link for my brother's auction was screwed up earlier. I fixed it. It's right now. check it in Monday's post. Just think... beer + a clock. genius.  Some new pictures added to  urlLink our picture site .  what else... i've been designing a lot. T-shirts and flyers and junk. Still haven't gotten paid yet. I'll charge one of these days.  Thinkin' bout buying a dot-com for  urlLink my art . And it's a great deal.  ok...that's it.  

						
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm proud of my brother Chris.  Go check out  urlLink his Ebay auction  for his new creation. classy.  

						
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     My friend Jeff and I were in LA county today... actually headed to the city of Compton. (it's not quiet like what NWA and Dre were talking about) but...we were out of gas....so we stoped here..... Who pays for 'Full Service'? dorks. 

						
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For those who know the story: remember guys... when we went to Indy to see MxPx and The Get Up Kids...that was cool....anyhoo... the Get Up Kids put out a new record today and out here in CA you can buy it at Best Buy for $5.99! how cheap! I just need to find 6 bucks now. Hopefully Best Buys in Indiana sell it for cheap too.      In some other weird junk: You can buy merch from me!  Well... the art junk i do... "Ignition Lab"....anyhoo...I made some coffee mugs, notebooks, stickers and postcards. Check them out  urlLink HERE(store 1)  and  urlLink HERE(store 2).    I've never seen the quality of work they do...so when Dusty get's his mug...he'll write a review.  But don't they look cool! (and there's a hidden store  urlLink here  for Dusty and the HC crew.) 

						
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey folks. Those of you who have a TV, this means nothing to you.  Last Sunday we (the student ministries) had a True Love Waits sunday four our whole youth ministry.  We did it in the church and on camera...so it's gonna air this weekend on the Hour of Power. so....if you want to see our kids and maybe a glimpse of me.... watch it. here is a link to the HOP TV schedule.  http://www.hourofpower.org/calendar/tvlistings.html 

						
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   so this weekend Leah and I got pretty sun burnt. that was fun. We went up to LA to watch a  urlLink student  in our college ministry row (or as i say 'crew it up') for UC Irvine.   Crew is a very interesting sport.  All the jargon and rules were very foreign to me.  Luckly-  urlLink Jessica's  dad was there to fill us all in. Anyhoo... it was fun watching these girls yell at each other, screaming some serious obcenities, just to motivate the girls to row harder or more in tandem. It was wacky, but a stinkin' beautiful day.   

						
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     You should see the smile on my face.  Morrissey has a new record coming out in May, and his  urlLink new video  is up to watch on the net. I've watched it a dozen times just today.  I'm so excited! I think this is a guilty pleasure. (Dusty...you know what I'm talking about:)Anyhoo...check  urlLink him  out. 

						
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Could 24 be a better show? the answer: none more bettter.   We had to tape the episode from Sunday cos we were at church... anyhoo... we watched it last night and I have to be honest- I was emotionally moved - big time.  If any of you saw it...it was brilliant. simply amazing.  I can't wait to see it tonight!  I'm listening to Kid Kilowatt right now.  This record "guitar method" is simply amazing. (just like 24)  It was recorded back in 99 and placed on the shelf for a few years. They are comprised of Stephen Brodsky from Cave In and some guys from Eulcid and Converge.  It was a side project deal that never took off cos each respecitve band took off.  Anyhoo...Hydra Head (the label) just sat on it for years. I remember getting a song in some zine comp and loving it. Looking forward to the full length that year (2000) i drove around Indiana listening to just the one song OVER AND OVER AGAIN.   It never came out... and never came out. Release date promises broken - but finally it came out a few weeks ago. I can't stop listening to it. pick it up. It's "indie-emo" done in a way that even in 99- no one has made anything like it yet.   For you music lovers...check out  urlLink Zombie Apocalypse's site  for a free cover of "Welcome to the Jungle: by GnR. It's rippin good.  

						
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      So my boss got a pre-release coppy of the soon to be released movie "Saved".  They sent it to him cos he's on some media think group...anyhoo.... I snagged it and watched it with Leah and Chad & Candy.   If you haven't seen the trailer for it yet... urlLink check it out.  It paints it in this really wacky light...that makes you kinda wanna watch it and also kinda stand against it.    Well...here's the deal.  It's an over the top, over spiritualized teen movie that paints Christians to look like complete A-holes. The movie makes the villian (the "non-Christian kids") to be the heroes in the end.  The "super-spiritual-sqeeky-clean" kids turn out to be the jerks, the back stabbers, the ones "with the problem."  It glorifies teen pregnancy, sexual promiscuity and "little sins".      I will say this though... there were times where I thought "man...we are like that"....and it poked fun at the nice Christan subculture we sometimes live in.  I found myself laughing at times and then wanting to turn the thing off at times too.    It's a movie that could be a double edged sword. Kids/people that come into the film with a pre-concieved distain for Christianity will love it. It will just fuel thier fire.  Kids that are super tight with Christ can possibly appreciate the movie for it's take on the Christian culture.  But only for study and dialoge would this be good.   And the kids on the edge...should steer clear of this movie.    I'll probably encourage students to NOT see it...but I can't make em.  My concern is that with the new found love of 'spiritual' entertainment...this could just be fuel for the other side of the fence.  People who think that this movie is going to "bring Glory to God" are gonna be dissapointed.  The glory ends up going to the enemy in this one.  

						
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     i addes some new photos to our  urlLink photo site . check em. 

						
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   happy easter!  I hope all of you are rockin' with your families and stuff.  Since Leah and I don't have any family around here...we'll hang out with good frieinds instead.   I've had the past few days off so we've been the laziest couple around.  Sleeping in till 9 everyday rules!!!  Just moping around So. Cal is great. It's not that we've seen it all...we're just sick of seeing any of it.   And the weather has been crummy lately too. ( for LA standards)   Leah tried to Hijack our NETFLIX last weekend while i was gone....which means she had a slew of 'chick' flicks rented....and they never got back to the warehouse this week...so we've been without good movies. (So i hijacked netflix and rented all guy movies!!)  Lets see....I'm pretty sick of So. Cal.   Any ideas?  OK....we love you all.....all of you who read this and know who we are. bye. 

						
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      hi. it's been a long time...at least for me, since i've posted. I've had a rough couple of weeks so....that's why.  I was in Oklahoma for 4 days.  You may be asking "what the heck was Brian doing in Oklahoma?"  I was asking the same question.   I felt as if i was just dropped in the middle of nowhere.  It was weird. I stayed on the north east side of town...where noone goes. The church i was visiting for a conference was up there.  It  was desloate.  The church was cool. real cool. It was a youth ministry of about 2500 students a week.  Seriously cool stuff...  anyhoo.... I AM SO TIRED LATELY. The jet-lag and the time change and not stoping are making me go crazy.  So...i'm taking off the next few days.  whew.  Lets see. The new  urlLink Beautiful Mistake  record came out today. It's really good. listent to it urlLink  here.    The new Modest Mouse came out today. It's really good. That's what I'm listening to right now. Um.... Lovedrug is playing in Anaheim tonight...and I'm so tired I don't even care to see it. You know you're down when you don't wanna go to great shows. I hope I get better.  Oh...I'm finally gonna go see Hellboy tonight with a student.  You may be asking " how can a youth pastor take a kid to a move with HELL in it?"  Well... I've read the comic book and I love the story line. It's actually a redemptive story. He's a demon fighting his nature (to be evil) and trying to do good.  We'll see how the movie shapes up. I'm excited though.     

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Isn't it nice to wake up in the morning and think "boy...everyone in the entire world hates us!"  At least that's how I think. I wake up every day watching the news. That may be a bad idea in and of it's self. Anyway... As a country we're so hated it's almost comical. We've been this "great" country for so long...now we're pissin' everyone off.   I'm excited for that new Michael Moore movie. I can't wait for that to just make everyone mad. Both right and left...just duking it out to the finish. I envision it to be like a Pyrrhic victory. just dead bodies laying around everywhere from both sides.      So I'm reading this great book called "Blue Like Jazz" by Donald Miller. It's quiet amazing. I can't put it down. It's as if I'm talking to the guy. really well written. It's one of those books that you say "man...i've thought that...but never said it! wow!"  And...it makes fun of modern religion...so....neato!    The new Brandtson record is stinkin' hot! I've been listing to it for a few weeks now...wozers! It's a "Dusty" record. :) Get it in a few weeks. rock.    Also in the rock world the new Pedro The Lion record is melting my mind.  Just gets you thinkin' you know?  So..what are you all doing over Memorial Day weeked? Go drive alot. I heard gas is real cheap theese days. It's like $2.31 at the cheapest place around here.  I guess Dundee,MI is slowly approaching that. (according to Leah's parents) That's redonkulous!    

						
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So...gas is friggin off the charts, this kid in my youth group dented the crap out of the hood of my car with a water bottle and I'm listening to Engine Down triping out to the cloudy weather....grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.  For a Monday today is sorta good. I'm tired and ready for Tuesday. But...Morrissey comes out tomorow. yea! that is always good.     ok..bye.  

						
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So the weather out here is great. Gas prices are stupid high. And I seem to hate where I'm at. I just had one of those days yesterday...you know?   The higlight to my day was getting the Killswitch Engage record...which shouldn't be the best part of my day. Actually..i take that back...the best part of my day was going ot sleep last night. That's how fun yesterday was.  Bad days happen..i realize that...but I'm just sick of em. Working too darn hard. Getting paid too little and and putting up with some stupid crap all day long. I just need a vacation. Or some drugs.  On a lighter note...everyone should  urlLink email Leah  and tell her to write something here. It's been way to long.  Van Helsing sucked rotten eggs.  I hope that crap bankrupts the company that funded it. It was a 2 and a half hour, high budget B-movie. Instead of seing that movie, go see all the old horror moives like the orignal Dracula, Frankenstein, and any old Evil Dead movies.  Wolverine...you let me down.  Ok..I'm in a bad mood. I'll stop writing.    

						
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I updated my   Ignition Lab Design   site. Unfortunately it's not a dot com yet... but soon enough. check it out  urlLink here.  It's got downloads and will soon have merch.  

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Leah is for real! Napoleon Dynamite is easily the funniest movie so far this year! Dodgeball sucked in light of this amazing film. It has that Wess Anderson feel to it, but more simple. And the beauty of it all, it's rated PG! Not PG-13 or R, but PG!   Not too many movies are very good with a PG rating. Somehow they did it! Go see it ASAP! BOO-YA! 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm not sure how much this new indie film has been previewed on the East coast, but I would give it two thumbs up. It's is hilarious and only rated PG to boot. It's one of those films you see and leave the theatre feeling happy. I'm not sure that I can completely describe it, but it's about this kid in Idaho or Iowa (somewhere in the middle) who is in HS and he's your average nerd/dork and all of his experiences at school and with his weird family. You'll just have to trust me on this one, it's worth the $7.50. So for all the folks in FWA, it might be at Cinema City downtown or I guess you'll have to wait for video. Either way, check it out. Great one-liners and it will make you laugh outloud.   That's it for my movie reviews, for now.  buh, bye. 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello all, I know that I am overdue for a quick synapsis of our lives. Ok, here goes. First and foremost,wild and crazy do not begin to describe life at present. Brian and I seem to be two ships passing in the night with our schedules. And he just got home this morning from an all-nighter so as he catches up on much needed sleep, I'm catching up on some much needed e-mail and blogging. It's been a full week complete with food tasting for a friend's upcoming wedding(yum), finishing up all invoicing and accounting for the end of our fiscal year at work (there was a reason I dropped my accounting class in college and not it's come full-circle to haunt me), workout at the gym (which actually add to my sanity these days while at the same time taking away from my hips...so it's a win, win) Brandtson concert at the chain reaction (always a good time and got to hang out with Clara's hubby John) and then Brian with youth group on Wednesday and all nighter Friday....and somehow Tuesday slipped away, I can't recall currently.  And yesterday I had my annual review.....it went well, but for some reason I was a bit anxious, the end result was a raise....YIPPEE!  Pfeeww!   So, all in all we are well. We feel as though God is leading but we're not quite sure which direction. So for those of you that pray, we would really appreciate some extra our way. And for those of you that already do, we REALLY appreciate it and can feel it!  i hope my post isn't a downer, just reporting life as it happens. sometimes it's happy, happy, joy, joy (ren&stimpy reference) and other times it's not, ya know.    

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey. i put up some new photos from Brandtson's visit to the OC. Not too many...but you'll see. www.hotwaterbrian.fotopages.com 

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Am I taking crazy pills? Doesn't that  urlLink Napoleon Dynomite  movie look amazing?  Everyone I talk to seems to think that this film looks stupid. I think it could be my favorite film of the summer (except for spiderman 2). COME ON! He uses words like "flippin sweet" and "boo-ya".  I mean...come one....we need more BOO-YA in AMERICA!!!  Anyhoo...I think I'm gonna go sell some blood to get some cash inorder for us to see it. (kidding) ok...bye.   

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Hey. My new favorite song is now on the internet. Further Seems Forever posted a new song with Jon Bunch on their  urlLink Purevolume site.  Wow... nearly made me cry. Maybe it's cos i'm feeling crummy..but this song is really amazing. 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So i get the weirdest voicemail from my brother last night. He was falling asleep to the television and mindlessly fliping through channels.  Then he ran across this show on Spike TV with this guy we went to school with. (for those who know Bryan,OH...Tim Newell) He was on the show "10 things every guy should experience".  Tim was competing against another guy to win tickets to the NBA finals. I'm not sure what happened.... but Tim won. Chris said it was surreal. I guess the show will re-air this Friday June 11 at 12am.  (i'm not sure if that's thursday night or Friday night....i'm stupid like that)  Then....my brother told me that Chris Carpenter from Bryan,OH, got drafted to the Detroit Tigers in the 7th round of the MLB draft.  Chris Carpenter was a neighbor of ours back in Bryan. So...that's pretty stinkin' cool.      --> The trip to LA this weekend was a smashing success. There were no problems and we served over 1500 meals. There are some new pictures of it in our photo site.   Anyone heard that Kanye West record yet? that's a great record. anyhoo...peace out!  

						
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Memorial day weekends are always fun aren't they? The whole "day off" thing just gets you all geeky. So...anyhoo...it was fun for Leah and I. We were sad to have to go back to work. Like really sad.  Now this weekend is the exact opposite of that for me. I'm taking a dozen or so teens to the heart of LA to work at a The Union Rescue Mission (the US's largest homless shelter) So...from Friday to Sunday...we're serving meals around the clock. Pray for us and our trip. thanks.  Oh...my brother showed this to me. It's really funny.  urlLink Click here to watch it ...but it's got some bad words in it. So...if you don't like bad words...don't do it.(i think the link works...but if it doesn't...i'll fix it later.    Also...I can't stop listening to this record.... "Love is worth it" by Silent Drive on Equal Vision Records. It's so addictive and beautiful! check it out  urlLink here...   You know what's really good travel music?  Rush.  Yep.  Ok..bye. 

						
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Holy crap! It's been a weird week. Lets start at the begining. Monday- I was going to quit my job. I was told to hold on. (thinking "i'll give God till tomorow till I'm out!") Tuesday- I was going to quit my job and work in the Internet dept. doing graphic and web design. I was told to hold on till Thursday. I did. (thinking "I'll give God till Thursday or I'm out!") Thursday- My boss resigned. (fired) That confirmed that I wasn't to walk out yet.  &nbsp; Now it looks as if I'm going to be taking over the high school ministries at the CC. &nbsp; It's amazing to me how God works. Yes I know...it's God....so it has to be amazing...but seriously. God's timing is so above and beyond our timing. At my rope's end... instead of tying a noose, God told me just to "HANG ON!" It's not what I wanted to hear, but It's what I needed to do.&nbsp; I'm really surprised that I was obedient enough to do that. :) &nbsp; Thanks to everyone who has been praying for Leah and I through this crappy time.&nbsp; The clouds have lifted and life is good.  &nbsp; It's nice to smile again.  

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   you can listen to a 30 sec bits of the new Jimmy Eat World stuff  urlLink here . (you'll need the Real Audio Player) It'll be fun to have a new record from them.  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Life has been pretty nutty lately. More on that to come at a later date. I promise.  Um...on a good note, the new Zao record came out today. (so did the polyphonic spree...what a contrast) Anyhoo...check out the  urlLink new video from Zao over here .  The I love the 90's show is a struggle to get through isn't it. anyhoo..bye. 

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So...our dear friends Chad and Jenny from AZ came out to visit us this weekend. It was quite a breath of fresh air for both Leah and myself.  It was fun to see some old familiar faces and just relax with them. Well...we didn't really relax, but we did to lots of stuff together.  They came out on Saturday, and right away we ate, and then went to buy more food for a bar-b-q with the Cronins and the Pearsons and some other friends at the CC Youth House. Then from there, after many games of Halo, we went to the Angels game. They got worked by the Dodgers and we sat it the furthest seats from home plate. That sorta stunk. After the game, we were itching for more Halo and burgers, so we went to the youth house again. We bought some fireworks, and since I'd like to keep my job, we set em off in an industrial park a few yards from the church.  Right as the last firework was going off, a cop rolled in.  As soon as we saw the cop my mind raced to the worst possible scenario. I'd be sent to jail, fired from my job all that stuff. But I stood still. My first inclination was to run, but that's pretty juvenile.  As I’m freaked out and wondering what to do, Chad Cronin is slipping behind or into the car, thinking that will save him. It was funny.  The rest of us stood still as the fire work was still going off as the cop was trying to roll up on us. It seemed like that firework just kept going and going and going.   Anyhoo…the cop rolled up, and all he said was (imagine this in your meanest, toughest cop voice) “clean up your trash.”    That’s all he said and did. He rolled out of there, and I about did a back flip. It was awesome!  On Sunday, we went to Church, saw the CC big ol' American flag and listened to Dr. Schuller do some horrible acrostic to A.M.E.R.I.C.A. yuk. But after that nightmare was over, we wanted to take Chad and Jenny to see our new favorite movie, NAPOLEON DYNAMITE! (seriously...this is my new favorite movie; every like is like a gift from God)  Ok...I'll speed it up, Sunday night, the night of the fourth; we couldn’t find a good place to see fireworks. But Leah and I had a crazy idea of trying to park near Angels stadium and watch their 4th of July show. And by the grace of God we turned into a hotel parking lot that had the best view of the fireworks.  It was great.  Monday, we had some breakfast in old town Orange, and they took off for home.   Now…I’m sick.  I was probably sick on Saturday, I just amped myself through it. I feel like walking around my office in a big warm blanket. That’s how good I feel.    Ok…Bye.  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So sorry that this is an old/out-dated post. It was written a couple weeks ago, but I couldn't get it to post. So, it's working now and here it is. You may have to scroll back a bit to review and catch up.    Everyone has those days, weeks or months that make you think one of two things...1)I better hang on to God for dear life since it's spinning so out of control or 2) oh crap this sucks, I think I've had enough and it seems like God can't help. bummer. I hate to admit it but during the last two months I've been bouncing back and forth between both of those, often not know which end was up. The lesson learned? (there always is one, you know.) God's timing is perfect and we will never understand that. Faith is blind and we have experienced this to a new level. The beauty of God's timing is unreal, literally everything came together in the last possible moment, hour and day. But the point is that it came together. God is good and justice is sweet.  I'm sure you all know someone who confirms daily that life is not fair and that their behavior toward others will never catch up with them. The type of person that makes you wonder if God is watching, and if he is why he would allow this person to continue to get away with horrible things and hurting everyone and everything they come into contact with. I (we) have witnessed the justice of God in this situation first hand and it has been a HUGE spiritual kick in the pants for me. What more can I say? Of course I echo Brian's thank you to everyone near and very dear to us who have faithfully upheld us in prayer and support. And have listened to us (me) cry, vent, question and now rejoice.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For those of you Midwest HxC kids...I got a cool email today from Dan and Geeta Tupps. Dan...the amazing singer-guy from the colossaly huge At Peace While Burning... and Geeta were living in Northern Indiana last I knew. I guess they just moved to HONG KONG! Here are some snippits from their email. Keep em' in yer Prayers!   After a couple weeks of apartment hunting we found a beautiful place called Laguna Verde. It is an Italian style apartment complex located right on the harbour. ww.lagunaverde.com.hk  Dan has been working for Hong Kong Mandarin Bible Church (HKMBC) for a little over a month. He has slowly been developing good relationships with the youth and parents, but many are traveling abroad through the summer. We really enjoy worshiping with the people of HKMBC. Dan is excited about this wonderful experience to be able to do youth ministry here.  Geeta will begin working at Christian Alliance International School (CAIS) later this month. School starts August 30. She will be teaching High School English and Christian Ethics. This is a tremendous opportunity for Geeta to be able to put to use the things that she has learned through college and seminary.  Tower 12A, 25th Floor, Flat G Laguna Verde Hung Hom, Kowloon HONG KONG   Tel: 852-3154-3369    

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I was driving into work today, thinking to myself that I'm 25 years old, and I still listen to heavy metal.  That really creeped me out. I remember being in high school hoping and praying that I would never get old and listen to booring music. Well...that hasn't happened yet.  I think I like metal more today than I did years ago.  It's weirding me out.  Brian Posheen, a comedian, talks about his love for metal and being old on his bit on Comedy Central. He's creepy and weird. I don't want to be that guy. yikes.  Um...last Sunday night's college group at the CC was easily the worst and weiredest moment in ministry for me.  It was surreal. The full moon was out, and all the weirdos showed up to our program.  I can't explain it all here, but suffice it to say this:  A local weirdo-radio-call-in guy showed up and kept asking me if he had the tallent to break into radio. So did this girl with the WORST body odor I have ever experienced...and we had to driver her home.  She salted our evening's conversation with her passion for collecting beanie babies, pound puppies and my little ponies.  She's 23 years old.  It was surreal.  Ok...Trading Spouses is wrong on so many levels.....but so stinkin' addicitve to watch.  This video on  urlLink Jib Jab  is really stinkin' funny.  Don't buy the new Jimmy Eat World EP on itunes. Only 1 song is new. The rest are just re-recorded old ones.  Has everyone gone to see the greatest movie yet..Napoleon Dynamite? Do it. Do it. 

						
</post>


</Blog>