<Blog>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to kick some ass.  Specifically idiot bitch of indecisive-would-be-sex boy.  Lol, one of my friends -let's call her banana- Banana said she knows a girl who hates idiot bitch (  DEWD!  Did anyone know that Hitler dropped out of highschool?!  Now don't be getting any ideas!  I already tried lol.  Wait...I was writing about idiot bitch.  Anyway 0_O she was apparently saying that she wanted to kick my ass.  Banana was one who heard her say this.  She described how she was able to retain laughter until she got home.  Kick MY ass?  Dude, I don't even care about her and idiot boy much, I do however become incredibly defensive when my power is threatened.  Call me overconfident, but if I let loose god help ya.  I have not done so, due to a lack of reason to.  But if I feel I have a reason, like I do now, heh, watch the fuck out idiot bitch.  Give me one week in Kung Fu.  One week...  So I have anger issues.  No one really makes me that mad.  Except my mom.  A few weeks ago, I thought if she said one more nasty thing to me I would kill her... but things are better now 8) heh hehe heh...  Better... yessss...  Really, they are.  I do not want to kil her or myself anymore!  Probably because I get to go back to Reno, and leave this hell.  SUCH ASPIRATIONS I HAVE!!!  Wewt!  Heh...  When I do go back, I plan to abstain (try to) from the poisons of teendom.  No more getting drunk.  Bad stuff that.  But because I like beer I choose not to give it up entirely.  Gimme a Corona and a lime!  Yum... no more hard alky-hall.  It not tasty.  As for smokin' I want to get in really good shape again.  I only need one hit to be satisfied, but I have goals, and I mustn't be distracted!  And doing that makes ya laaaaaaaazy.  So, yeah, abstinence.  Werd.  I only have 4 more days of school!!! YAY!!! Fuck you Healdsburg (though you are better than Galena)!  Fuck you Galena!  ...with a capital F!!! Ya bastards!!! I hope the administration, all of them, goes to Hades!!  RRAARR!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OY VEY!!  What the hell does it take to get a fucking tag-board on this mother fucker?!  ARG!  Spent 2 hours of my life working on fixing problems...blah.  Bored to the point of irritation...and not a single thing done on my LSD report... tralalalala.... Yall like the new digs?  I changed some shit, I like it more, the background will change, fo sho... alien blood or whatever it's called can't last...tain't that cool.  Fuckin wasted day.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Bondage movie! You're into BSDM (Bondage & Discipline, Dominance & Submission) and chances are, you're fond of whips, chains, harnesses, and tight leather outfits. You like to mix a little pain with a LOT of pleasure, baby!    urlLink   What kind of porno would you star in?    Who could not have guessed this?  Really?  Dur dur dur...     You have been involved in a shameful online RPG, and your soul will never be clean. You've soiled the memory of a dead author and neglected yourself and other human beings for months at a time; there is no way to make up for this. The Lord has turned His eyes from you forever!  Keep back, you utter trash!    urlLink   Why Will You Go To Hell?       Orlando Bloom: you like them dead sexy, with an orgasmic accent and looks. *drool*    urlLink   Which guy are you destined to have sex with?   He be smiling like my ex...*drool*     Seductive Flirt    urlLink   What Kind of FLIRT are you?      urlLink        You Should Teach  urlLink Sex Ed 101 !  You are destined to be a sex-ed teacher.  No doubt, you enjoyed the class back in school...  And the subject is one you've explored fully over the years :-)    You love to help your friends who have sexual difficulties.   You are a understanding mentor and completely non-judgmental.  You are destined to be the next Susie Bright or Dr. Ruth!     urlLink   What's Class Should You Teach?   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing  quite like a hug from a friend's boyfriend.  Heh, I was a friendly appreciative hug, I gave him a bunch of candy, he was happy.  Good times.  Despite my shitty day.  I think the males have begun to notice me.  Too bad for them, I am so jaded by shit that I am not receptive in the least.  I really hope my friend(s) got my yearbook, must have buke sigh-ned!!! I hold on to the past, dammit, CATER TO MY NEEDS!!!  I only have 4 days of school left.  Then it's off to boston...WHEE! Family reunion, whee. I am not looking forward to it, and I doubt that I'll have a good time.  Heh 14 of my 16 cousins are girls, I believe... and I'm the eldest.  Suckage, I doubt any of them will have hot boyfriends for me to steal away for that week... WRONG!! Bad Me, BAD!  Back to the sex thoughts.  Not too depressed to be horny.  Fuckin terrif.  I hate cell phones.  No, I hate my mother's cell phone.  There is no greater priority than the fucking plastic piece of shit.  I shouldn't be mad at the phone I should be mad at her, which I am, and the people who call her.  BLECK!  I feel sick to my tummy o_O think I may puke...never do though...ahh! bored...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      To all my friends: I know it was really shitty of me to write that I thought you were only friends with me out of pity, I know you aren't.  I know you're friends with me for a good and positive reason... however, I can't for the life of me think what that reason may be... I feel like a really worthless human right now.  I also know that this may upset some of you, and I'm sorry.    I don't know why I get this way.  I feel empty inside, like a shell of what and who I once was.  A darkness fills my void.  I do not know why I have reverted to this self torture.  I feel as though I am an uncaring and worthless person.  I can't imagine why anyone remains around me.  I should be put in a hole and starved, with nothing but a razor to punish myself and feed off my own blood.    I am continuously consumed by a black apathy that nags at me each time I begin to enjoy life again.    Sorry to instill doubt within all the readers, but, how realistic is that?  Honestly... look at the pattern (mine at least): more often than not when I look forward to, say, an event it somehow falls through.  When I say to myself, "I am going to have a good day," It is often far from good.  Maybe I set my expectations too high.... I do not know.  All I know is I had a good afternoon, I talked to friends on the phone.  I enjoyed talking to friends on the phone.  I had the idea that I had grown away from them, it is worry.   I fear that I am not the person I was when I left them.  I analyzed my feelings and that has to be what is my latest difficulty.  Writing is the only action that makes me feel any better, at all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, feeling better I am.  I am incredibly critical of myself, and it shows.  A LOT!    Brrr but I'm feelin better!  Fuck you it all goes away.  Hehe SOAD man.  I spent like 3 hours talking to two of my bestest friendses.  Put me in a fabulous mood.  I cannot wait to get back to Reno!  FRIENDS!!  KUNG FU!!! EXERCISE!!  and of course, sex.  Heh, I do not want as much sex as I think I want.  I want orgasms.  I want to give and recieve, however, not by sex other than oral.  Thag you very buch.       urlLink       You Should Be On Temptation Island!  You're a sexy showoff who is always looking for a good time.  Whether you're part of a troubled couple or appearing as a tempting single, you're sure to cause a stir...  urlLink   What Reality TV Show Should You Be On? Click Here to Find Out!    How many of yall could have guessed this??  REALLY?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am probably the most useless person on the planet.  I have been working on a project about ecstasy...I spelled ecstasy in big black letters on a poster ECSTACY thinking that that is the way it is spelled.  I figure out at 11pm tonight, the night before it is due, that I had been spelling it wrong the entire time.  You probably think I'm making too big of a deal about this, but I have high standards when it comes to certain things, and pardon me if thinking that knowing how to spell what your fucking project is about is important.  Not only am I socially retarded but I am an imbicile as well.  Who FUCKING makes a mistake like that? WHO?!  God, I'm such an ass... no wonder I have no friends here.  Everyone in reno: it's pity friendship, isn't it?  I need to go take a shower with my razor.  Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck I am so dumb.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink       Your Tongue's Talent is  urlLink Licking Pussy !  Your small slippery tongue is just perfect for fitting in those little folds. You're not shy about giving pleasure, and you demand it back. You're perfect at working it all over, licking and slurping. You love the warm moistness of coochie, and you savor the flavor. Watch out though, you don't want a permanent catfish smell on your breath. Next time you go down on her, throw in an Altoid for some flavor. You'd be most compatible with a Rimmer. You both absolutely love exploring deep, dark places with your tongue, and you can teach each other a couple of tricks. A Rimmer is sure to get you to open up a bit, and quit being so secretive!  urlLink   What's Your Tongue's Talent?      Certain people will be happy to read this...  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy fucking fuck.  Bad dream about being hunted by Nazis.  Brought on, I'm sure, by little Ignorami in training.  I fear the fear of the ignorant.  Good god damn.  I bet half, more than half of the "Neo-Nazis" have no idea what Nazi means.  National Socialist Worker's Party.  That's it.  Fuck.  I don't think the majority of them choose to be believers of that for any other reason than they think it is in some way cool.  Satan dammit.  What a fucking way to wake up... My dream, throwing possessions into a suitcase turning toward the door, then that fucking alarm clock.  Horrid.  I wanted to know what I was going to do next.   Can you BELIEVE some people think the Holocaust did not happen.  DID NOT HAPPEN?  Fuckin... like 10 million people were killed!  And other such events are occuring today, the people who are doing it aren't powerful enough so the U.S. media choses not to acknowledge it.  Third world countries could be having a holocaust type situation, and just because the people who do it are not capable of what Hitler was they are allowed to continue with it, unpunished.    I hate stupid people.  The more one knows, the less they think they know.  If that doesn't make sense, then it obviously does not apply to you.  o_0 arg
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I have had an excellent evening!  Dinner with my mother, Grandfather, and his friend Linda.  Food was incredible!!  Halibut...  An eggplant and mushroom puree soup, my god, who comes up with this shit?!  And the desert... pastry puff with ice cream and a chocolate sauce with liquor... I cannot describe the taste!  It was glorious!  Fucking ORGASMIC!  I went from being in a fairly shit mood to being happy again.  An my Grandfather has proven to me that he is not an asshole...I don't want him to die!!  Hooray!  Joyus be all!  Haha live is good for the time being.  Went from wanting to slit my wrists before the meal to wanting to love life.  What food can do.    Meanwhile, an online friend has just told me he's a neo-nazi.  With a "hehe" this poor boy is proud.  He hates "niggers and chinks" why?  Because he doesn't understand their culture.  People, this is what causes events such as the HOLOCAUST.  The blatant decision to be an ignoramus, I feel the time to post my essay "Ignorance is Fatal"  oh, and kiddies, try making a decision for yourself every now and then.  White Pride?  What the fuck is that?  Seriously?  I'm not proud to be white...who the fuck thinks it's a good thing?  The color of one's skin determines  nothing  relating to brain size or capacity or ability.  We are in no way superior to people with a different skin and culture... It is bullshit and I am constantly astounded as to how people get drawn into such nonsense.    And now, The Essay: Ignorance “Ignorance is fatal,” a conclusion expressed by a character, in The Martian Chronicles by Ray Bradbury, who was desperate to have the world remember that which it had destroyed.  Anything that came from the human imagination was made illegal and forgotten.  For those who knew of the wonders lost, it was a horror to watch the new generations grow and have no idea of creative possibilities.  One man makes a last attempt to show the people who took the fantasy away what they had in fact taken.  He creates a situation that he had read about in an “illegal” book and victimizes certain people.  He tells one that had he read the book he would know what would happen to him.  A world where only “pure” factual material is published and any imaginative product is outlawed is, well, unimaginable.   	The question, “How is restriction of imagination enforced” comes to mind.  Books not relating to solid facts were burned.  What of the people who are the source of the unbelievable? Are children merely discouraged and punished for suggesting the presence of an invisible friend or the wish to fly like a bird?  Scientific facts must be etched in the minds of the young early on.  Then there would be little chance of objection, the children would not know anything different.   	The teaching of the young is an old trick, so to speak, used many a time in the past.  An example of such teaching is religion.  How many people truly question the faith they have grown up with?  When one is subjected to years of “truth” it cannot be questioned.  Were it to be, all of life would seem unreal to that person.  “What is truth?” would rise in their minds.  The boundaries set by certain persons has now been breached.  If a mind questions, how can it be controlled?  It is assumed that without imagination many would not be able to think creatively and therefore would need others to think for them.  Control.    	Some question truth without having faith.  In society it is very difficult to decide what is “right”.  The beginning to such query may begin with thoughts like, “Maybe it is not weight I should worry about, but appearance,” or “Perhaps caloric intake is not what needs to be watched, but the fat and sugar content,” the steps to open the mind tend to begin with seeming insignificancies.  To question one idea will inevitably lead to questioning another.  Society’s ideals may eventually seem ridiculous to someone who began wondering about media’s pressures.  Wonder is an opening to learning, and learning is the path to knowledge.   	Learning is a strange action.  In some ways learning is beyond the control of the learner.  Personal learning such as touching a hot plate and getting burned is a fact of life and cannot be changed.  If someone is being taught a fact they are learning what has been learned by another, and the interpretation may not be what the learner would interpret.  Therefore, when being taught, a person may not learn what was intended to be learned.  Ignorance is also very complex.  To one person ignorance may be a lack of common sense, to another a lack of knowledge.  It is most likely both.  Whether ignorance is fatal depends on the situation in which one needs not to be ignorant.        Red Chii    urlLink   Chobits - What Color Chii Are You?     Dryad    urlLink   What magical female creature are you?   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oy vey, no food or money today.  At school, lunchtime, no lunch, very sad, very hungry.  ::Sob:: I guess I should not have put all that money in that drawer just to hoard it from my mum.  Heh, karma, man, it's been kicking my ass all month.  I reeeeeaally hope Dcik gets my yearbook today.  I want it signed by as mnay people as possible so I can have a false sense of popularity.  Weak me.  Ah well.  I cannot wait to return to Reno and see everyone again.  Yay!!    I'm going to get so bored this summer.  I bet I'll wear out every one of my plans within a week or two.  At least there will be the fitness goal to continuously work toward.  KUNG FUCKING FU BABY!!!  Lol tis my little thoughts that make me seem weird and idiotic.  Life shall continue when I return to my love.  I have figured things out... Kung Fu=my life, I will not have not done Kung Fu for 6 monthes when I go back to it, therefore I have lost 6 monthes of my life.  Grr.  The experience living here has been a complex formula of hate, depression, intigue, and sorrow.  Note: 1/4 of the mix is positive.  I conclude that this past time has not been worth it.  I choose not to sulk, by gum.  I shall take what I have learned here to expand my sense of being.  I have learned something about myself.  Many things actually.  I cannot survive without my friends or Kung Fu.  Whether I can survive with one and not the other has yet to be determined.  I also learned that I fear people if I have no one to go to.  In other words I need at least one good friend to turn to when the rest of the world hates me.  Lastly, I need to stay fit.  I get depressed when I am not sleek and energetic like I used to be.    My plan: Return to Reno-get GF to buy me a membership to 24 hour fitness-make nice with the body builders so they help me become one (Females who body build without steroids DO NOT end up looking like men...got that?!?  What knowledge can do...uninformed assholes...) then I can be all "I are Superwoman!! Don't fuck with me unless I say so!"  Hehe...Me and my crazy ideas.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Fucking hell.  Why can I not sleep?  Went to bed last night at like 11:30 and lay in bed for who knows how long.  JFC!!  I think I am becoming an insomniac.  Sleepy so sleepy.  In the immortal words of NIN "tried to save myself but myself keeps slipping away"...slipping away by way of benadryl.  I have been taking it because I have been having incredible headaches, and my mom thinks it is allergies.  I think otherwise but when I took it on Saturday I was out like a light.  I took more last night to try to sleep, I don't think it did much good.  At least I got a kick ass essay done, I doubt it will earn me a kick ass grade though.  I should put it on here, but I do not feel like it right now.  I am tired and it's early.  Too early.  Too fucking early to do anything more than type or stare blankly into my bowl of cereal.  I will later today maybe... 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, I found the last IM session I had with indecisive boy...Thank goodness I sent the convo to a friend so I can spite him now!  Though I am not so spiteful as to leave his screen name as what it is.  Here we go...   Him:  hey  CharmingEnigma:  finally  CharmingEnigma:  =)  Him:  hey nck said you e-ailed him the convo you had with my gf  Him:  do you still have it  CharmingEnigma:  yea  Him:  cause i want to read what she wrote  CharmingEnigma:  it's on my blog  Him:  blog?  CharmingEnigma:  online journal i'll send it to you in a moment  CharmingEnigma:  wait...how do I know this isn't her?  CharmingEnigma:  oh wait, I'm sure she wouldn't be able to think of something like pretending to be you  CharmingEnigma:  I think it may be a little beyond her mental grasp  CharmingEnigma:  no offense...to you  CharmingEnigma:  are you still there?  Him:  yeah  Him:  sorry bout that  CharmingEnigma:  sent ~*  CharmingEnigma:  how is she doing?  CharmingEnigma:  well, I hope...  Him:  yea shes doing ok  Him:  i dont know aanh i like her so much  Him:  annah  CharmingEnigma:  well, it is your choice  CharmingEnigma:  if you don't mind my asking....   CharmingEnigma:  How are her blowjobs?  Him:  she doesnt give me bjs  Him:  i cant talk to you about this  CharmingEnigma:  I see....  Him:  its just she is so important to me, more than sex or anything else in this world..  CharmingEnigma:  ******...are you alright?  CharmingEnigma:  more than sex...wow  Him:  no..  Him:  i dont want to loose her  Him:  i would loose myself completely  CharmingEnigma:  Like I said, it's your choice  Him:  i got to go hit something see ya later   CharmingEnigma:  night  I don't even know why I put this here.  It's not cuz I'm holding a grudge or anything, I just was looking forward to the sex.  And I'm pissed because most of my friends are in pain of some sort.  Heh, how many want to kill themselves this week?  JESUS CHRIST WHY CAN'T LIFE BE GOOD?!?!  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling better now.  Feeling fat.  Lumpy and such.  But it's all good.  Kung Fu soon, so so soon.  I need to stop eating badly.  My bad food is other's good food.  I am a fanatic that way...  Crazy ol' me.  I want to g to a party.  I want to prove to people here that I'm not some quiet unfriendly girl who wears black.  I stopped wearing a lot of black back in the day.  Lol 6 months ago I was easing out of my darkness... heh, after moving here I was thrown violently back into it.  So much so, that I want to become a goth.  Hehehehe...sexy sexy goth.  Goth guys and goth girls...now that's some nice angsty ass I'd like to... o_0 this is going to be read by friends... I'll stop.  Hehe but really...goth people.  Oh!  The eyeliner!!  The pain... S&M omg...I really need to stop, killing kitties just is not possible tonight.    Nine Inch Nails!!! This is some music I'd like to fuck by...Jesus, wasn't I supposed to stop the sex talk?!!  I guess I can't help myself.  I'm so tired of saying dumb shit.  No, asshole, I wasn't talking about what's on here.  I meant the crap that I say that's just me being an idiot.  I annoy myself more than I annoy anyone else.  Blat!  I think I'm going to edit some of my past entries now... I have some stuff explaining the guy with dumb girlfriend situation a bit better.  So yah...I'm off to edit!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my god, I am so sick.  I slept all morning.  I feel absolutely disgusting.  That'll show me, I'm never eatting garlic french fries again.  I have felt like throwing up since last night.  Did I? No, there was no toilet at the fair...and as easy as it would be to heave in a porta-potty I just wasn't in the mood to go that far.  Though now, I wish I had.  This cannot be allergies.  Maybe that's what is causing the headache but, damn.  I feel repulsive.  I feel like a lump of flesh sitting in a chair...oh wait... By the time I get back to Kung Fu I will have been gone for 6 months.  Fucking A.  I was so svelt!!  Sad, but to sick to cry.  What I would give to go back to that night when my uncle flipped out...sure it was kind of hell living with him.  But it is also hell living here.  I wasn't worrying whether I was going to pass my sophomore year.  I had friends.  For the first time since 3rd grade I had more than 1 or 2 people in my group of peers!  Woe is me.  Thank Satan I get to come back.  If I couldn't...heh...I fear the consequences.  I'm already gaining weight... dear god.  I think I need to go watch The Sweetest Thing...specifically the orgasm dream... yes... orgasm... I mean movie... orgasm...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink       Your Hidden Sexual Talent is Sniffing Out Big Dick  All your friends wonder your trick... You're an expert at finding big dick! You're the envy of every girl on the block. Because your man has the biggest cock.    urlLink   What's *Your* Hidden Sexual Talent?        urlLink      	 You Are Cumslut Barbie!  You come complete with press on suction lips, portable wet wipes, and skin toner. Add on "Spit-it-back" function sold separately. Not recommended for children under age 6.  urlLink   What Naughty Barbie Are *You*?        You are Neo, from "The Matrix." You display a perfect fusion of heroism and compassion.    urlLink   What Matrix Persona Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You have a mysterious kiss.  Your partner never knows what you're going to come up with next; this creates great excitement and arousal never knowing what to expect.  And it's sure to end in a kiss as great as your mystery.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       your asshole.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla            urlLink   WHAT TYPE OF WILD CREATURE ARE YOU? (New Pictures!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Tramp Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Okay I know this is a bullshit quiz...but DOES ANYONE WANT TO BELIEVE IT?????!!!!     Goddess of the Night. Beautiful yet a strange darkness and sadness lurk about you.    urlLink   What element would you rein over? (For Girls)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Who can tell how bored I am?  I ate too many garlic fries tonight...uhg...fries after very large burrito and chips...I need to find some ipicac.  Oy Vey.  Well...on to the other quizzes!!    You are Brian Molko!   urlLink   Who are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Who the fuck is this?   ...about 10 minutes later...Oh! The dude from Placebo, I knew I remembered him from somewhere...that hot mother fucker!!  I haven't seen a rockstar in eyeliner look this good for ages!!    You are a dominatrix!    urlLink   Which Ultimate Beautiful Woman are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Yah, I retook this test....again.  Hehe    Your Heart is Red    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Last one nightnight!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, very good night.  What a little social activity can do for your well-being.  Selling doughnuts for Key Club...I'm not in dat Club.  I volunteered to be in key club...isn't that funny?  Ah, spoke to some people at the Future Farmers of America fair.  Yeah buddy.  Heh heh, oh I wish I could socialize at school, I would have friends.  Friends!!  ...here.  It is so lonely being me.  ...here.  There are people I want to get to know, but I only have 2 weeks left.  E-mails!!  Sad now.  I was so happy.  I spent like 5 fucking hours at this place...okay 4, but still.  My headaches are getting progressively worse.  Ow.  I feel like my head is being squeezed, like a grape.  Ow.  Lol, for those hours I was with a teacher.  A teacher who is 25 and pretty fucking cool.  I love it when teachers are nice and easy to talk to.  Nice.  I saw the funny boy that I like at the fair.  THE ATTRACTION RAGES!!  He's a freshman too.  Mm...FRESH-man.  I like the sound of this... What? We aren't talking about sex yet?  Okay fine...alright alright, later.  Should I put his name on here...okay his first name.  Shane.  He is very funny.  Something about him, and I don't just mean the ADD.  I must be attracted to people with that intense energy  they  claim to be a problem.  They are out to get me.  They want me unhappy...Grr...What am I talking about?  I don't even know.    There's a real dumb fuck at school...Carey.  He tries to be that kind of smart/sarcastic/mean-ish funny, but he just seems like an idiot to me.  An arrogant idiot.  I just needed to write that.  And the rage submits to temporary relief.  Ahh...   I should not let myself getso pissed off.  NOT HEALTHY!!  No sir-ee.  Gotta think happy.  When one's thoughts are pleasant, one is pleasant.  It's all a mental thing.  Now what exactly do I mean by that?  Heh I'll keep ya guessing, wouldn't want any ClaritY would we?  AND NOW FOR SOME SEX!!!  The more I think about it, the more I want to have "a lesbian experience"...I find myself wanting to dominate preppy girls.  I think it's a sadistic urge more than anything else.  But when I see those superficial, hair-all-done, got-it-at-Macys bratty girls I just wanna... UH!  Motherfuckin fuck.  No wonder guys get so pissed at girls.  All they wanna do is boink em good and leave.  Like I'm wanting to do, anyone 18?  I think I'll need to get a strap on... let it be know that I am just kidding about that... I do have a tongue, and two hands ; )  Today, a day that shall forever be remembered as Bulimia Day...B-Day.  Heh, why?  Well, that's a little to personal to write in here isn't it?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink       You Are Always Horny  You are naughty, and your mind is almost always in the gutter. When you get horny, you want it fast! You're not into wasting your time playing hard to get.  Whether you've got a willing partner or not, you are going to give yourself a blast of a time. You aren't like most girls. You like porno, you are forward, and you are willing to experiment with both guys and girls. You are a rare breed. It isn't just your sex drive - it's your open mind as well. It's hard to being a horny girl in this world, but you handle yourself well!    urlLink   How Horny Are You?     Now isn't this interesing?  An improvement.  Lol, what can a nap do for you?  I feel better...=) 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And actually listening to this album, I become aware of the magnificent mind that is Jonathan Davis.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I feel like my life is shit.  I feel like it has not been good.  I know it has, but I do not feel like it has.  With every day at school I want to cut my wrists that much more.  I do not want to die.  I do, however, want to incapacitate myself.  I want to bathe in a pool of my own blood.  I have this image of myself laughing hysteriacally at my own despair and disgust with blood spilling out of open razor wounds.  Not exactly healthy.  And we wonder why so many people are fat.  Food is my comfort now, a one joy in life that sustains me when hope wears thin.  Music barely helps me anymore.  I'm listening to Korn right now, the first album, I know I would like it if I didn't hate everything so much now.  Track 3...I can relate to this shit.  I think I'll find the lyrics an post em... pretend like the lyrics in italics are about desperation and suicide and you have how I feel.  "Need To"   I, I am confused, fighting myself  Wanting to give in, needing your help  Skin cold with fear, feel it when we touch  Outside I don't know you, but inside I'm fine    Can you see it in me?  Skin cold from touch  Each day confronted with what I have done  You pull me closer, I push you away  You tell me it's okay, I can't help but feel the pain   I hate you!  Why are you taken?  I love you!  I feel so helpless  Why is it you?  ripping my insides each time I'm with you  why do I try?  why do I really need to?  Why!!  Fuck you, bitch!  need to. . . fuck. . .  slut
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       YOU CAN SUCK MY DICK AND FUCKING LIKE IT!!!  I will choke until I swallow... Choke this infant here before me. What is this but my reflection? Who am I to judge and strike you down? But you're pushing and shoving me. You still love me and you pushit on me. Rest your trigger on my finger, bang my head upon the fault line. Take care not to make me enter. 'cause if I do we both may disappear. But you're pushing me, shoving me. Pushit on me. Slipping back into the gap again. I'm alive when you're touching me, alive when you're shoving me down. But i'd trade it all for just a little bit of piece of mind. Put me somewhere I don't wanna be. Seeing someplace I don't wanna see. Never wanna see that place again. Saw that gap again today as you were begging me to stay. Managed to push myself away, and you, as well. If, when I say I may fade like a sigh if I stay, you minimize my movement anyway, I must persuade you another way. There's no love in fear. Staring down the hole again. Hands upon my back again. Survival is my only friend. Terrified of what may come. Just remember I will always love you, even as I tear your fucking throat away. But it will end no other way.   Some say the end is near. Some say we'll see armageddon soon. I certainly hope we will. I sure could use a vacation from this bullshit three ring circus sideshow of Freaks here in this hopeless fucking hole we call LA The only way to fix it is to flush it all away. Any fucking time. Any fucking day. Learn to swim, I'll see you down in Arizona bay. Fret for your figure and Fret for your latte and Fret for your hairpiece and Fret for your lawsuit and Fret for your prozac and Fret for your pilot and Fret for your contract and Fret for your car. It's a bullshit three ring circus sideshow of freaks here in this hopeless fucking hole we call LA The only way to fix it is to flush it all away. Any fucking time. Any fucking day. Learn to swim, I'll see you down in Arizona bay. Some say a comet will fall from the sky. Followed by meteor showers and tidal waves. Followed by faultlines that cannot sit still. Followed by millions of dumbfounded dipshits. Some say the end is near. Some say we'll see armageddon soon. I certainly hope we will cuz I sure could use a vacation from this Silly shit, stupid shit... One great big festering neon distraction, I've a suggestion to keep you all occupied. Learn to swim. Mom's gonna fix it all soon. Mom's comin' round to put it back the way it ought to be. Learn to swim. Fuck L Ron Hubbard and Fuck all his clones. Fuck all those gun-toting Hip gangster wannabes. Learn to swim. Fuck retro anything. Fuck your tattoos. Fuck all you junkies and Fuck your short memory. Learn to swim. Fuck smiley glad-hands With hidden agendas. Fuck these dysfunctional, Insecure actresses. Learn to swim. Cuz I'm praying for rain and I'm praying for tidal waves I wanna see the ground give way. I wanna watch it all go down. Mom please flush it all away. I wanna watch it go right in and down. I wanna watch it go right in. Watch you flush it all away. Time to bring it down again. Don't just call me pessimist. Try and read between the lines. I can't imagine why you wouldn't Welcome any change, my friend. I wanna see it all come down. suck it down. flush it down.   Black then white are all i see in my infancy. red and yellow then came to be, reaching out to me. lets me see. as below, so above and beyond, I imagine drawn beyond the lines of reason. Push the envelope. Watch it bend. Over thinking, over analyzing separates the body from the mind. Withering my intuition, missing opportunities and I must Feed my will to feel my moment drawing way outside the lines. Black then white are all i see in my infancy. red and yellow then came to be, reaching out to me. lets me see there is so much more and beckons me to look thru to these infinite possibilities. as below, so above and beyond, I imagine drawn outside the lines of reason. Push the envelope. Watch it bend. over thinking, over analyzing separates the body from the mind. Withering my intuition leaving opportunities behind. Feed my will to feel this moment urging me to cross the line. Reaching out to embrace the random. Reaching out to embrace whatever may come. I embrace my desire to I embrace my desire to feel the rhythm, to feel connected enough to step aside and weep like a widow to feel inspired to fathom the power, to witness the beauty, to bathe in the fountain, to swing on the spiral to swing on the spiral to swing on the spiral of our divinity and still be a human. With my feet upon the ground I move myeslf between the sounds and open wide to suck it in. I feel it move across my skin. I'm reaching up and reaching out. I'm reaching for the random or what ever will bewilder me. what ever will bewilder me. And following our will and wind we may just go where no one's been. We'll ride the spiral to the end and may just go where no one's been. Spiral out. Keep going.Spiral out. Keep going.Spiral out. Keep going.Spiral out. Keep going.Spiral out. Keep going.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       God dammit, I didn't post all that crap before I logged off.  Piss on rice.  Aw well, it was mostly me whining about how onions were burning my eyes.  Heh, anyway...history went well.  I think I got an A+ GO ME!  I really hope I have gotten an A, my grades are such shit right now.  This coming weekend will be nothing but homework.  Make up work that is.  Fuckin depression induced sicknesses!  Why does my mind allow this?  When I get upset now I get fuckin headaches...bad ones.  While I was living in Reno I got headaches like 3 times a year.  I feel like I have a continuous migrane... maybe it isn't that bad, but it still hurts.    I didn't get to see the finale of Buffy.  I are sad.  ~^~    With the birds I share this lonely view...Good ol' Peppers.  That Anthony Kiedis is a skinny jar of olives I'd like to sample.  Ooh.  At least he was, until he cut his muhfuhkin hair!  TO ALL MALES WHO HAPPEN TO BE READING THIS:  grow out your god damn hair.  Any girl who don't like that shit ain't worth a fuck, literally.  ::Smile:: I, as well as my friends, like long hair.  ::Smile:: Do the math.    I wanted to kill myself again.  Talkin with da counselor.  Not helpful.  Not really.  He's more depressed than I am.  I may be able to finish my highschool career through independent study.  YAY!  I would rather do that and be successful than stay stuck in this fucked school system.  I lose mind fast.  I need more teachers like the history Messiah I happened upon.  I  want  to do the assignments from him.  CrAzY@!(*^*&%$~~ Heh.  I want to get back to Reno more than I can bear.  [Is that the right bear...or is it bare...I think I am right]  I miss Kung Fu!!  I miss my friends!  I miss my life.  I have no life here.  No one understands my jokes.  You know, those subtle semi-sarcastic comments I make sometimes... I just get blank stares.  Tis sad it tis.  No friends for me.  Boo..hoo... I only have 2 or 3 more weeks til I'm out!  ~Dream of Californication~   Good song.  Speaking of Californicating... I remember back in middle school when I first heard that song my mom told me what fornication is...she was worried that a boy at a party would ask me, "Hey babe, wanna Californicate" - First of all - me? At a party back then?! Ha! haha ha! Second - me? At a party back then?! HA! haha ha!  ...Yeah I know what you were expecting the second to be...how could a lame ass line like that work on a chick, but I certainly fooled you, yeah I did, heh...  Dadadadada It's the motherfucking Do double P...hold up, Snoop Dopp?  Hehehe...Oh! the parody!  My oh my... [muhahaha]   I want to go to LA again, I wish I'd been a little older when I went before 7th grade, woulda enjoyed it more I'm sure.  Boy the clothes in 99' were sooo much better than they are now.  All dark n' shite.  Damn.  I miss the good old days when clothing I liked was easily accessable.  I think I'll become a goth...see if that becomes a trend next ...yeah fucking right.  Then maybe my individuality will be somewhat unique again.  Goth chicks are so hot... I've always wanted to be one, just never had the nerve or the budget.  Well, all I need now is the budget.  Lol I choose this before summer... black, velvet, and a lotta cloth, smart..really.  I want ice cream, I think I'll pester my mom into taking me to get some....
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         you're a dark girl you seem to be a little upset about something, or maybe thats just the way you are, dont let your own lack of confidence befall hatred towards others, if thats not the problem then I dont know what it is, maybe you just dont like people? whatever it is, hun, you may want to get over it before its too late I don't like being called hun, sweetie.  What a right on, yet shit quiz!   urlLink   What kind of girl are you?    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning Again!  I have been studying for history, why? Because it is the only class I care about anymore.  In my first entry I refer to the teacher as my Savior, to quote Choi in The Matrix: my own personal Jesus Christ...only in that he was happy that Neo had some computer thing.  Heh heh...shows how much I know.  Sing with me kids!  I don't want to go to school, I'm an apathetic teenage bastard!  I don't need to learn a thing cuz our shitty country has WELLFARE!!!  Therefore, I suppose, the country can't be that shitty.  Tralalala...I hope I pass this with a high grade.  I don't want to fail!  Not this class.  Dammit, I must prove that I try!!  I do, this class is inspiring!  Mm...teacher nice.  I mean...   I should put another marquee on here.  The other one is the entire song of H. by Tool.  OMFG I think I'm becoming trendy...the crap at Hot Topic is starting to look good again.  Mm, Slipknot tank top... white sparkly belt with stars.... and boots, Oh! the boots... buckles and black wrapped around my calf and foot.  Ah, the wonders of capitalism and what it does for fashion.  Let us bask in it, shall we.....    You are Pyrokinetic!    urlLink   What's Your Magic Power?  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      BUAHAHAHAHA!!! I am currently trying to convince my friend's boyfriend to have sex with her, at this friend's request.  It's fun.  SEXSEXSEX  This particular friend is about as horny as I am.  CRAZY!!!  She's more than I am... It's great, I was starting to think I was 'oversexed' like this blog haha.  I want to be out of school, the longer I am there the more I think about slicing veins.  Thoughts of my body spurting blood... this isn't healthy folkles.  How many ways I can die in one class period.  Too much stress of not passing.  I have decided not to care anymore.  There are always options, as he of the Contaminated Mind has told me.  Some of my faithful readers know of whom I speak... Haha...he of the contaminated mind...I should tell him that  When I get all my work done I get to have another piercing! Yay!  Mind you, I only have 5...4 in ears and my belly button.  Hehee, I'm trying to convince my mom to let me get my tongue pierced... she thinks the idea of that is vile.  Fuckin A.  I'm getting annoyed, this guy if afraid of fucking her!  He doesn't want it to fuck up their relationship, this chick wants to screw.  Nothing's going to get fucked up if he fucks her, it is what she fucking wants!! Dammit....   School is HELL.  It's even fucking with my sex drive dammit.  I cannot wait to get back to Reno... hehe, dumb girlfriend apparently called me a slut to some of my friends.  She wants to kick my ass.  I revel in this shit man.  2 years of Kung fuckin Fu... we'll see whose ass gets kicked.  One of my best buds maintained her composure and didn't burst out laughing at the claim of my ass getting kicked.  Another of my best buds didn't defend me, like I feel he should have, but it's all good.  I shall defend myself...all in good time....I shouldn't expect my friends to defend me when I'm called a slut, they probably think so too.  I'm a blowjob slut.  I need to quit that... if I don't have flavored condoms on hand anyway... and when I'm drunk, it's so much less fun when you already want to vomit from your blood alcohol level being fuckin exponential of the legal limit.  *Sigh* At least I don't deny what I am.  I am who I am.  I admit it.  At least I have the confidence in myself to know who I am and what I like, and I like sex.  I like oral...never been penetrated but I'm sure I'd like that too.  If coming out and saying that I enjoy an orgasm, or that I like someone's cock makes me a whore and a slut then fine.  They are just words.  Here are a few words just for the misinformed, specially from me: Fuck the hell off righeous bitch.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I are teh goth misery biatch.  DEPRESSED before school, has it ever been any other way?  Oh yeah...back in the day...when I was happy and had a grade other than F in school.  I have concluded something: Life is not shit, and then you die, a more accurate version is: Life is happy and then you move.  Let me grace you with onomatopoeia: hiss.  I hate living here.  School+Me going=My loss of good humor.  RRR!  I would rather lick a pubic toilet seat than go to school today.  What's the worst thing I would do if I didn't have to go to school anymore?...an exerpt from SLC Punk- "If she told me to lick a cop's asshole, I'd probably do it."  I don't think I'd go that far...unless...no no, definitely not that.  I'm not going near a cop!  Lol, anyone get the comedy in that? Anyone? ...okay...  Fuck fuck school... I'd rather go to a pool...where I can be cool...fool.  Am I down with the rhymin' shizza?!  Werd!  Ha, to think, some people may talk like that.  Apparently kids in a local Cat-licker school talk like that...Yo, Motha Mary, forgive me gurl!  You gots to know I still luv U.  She-it...I hate all this trendy nonsense.  Everyone has decided that wearing dark clothing is cool.  Fuck it.  Who endured the ridicule before it was 'cool to do'?  Haha... arm fucking warmers..."Why are you wearing socks on your arms?"  Der, I don't know, I must have thought my hands were my feet!  Boy, next to your magnificent observation how can I possibly comprehend comparison to your fantastic INTELLECT?!  FUCKIN A!!!  I resent so many people, and I would like to have a chance to beat the fuck out of each of them.  Violence is good, as long as I am not the recpient of it...muahaha, I shall inflict god dammit.  Well off to purgatory...
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I are disappointed.  Boy with dumb girlfriend seems to have fallen for her.  And, it seems, that I was correct in thinking I was too smart to date.  Sad at loss of sex, but there is plenty more where that came from.  It's probably better if I don't do anything with someone just to spite their girlfriend...it's wrong, doncha know.  Also he says he would lose himself if he lost her...which makes me think that she was standing next to him as he was typing...but if someone has found that kind of love [that inevitably leads to pain, at this age] then good for him.    This brings up a question I ask the world: Why look for "The One" at this age?  With Boy I can understand, he's had 'fun' but with most of my other friends it seems they are bent on finding a soul mate.  I analyze this as an attempt to quench the unrelenting thirst not to be lonely.  I have just chosen a different approach...though I have not yet acted upon it.  I am HONESTLY not interested in a relationship.  I have seen so much pain come from them, and so little good.  I ask anyone who reads this: What Is The Point?  How many couples are going to stay together, especially when started at this age?  We are fucking teenagers, what happened to having fun?  Is this all a manifestation of our angst?  I find it all confusing and undesirable.  I want to fuck.  Plain and simple.  Though maybe not that plain...I want to remain friends with the people I screw...so then I can screw em' again!  Sex and friendship are two amazing parts of life added together, how can one go wrong?    Me and these crazy tangents I go off on....ah me...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink       	 You Should Star in Cumshot Porn!  He said it was good for your skin.  Well, he lied.    urlLink   What Porn Should *You* Star In?     They say that if you have a job you love you never work a day in your life...heh heh heh     urlLink      My Favorite Color!  Your Sexual Energy is Red!  You are on fire, and it is no wonder, because you have a naturally hot libido. Your sexuality erupts spontaneously. And when you are hot, you seek release as quickly as possible. In bed, you know how to turn your lover on. How could you not?  You are a wild woman when you get it on. You will fondle and lick and stroke and suck to get you want you want. Only some people can handle your eagerness in bed, but those who can will never stray. You have the sexual appetite of a man with the stamina of a woman. It often feels like you could have a zillion orgasms. Your way of picking up lovers-to-be is no less outrageous. You will often go out on a limb in public to lure someone into bed. And you succeed easily, as many people are turned on by your aggressive flirting. Your sexual goal for self-improvement should be to learn how to love the little things in romance. You can learn to embrace the sensual, lighter pleasures in life... As much as you already appreciate the raw, physical aspects of sex. Madonna and Christina Aguilera both have red sexual energies full of passion and brilliance. Be sure to check out people who have outcomes of yellow, green, and pink, as they are pristine matches for you.    urlLink   What Color is Your Sexual Energy?      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oy Vey!  I am worn fucking out.  What I would give to just be done with highschool, or to re-do it.  If I could go back and do all my work when it was assigned...All this fucking work is taking it's toll on me.  I keep having the 'bad' thoughts.  And for once I am not referring to sex.  I mean the harmful 'bad' thoughts.  The ones that result in my bleeding from the wrist.  Is it so wrong to want to see my own blood? ...and to act upon that desire?  Is it?  I'm careful dammit.  It would be really cool to see a lot of my blood.  I know what you people reading this are thinking, yeah, I am wearing a thong today!  Heh, but really, I'm a strange masochistic fucker and I want to see blood.  My own.    I heard from one of my good friends today that boys from my old school were reading this blog when she was and was intigued with my speak of orgasms...well boys, aren't you just kicking yourselves now?  That semi-goth chick was a little more interesting than she appeared, huh?  Oh and just for kicks to improve your circle jerks: I masturbate.  Horrors!  A girl?!  With...her fingers...and...whoa, man... Yes.  I'm sure you'll be wacking off to that fantasy tonight.  P.S.  Sorry to ruin the fantasy but most of the preppy bitches that are 'so hot' don't bang their game on a regular basis the way some of the more intelligent female individuals [such as myself and friends] do.  Sorry to disappoint   -_-  In case any of you idiots didn't get that I was insulting any male who is not friends with me.  Nothing personal, really, I've just had a long day around many stupid people who I have to endure for another 3 weeks.  I hate teenagers. We're all so fucking stupid, and most of the time we don't even realize it.  It irritates me.  There was a girl who was sitting with me and my 'friends' [I use quotes because I was not spoken to the entire lunch period] and she said to a boy that she would "fucking hit him" if he did something...  I am not a violent person but I wanted to beat the shit out of her.  Hostility comes with unhappiness.  And I am very unhappy.  I just hope I can continue to surpress such urges until I get back to Reno.  I also hope I do not damage myself further during this misery we call life.  My mom is pissed at me because I'm not doing homework right now.  She left to get Schindler's List so I can get more info for the project and when she came back I was writing in this.  "I'm just tired of people saying one thing and doing another."  This isn't just me but whenever I lose her suppport I want to cut the fuck out of myself.  I have no one here, except her.  Without her I am completely alone, I need her not to be upset with me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink       Your Hottest Body Part is Your Butt!  From the back you're mistaken for J-Lo. You are a rump-shaking dynamo on the dance floor. Thongs were invented just for you. You're able to please your man sexually in all sorts of ways - especially through your back door. You put the ass in ASSett. Baby, you got back, and you're proud of it. Celebs who work their ass as hard as you do include: Britney Spears, Kylie Minogue, Christina Aguilera, and of course, J-Lo. Want to play up your ass even more? Try low rise jeans and vinyl pants, schoolgirl skirts, and form fitting shorts. And of course, g-strings and thongs only - no squishing that fine ass with panty lines.     urlLink   What's Your Hottest Body Part??        urlLink        You Get Off on Hansel and Gretel!  You're both lost in the woods: two unchaperoned virgins neglected by their parents and free to play doctor... But that jealous witch tries to upset your plans! Or maybe it's a morality tale about being a bit too greedy for a nibble on someone's sugar shack, and getting your goose cooked as a result? Then again, you could be confusing your lust for food with plain old lust.    urlLink   What Fairy Tale Gets *You* Off?        urlLink       Your pussy isn’t sweet or sour; IT’S SALTY!  You're not a sweet waif or a total bad ass, just a chick with a primal taste for life. (And you know how that taste has a trickle down effect.) Part of it is genetics; you were just born this way. Part of it is the way you were raised; your momma didn’t raise no fool. But most of your taste comes from living life and learning the lessons along the way. (And despite what your worst enemy claims, your taste does not come from too many trips to the free clinic.) You might think your distinct, signature taste would scare most men off. Truth is, they love it. Every second of it. They eat it up. Which brings us back to the whole pussy thing. It's a tight little circle.    urlLink   Is *Your* Pussy Sweet or Sour?   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you mind if I disturb your revery?  A question I must ponder myself, though it was originally asked of me.  I had been eating strawberries in cream... gazing off thinking of other things... a bottle of beer inches from my grasp, and in my possession too, I didn't have to go to the underhanded part of myself this evening.  A man asked that question, meaning could he sit down.  I promised I would remember it because it's a very good question.  I should expand on it but I am tired and I've, heh, 'been drinking'.    Don't drink kids.  You think you're depressed now?  Just fucking wait.  A nice breakdown with mom.  I do feel better, and more relaxed after all of it though.  The relaxation is a blessing.  I have felt so tense lately I find myself clenching my jaw shut, and then when I realize what I'm doing I get a headache.  I am getting headaches a lot more than I have lately.  At least they aren't as painful as the mind grinding misery I was put through as a child.  I fear getting a headache like that again.  To think, I used to endure them at least once a month as a child.  And why?  No one told me or my terrified mother.  My poor mom, she loves me so much.  I hope I never fuck up so badly that I die or something, merely for her sake.  She would be so devastated.  I am what she loves most in life, for the past 16 years she's had something to live for, and it's me, and I know it...it is a wonderful feeling.  I have given 8 orgasms to various males.  I have been given [this is *real* orgasm folks] one.  One.  How is this remotely fair?  The more I think about it the more pissed off I am.  I never cum from fingering, who the fuck can?  Most of the guys have NO IDEA what they are doing.  At least the ones who I have *tried*.  I am feeling sarcastic right now...CAN ANYONE TELL???  I just want to get off on a regular basis, and NO I can't just do it myself because it isn't the same.  Heh, maybe I can use that..."No, suck your own dick! Asshole..."  I think I have some issues I need to work through...Oh look I am seeing my psychologist tomorrow!  Lucky Day!  Whoop-de-fuckin-doo... Seeing her rarely does me muc good.  I go before school... I weep in her office... I complain about my life... then where do I go?  School.  In the mortal words of Tasha's away message: School.  Hell.  Synonomous.   
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't write at all yesterday...jeepers! is the blog getting old?!  How could that possibly be?!  Blat.  Ack.  Blah...and other such words.  I stayed up til midnight last night looking for Harry Potter fan fiction.  Specifically one where Draco rapes Hermione, it was suggested by a friend.  Oh I am a sick SOB.  WTF, I'm on the rag.  Lol I have to wonder what my friends think of me after reading each new entry.  Heh...Be afraid....Be  very  afraid.  I have decided that The Matrix 2 is good, the first is better, and the fight scenes rock.  So yeah...I should be continuing with my homeworking.  Hell, I want a break.  So many inner struggles...how do I manage?  HEHE I like this song...I don't know what it's called or who the artist is, but it's track 16 on the Snatch soundtrack.  Good movie that.  And good name.    I throw derrogatory meaning to the wind...Snatch, twat, rag...it's better than VAGINA or MENSTRUATING for crying out loud.  Those words are better than being blatent and blunt ie: I'm at the time of the month where my uterus is secreting blood in large amounts and causing me abdominal pain.  Better isn't it?!  People need to stop being so fucking sensitive about such things.  I get to see a performance of Fiddler On the Roof today.  My mumsie playeth an instrument in it.  He-heuck-heuck!  Back to the homework!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck me.  The Matrix: Reloaded was disappointing.  Either that or I am getting sick...or getting my rag.  I feel shitty right now.  I ache from head to toe.  The plans I have seem less and less fulfilling.  I doubt myself and my hope.  This is the feeling that begets that horrible downward spiral of depression.  No wonder NIN has an album with that title.  My depression feels like the peak of a mountain, then it slowly crumbles from the inside and little by little I am lowered.  /| |\    By myself, going to the movie theater, I thought it wouldn't bother me.  It never has.  It's the influence of my mother and my friends.  "I hate going to the movies alone...blahblah"  Thanks for ruining my time.  I saw people from school, people who I'd like to get to know.  But that shy side of me has returned.  I hate myself for it.  I have no friends here.  No one gets my jokes.  No one seems to comprehend what I say.  Blank stares and confusion from the girls I am around.  I am not who I am here.  I am weird, in a literal way, not that joking psudo-weird way that is socially acceptable.  I am just wierd.  The girl who wears a lot of black.  I feel I am unacceptable.  I feel like I am socially retarded.  I cannot connect with the people here.  I do not know if it is me, or if it is them.  All I know is that I feel the way I did in middle school - like the shreds of happiness I had left are slowly disappearing.  I feel I am alone, so unbelievably alone.  This pain is so intense I do not even want sex right now...so you know it is bad lol.    One may not have hope if one doubts that hope.  I doubt.  So, pretty much I'm fucked.  I don't know what I want.  I don't fucking know what I want.  There are things I think I want.  Like death.  Soooo appealing.  Like sex.  For the only reason of wanting to try it at this point.  God, I feel shitty.  I'll continue my sorrow talk tomorrow.  Sleep seems attainable, going to try it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I wish I was not so fucking dumb about some things.  Like people.  There are peole here who intrigue me beyond belief, yet I did not make an effort to talk to them because I resented that I was here.  Now I feel I have alienated them into not liking me.  Woe is me.  Very funny kid in Biology, got to be in a group with him to make a timeline.  He said he has severe ADD.  Lately I find that to be a highly desirable quality, in males at least.  This boy is the kind of person who can come up with the strangest things...the funniest things as well.  I am sad I have not gotten to know him better and that I am moving away, and shall possibly never see him [or hear him] ever again.  Sad.  I actually had a good day today.  Wowie.  Food was brought in Yearbook...carb it up, yo.  2 brownies, 2 cookies, potato chips, and soda.  Things I have not eaten in god knows how long.  I felt pretty shitty afterward.  I do not know how the rest of the population does it.  Honestly, after eating well for so long it makes ya feel like crap. CRAP!  Oy vey.  Yearbook is a lot of fun.  The book is done so there is little to do but hang out and watch movies.  We had brainstormed for next year's book... we were making jokes about having page 420 and there being a little surprise in the pages.  The teacher joked that yearbook could become a term- Hey man, you wanna get some yearbook?  Then we'd be dealing yearbooks- I got some yearook, huh? Huh?  Yearbook, good stuff.  The hilarity of it all!  We also ['we' is pretty much the teacher] came up with the idea of the antiyearbook.  Worst pictures, meanest teacher ect.  Also the Fuck Windsor yearbook "We can incorporate the F Windsor theme into every page!"  Windsor is my school's arch rival. Dammit, the school becomes a place I want to be at the end of the year and when I am going to leave!  This must be some kind of psychological issue.   Or there are forces at work to ruin me!!  I choose the latter of the two.  I don't know which one that is though...hehe I don't know what latter is =)    I have me a vegetarian burrito.  It tastes gude.  It needs a bit mo flava doe... more spices to be somewhat more precise.  It is a bland burrito, good, but bland.  Whenever I use the word "but" I cannot help feeling that everything before that word is wiped away.  With that logic my burrito is, therefore, bland.  And now, a barage of worthless information:     urlLink       You Are  urlLink 1/2 Virgin, 1/2 Whore !  50-50, baby! Ah, you are fairly normal. You have sex, though to you it's not more exciting than a new designer outfit. Secretly, you are a adventurous soul just waiting for someone to take control. Open up a little, and you'll show your guy the best sex ever. There's nothing to be afraid of - except fainting from multiple orgasms! You are great at kissing, getting yourself off, and using your hands.    urlLink   What Do Girls Whisper Behind Your Back? Virgin or Whore Quiz Tells All!        Electra!    urlLink   Which Sexy Comic Book Villainess Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You're not into anything. You're not special.    urlLink   What Bizarre Sex Act Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You're Sun!    urlLink   Which Snapple Elements are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     God DAMN!!!   The Dante's Inferno Test has banished you to  the Eigth Level of Hell - the Malebolge!   Here is how you matched up against all the levels:     Level    Score       urlLink Purgatory   (Repenting Believers)   Very Low       urlLink Level 1 - Limbo   (Virtuous Non-Believers)   Very Low       urlLink Level 2   (Lustful)   Very High       urlLink Level 3   (Gluttonous)   High       urlLink Level 4   (Prodigal and Avaricious)   Very High       urlLink Level 5   (Wrathful and Gloomy)   Moderate       urlLink Level 6 - The City of Dis   (Heretics)   Extreme       urlLink Level 7   (Violent)   Very High       urlLink Level 8- the Malebolge   (Fraudulent, Malicious, Panderers)   Extreme       urlLink Level 9 - Cocytus   (Treacherous)   High      Take the  urlLink Dante's Inferno Hell Test   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       HAAHAAA!!  I am a low level html goddess!  Look at that background!  Look at the marquee and buttons down there!  I love knowledge...especially when I can put it to good use.  *Sigh* school was very boring today.  I thought I was going to explode.  Last class of the day: Biology.  Two FUCKING hours of absolutely nothing.  Anything I retain from that class will have been purely from reading the book-our main assignment.  GEEZ  heh sometimes the things she says reminds me of my mom.  It is kind of scary.  I  really  hope my mother does not become similar to this woman.  I would cry.  She won't though, she's on a new wild path of insanity...Biobitch is stuck in her teaching hell.  More Schindler's List in History.  I like that movie, not for the topic, but for the way is was filmed and how wonderfully each actor fits his or her role.  And the music, cannot forget that, love the violin.  Itzhak Pearlman you rock my socks!  As for the scenes we saw today...good mother fucking god.  I was feeling ill just watching it, I CANNOT IMAGINE WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO LIVE THROUGH THAT  it makes me very angry.  I want to torture the people who thoughtlessly killed the Jews for no reason.  I would like 24 hours with Hitler bound and gagged in a chair, a lighter, pliers, and a hammer.  Give me 24 hours...  I really like being a vegetarian.  All this fake meat...it is simply marvelous.  I bet all you carnivores are thinking "God damn, how the fuck can she eat that shit?"  I'll tell you: with a fork.  It is better than a chunk of cow with all the fat and vile grease.  I prefer not to eat the charred tissues of other animals who walk among us (in pastures) I choose only to comsume that which is of the sea...and even then I have my limits.  I worry about my future relationships, yes there are a lot of hot vegans/vegetarians but they're usually already taken by the poseur vegan/vegetarian/environmentalist type gals.  And find me a vegetarian male in highschool (who isn't a drunk-I know one who is) and I'll thank you profusely.  Also, that bummer sticker that says "Vegetarians taste better" is quite true.  Guys, if you want a girl to swallow, eat your veggies, and if other chicks won't suck you off god knows I might.  Bad tasting cum kind of ruins the mood, man...men.  Who's seen Monsoon Wedding?!  God damn is that a good movie, it is not a chick flick but it's nice.  About a weddin' in case you could not tell.  OMFG the early showing of The Matrix: Reloaded is at 10:00 tonight!!!! AAAAHHHH!!!! I wish I could go, but I can't.  Suckage.  I have to go walk the dog with my mum...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh the joys of being at school and working on this blog.  Lunch it may be, but I would rather be in here-the library- than out conversing with the students.  I am having a fairly good day, amazingly.  However, I still resent the people here.  Now I'm paranoid about other students looking over my shoulder.  Ack, that damn bell.  Well, until I get home...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         ~>   She IMed me from his screen name, here we go...    HER:  look you bitch stop talking to my fucking boyfriend i was nice to you the first time i talk to you now i am going to be nice   HER:  i fucked him last night and it was the best sex i have ever had  HER:  what now bitch  ME:  okay  ME:  good for you  HER:  are you getting this through your dumb ass hore head  ME:  you spelled whore wrong  HER:  do not tell me ok ypu better lose his fucking e mail number  ME:  sorry  ME:  i'm not giving up a friend for you  HER:  who gives a shit you got the fucking point  ME:  actually you were a bit vague  ME:  care to reiterate?  HER:  he is not a fucking friend when you talk to him like i love your cock  ME:  but i do  ME:  in case you haven't noticed, he has a very nice penis  HER:  i read the e mail you sent him what school do you go to  ME:  i live in Cali  HER:  have you had sex with him ?  ME:  no  HER:  then how the hll do you Know   ME:  I have, however, seen his penis...  HER:  hell  HER:  when and where?  HER:  what part of cali   ME:  why don't you ask him  ME:  I do not even need to answer you  HER:  he is telling me  HER:  you are a dumb ass whore i can not belive you would ever belittle yourself like that  ME:  what?  HER:  to get drunk and show off your tits  HER:  that is such a whore thing to do  ME:  Lol   ME:  you use that word a lot better when you know how to spell it  ME:  so what if it's a whore thing to do  ME:  it was fun  ME:  the only thing I regret about that night is that it was on film  ME:  aren't you a senior?  HER:  ya i saw it and you are a ulgy fat bitch  ME:  this from the jealous girlfriend...  HER:  yes i am a senior  HER:  yes i am   ME:  you have a lot of credibility... then why can't you form a good sentence?  HER:  what do you and ****** talk about   ME:  flowers and beer  ME:  and pretty little butterflies  HER:  ****** is freaking out becaues i am talking to you  ME:  we talk about sex occasionally  ME:  he is very loyal to you, you know  ME:  he knows i have a crush on him  ME:  so what if i talk about his cock   And that, my friends, is why we do not write a suggestive e-mail to boy who you plan to screw who currently has a girlfriend...little does she know...call me a vicious sadist but I'm going to enjoy every evil minute I'm with him if for no other reason than to spite her ;)  5/25>>>Here's something wonderboy IMed me before all this, unfortunately he caught my away message: Him:  hey aanh Auto response from ME: I'm off killing a kitten or two... I won't be back for a long time =)   Him:  annah  Him:  hey i just fucked my gf  Him:  good call        Him:  i need t fuck your pussy too   Him:  hye im gonna go fuck my gf in the ass so im me back cause i ned to fuck you in your ass too cause my gf says its the shit    And the infamous e-mail I sent him that got me the feeble repremand from the gf: Well, I'm glad I made you horny...not necessarily a hard thing [no pun intended] but always a good thing.  As for cock craving, whenever I think about it i can't stop thinking "I worship your cock!"  sure I've gotten it from a quiz, but it is inspiring, don't you think?  I am looking forward to this summer...hopefully the weather won't be too hot, because god knows if it is I'll be passing out a lot *wink wink*  Anyway, you've just signed on so i'll stop writing this and talk...  This e-mail was a response to one he sent me thanking me for making him horny.  He also said he was glad to have someone "crave his cock so badly" (readers...you know me by now, he's right)  So I sent him this e-mail.  Thank Satan, for his sake, I didn't write about any of our 'plans'.  He gets to keep his girlfriend because I saved his ass.  And I haven't talked to him since he told me he wouldn't know what to do if he lost her... he would "lose himself" if he lost her.  Great, another friend lost to the angst of teenage relationship.  A word to the wise regarding finding "the one" before you're 25: IT IS BULLSHIT!!!  Have some fucking fun while you can....
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       What's coming through is alive. What's holding up is a mirror. But what's singing songs is a snake looking to turn this piss to wine. They're both totally void of hate, but killing me just the same. The snake behind me hisses what my damage could have been. My blood before me begs meopen up my heart again. And I feel this coming over like a storm again. considerately. Venomous voice, tempts me, drains me, bleeds me, leaves me cracked and empty. Drags me down like some sweet gravity. The snake behind me hisses what my damage could have been. My blood before me begs me open up my heart again. And I feel this coming over like a storm again. I am too connected to you to slip away, to fade away. Days away I still feel you touching me, changing me, and considerately killing me. Without the skin, beneath the storm, under these tears the walls came down. And the snake is drowned and as I look in his eyes, my fear begins to fade recalling all of those times. I could have cried then. I should have cried then. And as the walls come down and as I look in your eyes my fear begins to fade recalling all of the times I have died and will die. It's all right. I don't mind. I am too connected to you to slip away, to fade away. Days away I still feel you touching me, changing me, and considerately killing me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Such a long, boring day at school...my body walks in but my brain is checked at the door.  Watching Schindler's List in history.  It's even worse than the first half hour of Saving Private Ryan.  Luckily no one laughed when the Jews were shot in their heads.  That was relieving, when the first was I awaited the ignorant giggles...thankfully my expectations were proven wrong.  SL is a very disturbing movie.  It makes me feel ill and bad tempered.  For those who are not familiar with the film, it's about a man named Oscar Schindler who takes advantage of the war by using some of the be-ghettoed Jews as workers in a factory.  Jews who were not considered "essential" were taken off to be killed.  In one scene a Jew with one arm is brought to Schindler to thank him.  This man has one arm, is elderly, and is soooo greatful, because Schindler has saved his life.  His persistent "thank you"s summoned various chortles, I, however-being the serious person I am when it comes to such things, found it heart wrenching.  Later when the group of Jews are forced to shovel snow on the way to the factory the man with one arm is taken away and shot in the head.  Humanity disgusts me beyond words at times.  In biology, the class began with a vote...a vote for what we should call the turtle that was brought in by some students.  Now, this turtle was brought in because it would not survive in the world...it only has one eye and was bleeding from the tail with a chip in its shell.  I have to wonder what causes such idiocy, then I remember it is ignorance, which, by the way, is getting very annoying.  Thems kids were just tryin' to be nyce!  Nice does not = smart...sorry.    My mother just called me a nasty girl because I do not care that we missed the farmer's market, my response: yes, that is me...to a T...now let me be...followed by laughter hehe.  She is being particularly annoying.  Oh how lovely it would be for the computer to be located somewhere other than the kitchen!  Woe behold!  At least she is making dinner and is happy.  Quite a change from the  former  usual.  She quit one of her 3 jobs so the stress level has gone down a good deal.  It's nice because now I don't hurt myself when she's mad and takes it out on me.  She's not mad anymore.  I fear the next time she does get mad.  Hopefully I will make it through without damaging myself.    The Chocolate War  is a very good book.  I'm reading it for english and it almost makes me want to go to a private catholic school...lol not fucking likely!  I would not want to be a school like Trinity, things are rather fucked up in this book.  It's great.  My favorite character is Archie, the powerful asshole.  He reminds me of me, were I more sadistic and mischievous.  But I'm not, I am sweet as a summer cherry pie ;)  yet dirty as a used condom...well maybe not that dirty.  In fact definitely not, I never use condoms!!  Haha, how could one use condoms if one does not have sex?  Yes, yes I know what else they may be used for...what do you think I am? Stupid? Well, ....pfft, shut up!  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh what is learned!!!  ::maniacal laugh:: Muahahaha!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
            
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Scary in a very good way, you're Fairuza Balk. Intense.   urlLink   What sexy girl are you     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Gotta love this chick!  God damn, I'd like to ...are you reading this?...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha, I'm a Dark Tempting Goddess!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are a temptress    urlLink   Which Ultimate Beautiful Woman are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    A slight modification in the quiz and I am defined!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are a dark goddess!   urlLink   Which Ultimate Beautiful Woman are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Could they be anymore accurate? Muah baby! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are Rogue!  You are sexy and strong willed, and able to take on just about anyone.  You long for a serious relationship, but whenever you begin to get close to someone things always seem to take turns for the worse.  But you have dealt with this lack of closeness with an almost constant flirtacious behavior.   urlLink   Which X-Men character are you most like?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Sheesh, another fangirl.  Well, I dont blame you. How can any woman resist a sexy body, and the ruggedness that is Wolverine?  Hes a loner by nature, a heavy drinker, and is plagued by memories of his past...or lack thereof.  It may take time to work your way into his heart, but when you do, he'll do anything for his woman. Just be careful, he has a tendency to stab people in his sleep. ^_^;;   urlLink   Who Is Your Ideal X-Men 2 Mate? (ladies only)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Goth    urlLink   What Kind of Goth Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Speaks for itself, don't it?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      	 You are a SHAMELESS Flirt!  Some might consider this kind of flirt a borderline whore. You, on the other hand, see it differently. This kind of flirt is bold, fearless, and brave. Your brazenness pays off in other areas of your life. You get promotions and lucky breaks. And even if your efforts aren’t always successful, there’s another factor that’s in your favor: You, O Shameless One, know how to have fun! Kick your heels up, or kick them off entirely.    urlLink   What Kind of Flirt Are *You*?   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I put the bra in Libra, baby!!! Fuck yeah!   urlLink       Your Sex Sign is Libra!  You've got a ton of girls and guys trying to get with you! You're pratically booked up for the next four years. Not only are you great in bed - you're great at making people feel sexy. No wonder you're so popular! Libra, as you probably have noticed, you are always surrounded by scores of admiring suitors. You are a very accomplished flirt. Catching you is not for the faint hearted. Competition is always fierce. Your innate charm and incredible looks instantly attract - and keep - your lovers. Old flames and rejected suitors always keep coming back for more. There is a strong bisexual element in your personality. You're more likely to be aroused by the same sex than other signs. In threesomes, you are more likely to prefer that one partner is opposite sex and that the third is same sex. Your lovers adore you because you are a real ego stroker. You are eager to please and will do almost anything they ask. You are a born diplomat, which comes in handy with all of your suitors. You always win fights too, because your charm is irresistable!     urlLink What's *Your* Sex Sign?    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My god, I'm happy.  Just had dinner with my mom at a nice restaurant with unbelieveably amazing food.  Steamed artichoke with a basil dip and caramelized onions and shrimp cakes resting in a delicate mango sauce as an appetizer.  Spicy minestroni soup with lovely golden sourdough bread.  The main course was angel hair pasta with sauteed vegetables and garlic, absolutely FABULOUS!!  I also had a drink called Midnight Kiss...chocolate, hazelnut, cream, and ice blended together to concoct one of the most glorious treats I've ever had.  Liquid ecstacy it was.  I could just die [I use 'die' as Shakespeare did, find out, or ask me if you  really  want to know hehe]... I'm also wearing a magnificent dress with that electric blue and light brown lightning bolts on black, it's slinky and sexy and I love feeling this way again.  My body is so feminine now, I used to be all muscular and athletic looking.  Now I feel soft and approachable.    When I told my friend a little while ago that I feel sexy for the first time in a long time his response was enough to make me jump him, had he been here.  Here's our IM conversation:    Me:  Hello M, how are you?   Him:  hey ***** im good how are yuo doing   Me:  i feel great   Me:  i have the prettiest dress   Me:  and i feel sexy    Me:  and i haven't felt that way for a while   Him:  as always   Him:  you may not feel it but it dont mean you aren't  Why am I not in RENO?!  I wish I could be there to be around him more often before he leaves.  Most of our friendship has been through Aol.  :: sniffle ::  I better not rant about how much I like him in case he ever reads this. Why do I always end up wanting the person I can't have?  Why?!  It is a hell I return to time and time again.  Such a masochist am I...I must enjoy my pain  God knows I'm enjoying not masturbating.  It's intense because everything is a turn on now.  "OMFG, carpet!  You can fuck on carpet!"      Have you ever felt like the golden crayon in a box full of dull colors?      This was during a conversation with my mother about stupid people.  We'd both paused to ponder.  It was great.  Things are great right now.  To all you faithful readers my attitude may have a severe decline tomorrow...school.  How many more weeks?  About three.  Just three.  I can survive because I have hope!  I am returning to my love and friends.  I return to my life!  Blissful me!!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is that anniversary of Joana Burman's last performance!  A performance I saw a year ago.  Ballerinas are pretty, to think I could have been one had I kept up with it.  I honestly wish I had, but then I may not have come across Kung Fu... so ...yeah.  I have quit so many things.  Violin, viola, piano, guitar, clarinet, swimming.  I hope that's it... I need to get active dammit.  There is so much to do out there, and life is so short.  It's kind of depressing...   At least I have somethings to keep me occuped, the problem is I may become bored with them soon.  So so sad.  I have FictionPress.net to enthrall my imagination with the works of many writers-some who have horrifying story telling skills- I also have a new found hobby: htlm shit.  Yep, I can change colors of text!!! Whee!  It's frutrating because I have no idea what I'm doing.  Uh... you use these thingies <> and hexadecimal codes for the codes.  HEX-A-DE-CIM-AAAAL  hexa-there's 6 characters...#OOOOOO     Once one tells themselves not to do something, immediatly, the desire to do it becomes that much more intense... yes, I am referring to my vow to not hit the slit.  So I have to make my own fun.  I always say I worry about myself... meaning my inclination to go suck face->suck dick->fuck etc.  I think what I really worry about is what my friends will think.  A certain friend once said, "PLeeeeeeaSe don't become a slut!"  I didn't know what to say to that.    What is wrong with it?  Seriously?  Because sOcietY thinks it is wrong... there's a good reason *scoff* let's just conform to the wishes of anyone but ourselves.  People say 'slut' like it is a bad thing.  If you enjoy that lifestyle then right on.  Being a slut is *bad* if one does it for another reason than their own enjoyment.  Despite my virginity, I tend to be fairly slutty when it comes to other things... I enjoy it until the guy I am gambing is a shit to me.  I just need to detatch.  And I am.  As experience progresses I learn that I shouldn't expect anything but cum from any guy I'm with.  That is the truth.  Even if the guy is your best friend... once you go down on a guy your integrity goes down with it [less and less respect, but then again I am in highschool].  Especially if you want it to be special between you and that friend.  He'd probably just go brag about it to his exgf to make her jealous.  In no way could I possibly be relating this to MY life...enough of my pain.  I need to do my report about acid now...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      You Are Very Horny  Your sex drive catchs you in a trap! You want to be sensible and sexy, but it's hard to be both! You are a horny chick riding on a derailed speeding train. Chances are your body will win out over your mind, and you'll let your sexual spirit free. Sure your sexuality has caused a bit of drama, but what's live without the drama? You have come a long way, though, and it never hurts to travel a bit more!   urlLink   How Horny Are You?    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, deary dear me.  I am so flucking horny right now.  To any guy out there: if you want to get into my pants fuckin take me to an 'action packed' movie.  Yeah, I just saw X2.  I like fighting.  Fighting pretty and turn on-y... hahaa!  Between Nightcrawler's fighting scene and Wolverine's gruff and greasy raging self I am just about ready to cream my black panties.  Some may think it is desperately pathetic to get turned on by such a simple thing as a movie.  At least I'm gettin horny, motherfucker!  I ain't no fridgid bitch.  Though, the tension shall build!  Because I'm a masochistic fucker I have decided to cease masturbating, for now.  I shall resume the one purpose I have in life once I get laid.  Oh the sweet torment!!!     Without going into too many details, while watching X2 I was imagining a certain promiscous friend of mine taking my virginity.  I am hesitant to let him, because it wouldn't be meaningful.  I want my first to mean something more than "Yes! Yes! Yes!" .... I want a "Harder, bitch!" in there too...lol...THE GLORY OF PUBERTY!!!  Got hormones?!!!  I THINK SO!!!     I can semi control my dreams on occasion... what have I used my new power for? Fucking a horse.  Yeah, I dreamt that I *did* a horse.  It was weird cuz I knew that I was dreaming and I knew that it was in fact my idea...the horse just said sure.  The horse [I've analyzed this] represents my promiscous friend---let's call him D.  D and I have fooled around and his experience intrigues me, I'm curious ~~> curiosity transferred to dream + seeing some disturbing porn involving animals = dream fucking a horse.     Did we really need that?  A well, I need to maintain some integrity with whoever reads this... a maximum of about 3 people.  Hi y'all!  I walked home from the movie theater...I went alone...NeRvE rAcKiNg MuCh?!?!?  As the paranoia set in I remembered how confident I used to be... I MISS KUNG FU~ People speak of loving someone so much it hurts, that is how it was for me with Choy Li Fut-my love, my art, my soul-People also don't think my love of it is the same as love of a person... well, I've never loved a person as much as I loved CLF.  It was my purpose.  My reason for living.  People make other people feel that way.  IT IS NO DIFFERENT!  When I had to move here I felt like the core of my beng had been voilently ripped out of my body.     I still feel that way, however, I am able to heal slightly with the knowledge that I am going back to it in about 35 days... 34, it's midnight.  Life is good right now.  I am letting myself enjoy the world around me.  It's nice.  I have a plan of what I'm going to do.  I have no doubts, and I will not write 'yet'. Haha!  I survive!  With the internet, hope, and friends.  And, of course, music.  Thank satan for music.     I am not a satanist, thou fearful asshole!  I've just been doing some reading [http://www.angelfire.com/me4/baphometthief/index.html] and some of their shit makes sense.  As does some of the shit the Christians have.  I collect the good.  Indulgence verus abstinence.  I like that.  If you couldn't tell...HA  ...no religion is perfect.  Which is why I have no religion.  Learning about it is great though, gotta love that knowledge ya pick up from this crazy activity we call  reading ...   Truly astonishing.   It's sad what humans are becoming.  Mostly sad that we're getting fatter and fatter.  At least with a good physique one may get away with being an imbicile.  But hey at least I know what kind of panties I am!     urlLink       You Are Thong Panties!  Lusty, and a little slutty. You turn heads everywhere!    urlLink   What's Kind of Panties Are *You*?    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      To all my friends who read this, you should already know what kind of sick fuck I am...     urlLink       Your Secret Fetish Is BDSM!  Tie me up! Tie me down!  Whether you're doing the tying, or doing the crying, you love BDSM.  For you, love hurts- and sex hurts even more. So make that spanking a little harder. The more you bleed, the more you come.    urlLink   What's *Your* Secret Fetish? Click Here to Find Out!    
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Good to know    urlLink     You Are A  urlLink Insatiable Bitch !  You reek of sex. Married men, old men, and young men... You don't discriminate - as long as they get you off. You'll seduce anyone, from gay guys to your friends' boyfriends.   urlLink   What Kind of Bitch Are *You*?   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     You Are A  urlLink Carnal Kisser !  For you, kissing is just an appetizer - and a brief one at that. It's not unusual for your hands to wander elsewhere when kissing, even on a first date. Truth be told, you much rather be kissed some where other than your lips!   What Your Kissing Style Says About You:  You're a highly sexual person and not ashamed of it. What's the big deal about sex, anyway? Of all your friends, you're the best in bed... no wonder their lovers are always eyeing you. You're biggest problem in relationships is having too many to choose from. You're in demand, babe!   Your Personal Kissing Matches and Mismatches:  Get together with another Carnal Kisser, and you'll be intwined all night. Not that you'll mind...  If you're ready for a wild ride, then search out an Intense Kisser.  (Not hard, they're usually obsessed with you anyway.) Kissing an Intense Kisser is... well, mind blowing for you.  Word of advice, keep away from Juicy Kissers. They aren't prepared for the amount of lust in your little heart and will be scared away easily. And Romanic Kissers? Please! They want a ring before they'll get down with you!    urlLink   How Do *You* Kiss?   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      Your Sex Position is  urlLink Upside Down 69    Daring. Dangerous. And oh so tasty.  You go crazy when you go south- And you love getting it in the mouth.    urlLink   What's Your Sex Position?     -these fuckin tests...haha i almost wrote testes
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      THIS IS THE LAST ONE, I PROMISE!!!!!  May 11~Clearly, I lied.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        You Are an EXPERT in Bed  You know precisely what you’re doing when the sheets are pulled down and the panties go right along with them. You’re also super confident, and rightly so. Because any man who may be fortunate enough to find himself between your legs is a happy man, indeed. You’re the type of woman men brag about in locker rooms: knowledgeable, adorable, and lickable. You’ve gotten to the point that you don’t even have to try so hard. It all just comes naturally: the mouth, the hips, everything underneath. One lovely little package.    urlLink   Are *You* Good In Bed?   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Jebuz, these frickin quizzes rock my socks!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Now isn't that informative?  Kind of a 'yeah right' thing going on isn't it?  But yeah, I don't need a dumb little test to tell me that ; )  No sir-ree!  I certainly would like to have a boyfriend of some sort again.  Necking on a regular basis, why am I against relationships again?  Oh yeah, the anguish of being loyal.   I feel like I'm the best fucking girlfriend.  I am a nympho, I know it.  Sex is all I want.  And having a bf has not been good, why? because I've only had one.  And he was too much of a gentleman to fuck me... Doesn't it suck?  Virginity is intact...not for long hopefully.  I want to get laid-like any other self respecting teenager!   I'm damn sick of the stigma that goes along with screwing... we've all heard the bitch-bitch about how guys can fuck whoever and whatever and if girls do it they're sluts... well, call me a fuckin slut... cause god damn, society made that little rule and all I have to say about it is: FUCK SOCIETY   I am so sick of all these implied/ingrained rules of how to live.  Bring on the cock  and  the pussy baby!  I'm tired of be told that living a certain way I want is wrong... "I wanna fuck" (-SMG "Cruel Intentions") and if anyone thinks screwing is wrong they can suck my fuckin dick, and I don't even have one, cause I'm obviously getting more jamoke and poonce than you are!!  (Thanks A, by the way, for not fucking me you knew I wasn't ready...dammit this could undermine all i've just said, fuck it, i'm appreciative).  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        I'll be damned. You ARE bisexual AFTER all!  You sees "31 Flavors" as the ideal place to work.  You can get unequivocally turned on by eating Cheese 'n Crackers- taking the little sticks from the wrapper and sliding them into the cheese.  You are definitely a sexual glutton, taking as much as you can ;)    urlLink   Are *You* Bisexual? Click Here to Find Out!    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, a blog of my very own, what fun.  A big thank you to Allison who was able to excede my incompetence and actually set up this wretched excuse for an easy program.  ::Large phony smile:: Anyway, I will hopefully write in this every day, and if not every week.  Currently I must wisk myself off to Microsoft Word to bask in a history project about Hitler.  Though before I go, I must mention this:  in history class today we watched the beginning scene of Saving Private Ryan.    D-Day on Omaha beach, the most difficult of battles that day. Blood splattering on Tom Hanks' face as a soldier is shot before him recieved a mere "Ew" from the boy sitting behind me.  As Giovani Ribci (I know that's probably spelled wrong, however I have more important things in my life than obsessing about actors) stops a bleeding neck wound he yells out that he has, the soldier he is trying to save is shot in the head.  The ironic misfortune earned a sympathetic smile from myself and various snickers from around the class.  My smile was quickly torn from my face at the realization that my classmates were clearly oblivious to the notion that this had all actually happened, in fact it probably had been worse.    I am currently in a somewhat fragile state of mind...seeing these things was traumatic.  Later, two German soldiers try to surrender.  They emerge from hinding with their hands above their heads cautious and pleading in their language.  Two American soldiers taunt them with "What?! I can't understand what you're saying!" and shoot them both.  I begin to cry at this point.  My class laughs.  The savior of my sanity at this school is my history teacher.  Upon the uproar of my fellow students Savior says to them, in what I've percieved as disgust, "What are you laughing about? There's nothing funny about what's going on." Silence from all who are amused by the sick destruction of human life we call war.    War is quarreling amongst the leaders who then use the people they lead to die for them.  I cried because it is my belief that everyone deserves the right to live.  What a waste it is to just send people somewhere to get killed.  That's what battle is, killing.  Those in power  expect  it.  Do you really think Bush sends troops to Iraq thinking they'll come back safe and unharmed?  oh wait...it's Bush... What I mean to say is that the public doesn't have a realistic view of what war and battle are and very little appreciation for life. 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        You Have a  urlLink Tight Pussy !  When you get it on, it doesn't fit quite right.  You're pussy's a near virgin - and very tight.  No doubt that sex makes you moan and shout.  But the real trick is getting everything back out!       urlLink   What Kind of Pussy Do *You* Have?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Alrighty, I am back in RENO!  And I'm glad.  Glad glad glad glad glad!  This blog is annoying... does anyone fuckin read it anymore?  Arg.  Well, latest news: met 2 very, very cool vegetarian males.  Jeremy and Galen.  Jeremy and I have been hangin out a lot for having just met... He calls himself "lurpy"... my opinion: ----! I fear that he may read this sometime and discover THE TRUTH!  The only hint I shall give is that 4 letter word starts with S and ends in -exy... WAS THAT TOO FUCKING BLATENT?!?!?!  *shifty eyes*... *hums to self for a bit* Anywho... I'd any his who...  I mean... yeeeaaaah... Galen is very cool as well... BUDDHIST DUDE!  Just talking to him and I feel enlightened... I should take his advice and study ZEN! As for me.. I need sleep... *snore***************************
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What would you do? What would you do if I followed you?  Holy muthafook.... I think I'm liking romance...     I am leaving for Reno tomorrow, so there may not be a post for a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      THE LATEST CONCLUSION:  everyone looks better with eyeliner.  everyone.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Grr...Arg... God what a day.  Hot.  Bored.  Not one, but two finals taken.  Too many fluids... feeling like I may vomit.  *dry heaves*  Need AC!  Interpret that as Air Conditioning or Asheron's Call.  Sweating, and yet I sit with a blanket wrapped around waist.  Bralessness is a gift.  *Sigh*  So yah.. today nothing too mystifying occurred.  Breakfast with mom at a local diner, sleep due to illness, finals due to family reunion, looking at pics of a goth chick for about an hour and a half, and watching The Pianist.  My review of this film: Long, drawn out, too dramatic, Schindler's List was much much better.  And may the news be spread that, upon seeing the credits, I exclaimed, "Oooh!  It's a Roman Polanski film!" Not referring to it being bad... just looooonnnnnnggggggg.  Have any of you seen The Ninth Gate?  Good, but LONG!  RRarrg!   So.  My vacacacation to the East.  Boston! was not where I was actually staying.  I said Boston because no one knows what Nonquitt is.  It is a rich area.  Summer houses.  Very expensive, but my family was renting one of them from a "friend".... Now really.  Would a friend really make another friend pay 3k a week for a house?  Sure, it's a big house... in fact it's two... but REALLY!  Friend indeed.  Blah! It was fun though.  Got me a sunburn the last day while cohoggin'.  That's right, I was digging for clams, and I got a good load too.  Nothing quite like it.  Very fun.... I will wear sunscreen somewhere other than my face next time.  BuRN!  That was a little play on words there, yah.     A good bt of my time was spent playing with the childrenses.  Tiger Lily-19 months- and Elizabeth-3- were the two who recieved the most attention.  Tiger is my first cousin, I believe.  Elizabeth is my mom's cousin's daughter--what does that make her to me?  Never really understood it.... oh well.  GF (once Grand Fuck, now Grand Father again) has gotten nice!  Like, seriously nice and loving.  THE GLORY OF ANTIDEPRESSANTS!!!  I sing praise...    I notice that I do not describe much.  GF was just really calm and reassuring and offering help.  Twas great.  I actually enjoyed entertaining the kids more than talking to the adults.  Was fun, though I did feel like my IQ was consistently dropping the more I was around them.  "Das Dutch"  was one of Tiger's catch phrases...so to speak... when the week was over she had learned some new words.  Like boat, No-no (she'd say that whenever she saw my mom, poor mom), Ka (car) and that's all I can remember.      Seeing my 96 year old great grandfather was really cool.  Him sitting on the couch with thick glasses and a sweatsuit on looking around at some of the family.  I come in the first night and sit next to him, say "hi... how are you" and such.  It is rather akward because sometimes when he speaks it is difficult to understand... However, that same night my mum asked how he was and he looked up at her, paused, and pronouced, "I am so well!"  That made my trip.  Werd.  Most of the family ignores him.  I hate it.  I tried to talk to him at most opportunities.  He's not senile, and has a lethal wit (   Boston was fun.  Went for a day.  Saw the Constitution... it's a ship, the oldest that is still in use.  Old Iron Sides.  w00t!  I have decided I want to be part of a crew.  Whether that crew is that of pirates has yet to be decided.  Muahaha!  Mm.... ship.  Went on a small tour of the city because the streets are fucked and one can go no where but a circle... well a square... a figurative circle.  Tour amusing... the trolly driver was great.  Loud and funny.  I shopped with mummy too.  Faneuil Hall.  I have new earrings... now if only I could get my originals out.  Ha!  Well, it's hot I'm tired.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Very tired and fairly sick... shall write much later....     urlLink        You Are A  urlLink Sexual Healer !  Instead of bringing lovers to their knees with your use of feminine wiles, you simply use your mere presence.    Sexual healers treat bodies as temples - and not merely somewhere to place their bounty upon again and again.    As one of the select few, you are praised for your diligence.  You are not as flashy as other lovers out there.    Those who find you in their bed are very lucky indeed and are in for a treat of never-ending pleasure.  Healing every bit of your lovers both physically and spiritually.  No one will ever leave your bed without a sense of peace and relaxation. If they leave it at all!      urlLink   What Sexy Woman Are You?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I are in teh Nonquitt, full of teh richa sunna teh bitchas!!  Tis funne!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so fulled with hate right now.  Some may think this is a bit extreme, but I am at the point where I would like to kill someone.  Not just any old fuck out there with nothing to do in life, but a particularly assinine fuck who is so bitter and absolutely shit in the world that he must damage others.  You guessed it-- My bastard fuck uncle.  That son of a bitch just spent 10 minutes telling my mother how worthless she is.  Why?  Because he's an asshole.  Other than that, because my belongings have been sitting in his house for however long.  Six months.  My things may end up thrown out.  Honestly, I will miss that red comfortor the most.  That god damn fuck.  I want him dead.  No... I want him tortured and then dead.  And I want someone else to do it for me.  Why?  Because I don't ever want to see his disgusting face as long as I live.  That mother fucking drunk cunt son of a raped bitch.  In the immortal words of Allison: "...you're a shame. Well, let me fill you in on something. You only have one set of balls left, your mental nads never dropped and that in turn has made you one fucking old, tight, dried up, crusty ass pussy."  Thank you Allie.     God Lordy, do I have one hellish headache!!  Fucking family reunion in Boston.... fucked my last period of the day.  Story shortened:  Missing finals.  English teacher has problem with it, doesn't want to give it to me after finals week like the rest of my teachers are.  Thought I was going to fail sophomore english.  If mom hadn't come to pick e up, I would have.  Big arguement between teacher and mom.  I managed not to burst into tears until I walked away.  So, go me, a life improvement.  Next time, maybe I won't start shaking uncontrollably.  Maybe....   On a lighter note, I am going to Boston.  ...yay... with the breakdown I had and the one my mom had later... I feel like shit and am amazed that there aren't bloody cuts all over my arms.  I must be developing some kind of intelligence and control over my emotions... WTF?!  Aren't I supposed to be condemned to self punishment for the rest of my days?  My world is shaken yet again.    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      At long god damn last!  A moment to write in this fucker.  We are not bitter about all the shit we had to do for school though... dear me, no... Ack hellish work.  Now it's 7 something 2 days after my last entry.  Wheee.  Very tired.  I am going to Boston tomorrow.  Unless I can get to a computer no writing shall occur for about a week.  Not bad, but it'll be long, I don't know how all of you will live witout new entries.  Heh, poor you.     I am listening to Tool.  It is niiiiice.  Undertow...mm, "Prison Sex" haha some people think it's about child abuse... I can see that.  But I don't think so, unless it's some really bad fucking abuse.  Lol I didn't even mean to make "fucking" literal, but it works both ways, go English Me!  Muahaha!!  Banana got a senoir friend who is leaving to sign m yearbook.  I am happy.  As I said to him, "Love in the form of signature, at least to me anyway," and it is true.  The year I have people who I don't have to beg to sign it... I have someone else do it! Hahaha, she doesn't need to beg tho... neither did I really.  Only with that asshole fucker Jayson.  He just wrote his name, not even have a good summer.  Bastard...  There's a shadow just behind me, trying every step I take, making every promise empty, pointing every finger at me, waiting like a stalking butler, who upon the finger rests murder now the path must we, just because the son has come.... Dat Der Is Teh "SOBER"  Ya... Sick of writing thi morning, I sleepy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The fucking tag-board is back up...there had been something wrong with the site.  I got 4 hours, or so, of sleep last night, and because I've actally been doing homework now I couldn't write today either.  Blah, my neighbor is insane and his is the only dog I would kill, for the mere purpose of my sanity.  He yells at his lawn mower... enough said.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      THE FUCKING TAG-BOARD IS DOWN!!! MOTHERFUCKINGBITCHCUNTSUCKINGSHITDAMNASSWHORESHITLICKING...o_O I'm okay....
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        This is the most recent conversation I have had with my friend Alex.  Her parents are FUCKING insane!  Read and tag your thoughts at the bottom of the page~   CharmingEnigma:  Ooh! It's Alex, and she's online!!!   Tralala5505:  yes, but not for long. my computer is being taken away, so this is my last night   CharmingEnigma:  what why?   Tralala5505:  i'm grounded for life and never allowed to see my friends again   Tralala5505:  no phone, or tv, or car, or anything   CharmingEnigma:  what have you 'done now'?   Tralala5505:  they found out about me and ruby   CharmingEnigma:  grounding you isn't going to help   Tralala5505:  yes, but it sure will make me depressed   CharmingEnigma:  how did they find out   Tralala5505:  they listened in on my phone calls   CharmingEnigma:  jeez   CharmingEnigma:  what did you say   Tralala5505:  something about me being in love with her   CharmingEnigma:  was it just like "i love you" kind a stuff?   CharmingEnigma:  ah   CharmingEnigma:  I think you should fake a psychotic episode   Tralala5505:  urk! i'm just sooo mad.  I haven't even been able to use the phone to tell everybody that they can't call me anymore   Tralala5505:  I tried, it doesn't phaze them   Tralala5505:  faze?   CharmingEnigma:  phase...?   CharmingEnigma:  i duno   CharmingEnigma:  dunno   CharmingEnigma:  ack spelling   Tralala5505:  yeah, it's useless   CharmingEnigma:  no like draw on the walls and stuff   CharmingEnigma:  break things    CharmingEnigma:  let the rage out   CharmingEnigma:  have them send you away to a mental institution   CharmingEnigma:  !!    CharmingEnigma:  it would be better I'm sure   Tralala5505:  maybe, i've already threatened running away, and they decided that they would call the bank and shut dow my savings account, so that I would have no money if I did run away   CharmingEnigma:  get all your money out   CharmingEnigma:  then do it   Tralala5505:  they already took my money out this afternoon   CharmingEnigma:  this is like a fucking soap opera   Tralala5505:  lol, yes it is!   Tralala5505:  and what's even funnier, my mother quit her job to stay home with me full time to make sure that I behave myself.   CharmingEnigma:  Alex, I can come back all "reformed" and stuff if you would like   CharmingEnigma:  omg   Tralala5505:  ha, you reformed?   CharmingEnigma:  they won't know any difference   CharmingEnigma:  lol I have white clothing   Tralala5505:  lol, omg! what's happened to you!   CharmingEnigma:  It's fucking hot man   Tralala5505:  lol   Tralala5505:  i have to go now.  i'll try to talk to you soon.   CharmingEnigma:  okay   Tralala5505:  bye bye   CharmingEnigma:  what's your phone #   Tralala5505:  775-852-9190   CharmingEnigma:  okie i'll try and call ya maybe   Tralala5505:  ok, bye   CharmingEnigma:  have caller id?   Tralala5505:  yes   CharmingEnigma:  dammit   CharmingEnigma:  what's the thing to block it   CharmingEnigma:  star something   CharmingEnigma:  i'll tell them it is school related   Tralala5505:  ok, but school's over in 3 days   CharmingEnigma:  dammit   CharmingEnigma:  I'll try anyway   Tralala5505:  ok   CharmingEnigma:  ttyl   CharmingEnigma:  and remember- there are always options!   Tralala5505:  yes, like cutting off my hair and becoming a nun!   Tralala5505:  ok, goodnight annah   CharmingEnigma:  nightnight 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are the one who holds back your feelings from others and yourself. You dont want to show people your weak u dont want sympathy. Your strong but maybe... you should show ur feelings, just alittle*    urlLink   The type of pain ur eyes behold     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Heh, how did they guess?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have got to write/learn/research about accupuncture, not about my good day.  Dammit.  Latest news... I am going to read  Ishmael  and the first 3 pages are fab.  So, off to work, so to speak.  SuckiGe!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      A young girl was having a heart-to-heart talk with her mother on her first visit home since starting university.  "Mum, I have to tell you," the girl confessed. "I lost my virginity last weekend."  "I'm not surprised," said her mother. "It was bound to happen sooner or later. I just hope it was a romantic and pleasurable experience."  "Well, yes and no," the pretty student remarked. "The first eight guys felt great, but after them my pussy got really sore."   Is this really a joke?  No, seriously, I may be involved in something like this... 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        The joy of cock  I have a little poem, I'll try to make it quick;  The subject is quite simple: the joy of owning dick. A penis is a splendid thing; you ladies should be jealous.  An organ with such lovely skin, it's smooth and mostly hairless. It starts to grow so quickly when a guy's about thirteen, His testicles on either side, his willy in between. It dangles neatly down below; it's softly warm and loyal. But at the slightest hint of lust, it's ready to uncoil. It seems to have a mind all of its own; it's like an untamed beast, It squirms and writhes and stretches out, just when you 'spect it least. Sometimes, yes, it misbehaves, erecting when it shouldn't. A bumpy train ride sets it off, and then I wish it wouldn't. During summer, wearing little, sunning on the beach, A glimpse of wobbly boobs or bums will make it squirm and reach. But handle it with love and care, for it will give great pleasure.  I often check if it has grown - now when did I last measure? Some men will fret about their size: they give it lots of thought;  Is seven inches long enough? It makes them quite distraught. They sneak a look in toilets, wondering what they'll see, But if another glances back at them, there's no way they can pee! Masturbating is a sin - at least some folks believe.  That's just some old wives' tale, 'cause it really can relieve. Without this super organ, no shag would be complete.  Lesbians can try their best, but must admit defeat. It has some splendid functions, I'm sure you will agree: To start a whole new life, and more than that - to pee! But what seems most amazing about my one-eyed flute, Whatever it is doing, it knows which juice to shoot. And better yet, it stays with one, until one's old and frail. Don't take it out in public though, or you'll be thrown in jail. And so I'd say with certainty That every man just loves his tool: But girls, be sure you never chew,  Just suck and fondle, lick and play,  And never, ever bend!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Tag-board is up AND running!!!  Booya!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       All I want in life are a few good pokes.   Ahh, figurative language...how I do love thee!  I am back to my "fuck virginity" state of mind.  I was thinking.  When I masturbate, it is practically having sex, it is just by myself.  So, therefore I am not a virgin anyway, and also, with all I have already done with guys, it's not going to be that big of a step.  Really.  I could just go fuck girls.  Then I'd be a virgin forever.  Which would be pretty cool.  Orgasms...without ever losing virginity...no penis no loss...  The only reason virginity is such a big deal is because of the fucked religions.  Pagans would celebrate sex, no waiting... and the Greeks!  JFC!  They embraced 'adultery' and homosexuality.  A wife was just to hatch out the brats.  Mistresses and (yea) young boys were preferred.  Beside the purpose of sex is to make fuckin kids, so, it is only such a big deal because our 'advanced' human society makes it one ... do you see a fucking dog crying about how Rover is off mounting Muffin instead of her?  Bullshit, the lot!!!    Sex is for pleasure.  Sex is to express your love to someone when you find them.  Simple.  Plain.  There you go.  As indecisive boy once told me "It doesn't matter who you do it with for your first time, it's about a first time with the right person,"  Now does that make sense to anyone but me and my horny friends?  DOES IT?! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What all of you don't know...   Psycho. You are overwhelmed by anger. You may even hate the world and everything in it and you believe revenge is the way of the world. An eye for an eye.    urlLink   How Emotional Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Heh, maybe ya do
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Tomboy    urlLink   What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    At least I'm providing amusement, right? RIGHT?!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           You are red. You are impure, but noble. You are precious and true to yourself and others. When you love, you love entirely, and will do anything to make your love happy. You are sure of your identity, therefore, you cannot change others or be changed. You are a true prince, you may be forgotten, but without you, none of us could go on.   What inner color are you?          I have better things to do, really, I'm just not doing them
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         Also known widely as the Fire Bird, the phoenix is a profound symbol of life and rebirth. It has a life cycle of 500 to 600 years and after that amount of time, it sets itself on fire and dies in the flames. Then, after three days, it rises again from the ashes. It is a completely benign creature who lives in dew. It is said that the phoenix has a beautiful melodious song which grows ever more mournful as its life comes to an end. It is also a symbol of the sun and immortality.   What mythical beast best represents you? urlLink Take the quiz!     HOW GOD DAMN UNPRODUCTIVE CAN I BE?!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       My Iraqi Leadership Name is  Abdallah al-Jizrawi .  urlLink What's yours?   Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey .    Shoulda known the word Jiz would be in there somewhere
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Can anyone tell that I'm procrastinating?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       My Mormon name is  Anniyah Laertis !  urlLink What's yours?  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       My goddamn rock solid ghetto shiznit name is  Wankmaster Kawfi .  urlLink What's yours?   Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey .  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink Which Evil Criminal are  You ? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are a dark writer. A fierce and loyal follower of Poe and the other gothic authors, you LOVE to instill a sense of revulsion and somewhat fear in your readers. You love to poke their brains with logic dealing with the darker side of the human mind and character. Truly surprising and a true individual, you'll do ANYTHING to create a scene. :)    urlLink   What's YOUR Writing Style?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Evil, you like to take over other fairys and make then yours, at the same time you fallow someoen else. You are a winter fairy , and i do have to say mostlikely pretty cute or sexy    urlLink   What kind of fairy are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        You are a Day Dreamer..   Daydreamers tend to be away from the normal, and have a deeper aspect when looking at things. Most of the time, thier outcasts of the social society, but don't worry. It just means your so deep it scares thier simple little brains.    urlLink   What kind of Dreamer are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OMFG I am in love.  In love with my brush handle.  Jesus Christ!  Best fucking shower ever!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Doodoodoodiedoo...REPORTS ON ACID AND ACCUPUNCTURE BEING DONE TODAY!  FUCK YAY!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OOOoookaaaayyy....  I have been awake for a while now, almost 2 days, wheee!  Saw a concert at this house on Wells and ended up getting ditched by Jeremy ...snarl... but at least he had introduced me to his friend Crystal, who, by the way, is very cool and fun.  So that was good, I wasn't left completely alone in a part of town I was unfamiliar with! Yay!  The band that played was The Great Redneck Hope.  Crystal and I spent all night talking to the singer, who is also very cool.  Haha! He shot a bottle rocket (I think, it was some kind of explosive heh) out of his ass.  Lol, it was funny.  One of the guys who lived in the house where the conceret was gave me his sweatshirt to wear (because it gets fucking cold at 4 in the morning!) he was really nice as well, I plan to speak with him again sometime soon... and no, I am attracted to him.  Am not!  Aw, bloody hell, I gave it away again, damn me.  I would like to keep the sweatshirt.  Or return it and become friends with the dude.  But yea, that's the most recent news in my life, nothing else is too enthralling...  I was in the 4th of July parade downtown! YAY!  I was holding a flag for Kung Fu... hehehe I got the red and gold one.  It was fun.  Sleeeeeeeeeeep deprivation-self induced.  Hehe!  And I feel fine! A little tired, but I also just shared a corona with Allison before watching the shitty fireworks. Since I'm fairly buzzed I might as well say that it pisses me off that Jeremy gets so different around his friends.  Jesus Christ, he's like a fuckin smarter, kinder Jayson.  That fuck.  Why'd he have to be so amusing and charming when we met?! That fuck.  And dammit all to hell, why do I have to be attracted to him in such an intense fashion?  That fuck... Bah!   On a lighter note:  I am getting my flying spinning rear kicks down with the shizza yo!  I kicked the bag and sent it into the damn wall!  Hell yes!!!  And (ha!) I totally freaked out one of the white belts.  I was partnered with this beginner guy to practice kicks, and apparently I have a mean fucking rear kick.  Hell yes... I am so going to work on pop ups now that I'm getting the F.S.R.K.s down.  Oh yes, we are obsessessed.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I had to put this on here, I just had to!  Never was a characteristic of mine so easily described!     urlLink        You Are a Playmate Lay!  All the guys love getting with you,  But respect isn't exactly something you're used to.  Not that you care ~ you just love SEX!  As far as you are concerned...you're using them!     urlLink   What Kind of Lay Are You?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      THIS IS AMUSING    urlLink        There is 50-50 CHANCE of a boyfriend in your future.  You’re interested, most of the time, but also rather unsure of how to  proceed. It’s like your mom or older sister never took you by the hand,  led you into the garden and had the heart-to-heart instructional talk  that other girls seem to have had.     You know the one, with all the juicy stuff about how to handle men.  But don’t feel like you’re missing out; you’re not! You’re learning  the ropes and eventually you’ll reach the point where you’re beating  men off with a stick.     urlLink   Is There A Boyfriend In Your Future?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Passed through a very low time these recent days.  Cut into my arm more than I have before, intent on drawning blood.  I did, it was beautiful and sad.  All I could really think about when doing it, though, was how much I was shortening my life (the DNA replication thing...lacking details...bah).  Today I had a short breakdown with best friend, things were said that, I think, needed to be said for  while now.  I feel like the sky is no longer being held up by me alone.  I get help =)  A big Thank You to Spud for caring, and a big FUCK THE HELL OFF to his brother for being a careless idiot... for you Satanists out there he's an ungrateful psychic vampire who deserves my vengance (so I've been reading the 9 statements...) his dumbfuck rapist friend as well.  KUDOS TO SPUD!!!  for being a smarter alcohol consumer.  Thank you to Jana, Judith, Betsy, and...Kayla because they all rock when I'm down.  I have to get up early so yah.  Less and less info...whee.  At least I'm not in Cali.  Kung fu shall get better, it has to, I will not survive without it.    Oh the DRAMA of it all!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay!  I am back! (WAAA!! screams Jana) I am having a good time living, existing etc.  Kung Fu is losing it's meaning to me but hey!  I've found a new band, VAST.  The song "touched" was on Angel 4 years ago and I finally found it yesterday!  I HIGHLY recommend ggetting the cd to anyone who wants to have a truly good musical experience...  GET IT GOD DAMN YOU!!!  *snarl, spit, growl* So yah, more writing to come... later.   BOOWA! Read this!!!: A group of kindergartners were trying to become accustomed to the first grade. The biggest hurdle they faced was that the teacher insisted on "No baby talk"! "You need to use 'Big People' words," she was always reminding them. She asked Chris what he had done over the weekend..."I went to visit my Nana."  "No, you went to visit your GRANDMOTHER. Use Big People words!" She then asked Mitchell what he had done... "I took a ride on a choo-choo." She said, "No, you took a ride on a TRAIN. You must remember to use 'BigPeople' words." She then asked Alex what he had done... "I read a book," he replied. "That's" WONDERFUL!" the teacher said. "What book did you read?" Alex thought real hard about it, then puffed out his little chest with great pride and said, "Winnie the SHIT." 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It is 2:51 in the morning.  Let this teach me to sleep in the afternoon...again.  Why am I subjected to this? WHY?  I just wanted to sleep.  It seems, however, that there is some force bent on keeping me from that particular desire.  I say to that force, "Let me fuckin' sleep!" why why why why why! This isn't fair.  The moment I go back to bed and TRY to sleep I'll get uncomfortable and restless.  There's no point in trying.  I think I'll have some juice... yes juice.  If I stay awake all night I wonder what tomorrow will be like?  Mom is driving Jana to school...yay...If I don't sleep I'll be high, high on lack of sleep, I've done it before.  oh, if only the school gave a shit about the individual student.  "I haven't slept for eight days" "Well, you could have gotten some homework done." Thanks teach, I appreciate your attempt at learnin me wut the world is lyk. Fuck off, all of you bastards!  Damn school, dammit dammit dammit.  If it weren't for school I would probably be asleep.  dammit dammit.  Ahh! juice...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well yah, gave head on monday and today.  It's so much fun, I feel that I haven't been trying as much as I could be... will fix!  Oh yes... must regain determination to be the best at sucking dick.  mustmustmust.  hahaha!   Here's the e-mail the head givee sent me a while back...Sept 23... Hey annah. What have you been up too? well i was just watching this porno and i thought about you and wanted to say hi. Oh me and my girl broke up. and i sure do miss your awsome mouth so email me back or give me a call   my reply Silly Rabbit... I'm not up to that much, school and kung fu as usual.  Nick said you're in ...trade school? Something that isn't Galena.  Heh.  How's that going?  As for my "awesome mouth" (thank you, by the way) it's currently quite out of practice and for the most part (this will break your heart) retired.   Yet, somehow this may change, I forsee... wow that wasn't blatent enough.  Why don't you call me Hope to talk to you soon  his reply what? i dont belive that....i miss how good you sucked me off (to put it blatently) ohh hell yea i'll call you thanks for writing back.....   needless to say, my mouth is out of retirement and on the way to superstardom...not really... but I want to get really good again.   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay need to document this: first vibrator experience.  Holy fuck.  30 minutes of amazement.  Holy fuck.  Why did I want a boyfriend again? Holy FUCK!  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      UN-god damn-believeable    Fight Club!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Nemesis    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Again with the obsessive test taking.... WHAT DO YOU WANT PEOPLE!?  My nighttime minutes don't start til seven...RINGTONES!!! dahaaaaaa!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This fucking site is too accurate!  Gawd damn!    urlLink        You Are a Drunken Kiss!  You are an impulsive kisser - kiss first, think later  And sometimes you end up suffering from a little kissing amnesia  It's all good though… your little condition allows you to kiss freely  Without headache or heartache the next morning     urlLink   What Type of Kiss Are You?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This was too good not to post, sorry to all the dear fans of my writing, it will happen when it happens...so here you go, a lovely addition to my collection of idiocy amidst the people I waste my time with:  CharmingEnigma: I'm a sick sick girl Vampyro321: well DUH CharmingEnigma: nice  CharmingEnigma: real nice CharmingEnigma: jerk  Vampyro321: thank you CharmingEnigma: smart ass as well Vampyro321: I agree CharmingEnigma: ass! CharmingEnigma: tehe Vampyro321: havent you learned its impossible to insult me yet? CharmingEnigma: i'm not trying Vampyro321: good Vampyro321: cause you suck at it CharmingEnigma: you don't know whether i suck or not CharmingEnigma: because you've never seen me try Vampyro321: "suck at it" Vampyro321: that has no verbal meaning towards actually sucking CharmingEnigma: i'm afraid that does not make sense Vampyro321: good CharmingEnigma: oh so you like being inarticulate? Vampyro321: no I like when you dont understand something  CharmingEnigma: from your lack of eloquence? how sad.... Vampyro321: what even sadder is that its not my lack of eloquence but your lack of knowing things Vampyro321: hahahhaha CharmingEnigma: if you knew how to put a sentence together in a way in which others than yourself could understand, then you could reasonably be proud CharmingEnigma: and tell me, dearest, do you know what eloquence is? Vampyro321: well its not my fault you dont understand clear WORDS CharmingEnigma: i understand the words, i just don't understand how you string them together and think they make sense that way Vampyro321: I love our conversations CharmingEnigma: I as well Vampyro321: me 3  Please don't IM this poor soul, I'd hate for you to suffer the inadequacies of his playfully scathing reparte (there should be an accent there, but hey, I'm not that computer literate.)
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a while.  Tra la la la la... things are going on...yea, fuck. I have nothing to write.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah.  It is a Sunday evening, Bernie Mac is on and I do not want to watch it.  So, due to the lack of boys online at this time I write about how boy crazy I am at the moment.  Three boys in particular.  Not so much ''crazy'' about, just, on my mind.  Shane, Scott, and Austin.  I just finished a 9 minute conversation with Shane on the cell phone.  This boy has such bad luck in relation to his car...you wouldn't believe.  Just one problem after the other... I promised him sometime later in life I'd buy him a car that will make up for all the troubles he has now.  If I make it big in some area of life I will.  Scott is very good lookin'.  A while back (a few weeks ago...not quite 'a while' but...yah) he said I am the nicest person he knows.  I felt special.  I feel more special because he writes music and has asked if I wanted to hear... yes, of course.  I have called him twice and listened to wonderful A Perfect Circle inspired creations.  *starry eyed sigh* Now the third boy who plagues my thoughts is a dear freshman imbicile.  Austin.  The boy must be afraid of me because it seems he avoids me, as well as blows me off.  There was a debacle today in which he and some of his friends were to help me and my mum move boxes.  Needless to say, he and his friends only managed to help with one chair.  Why must the little beast be ever so cute, yet so damn unenthusiastic about my interest in him.  Does he not see that I want his body?!  Sexy little beast.  Bah!  Boys... oy vey.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday I realized how much I want Austin Saturday I realized how much I don't want him Sunday I made a new friend Today I found my best friend.  Truly.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.  I said GOD DAMN! God damn... god damn.  I went to a rave on Saturday.  It was quite an experience.  And due to my enthusiasm for this new-found enjoyment my former raver friend has bestowed the title "skittle puke" upon me.  I like it.  It may become my raver name....hehe.  Me=nuts.  Almonds in fact..but I'm getting off topic.    So, at this rave, I became entranced.  Complete and utter awe at all that was happening around me.  I am in love with that scene.  Rave Rave Rave!  I was offered muchas drugas.... didn't accept, but now I want to go to one of these so called "parties" totally FUBAR.    My old crush was there.  Austin.  That bastard.  He was fucked up.  Fucked FUCKED  FUCKED  up.  His friend, Oscar, no doubt was as well.  In fact I know he was, he told me he was on Ecstasy, and put his hand on my ass.  Yay!  Austin keeps blowing me off.  It mak-es me sayad.  I really liked talking to him in metal shop last semester.  I miss our flirtation.  Since that rave I can't get him out of my head.  Maddening I tell you!  I want him so badly [AGAIN] and he ignores me.  Must tell him he ith a thexy beatht and I want his nutz.  That isn't the way to get a guy, but I'm damn desperate for him.  I'll try the "Heydoyouwanttogotoamovie?" routine.  Druggy bastard will probably say no again.   I hope he is more empathetic to my feelings for him... or feelings for his dick, as it were....  I'm allowed back in the mall today.  My 30 suspension is up!  I am free to return!  Yeyah!  Another return--> AC has it's claws in my mind flesh and I can no longer function w/o it.  Eep!  The obsession is back with a vengance.  Xanthea is at level 43 and on the rise!  ~~~FO SHO~~~  For the purpose of incriminating myself--> The dewds I got my eye on:  Austin Nick David Michael Craig Alex Scott ...as hopeful always .........guess which one (other than Scott) is not a Freshman. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My virginity has gone missing.....can anyone help me find it?  Where oh where has my innocence gone....Oh where oh where could it be?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bleh, AIM isn't working... I have ideas about why, but I chose not to think about such vindication.... ANYWHO! I done spent the afternoon with my friend Jeremy.  We were supposed to be doing english... well, we tried, and after a milkshake, anime, a bagel, and video games it was not to be. His girlfriend came over, luckily she's my friend too, and we all hung oot.  Twas fun.   Eating my vegetaroon fude.  Iz yummy.  I'm going going back back to Cali Cali.  Scared/Relieved. Bah.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's what I wrote after my wonderous date rape~ yes, that's what it was~  How do I feel? I wanted to save myself, so I would have something new to experience one day and hopefully feel intimate with my chosen person.  But I can't wait anymore and my curiosity has led only to disappointment  I can hear my heart beat though my aching chest.  Regret. It is not always better to regret something you did versus something you didn't do.   Though, I didn't consent, so this was not my doing.  I have nothing to regret.  There should only be blazing fury.  Forgiveness eventually.  I think acceptance has already been achieved.  Not mad at self as much as mad at him.  Not mad at him as much as mad at male bodily functions.    The option to save myself was robbed from me and I am left wondering whether I will ever be wanted for more than mere fucking.  ~~~~~~Two days later~~~~~~>  Somewhat more at peace now.  Inner pain resides and reigns.    I want him to know how hurt I am.  I do not want to blame, together we made a mistake.  I suffer more for the mistake.  I wish the loss could have been as I'd imagined.  With a trusted friend, for more than physical sensation.  I do believe such a thing can exist until much later in life.    I tried not to, but I do desire romance and intimacy.  I want to be more than just a doll.  I want to feel loved and appreciated for so much more than my sex.   I feel alone again.   Am capable of more compassion toward people, but, still do not feel connected.    My desire for connection has clouded judgement one too many times.   I should dedicate and condemn myself to celibacy for the sake of certainty that there is no good outcome of sex.  ~~~~~~~The Next Day~~~~~~>  Today I am worried, more so than the previous.  I fear infection.  I could be carrying any number of putrescent diseases.  I recieve punishment for being indecisive. Why did I let him get away without seeing my tears? The tears of further damage.  Why should it hurt so much? Never knowing true intimacy, this should be considered just another "day" for me.  I can't feel that way when I feel robbed.  If only I could go back in time. Lord, this hurts too much! Stolen from my body was the purity I held dear.  I am defiled. Soiled. Impure and unfit.  I now understand how it feels.   They do take a piece of you they cannot return.  They don't care the way we do. All that is missed is the act.  My poor body. It was not his to USE. None of our bodies are. They need to be punished for this reckless and careless behavior.  Not me, or any of us.  I see how homosexuality is, in a way, much purer. Females are much more pure.   They harbor disease and childish minds, always nagging and begging to get what they want. It's dispicable.  The world orbits the penis, whether I like it or not.  I am here to gratify, but what happens if I don't? What if I do the opposite?  I will find a way and seek revenge for myself and my poor dirty body.  They will pay.  ~~~~~zing!~~~~~> Needless to say, I went a bit kooky.  I've transmogrified to "man-hating psycho bitch"...hi everybody! The revenge I've sought is subtle, but deadly.   A male friend of mine once said the worst thing a girl can do is lead a guy on... well then.  Thanks for my ammo, Richie.    And as for the crushes go, the only remaining is the senior [if ya dun kno who dat iz, read old posts] b/c he's the most supportive person I know at this point in my life.    And to end on a vulgar/peculiar note:  If I had a dick, you'd be sucking it.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     I'm pretty damn hard core!  Fear me!      Dare I type it...I dare:  W00T!!  I rock the feminist sock! hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OOoo, Senior prom was last night.  It makes up for Junior Prom's shittasticness.  Going with a group of friends really does change how much fun one is able to have.  Iz kinduh sad.  But I had a great time.  The thing I want to remember most is the uncomfortable situation which transpired between me, a boy me gusto mucho, and his girlfiend...yes, yes, I am soo clever.  ANYWAY-he comes over to me after I wave to him and he gives me a sideways hug.  He usually hugs me full on, but his girl was right there.  We stand and talk for a moment and she (who's in my chem class-we've spoke minimally) comes over and says my dress looks really pretty.  I'm always a bit dumbstruck when complimented so it takes me a moment to return the compliment.  All I am able to muster is you look really nice tonight. OH THE HUMANITY!!! I feel so bad.  My friend Jana brought my attention to the fact that it took me a moment to return the favor.  And said The Boy wanted to hug me the real way.  I don't mean to have such a crippling crush on the boy!! I wish I didn't.  If only I could forget how much I want him.  I can if it's  newly developed crush, but i've noticed this guy since 7th grade!! Owie, woe is my achy breaky heart. 
     
    
</post>


<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is this pain?&nbsp; It is the pain of my muscles building new tissue... that's what I get for working out for four hours.&nbsp; My woed legs.&nbsp; My tormented back... and ohh! my glutes!&nbsp; Heh heh heh, I am soo very clever.&nbsp;   So there ya go, another, satan help us, another blog!&nbsp;   AAAHHH!!!  Check this out, it's an awesome website, and it's radical music.&nbsp; The Birthday Massacre, goth is not dead!&nbsp; Hackalugie!!!  urlLink http://nothingandnowhere.com/flash3.html  
    
</post>


</Blog>