<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to an  urlLink NCRC  session today, "Writing for Radio." It was alright. Sat with Leah. Afterwards, while I was talking to Sam Power, Leaha left without even saying goodbye. It made me sad, and then I cried. Or would have, had I not been talking to Sam. As it was, I mostly just talked and laughed. But still. In conclusion: "Stauffer on Sports" on Saturday should be pretty neat.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "PS: Anyone else feel like you received a huge kick in the junk last night? And, moreover, like you would've felt the same way regardless of what happened?" -- Jake  Actually I think that the results of this election were exactly as I hoped they would be (and was still predicting they would be till the end). I felt that the Liberals were probably the best party to rule the country, but they needed to be shaken up to stop them from becoming stagnant and lazy (see Sponsorship Scandal, HBC boondoggle and the Alberta PC party). I also liked the NDP's mandate, but feared that if they were ever to get into power that they would murder the economy.  Hopefully the NDP won't kill the Liberal's fiscal pragmatism (which is different from fiscal conservatism) and kill the economy leading to a Conservative victory in the next election.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Perhaps I've just forgotten how elections generally work, but is it normal to be able to cast a ballot without producing ID? 'Cuz it ain't like those cards you get in the mail have your picture or anything.  Not that I care in any particularly meaningful sense; it just seems odd.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You don't support the Democrats. Why should your  urlLink Ketchup ?
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I used to have three Gizmo bobbleheads. Now I have two. Hopefully, I'll soon have only one.  That's right, folks; one of my severely-limited edition Henry "Gizmo" Williams bobbleheads (the unopened one, natch) is up for sale. Some pictures:   urlLink Picture!   urlLink Another picture!   urlLink And another!   urlLink One more!   Note that neither the box nor the bobblehead is fuzzy; that's just my camera. Note also that only about 3000 of these were made, and they're quite valuable. I'm asking $125 for this one. If you're interested, or know anyone who might be, email me. You all know the address(es).
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My roomate has made an interesting  urlLink post  on our house blog... urlLink DISCUSS! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah yes, that age old question: if ever faced with two of nature's most beastly beasts, which would you rather fight, a gorilla or a bear?  After taking a look at this:    But really, what kind of silly question is this? I mean, if Superman, Batman, Robin, and even the Flash can't take on what may very well be "the mightiest beast of all," well, what hope could humankind, no less little ol' me, possibly hold? 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Dave's travel feature!   Woot.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should probably point out that I found the picture below while searching for information regarding some rather good giant panda-related news; namely, that  urlLink there are more of them than previously thought .
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, not to be nitpicky or anything, but are we going to inform our illustrious volunteers of this blog switch? I tried posting something on the old blog, but it don't theoretically exist no more, so should we send petitions an e-mail or something?   As much as I love talking only to you guys, and I don't, those lovely little not-paid members of our society deserve to spread lies and insults just as much as the rest of us, especially since we are sue-free now. But then, you know, maybe you want to keep this elitist--I'm cool with that too.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I also think this is pretty and good.   Pretty good.   I would also like to utter libelous things, however, I currently can't think of anything funny.   The end.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow!  Kristine's got the  urlLink Vue  cover story this week. We should all go and drink little glasses of cheap beer to celebrate.  Now!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I totally heard Rod Fraser has sex with a cat, and that Carl Amhrein has been indited on multiple accounts of tax fraud. And don't even get me started on Daniel Woolf.   I'm not very funny at all.   Also, if for some reason my name appears as "hobs", it's because I don't like giving real information to online sources, but if you can't tell, it's me Dave. ¡YAY!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for setting up the new blog, Mr. Dan.  Now if only I'd had the forethought to dream up a pretty new name like "Thomas," gone done.   Pfft. Leah. So literal. Maybe I'll add an extra "a." 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testes, testes. one, two...  EDIT: I should specify, and I suppose let the cat out of the bag. I blog under the name Thomas. But you all know me as your trusty Hellraiser-in-Chief.  Word!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Test
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, no, that hasn't been confirmed yet, but nevertheless, everyone's favorite Senior News Editor (mostly because she's theoretically the only one we've ever had, thus also making her everyone's least favorite Senior News editor) Cosanna, is currently hospitalized in jolly olde Englande due to some kind of spider bite incurred whilst in Europe. I don't have a lot of details, other than the fact that it probably wasn't a radioactive (or genetically enhanced, for you movie buffs) spider that bit her, but apparently it required some surgery.&nbsp;Fortunately, she's now doing just fine, and will likely be up writing news stories and battling supervillians in no time.   Anyway, perhaps you'd want to pass along your encouraging words, or at the very least some directions for making web fluid.   Can she swing from a thread? Take a look overhead!   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I would think that even omnivores would want to find vegan cosmetics when lipstick is made with things like  urlLink cow brains  and  urlLink cod semen .
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy Shite! According to Aint-it-Cool-News a new live action Transformers movie is go for 2006 and it looks like Steven Speilberg might direct it! Wow!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'll let Roman  urlLink speak for himself .
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember those Heritage Minutes? Well, you can totally  urlLink watch them online . Awesome.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Avast me hearties,  Just a reminder that tomorrow is going to be one glorious day, weather-wise anyway. A balmy 24 degrees, sunny with a chance of awesome, and none of these scattered showers, thunderstorms, tornadoes, and other natural disasters we've been subjected to for the past few days.   Perfect weather to set out a garage sailing.  Hint.  See you all tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember to watch the Euro 2004 final tomorrow at 12:30pm on TSN and CTV. Portugal vs Greece. Who will win? I haven't the foggiest. But I do know that it'll be awesome. I'd suggest some sort of viewing party, but I don't intend to be awake until 12:29pm. So you'll just have to revel in the awesomeness without me, as weird as that sounds.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, you all make ME cry! The hell with you.   But seriously, Leah and I think it would be superb to go garage sailing.  There ismany an awesome garage sale around, and so the plan is to go scrounging for awesomeness next saturday (not this one, the one after).   Anyone wanna come?   No skill testing question required.  Just show up in  pair of pants, shoes, and perhaps with snacks for everyone, and fun will prevail.     
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am happy to report that the demonic influence of the Gateway is continuing to spread.  First off, our good friend Nick Tam spent this week in New Orleans competing at the  urlLink National Scrabble Championship , and he was kind enough to  urlLink blog about it , brilliantly as always.  In other news, our esteemed Director John Ross Prusakowski will serve as a guest host on TEAM 1260 Sports Radio during the morning show on Friday, 13 August. He'll be on the air from 7-9am, if memory serves. While I don't think I even want to know exactly what they were smoking over there when they made this decision, it should be an entertaining couple of hours and you should all tune in if you happen to be awake at that hour for some reason. And if you can't listen live, I'm sure Ross will have dozens upon dozens of tapes that he'll be handing out like candy after the fact.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, as I've been doing all week, I went down to Telus Field to watch  urlLink baseball , specifically Australia versus Japan on this night. Coincidentally, I had recently rediscovered my old " urlLink looking for a Japanese girlfriend " t-shirt. So I was all like "what the hell?" and I tossed it on before heading down to the park.  Now, rather surprisingly--shockingly, one might say--Australia ended up taking the boots to Japan, winning 7-1. But after the game, I decided to station myself behind the Japanese dugout, in hopes of attracting the team's attention and endearing myself to them enough that I could convince one of them to toss me a ball. (The one thing about this tournament that's really angering me thus far is that I've yet to get a foul ball.)  Well, one of the players did indeed spot me right away, at which point she started laughing and pointed me out to one of her teammates, who waved at me and laughed, and it went on like this until the whole team had seen me and my shirt, and got some enjoyment out of the sight (see, sometimes women DO enjoy seeing me!). So at the very least, I was able to cheer them up some after a tough loss.  But did I get a baseball out of the deal? No! After all I did for them, they couldn't even be bothered to toss me a lousy baseball. I tell you, that's the last time I ever cheer for Japan. Which, come to think of it, will probably work out well for them; but it's the principle of the thing. For shame, Team Japan: for shame.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know who I love?  urlLink Dave Barry . Yep,  urlLink Dave Barry  sure is awesome. I wish  urlLink Dave Barry  were here right now.
     

    
</post>


<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So this is a blog eh?   Well oddly enough Dan is the only one to NOT post here yet.    Well I don't have much to say, just thought I'd check it out and see what the deal was.  Memories of the old biolite website are resurfacing, man....  Rule number 1 of blog club is don't tell Adam Sanderman Rule number 2 of blog club is Brad Pitt is hot  and that's all. Man posting on here is lame when you have nothing to say.    LAter  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Why do rap DJ's always have to yell?   It is not uncommon for "Funk Master Flex" to continuously yell "THIS IS FUNK MASTER FLEX BRINGING YOU 60 MINUTES OF FUNK!" on the minute, every minute, during his mixtapes.  However, I had thought he was the only one. That is until I saw DJ Kool last night at the Pete Rock on CL Smooth show. Not only did he yell, but he just yelled random syllables, at least funk master flex had the decency to include an english word. I'd rather hear:  "THIS IS FUNK MASTER FLEX BRINING YOU 60 MINUTES OF ANNOYING YELLING" than "AHHHHHHH! HOLD UP! AAHHHHHHHHHHH HEY YOUR HOT! AHHHHHHHHHH"  I can just imagine what he would be like at your parents house for dinner...   Also, why do only rap DJ's do this? I've never heard someone say:  "THIS IS DJ PRETENTIOUS BRINING YOU 60 MINUTES OF INDIE ROCK!"  -levinski
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome to the blog of the '4 bad men', or whatever you want to call us. Our names are Dan, Matt, Aaron and Chris, and we will be filling this blog with thoughts, tales of exploits, lies, and other general crap that you will either become addicted to or you will find disgusting and childish. Regardless, this is our diary, er...  MAN-JOURNAL.   This wasn't really a great big 'roundtable' discussion item, just something that we decided on doing in passing, and there is a very real chance that it will deteriorate into just Dan and myself or possibly just me as the primary poster.  That is all for now.  -Chris
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I'm disappointed with that dumb bitch Avril.   Okay so Avril Lavigne has a new single out that I find very difficult to completely ignore. But, since I am constantly harassed for being a over-critical prick by the other three trolls that live here, I listened to it, carefully thinking about the lyrics contained within. Perhaps a spoiled, half-retarded nubile like Avril Lavigne could in someway relate to me, a 22 year-old university loser. Alas, no, but I do have some thoughts on her stupid song "Don't Tell Me".   Basically the song is about how Avril doesn't give pony rides to just any flashy guy wearing a cool wallet chain that comes along. While the message in and of itself is admirable, I'm docking her points for being socially irresponsible with her stupid song.  Why? Because her song isn't explicit enough. I don't mean  that  kind of explicit, I mean the kind where you clearly explain exactly what you are talking about. Female sexuality seems to be something that gets explored earlier and earlier in young girls lives (admittedly, that might be partly because I'm getting older), I think that someone like Avril Lavigne has an obligation to be a role model to that captive audience of 11-16 year old girls she has. Now, that said, I don't think a skank like Britney Spears should have to do that, but that is only because Avril has vowed to be  different , or Anti-teeny bopper, which, I feel by definition, forces her to have a strong social conscience.   At the same time, I'm not saying that Avril can't write and say whatever she wants in her crappy songs, but if she is going to explore an issue, she should do it clearly.  Anyway, it took me a long time to realize that the song is about refusing to have wonton sexual relations, and if it took me that long, how long do you think it will take a thirteen year old girl who giggles when she hears the word 'testicles'?   I'm not saying that the song should be called "Penises are the spears of the Devil", but seriously, her song lyrics shouldn't be cloaked in mystery like the fucking Nosferatu. I know a lot of parents would be somewhat upset with a more black and white sexual description, but if I were a parent, I'd be a little pissed off about the level of coyness that she is approaching the topic with. It's one thing for parents (who when you are 10-20, are not cool) to talk to their kids about sex, but it's quite another when your role models renforce approximate views put forward by your parents.   In conclusion, Avril should have to pay for all the teen pregnancies for everyone that owns her new CD.  -Chris
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Old Guys with 10,000+ prog record collections == Drum breaks!  For anyone who doesn't know what a break is, it's a vague definition but a lot of people consider it as a portion of a song with distinguished characteristics from the rest. Many people may argue, but that isn't the point of this thread, for the most part those involved in "digging" call them 'breaks'.  Rap is all about stealing. You take a certain "break" on a record and sample it, loop it, fuck with it, add some drums, add a baseline... boo-ya track is made. The talent comes in two parts: 1) finding the records, and 2) flipping that shit so you can't recognize it (i.e. so other break collectors can't be like "that was wack, he just straight looped Eugene McDaniels, laaaame... Or something equally ridiculous).  I went to this one guy who had a huge prog rock collection and spotted two things:  1) Rare Earth - One World 2) Grand Funk - all the girls in the world Beware!!!  Both albums have wicked awesome drum breaks. Download the song "I just want to celebrate" by rare earth and wait until the end for an awesome drum break!  woo!  Levin == happy
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yep
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So it's a Saturday morning, and I'm working with the Living Comic Encyclopedia KYLE!  A regular customer who is also a huge comic nerd came in, and for the last half an hour they have been discussing comics, including a discussion on their comic bag taping philosophies.  One piece or two?  Tape straight or diagonal?  Which finger do you use to open?     CRAZY!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Yep that is about all I have to say about that.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know if that title was:  a) A clever line. b) A reference to  White Men Can't Jump  c) or just stupid.  Anyways, the deal with Mona is that she's the one everyone notices. Can you name any of the others? She has also been there for a long time.   I would also like to get a hold of the guy who did the "Pick up the phone" tv infomercial. That was marketting genius... you find me someone who hasn't heard that.  Dan, I'll compile a small list of cool questions to ask the dude, maybe I'll do it up or something for the gateway, being that I'll be a student in september.  "on the real, all you crab n****s know the deal" - nas
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      but I don't really see what all the fuss is about. Just looks like any other sleezy back page See ad.  As for the idea for interviewing the guy who invented Pong it is a good idea. As far as I know the only people who have done that are the guys at EGM (they also did the guy who invented Tetris, the guy who invented Adventure and the guy who did the ET video game for the Atari). So it is kinda played out but might still work on a local level.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhhh, with some cutting-edge, hardcore computer haxing I think I figured out how to get my user name when I post.  WHEW.  For my profile I did an image search for bolding on google, check out my awesome picture.    Matt
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Everyone grab a SEE magazine, go to the back and turn 1 or 2 pages back.  Near the bottom you will see an ass. Not just any ass, but the ass belonging to Mona. Mona has been in the back-pages since I first picked up a SEE magazine. I don't know when that was, but it was some length of time ago.  I would like to meet Mona, or perhaps interview her and see what it's like to have your ass in the back-pages of SEE for longer than 5 years.  Also, this is for Dan, an interesting idea for an interview would be the guy who created PONG. Perhaps it's a played idea, but I've never seen an interview with him before (not that I've looked). But it might be cool to see what his opinions are on games, and if he ever expected the gaming industry to be this big and what was going on in his mind when he made the game.  C++ hurts my back.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well here I was sitting at work, sick, and listening to Cotton Eyed Joe on the new Joe FM and I thought, hey lets see what new crap is on the blog.  ....Man you guys talk alot.  Firstly:  Aaron, the reason gyms have mirrors everywhere is so people working out can see themselves ALL THE TIME.  This lets them see how fat they still are, and if they're fat, they'll come back to the gym.  That was the gym gets more cash, it's all about the cash.  Oh, and your baby....it's going to take more then a few games of badminton to get rid of that thing.    Secondly: Chris,  the buildings on campus are UGLY intentionally.  I mean if you're walking through campus and you see a nice building like ETLC then you see an ug building like the Butterdome it will mindfuck you SO HARD that you will bomb the exam you were on the way to write.  THEN you have to take the course again which means more cash for the school, it's all about the cash.    INTERESTING NOTE: The above was written twice as John erased the first draft.  While writing the first draft and listening to Joe FM I though "man I should mention that I'll probably hear Cotton Eyed Joe today" then before I wrote the second draft I did.  Also, some chick just gave me a 12-pack of Diet Coke with Lime.  WTF??  Thirdly: Dan, you mentioned that you didn't have much money and you shouldn't of bought Samurai Jack (or something like that).  Well I think you solved your own problem....Samurai Dan.    Fourthly: Aaron, you DO talk too much about Rap on this Blog.  When I am King Rap will be first against the wall.  ...whatever that means.   So, when work is slow, there is a danger that this may become my Live Journal for work.  So I'll say things like "fuckshit here comes super meek heroclix kid.  This kid is so meek it sounds like he's going to cry everytime he talks.  I just want to punch him in his stupid meek face!!!"  Fuckin kids.    Anyway I should do some "actual work" I'll bring each of you a can of diet coke with lime....though the more I stare at them, the more worried I get.  If they're poisned or have syringes in them I'll let you know first.    Later kids.   MAtt  PS Unlike Aaron, I don't know how to change my username so this isn't from Chris.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      he's a fanboy.   Get him, Steve-Dave! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So they have started filming a new  Hitchhikers Guide to the Galaxy  movie (for those who don't know, it's a very famous, really funny, Sci Fi novel by the now deceased Douglas Adams).  The particular story has a really great character. That of Ford Perfect, an alien to earth who grew accustom too well to England's pub scene. According to IMDB they have casted rapper  Mos Def  as Ford Prefect.  Perhaps it won't be such an issue to those who are not familiar with Mr. Def, however placing him in this movie will take me right out of the movie. As every time I see Ford Prefect I will be thinking "hey, there's mos def". As the hitchhiker series is one of my favorite books, you can see why this would anger me, or even you.  end.  For more information: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0371724/
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      From my office all day, I look at some of the most atrocious architecture that the University of Alberta has to offer. The chief eyesore that stands out is a large yellow building that most of you affectionately refer to as the ‘Butterdome’. As someone who has sat on a committee that approves buildings for the U of A, the very fact that the approved color for this building is YELLOW puzzles me. Usually, at least in my experience, the company presenting their plan for the building will be forced to justify most cosmetic aspects, such as entranceways, window locations and, of course, color.   “Well, seeing as though this will be such a large building near such a major roadway, we feel that the building should be as yellow as possible, as to draw the eye.”  I don’t think that the building draws the eye as much as it does molest it.   On days when the sun isn’t shining off the Butterdome and sending my retina straight to Hell, I can see a set of buildings of mismatching shape and color called “Lister Center”. The Lister Center is our main undergraduate residence at the U of A, as you all know, and it is also the soul regret I have of my undergraduate education. When I was in first and second year, I thought that living in residence would be awesome because I could drink beer all day and then make out with all the homesick farmgirls and lonely (read: horny) Swedish exchange students on my floor, of which there would be many. Of course, this would be at the expense of my education, but who cares. If any of you follow Futurama, they once had an episode where Bender became human and all he did was drink beer, eat hot dogs, dance and make out with hot women, often all at the same time while the song “Do the Conga” by the Miami Sound Machine played in the background. I thought that living in residence would be a lot like that.   That is, I did until very early last year. Everything I thought about residence was basically wrong except the drinking part. And even then I was wrong about that, because I severely underestimated the scale that activity occurs at. That includes the stuff about academic performance (students in residence at the U of A, at least, have higher GPA’s on average than non-residence students). However, because you spend so much time with the same people who are going through the same thing at the same time as you, you build bonds with people that are unlike most others. I think that residence is a very good idea, and I will be forwarding it as a recommendation to the mother of my illegitimate children in the form of a note in the envelope carrying the cheque for my court enforced child support. Unfortunately, that skazz will probably blow the money on weed and use the note for rolling papers (City of God, anyone??).   But honestly, I do think that is worthwhile to live in residence for some of your university career, hopefully at the beginning, when you have some growing up to do.  Don’t get me wrong, I wouldn’t trade my (many) years at the U of A for anything, and only every now and then do I wish that I had maybe gone to Queens or some other school. They apparently have a female white supremacist group at Queens. Damn near anything goes out in Kingston.   Anyway, while I’m not a person of a lot of concrete regrets, I suppose the whole ‘never living in rez’ thing kind of irks me because it something that I CAN’T do anymore. There are lots of things I know I will never do, such as have sex on (or with) a donkey, own a donkey or go donkey racing with Sting. I know I will never do these things because of my own personal limitations (additionally, I have no desire to do any of these things, save one. You can decide for yourself which.). However, these three activities certainly exist as real and viable options, in that there is no administrative statute limiting the time frame in which I can participate in these activities. And it is just that, I’m not sorry that I miss out on meeting a new bunch of people, but I am sorry that I will never be able to do that, realistically or otherwise. It’s a fairly idiosyncratic concern on my behalf, but it’s difficult to forget about when I spend the better part of my day with the Lister complex staring me in the face, taunting me and my unfulfilled life.   I’m afraid I’m going to have to burn the buildings down.  PS - Next time you are driving down the highway, and you are listening to ‘Money for Nothing” by Dire Straits, make sure to punch the gas really hard at the 1:36 mark. You’ll be glad you did.      
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mad Props to the levinator for figuring out how to post using his own user name. Oh wait there was some other point to that last post. Something about rip or rap or hippity hop or something like that. Whatever.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes gangster rappers spit really poignant lines. I was listening to this Ill Bill guy, he's part of a group called Non Phixion which I really like. Usually their stuff is pretty underground gangster, with some CIA conspiracy shit tossed in here and there (see the song "I Shot Regan"). Anyways, he has this line in this one song that has really stuck in my head the past couple of days:   violence is more american than apple pie and soul train baseball, nickle plated nines and cocaine.  Ill Bill - American History X  It is for this reason that Nas was so famous for illmatic. His abillity to attatch a sublte element of poetry to writting about guns, violence, and drugs. I see alot of Nas in Ill Bill, especially with this next verse off the same song:   And the older generation's no better Matter of fact they worse They oughta know better These greedy motherfuckers trade blood for oil An American graveyard on another man's soil Makes no sense The Roman Empire in the present tense Murder for corporations that they represent Whether Democrat or Republican The same scumbag government Where scumbag brains are running shit   I promised myself I wouldn't talk about rap too much on the blog, but I thought those were some pretty good lyrics from a gangster rapper. Ill Bill's solo LP dropped on tuesday, it's called "What's Wrong With Bill?" I suggest you listen to it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah just bought the first season of Samurai Jack which I can't afford. Radular!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What I don't understand about the gym are mirrors. Wait, I guess I should mention I started going to the gym, but not to work out, that would be totally homoerotic. I go to the gym to play "badmington". Why? Because I'm terrible at all things that involve "movement".  Mirrors. You use them to look at yourself, or you put one behind you and one in front of you and say "INFINITY!". However, I don't know why they are all over the gym. It's not like you are going to see the fat leave your body, nor will you see your muscles grow.  Also, have you ever looked at yourself while your working out? Three words: Red Old Men. I don't know how they can keep concentrating with blood rushing to their grimaced faces. I also try to avoid all eye contact with myself, I cannot trust a person who continually to stares me in the face every time I see them.  What they should really do at the gym is put up pictures of really hot people and have captions beside them that say:   "If you do this 5 times a week for the next 4 years you MIGHT look like this! Buy Powerade!"  But back to the title. I have played three games of badmington, and my baby is still there, when will it go away... :(  - Leibniz  ps - This spell check sucks, it made me replace "Levinski" with "Leibniz"... which is now my new name.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey this is dan's first post. See how it says posted by Dan at the bottom there. That is cuz' I'm at least 15% more awesome than the rest of the stooges in the 'witz.  --dan
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Quick post to test the comments.    Right now I'm gonna throw it down for my Anna Grimsrud, it's her birthday today. Happy Birthday, Anna.    Oh, and it was Matt's birthday on Saturday. He turned 40.   -Chris 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       BBC's "The Office" and how I can relate to it...   On Saturday night, after fighting a very short losing battle with a combination of 250ml of a Mountain Dew imitation drink and the good-as-an-idea-but-bad-as-a-drink moonshine imitation Everclear (95% Alcohol), I had the distinct pleasure of seeing a few episodes of a show called 'The Office' that airs on the BBC. This show is about the goings on in the office of a British paper manufacturer and involves a number of 'characters' that we can all 'relate to' (ie, the stiff I-need-to-feel-important-when-I-clearly-am-not person, the 'I don't care about my job' type person, etc, etc.). But, the show pretty much revolves around the boss character, a man named David Brent. He is a boss who wants all his employees to like him, so he keeps a forcefully relaxed office environment where he pretty much makes up rules regarding what is and what is not cool arbitrarily. At the same time, he is not funny. Not by any long stretch of the imagination. While this 'in and of itself' is not bad, he has no idea that he isn't funny.   I know a couple of people like this. None of the people I would expect to read this blog of course, mostly old coworkers and former acquaintances. Basically, the process for these kinds of people goes something like this:  1.) Attempt at making a joke 2.) Look for approval of joke 2a.) Slight heartbreak when the realization that the joke bombed and in turn, they are not funny.  3.) They stuff the feelings mentioned in 2a into the back of their brain into the 'denial' section of their psyche, where they ferment into 'anger and self-loathing', only to explode on 10 years later when their 2 year old kid gets chocolate ice cream all over it's face..  This kind of behavior is almost unbearable to watch, mostly because I hate seeing people embarrass themselves, and while I have wanted to validate these people, I just can't. I just want to duck my head into sand and pretend like it never happened. It's kind of like when a little puppy shits on your rug, right in front of you and then looks at you like they just fetched a ball for the first time: You want to smack them, but you know that they don't know any better, and so you just smile and let the dog on it's way, then you clean up the poop.  Beyond that, the boss character in 'The Office' was a lot like my old boss at HMV. When I worked at HMV, the first general manager got canned, and everyone was really happy about it, because he was a class A douchebag, his name was Jerry, and I hated him. Every time I saw him, I wanted to punch him in the stupid face.  So, after getting a sizable severigns package, he got kicked out the door and a new fellow, named Ian came in. Ian was super cool for the first month, and then he was such a total asshole that I wanted Jerry back, even if it meant I had to put up with his stupid shit.  The major difference, I learned, between Jerry and Ian, was that Ian would sell his own mother if it meant that head office would give him a raise. The major incident that made me hate Ian was where he cut hours for 30 people buy one third so that he could get a bonus.  Basically at HMV, if your store makes a sales target, your employees get a 5% bonus, each. However, management gets a sales target bonus as well as a substantially larger operational target bonus. In order to meet your operational target, you have to be able to get X amount of sales with X amount of operational targets. Anyway, Ian figured out, with three weeks to go until the bonus deadline, that he had met the sales target, but not the operational target. So, in order to meet the operational target, he cut the hours of 30 people buy one third and viola!: Ian gets a $6000 bonus.   I know that three of those people who took hour cuts got THIRD jobs to keep from being kicked out of their apartments for that month. All the while Ian tried to be buddy-buddy with the staff, acting like he was just one of the guys/gals.  While Jerry was totally bipolar, he would have never sold out his employees for a flatscreen TV. This David Brent character on "The Office" seems to be the same sort of person as Ian. Totally spineless around employees, but a total predator in his own office.  But, I think that you should check out 'The Office'. It is really funny, but half the time I wanted to turn away so that I didn't feel bad for the boss character. Matt and I spent a lot of time cringing at the antics of the David Brent character.  -Chris
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey Chris look at this, Rozenhart is trying to pull a fast one on you.        urlLink ">Check it right here.   .  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I listed Console Gaming as an interest on my resume once.   Of course I was applying for a job at Electronics Boutique.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      *Looking at Aaron’s resume*  ME: Aaron, are you really going to hand out resume’s that list “Console System Gaming” as a hobby?  AARON: Yeah, man… you never know when a potential employer is a gamer. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2 years ago I worked for Dr. Erik Talvila in the math department for 1 summer... he forever changed my life.  I first met Erik when he taught me the calculus of complex numbers. He was an awesome teacher, albeit somewhat weird. The first thing I noticed where his shirts. He had one shirt that was solid bands of different colours... all the colors. He also had a shirt that had  skeletons having sex with each other and a banner that said "sex is bad to the bone" .  He would also stop the lecture to do random things. He once stopped the lecture to say " If I could live my life over I would have gone pee before I came here... I gotta go ". In my friends class he randomly stopped and said " Pink Floyd - Dark side of the moon is such a good album... I'll be right back, I'm gonna go get it! " He then went to his office and came back and put in the CD and the whole class listened to pink floyd.  Did I mention he looks like this:     His resume is awesome, it has the following two lines:  "Aside from math I enjoy mountain climbing and mountain biking, although not at the same time. I also collect board games"  "I am a very 3-dimmensional person, but I'm working hard at becoming n-dimmensional"  I was recently talking to him about graduate studies (I have kept in contact with him). I then mentioned to him that I finally listened to Dark Side of the Moon. His only reply was:   Dark Side is one of the all time best albums. Welcome to the club man.   Erik 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Slipknot is an interesting band. Interesting in the same way that a severed head pearched on the top of a stick in the middle of the jungle is interesting. It makes you gag and it scares you, but at the same time, you can't help but wonder about the circumstances surrounding the eventual desecration of that particular head. Add to that, they have a legion of fans that hate their parents and love whining on the internet (yes, I understand the irony of making a comment like that on a blog. *YoU dOn'T KnOw My PaIn!!!!1!!*) about said parents. I'm trying to say that they're stupid, but in a really nice way.  When I worked at a record store, I learned very quickly to seperate the fans of a band from the band itself, which admittedly, can be difficult to do. I think that the best example of this is the band Tool. Tool has managed, at least in this city, to garner legions of total as fans, all of whom hate their father for not buying them a pony when they were little. I went to seen Tool shows, and the thing that strikes you the most is that everyone in the audience is sitting and just listening, because that is all the music is really good for.  EXCEPT  the 150+ people right in front of the stage who are all moving around like live bullets are being shot into the crowd. These are the people who have the Tool patch on their clothing and bark at you on Whyte Ave. Off-hand, I cannot think of a band who's fans represent them worse than the vocal fans of the band Tool. The actual band and their music is actually quite sophisticated and very, very good.  I suspected as much with Slipknot when they first arrived on the scene. Oddly enough, this is not the case. However, every time they put out an album, I actually give it a listen. I don't do this for most bands, but I can't help shake the feeling that they could be a really worthwhile band if they just didn't have their heads so far up their asses. With a band like Slipknot, you don't need to listen to it 2wice or more, the band really lacks nuance and subtlety. Anyway, Slipknot, a band of 9 people (including three drummers and percussionists and three guitarists) always amazes me in how underwhelming they are. Which amazes me, because on paper, Slipknot looks like the roughest band ever. They wear masks, throw up on stage, smash shit, hurt themselves, and have THREE drummers.  Yet, it never sounds like that. Every time I listen to one of their CD's, I can't help but think that they make metal that your mom can feel good about. Seriously, I've heard 9 piece Jazz combos that kick my ass more than Slipknot. I dunno. I just can't stand it sometimes, a band with three drummers should be really, really amazing, and Slipknot is the definition of 'fucking awful'. A band with three drummers should really be able to kick your ass, but Slipnot sounds like a .  So why is this? It's a gimmick. It allows kids who aren't actually angry to validate themselves as such. I bet you that the same kids who are fanatical Slipknot fans are the same ones who rush to set the table when their mom asks and get their parents heart shaped cards on Mothers and Fathers day. Beyond that I bet these kids are all of the following: White, in a two parent family, a good student, living in suburbia and probably listen to their Slipknot in their Red or Green Pontiac Sunfire. The gimmick is that you are a angry kid, and the music lets you play that part, but when you get home, you're Mommy's little girl/boy, except you're wearing black eyeliner. It's kind of like 'Work-At-Home Rebellion'. You do it whenever you have the time.   I remember distinctly working a midnight release of Slipknot. No one wore a mask. No one beat anyone else up. There was no ritual killing. Everyone lined up really nicely and everyone was really polite, and it was quite clear who came with their mom, who had their mom pick them up outside and the other kid could drive.   This post is long. It's long because I didn't like the way that this post was going so I tried to save it by writing more. I think my posts will be slightly more concise from now on.   -Chris  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      All of the bottom is true, except that Aaron isn't home enough to actually make that assessement.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      He eats risotto and perogies as too.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Life begins.   Chris gets out of bed much in the same way a sloth climes out of the water. The first item on his agenda is harassing Aaron. Let me list the ways in which he can do this:  1) Monkey wakeup. 2) Rape him. 3) Threaten to slap his girlfriends tits. 4) Throw crackers into his room.  After doing one or more of items 1-4, he will weasel his way downstairs to put on some clothes (I should have mentioned that at this point he was dressed solely in a bathroom and would constantly attempt to show his penis).   At this point Chris will be in his room looking at his laptop screen ignoring everyone. Any question you ask him will be answered by "no" followed by the soft, subtle sound of a cracker being slowly eaten.  Chris then goes to work. He likes working with hacks because it allows him to argue about pointless shit all day and get payed for it. He especially likes "showing people up" in board meetings which have questionable agendas. He will occasionally refer you to the minutes of his last meeting to which he said something remarkably witty about another hack clone.  After a hard day at work, message boarding, being the man around the office, and consuming a large quantity of crackers, Chris will come home. He will first go to the cupboard and grab some more crackers. After this if I happen to be home he will do to me:  1) Monkey wakeup. 2) Rape me. 3) Threaten to slap my girlfriends tits. 4) Throw crackers into my room.  Chris sometimes grows tired of harassing me and will often go and watch CI.  In this mode, Chris is much like the morning. All his answers will be "no" and he constantly consumes crackers. Really the only difference between evening Chris and morning Chris is the excessive consumption of crackers (sometimes he will eat those pink waffers as a cracker substitute, probably to build up his blood sugar level to counter all the salt).  After about 4 hours of doing "stuff", Chris will retire to his bedroom and go on the internet.   Scientists have marveled over his sleep patterns for years, however, only one thing can be concluded. Chris stays up really late. Every night.   Actually, Chris never sleeps, it is my theory that every night when he is on the internet in his room he dies. Yes, Chris dies 365 days a year. Chris dies everynight. He has to be resurrected each morning, which is the only reasonable assumption to account for his infinite bad mood.   And hence, a day in the life of Chris is over.  Life ends.  # of crackers eaten = 20-30 # of times Aaron raped = 2-3
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       EVERYTHING  that Aaron owns smells like cold semen.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      you think that's bad? One time I was awoken by a large, burly man, pulling my arm up and down screaming like a harpy.  After further analysis I found out that was called "Monkey Wakeup".  I'd have a cold shower over "monkey wakeup" any day.  - levinski
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Who's got em?  We all have one?  C'mon, don't be shy!  For example:  This morning I went to have a shower, and it was cold....so I turned up the heat as high as it would go...it was cold.  And I was already cold, so after the cold shower I was worried that our hot water heater had broken on us.  If that was the case we would of needed to jury-rig some sort of coal driven steampowerd hot water ma-jigger operated by Aaron of course.  I mean I've taken last place in the shower que before, but it's never been that cold.    So I'm telling Dan about this when Chris galumph's out of bed and lumbers up stairs.  So I ask Chris if he'd had a shower and I explain the situation.....  Now for those of you who have had limited exposure to Chris in a home setting he is border-line narcoleptic.  After a ...days work, or maybe a days sleep, he'll become prone to falling asleep.  In front of the TV, computer, standing, you name it.  SO IT TURNS OUT that this morning Chris had gotten up to have a shower.  He walked into the bathroom, turned on the shower, and while it was warming up, went back to his bedroom and fell asleep.  When he woke up there was no hot water, and I was the one to find out.    I thought that was pretty funny.    MAtt
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In a very Janet Lo (Type A) move, I had a whiteboard installed into my office today. Why? So I could make lists. To-do lists. Lists of dates. As well, charts.   For those of you who don't know, damn near every time I walked into Janet's office last year, she had some kind of new list on her whiteboard. She even had the nicest whiteboard markers, making her a full-fledged whiteboard ninja.   However, I put the whiteboard high enough that Janet cannot reach it, so that she will not be able to make lists when she comes to visit me. Yet, I can use it, because I'm about a foot taller than Janet 'I-can-fit-in-an-eMac-box' Lo.  Actually, the reason I had this stuff put up in my office today is because A.) it makes me look really busy and B.) because I didn't want to spend the extra money on Art for that wall. I have only one clear wall now that will fit two medium sized peices of art, which will be much cheaper than the original Million dollars it was going to take to make my office look all respectable like.   You see, I have my full name and middle initial on my nameplate outside my door, which pretty much cements that I will have to get this art framed to boot.   Woe is me.    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Aaron will be performing sexual favours on Matt, Dan and of course, myself in order to pay his rent, which he cannot afford since blowing his money on crack cocaine, betting against the Harlem Globetrotters and wonton computer purchases!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If everything goes as planned, by tomorrow (Tuesday) afternoon I will be the proud owner of a 15" G4 powerbook.  go levin!  ps - fat beats pending.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not much nerdy to report today, but at one point a baby farted really loudly.     Matt
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So Matt do you have the ability to watch the live tourny at work?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow the script writer of the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy movie interviewed himself. Cool. Click above to see.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Nertz to you Stalin, it's the Clash of the Century!   The one, the only, THE BRITISH BULLDOG HIMSELF...  Winston Churchill!!  VERSUS  The Berlin Benny, the guy who likes shit on his tummy...  HITLER!!!!    They've met once already, and Winston hammered the kraut home, but Adolf is back for  BLOOD  and maybe a people lamp.    WHO'S IT GOING TO BE!?  WHO WILL WALK AWAY WITH  TOTAL WORLD DOMINATION!!   STAY TUNED!  *now taking bets* 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The culprits of this crime have been stopped. Acting on a tip from Janet Lo, who mentioned that she could identify the handwriting on the note in the comments of the post where I posted the randsom note, police were able to identify the kidnappers as the following two people:     These two are known as Anna "Knuckles" Grimsrud and Mike "Michael" Horler. The police immediately acted on the tip, and surrounded their home. Sensing that they were trapped and that this was the end, they erupted from the house, guns blazing. They were both taken down in a hail of gunfire, rendering their corpses unidentifiable except for the print from Grimsrud's pinky finger (which was found 8 blocks away) and matching the DNA from one of Horler's hair with a sperm donation he made earlier in the summer when he didn't have a job and times were desperate. Horler often times referred to himself as a "Sperm Philanthropist"  When police entered the house, they had found that Jerry's eletrical cord had been cut and glass had been smashed. Jerry is dead. Jerry never wanted to do anything to anyone except illuminate back yards and front porches, so people could see how well done their BBQ'ed steak was or so that they wouldn't trip on their way to the garage. Why these two horrific people would ruin a life so innocent is truly a sign of our times. How could these two deprived minds ruin something so pure?   Anna and Mike: May you both burn in hell.    R.I.P Jerry: 15 May 2004 - 25 May 2004   In lieu of flowers, please buy us something from our registry at Home Depot.    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just before I read that Dan came home. I knew something was wrong when I noticed he shaved his moustache. He couldn't even look me in the eye and he kept stuttering all his words. I've never seen Dan nervous in my life.  After seeing Dan I went back to the scene and found the following item:     Perhaps one of the perpetrators put this in the wheel of his bike to make the menacing "clicking" sound.  I'm really scared... 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sorry to make you worry Aaron, me and Chris have been at the hospital.  We went to make the drop off, not expecting much, but there was Jerry waiting at the bus stop, alone.  I thought something was amiss, but Chris was so overjoyed to see Jerry that he ran up to the bus stop....  Just as he was going to give Jerry a hug, Jerry jumped up and smashed his head into Chris face!  Then the kidnappers grabbed the cash and Jerry, jumped onto their bikes and took off...  At first we wern't too sure what happened...but then we realized... Jerry has Stockholm syndrome.  We don't know what to do, Dan is freaking out, and Chris...Chris isn't really saying anything anymore.    I don't know what to do, I'm running out of ideas...I just want him back.    Matt
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I havn't been home in a couple days, but when I was dropped off at the bustop described in the ransom note I noticed a small pool of dried blood and some shards of glass.  Noone is home right now, neither are you guys answering your phones. I hope you are slacking off at work and will see this post. Please let me know what is up.  - aaron
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The following was left in our mailbox today:     We don't know who has done this, but please! PLEASE! we will pay! Don't hurt Jerry! You will get your money, you  MONSTERS !   If anyone has any information regarding the wearabouts of Jerry, please let us know! We are so worried about him. Please!   Praying with each passing day,  Chris 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I post sad news...Jerry, the lovable midget faux gaslight, has been kidnapped.  As of right now we don't know if this is a ransom situation, or meerly a malicious abduction.  Jerry hasn't been with us for long, but it feels like he's been in our hearts forever.  We miss you Jerry.  To those of you that knew Jerry we ask for your support in this time of hardship.  To those of you that are responsible for taking Jerry from us we ask only for his safe return.  Jerry was like a son to Chris, and I know he feels the most pain inside.  Please, if anyone has any information on the whereabouts of Jerry or those who took him come forward, you will be saving five lives.    The following is a projection of what Jerry might look like today  urlLink Jerry 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HA! The band that I hate more than any other band, except for one (KISS) has broken up. That hairy-chested guido singer and the group of vagina pilots that we know as "Creed" is done. It's over. HA!  My hate for Creed and their brand of Jesus-infused cock-rock started many years ago when I heard them for the first time, at Edgefest. I was so disgusted that I tossed a bottle of sunscreen at the stage. It hit the singer right in the face. Initally, I felt bad, but after their second ablum came out, I felt as if he had finally gotten me back for that toss. For me, Creed is like second hand smoke; I didn't have any real control over it lingering in the air, but it killed me just a little bit on the inside everytime I was around it.   Working at HMV didn't make my hate for Creed any easier. Espeically in the 3 months where the manager thought it would be a really good idea to BLAST the music as loud as we could to get 'the vibe' going. Creed came out just around that time. Plus, people would always ask me if I liked Creed, and I would always tell them the truth and then they would get mad. I should note that Creed t-shirts only come in sleeveless.   Alright. Now hopefully the members of KISS will start dying. Then again, they are fairly entertaining, what with trying to sell you "Kiss Kaskets" and making comments about how Islam is a 'disgusting' religion. Yeah. Keep making comments like that, Gene, and you'll end up in your own KISS Kasket. GAH! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Kill Bill vol 1 & 2 are together and will go on tour in theaters. Cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Google (who owns blogger and blogspot) has ads which are context sensitive, their computers scan each page for information and then present context sensitive ads for that page. For example if I started mentioning Star Trek or StarTrek or DS9 or Enterprise over and over and over again, like this:  Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise, Star Trek, StarTrek, DS9, Enterprise  the top of the page ads would probably show something relating to Star Trek. The hitler ad came because you talked about Hitler.  -- dan
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why is the Blog trying to sell me Mein Kampf?   MAtt
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Don't worry Levin, just go into the registrar's office and they'll print you off a copy of your degree on the dot matirix printer.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I didn't go to my convocation...  *gasp*   SCANDALOUS! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Man, I don't know why, but I keep drinking the stuff.  It's terrible, but I still drink it.  WHY>???
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, my lame Hichhiker's post has stayed on the top of the main page for four days. You guys all suck.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright. So, at the house, there has been not only a near screaming match over whether 15-inch Apple Powerbooks would be created under a Communist or even a 'Democratic Socialist' state. However, there has also been talk about a far less idiotic and more practical kind of politics: Our own Federal election.   I think this federal election is kinda of silly. It's not the football game that the US election is and even though it is beginning to be characterized by personal attacks, there have been no big surprises and to be perfectly frank, it's kind of boring. Not that the election should be entertaining, per se, but I think that it should at the very least, capture our attention, no? The major issue that the Conservative Party is bringing forward is Accountability. The major issue that the Liberal Party is bringing forward is Canadian Identity. The NDP's main message is that they REALLY REALLY REALLY WANT YOUR VOTE.... "PLEASEEE! PLEASSSEEE! COME ON! FUCK!" Of course the Bloc are pushing for a strong unified Canada. oh...wait.  I find this sad because last summer was one of the most exciting times in Canadian policital history. With the decriminalization and possible legalization of pot, more positive steps made for the legalization of gay marriage, and the rejection of joining the US in their authorized-by-a-Ouija-board war on Iraq, Canada was beginning to look like one of the most progressive nations on earth, especially when you compare us to our Butter-Troll neighbor to the south.  So, what the fuck happened? This shit is boring! The only issue of the above three that has been brought up by the major parties is defense, all the other ones have gotten lip-service, at least from what I have seen. This is a classic case of everyone taking a safe road, trying to get you to vote for the party's values and not the policies. I'm really hoping for a minority government so we can have another election in 6 months or so and maybe that one will actually be GOOD.  Anyway, at our house, Dan and I have been having a mini-argument about me voting for the Green party. So, more for Dan's edification rather than anyone else's I will outline why I am voting for the Green Party.  1.) I believe that the three major parties in Canada have gone unchallenged long enough and that once the opportunity for another party to enter the fray of Canadian politics, the voters should invite them in. I think that this is a win-win for everyone. You vote, they get a seat. If they totally shit the bed, you don't vote for them again and pass them off as a bunch of dreadlocked hippies. If they work well, make some good changes then Canadians will start to vote for them and maybe they will gain a little bit of power down the road.   2.) For the most part, I don't think that the Green Party is a party of politicians. I think they are normal citizens who just want to see a change or two. I like that alot. I think that is more or less the way that our electoral system was first envisioned and I think that it can still work that way.  3.) For the issues I care about, the Green party is dead on. Pro-Gay marriage, a new outlook on health care and responsible foreign policy are what I'm looking for a party to represent me right now and the green party is the only party that addresses these issues to my satisfaction.   I know that I am taking a big chance with the Green party, and maybe I'm 'throwing away' my vote, but elections are about being heard and expressing an opinion. A vote in favor of the Green party is essentially a vote against the other three (or 4 if you live in Quebec), which is what I want to do with my vote. Hopefully, if the parties lose a seat or two (collectively. I have hopes, but I'm not an idiot) they'll sit up, take notice and maybe make an effort to distinguish themselves outside of basic political attributes that I expect every party to have, regardless of ideology.  On a side note, Metallica's drummer had to skip out of a show not half an hour before he had to go on stage. My guess is that since he's a scared little girl (or at least the size of one), he didn't want to play any Rock 'n' Roll. But, the drummer from Slipknot filled in for the majority of the show. That's intense. Metallica sucks, and so does Slipknot, but Slipknot's drummer is AWESOME, apparently. This guy, with not even 15 minutes notice, just got up and played drums for another band that he has had no experience playing with. Holy fuck! That's wicked.   Ta-ta.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, so this morning I'm on my way to work, and i go to put hte roof of my car up and SNAP, one of the handles that locks the roof down snaps off, so the passenger side of my roof isn't locked down.  IT sucks because i'm sitting at work right now watching rain slowly fill up my car.  FUCKSHITFUCK   matt
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I'm sitting up here listening to Levin argue about the merits of Communism versus Capitalism with Chris and Matt, and I want to gouge my brain out. I'm sure after there done jacking each other off for two hours accomplishing nothing they can be all angry at each other and stuff. Can't we just agree that both Capitalism and Communism are fucked up and move on? Holy Shit all this arguing is USEFUL! FUCK! I love everyone now seems to have a degree in economics now and are all read up on their Adam Smith and Marx. Oh wait, they don't and they aren't.  I think the thing that bugs me most about these types of arguments (other than reminding me of stupid classes from first and second year polisci) is that they assume two diametrically opposed viewpoints without room for other ideas or compromise.  EDIT: Oh yeah and Prince of Persia 2 looks RAD.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was at work the other day really, really bored. I'm browsing the internet, going on webpages, downloading porn on a public university network, jeprodized my academic career, and finished by searching for pictures of ugly dogs on google.  Something was missing.   BLOGSPOT! I totally forgot we had this.  Alas, since I've been gone I'ved noticed three things:  1) Matt made a reboot joke.  2) Dan talked about star trek.  3) Matt wrote penis over 30 times.  ahhh... it's good to be home.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh man, rolling into the 10th hour of work today and I'm going crazy!  GOD, someone ease my insanity, send me something funny, stop in, or at the very least give me a 5 letter word for wild ducks...possibly starting with a T.     Matt
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alas boys and girls, the following email was in my inbox:   Hi Aaron,  The materials just got posted and I had a look. We need to wait until the committee has had a chance to review your materials, but I don't think that that will be a problem.  So, can you start this September?  Looking forward to having you join our group.  Best regards,  Tom    You might be asking "Who is Tom?". Well, he's one strongly-correlated-electron-material-researching BADASS.     You can look at his webpage  urlLink here .  Cross your fingers. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The best part of today was when I heard "Scotty Dosen't Know" on CJSR.  HA HA HA HA HA  IT WAS AWESOME 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I'm at work right now, and there's this dude waltzing around looking at comics, and it's pissing me off....  Because I have to pee.  So I'm thinking, wouldn't it be cool if I could run into the back and pee at Flash speed...then I got to wondering, can the Flash pee at super-speed?  I know he thinks at super-speed, but if he was moving at super speed would he pee at super-speed? or would he have to stop and then pee?  Because if he could pee at super-speed it would be like a water laser.  He could cut through anything with his super-fast pee.  So Dan, what's the verdict?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "I hate sweaters, I hate pants, I love Greece, Because I hate France." -Alex 'G' Glancy
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Levin will be going to Waterloo in september.  MSc Physics pending.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      EDITORIAL: HOW TO WORK A RAP RECORD         You often hear rappers whine about "my album didn't do shit because my label didn't push me", and most of the time, it seems like simply the disgruntled musings of a starving artist, and nothing more. However, after studying the rap industry over the last twenty years, there is something to be said for labels simply dropping the ball and not pushing their artists. Case in point is someone like Dilated Peoples  - we saw "This Way" catch significant B.E.T. airplay, and even mainstream radio play in certain markets (KLUC added it! Yes, KLUC....), however we have yet to see a follow-up single or video. While Dilated remains one of the most consistant crews in hip-hop music, there has to be something on that album, or even something that could at least be remixed, so that the label could continue to work the album and squeeze a gold or platinum plaque out of it. Sound impossible? It's not, read on.      Case in point is Black Eyed Peas' Elephunk, which like Dilated's Nieghborhood Watch, is the third album from a three-man, multi-ethnic Los Angeles based crew, however the difference is that Elephunk is probably the worst Black Eyed Peas album ever, while Neighborhood Watch ain't half bad. And also, Black Eyed Peas are platinum, and Dilated aren't gold yet. Granted, Black Eyed Peas record has been out for exactly one year as June 24th, so it has the calculated advantage. But get this, Interscope is still marketing the BEP record. They had a little hit out of the Justin Timberlake featured "Where Is The Love" last summer - and though it's follow-up singles "Let's Get Retarded" and "Shut Up" didn't crossover, this didn't stop Jimmy Iovine's team from pushing the record platinum. Instead, they liscensed "Hey Mama" to Apple for the IPod commercials (next to Jet's "Are You Gonna Be My Girl"), and redid "Let's Get Retarded" as "Let's Get It Started" (word to Hammer, proper) using it as the theme song for the NBA season. In fact, Interscope even re-released Elephunk on May 18, 2004 - eleven months after the initial street date - to include the new, friendlier "Let's Get It Started", for all you basketball loving family people out there who are offended by retards. But seriously folks. That is working a record.     And this isn't just a fluke either - the same example can be made out of Ludacris' Chicken & Beer, which dropped on October 21st, 2003. Entering the ninth month of this album's existence (and with Luda planning on dropping Red Light District by year's end), Def Jam has filmed an amazing SIX VIDEOS from this ONE release!! Of course, Luda saw success with his first Kanye West produced single (hey, just like Dilated), "Stand Up", but then Def Jam went on to release videos for "Splash Waterfalls" (including a new remix), the R-rated "P-Poppin'", "Blow It Out", "Southern Fried Intro" (which was attatched as an intro to one of these vids), and now most recently, "Diamond In The Back". And of course, Luda is way past Platinum. Again, that is working a record.     So where does this leave us? Hopefully at the beginning of an era where hip-hop albums are not treated as "two singles and it's done". Right now the norm seems to be about three or four videos on the "big" releases, but most promotion is usually done after sixth months. Bigger artists usually get this standard treatment: Jay-Z ("Change Clothes", "Encore", "Dirt Off Your Shoulder"), Outkast ("The Way You Move", "Hey Ya", "Roses"), Kanye West ("Through The Wire", "All Falls Down", "Jesus Walks"), D12 ("My Band", "40oz", "How Come"). But if you notice, Kanye West and D12 have only been considered "big" since the record label began pushing them. Perception is reality, labels. Treat your artists big, and most likely the audience will too. Until next time, I'm looking foward to that fifth Roots Tipping Point video and fourth Slum Village Detroit Deli video in a year from now. Peace. - Pizzo  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In an effort to move dumb rap posts from the top of the page I will reprint my comments from the  urlLink Unofficial Gateway blog  about the election:  "PS: Anyone else feel like you received a huge kick in the junk last night? And, moreover, like you would've felt the same way regardless of what happened?" -- Jake  Actually I think that the results of this election were exactly as I hoped they would be (and was still predicting they would be till the end). I felt that the Liberals were probably the best party to rule the country, but they needed to be shaken up to stop them from becoming stagnant and lazy (see Sponsorship Scandal, HBC boondoggle and the Alberta PC party). I also liked the NDP's mandate, but feared that if they were ever to get into power that they would murder the economy.  Hopefully the NDP won't kill the Liberal's fiscal pragmatism (which is different from fiscal conservatism) and kill the economy leading to a Conservative victory in the next election.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Your song, "All That I Got Is You,", opened up a lot of emotions for people. When you think about your childhood, are they happy or sad thoughts?  It's both, "All That I Got Is You" is my life. And don't get it twisted. You might see Ghost half decent, but best believe there are still days when a nigga gotta rock his socks for three days straight. I just had my other pants on for seven days. Don't get me wrong, I showered, but I had to rock my pants out like that. That's why I can write songs how I write them, because I'm a real nigga. I take a shit in front of all my bitches. I don't gotta close the door if I don't want to. I love my women, and I do all that shit to them. See when I love, I love deep, man. And we can laugh, just like we brothers and sisters. Ain't no shame in my game. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You don't support the Democrats. Why should your  urlLink Ketchup ?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Does anyone find it strange that the google ads have been blank on this page for at least a week?
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1) Wait for him to diss you.  2) Make sure he plays basketball.  3) Listen to "99 problems by Jay-Z"  4) Make an entire CD dissing him, including the following line:  If you having shot problems I feel bad for you son you had 99 freethrows and you ain't make one!! - Skillz  Skillz > Shaq
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just learned that SONY was sued because of the number of Disc Read Error PS2s there are and was forced to service them out of warranty, FOR FREE! I'm calling them up tonight!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, yes, yes. I know it's more rap. But this has to do with COMICS too, so I thought it would be ok.  Marvel has finally caught buzz about MF Doom using Fantastic Four art for his album covers.  Covers like these:           Will the masked villain ever be stopped?     Not when he does that. Those hands will keep any security guard within 10 feet away form him.  But what does this mean for Levin? Well, since all those albums where pulled off the shelves and are given new artwork, I now have some albums that will go up in price tremendously! WOO HOO!  To combat this, I have decided to name the dog I'm going to get MF Sauce.   ps - If you don't get it, watch Seinfeld.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, yes. There comes a time in every mans life when he falls in love with a hat.    Rewind 3 months ago and that was me.    For anyone who attended our party that was 2 parties ago. I was wearing a toque. And that toque is gone. It was dear to me, and I would never have put it down even if it raped the girl next door.    what?    but seriously, has anyone seen my hat?    Although I don't have a picture of it, I can link some pictures of hats that it wasn't:                 ^-- This one was made of brass. Obviously not my hat.       ^-- Although a very pretty poem, it can neither be put on a head, nor is it my hat.       ^-- This hat doesn't even exist in real life. It was made on a computer.    Please, help me find my hat.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Man, there's some movies they should just NOT make   urlLink http://www.dtheatre.com/read.php?sid=2517    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Holy Shite! According to Aint-it-Cool-News a new live action Transformers movie is go for 2006 and it looks like Steven Speilberg might direct it! Wow!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The new BATMAN trailer has hit the net. I'm still not sure if this will be any good or not. For some strange reason this trailer reminded me more of the HULK movie than anything else. Bale's voice sounds a lot like Bana's and the words could be straight out of Ang Lee's HULK.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We've seen the terrible trailer. We've all secretly wanted to see it just cause (wait maybe that was just me). Now I get to go see "Going the Distance" tomorrow at 10am. Woo for me.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>