<Blog>

<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HI! I slept for 2 and a half hours after watching some TV programmes. Nothing much, finished the DNA course and now waiting for the bacteria to grow. And then after the course, a group of four of us went to Bishan J8. I went and ate the hot and spicy noodle in the food court. The more you eat, the hotter you get. But I think it is alright. I could ''tahan''. Seiyu Bishan now has MUJI. Yeah! I went there. Very interesting. It is combined with clothing, stationery sets and food. Quite expensive but cool. The colours are not very flashy and are all on the cool side. Ya know, brown, silver, white and blue.... I actually wanted to buy some stuff but a friend of mine was rushing for time... Too bad, I will try my luck tomorrow. OH, Dragon Boat Festival is next week and my mother had already made the dumplings AND I am having it for dinner...  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Fresh out of my bathroom and is sweating already... ''+_+' Came back from school at 6.30pm. WHY? I had a DNA course in school from 2.30pm to 5.45pm. WHAT DID I DO? Absolutely nothing. We went through what is DNA, how to extract it and blah blah blah. And I spend $110 on it. And what did the instructor said? " It cost $400 for the whole kit" So, for our course, she gave a discount izzit? Anyway, the course did not end here, tomorrow we have to return to school. What we did today is to extract out the PURE DNA and cool it for tomorrow's 'GREEN' EXPERIMENT..... And the whole process took us more than an hour or so AND MORE! We put in solution to prevent bacteria, or to break up OR to 'eat' it up.... And then we centrifudge, centrifudge AND centrifudge for a hundred times before we could get a pure solution which its amount did not even reached to my pinky. And the Bio lab was so hot and stuffy. And in order to entertain ourselves, the boys decided to twist the tap's head upwards instead of the normal position during break time. And what they did was to turn the tap on and off with skillful hands and the end product is that you will see a so- called 'fountain' that spurted out water. It was beautiful in a way, providing you did it when the teacher is not looking and you don't mind wetting your classmates' table and chairs and the ceiling too. So, that's was what we fooled around this afternoon.... Oh, I also wanted to buy FIRST Magazine but I was so tried and exhausted even though I had the money... The front page is Charlie's Angels and The Hulk... Check it out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! My stomach muscles are STRETCHING, my arms are aching and my head is spinning around.... The Reasons are below:  * Releasing of exams results - - - -  - English 27/50 (^_^) (HEY! Not many pupils can pass, YA KNOW!) - Chinese B3 (-_-) (MUST STUDY HARDER!) - E- Maths B4 (-_-) (THE LOWEST GRADE IN THE CLASS, MY TEACHER SAID THAT) - A- Maths F9 (-___-) (BUT I AM NOT THE LAST ONE !)  - Sub- Science (chem/phy) B4 (^_^) (I HATE BOTH OF THEM) - Biology C5 (HEY! 1 MORE MARK AND I CAN GET A B4!) (-_-) - Humanities (geo/S.S) B4 (-_-) (GEO PULL ME DOWN...)  * ALSO...I did all the sit- ups, pull- ups and etc, except 2.4 km in ONE hour. I skipped PE a few weeks ago for my dental appointment -_- So that's why my body is aching like HELL ! ! !   So, you can see my stupid exams results never fare very well, but, in all, at least I pass all my subjects EXCEPT A- Maths which I KNEW I can never pass and I have given up hope. My dearest A- Maths teacher -_- can dream on to have 100% all passes for O Levels....  Alright, alright, enough of me fussing and grumbling around. I think everybody is sick of clicking all the Singapore's teens' Blogs and see everybody grumbling about their exams or getting their results in a few days time.... I foresee a disaster in my home during the evening. My brother AGAIN skipped school and played traunt. And his stupid teacher called my mother and boy, was she sad and desparated at the same time, or WHAT! She called my father and when my father is brought to the 'STAGE', my brother can dream on to try again the next time.... My father is that POWERFUL !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Boring AND hot day. So, what did I do? I took off my old cover of A- Maths t/bk and made a new cover with lots of checked blue, pink and orange, MY favourite colour. While doing, I was watching the last episode of Duke Of Mount Deer 2000. Very sad for the last three episodes. I mean, Wei Xiaobao was 'excuted', one of his wifes was dead and he had to end off his friendship with Kang Xi.... Haiz... But everything turned out quite well. But actually I already knew the ending, like twenty episodes ago... I was clever enough to surf all the lead actor's fans' website and I was so fortunate to find this die- hard fan captured all the episodes screenshots and I clicked it all the way to the end. And I told one of my die- hard Channel U friend and she did not believe me. Ha! Let's see what she will say for the last episode.... I hope I will be able to buy a Super Dollfie during my June holidays through the net. But I think I cannot accomplish the 'mission', it is so expensive and I REALLY hope I can get a Lucas male Super Dollfie.... ((o-_-o)''
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I can only say today's weather is so DAMN HOT ! ! ! You can relate to Adidas' commercial 'SO DAMN HOT'... ' 0_0" Anyway, today is a boring day, I predict... Firstly school was so boring and on my way to school, I fell asleep which I am not supposed to, IF NOT, my father will KILL ME! 0_o Luckily, he was also sleepy and blamed it on the BBC news and quickly switched to Newsradio 93.8 FM. I can tell you, I have been listening to BBC since the day my father fetched me to school. Their English is actually not very accurate especially their overseas correspondent, and their babbling can put me to sleep easily.... Only recently my father switched to a more interesting 93.8 FM for the recent SARS case and situation and they will only report at 7am and I am already in my car by 6.50am and have to suffer for 10 minutes of sheer torture trying to open my eyes before getting a scolding and 'beating' from my father. Haiz... what to do? As long I can 'tahan' for a few months, everything will be fine.... -___-
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Cool... I found it at a website. Very touching.... Edgar Allan Poe. (1809-1849) [ Annabel Lee]   It was many and many a year ago,  In a kingdom by the sea, That a maiden there lived whom you may know By the name of Annabel Lee;-- And this maiden she lived with no other thought Than to love and be loved by me.  I was a child and she was a child,  In this kingdom by the sea;  But we loved with a love that was more than love--  I and my Annabel Lee-- With a love that the winged seraphs in Heaven Coveted her and me.   And this was the reason that, long ago, In this kingdom by the sea, A wind blew out of a cloud, chilling My beautiful Annabel Lee; So that her high-born kinsmen came And bore her away from me, To shut her up in a sepulchre,  In this kingdom by the sea.  The angels, not half so happy in Heaven,  Went envying her and me--  Yes!--that was the reason (as all men know,  In this kingdom by the sea) That the wind came out of the cloud by night,  Chilling and killing my Annabel Lee.   But our love it was stronger by far than the love  Of those who were older than we--  Of many far wiser than we-- And neither the angels in Heaven above,  Nor the demons down under the sea, Can ever dissever my soul from the soul  Of the beautiful Annabel Lee:--   For the moon never beams, without bringing me dreams  Of the beautiful Annabel Lee; And the stars never rise, but I feel the bright eyes Of the beautiful Annabel Lee:-- And so, all the night-tide, I lie down by the side  Of my darling--my darling--my life and my bride, In her sepulchre there by the sea-- In her tomb by the sounding sea.  Arthur Quiller-Couch, ed. 1919.  The Oxford Book of English Verse: 1250-1900.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Wanted to watch 'Matrix Reloaded' but not in the mood. -__- So, decided to come home and realised that my father is at home studying for his upcoming exam. How bad a day can be.... -___- Anyway, I visited this 'The Tribe' website, I think this show is about a toxic waste that caused teachers and adults to disppear but left with children and teenagers with funny and exotic face paints and hairstyles. And, Boy! Is this show long or what! It is showing on Channel i on Sunday in the afternoon for about 2 hours and we are still st Series 1 while 'The Tribe' had proceeded to Series 5 with so many twists and I doubt that I am able to keep up with it... -____- Haiz.... I hope I can link to this website and everybody can visit it. On the whole, this show is interesting as it shows the world CAN go wrong without adults and now every kid is fighting for a place, for a position, a time to be able to dominate the world, while some just want peace and harmony.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I never go to my Grandpa's house! Ya! It is due to the fact that I woke up late in the morning and my mother was so angry and I kept insisting I am not going... Anyway, my brother will not be going as he is having tution and there is Matrix tonight! ^_^ Oh, by the way, I vivited this Super Dollfie's website. It is actually dolls with very real human features acept that they have this very very big eyes. And they are very expensive as they are made in Japan. You can even customize their faces and body...Haiz... How I wish I can have one.... ( o * - * o )....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing much... Watch 'Top Secret' starring Vil Kilmar. Very funny and sweet... (o^ - ^o). Anyway, I did not go out tonight, ate at home and tried to finish my unfinished drawing of Cardcaptor Sakura, Tomoyo and Meilin in their kimono costumes. All those Sakura fans should know which picture I am drawing and painting. It is a little bit different as I made it simpler for me to draw and paint. But on the whole, it is still alike to the original picture. I am so proud of myself ! * v * Haiz... I need to visit my Grandpa tomorrow. I kind of dread it although I used to like it very much as I can escaped from home work and watch TV. But now, I go there is like going to visit Hell -_-... Do you like it if there is an uncle telling you to lose weight the moment he sees you eating sweet stuff? I mean I am not a junk person, it just that I never exercise much, thats why I am plump. Yeah, so what he is a diabetic person? He cant just judge everything IN HIS VIEW... Jeezzz..... my temper flare everything time I go there or talk about it. But the relatives there are fine in a way... -___- So, I think you will not see me in the morning or afternoon... Hope to see you in the night and awake... MUST REMEMBER TO WATCH....  :+:  THE TWINS EFFECT  :+:   It is a vampire movie starring Hongkong famous' Twins, Ekin Cheung, Edison and Guest Appearance--- Jackie Chan. Hmmm, I like to watch vampire show about torn between love and duty and I kind of like Edison. But I am NOT like a fantic, having poster or CD or know how old he is, etc... I just like his very boyish yet mature look in every angle...^_^ But it is not coming until June, and I will be having Pratical Mock Exam =__= Haiz....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, AND CHECK OUT MY NEOPETS! So cute!        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I went to Bishan Junction 8 at about 12 in the afternoon juz now... All I can say is that there are A LOT OF PEOPLE ! It is really a crowd. I think it is because they renovated the place and J8 was featured in The Straits Times a few days ago AND there is this BIG MEGA PROJECT that was going on and our school was chosen. It is actually a stall you would be setting up and sell all kinds of stuff in order to earn money and PROFITS $_$. And GB, NPCC, ART club and others were set up in May and the weather was very very hot! We were sweating profusely in the open space although it was very fun and exciting. I did not even know there was this 'House Rabbit Society Singapore'. Their stall was very cool with their hand- printed items like bookmarks, postcards and keychains. I bought a bookmark for $2 and my friend bought postcards and bookmarks. This society is actually to help reduce the number of unwanted pets and improve rabbits' lives through education. Hmmm, very meaningful but I can't join as they need a membership dee of S$25 and I don't have a pet right now... I send away my CUTE quails a year ago, and I never even take photos of them. :~ The reason was that my brother and I could not have the time to take care of them (It was given to my brother in Pri 6 as his Birthday present -_-) So, all I could say that looking after a pet is a life- long responsibility. DON'T EVER ABANDON YOUR PETS ! ! ! To check out the House Rabbit Society Singapore, the website is ---  http://www.hrss.net/  Happy surfing!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really thought that I am angel of peace...    You are an Angel of Wind.  You ride the wind and run across the world. You're everywhere at once. You're wild and free and live by no one's rules! You've met a few of the other Angels, but find that traveling alone suits you best.     urlLink   What Kind of Angel are you? (For Girls: With Pictures)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        You are Tank, from "The Matrix." Loyal till the end, you spare no expense in ensuring the well-being of others.    urlLink   What Matrix Persona Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Mid- year exams are FINALLY, FINALLY OVER! ! ! And to celebrate that, a group of 7 girls went to cineplex at orchard to watch 'Darkness Falls' instead of 'Matrix'. I mean initially I really wanted to watch Matrix, but the others suggested that we will watch 'Matrix Reloaded' after watching 'Matrix' on Channel 5 on Sunday.... Never mind, but A Word Of Caution For You for 'Darkness Falls' ---- Bring EARMUFFS. The movie was only about 1 and a half hours short and although I was covering my ears the whole time, the 'ghost' a.k.a 'the tooth fairy', I could hear her screaming throughout the movie. @_@ Actually this movie in short is about this disfigured 'tooth fairy' who would kill children or adults if anybody sees her. But usually it is the kids, as after dropping their last baby tooth, they must not peek at the tooth fairy or she will kill you.. Fortunately, she is scared of light, so, stay in lighted places. So this male character saw her when he was small and it killed her mother, thus, he lived in fear of darkness till he grew up. He saw his childhood sweetheart's brother having the same experience and this 'tooth fairy' began to terrorise the whole neighourbood. I really hate watching horror movies so I praticularly covered my ears throughout the movie....   And in a way it is very funny as I used to keep my baby teeth (2 of them) and kept it under my bed.. Nothing happened.... BUT NOW, I have four adult teeth (extraction for braces) kept in a bottle and STILL NOTHING HAPPENED! So this is a living proof that tooth fairy does not exist, OK,  maybe she does not exist in my area or Singapore...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        only one thing is more infectious than sars        - and that's prejudice   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink   What kinda pet are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Weather is so hot nowadays in Singapore... *sweating and swearing* Going to watch The Matrix- Reloaded. the first marix movie, I was sitting comfortably on my sofa watching a rented Matrix video.... This time, with my friends... But in a way, I prefer to watch at home. I don't mind at all, ya know... ((^ - ^))--- Izzit nice? I thought of it just now. Oh, do you think I should go for tution tomorrow? I rejected my teacher since she had to go to malacca in the weekends AND my tution is in the weekends... I am at a loss... I feel that if I do not attend tution, I feel like I am a very proud and clever person, which in this case, I AM NOT !!! But if I attend, I feel so stupid and I also have a movie to catch... haiz... What Should I Do ? ? ?  Life has so many choices, but we always miss it and regret it for the rest of our life...   Waaahhhh, I can be so  profound ...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      nothing much, found out that my playlist in Window Media Player is gone. Must be something to do with my bro. All my songs and video.... *SOB SOB* :~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Change a new template and title... Hope you like it ! ! ! Pssstt.... I learned a new 'face', but my brother does not allow me to do it. But he is in who know's where! Here: ( 0 '-' 0 ) A plump one...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Are you surprised that I am here in the morning when everybody supposed to be in school having their exams? Yup, I am not having exams today! Ya! But.... my classmates' paper finished at about 11am in the morning, it is only 2 and a half hours paper. So no much happiness. They are about to finish their paper. CHEERS TO MY CLASSMATES.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I FINALLY FOUND IT! A very good and touching song. A SALUTE (GB, BB, NPCC,NCC, Girl Guides, Scout, St John or First Aid? And others) TO ALL HOSPITALS STAFF FOR FIGHTING AGAINST SARS!    Thru' Your Eyes    of heroes and angels, who'll always stand beside us when all fear surrounds us don't despair you know that someone's there  like the lady in calcutta alex fleming and nightingale where would we be without your love, your courage, your strength and your care  chorus	thru' your eyes 	i see the courage of the world 	thru' your eyes 	tella thousand different words 	thru' your eyes, your eyes 	a hero is what i see 	thru' your eyes  how the mighty they might fall never let your spirit falter where would we be without your love, your courage, your strength and your care (repeat chorus)  spoken	heroes rise when pretenders fall 	stacked up high against the wall 	forming the frontline in the brawl 	risking their lives to protect us all  	heroes rise when the time is right 	like a rescue beacon's shining light 	never to give up on the fight 	so we can all sleep tight tonight (repeat chorus to end) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I am back... Very sad.... Singapore still cannot be removed from the WHO's SARS list. I mean I am not angry or fustrated at the 39 year- old PR guy (Lim Something, something...) but WE ARE JUST  A FEW HOURS AWAY FROM FREEDOM ! ! ! But I tell you, the most funny and amazing part was that my 2 very cute friends did not even know th news UNTIL I told them around 10am today. One was shock, the other, calm, of course, she is also a malaysian. Hey... no hard feelings or meant to hurt anybody or country.... Hope that Singapore can be free from SARS ! ^_^
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, by the way, I found my wallet. Actually my aunt found the wallet in my father's car. And my father kept insisting my wallet was not in his car. -_- I knew I will not lost it as I was not that anxious or scared when I lost things. I lose a science file which contained all my precious notes when I was in primary school. And what I did? I cried and made a fuss and in the end the VP had to bother into the matter, till this day I STILL cannot find my file.... Life's like that, face it ~~~~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I want to be a rabbit.....   urlLink     What Is Your Animal Personality?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY! I drink 3- in- 1 instant coffee. I suppose to be carefree, RIGHT? OR WRONG?    You are the whatever coffee. No one really knows who you are, you're kind of just there...you're just blan...    urlLink   What Kind Of Coffee Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I never read this comic before, nut I heard it is quite cute and I like my character A LOT ! ! ! ^_^    You are Rinna! You're extremely polite and like to make new friends, but you have a problem with falling asleep waaay too often.    urlLink   Which Panyo Panyo Di Gi Charat Character Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now I REALLY lost my wallet....  My -_- dad helped me to make a new Ezlink card, it cost $30 for a lost card ! ! o_0 Other than that, my library card is ' terminated ', I will have to pay $1 for a new library card. Boy, everything cost so much nowadays... And I am STILL sad over my wallet, it cost $10, and I still never tell my parents I lose $27 in cash, I told them I lose $7... :p
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Lost my wallet * Lime green in colour * $27 cash in it * my library card, 2 photocop cards, my student pass AND my Ezlink card * And 2 Photo cards (:~) and other neoprint stickers Quite sad but nothing much grief or what. Just sad for my photo cards. They are expensive, although I don't mind taking photos again... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing much, just watched SHE SPIES at 8.30pm. Very sweet, Jack, the manager of the girls and the 'complainer', met the ex- spy girl he used to fall in love with. But, unfortunately, the girl had gone bad. Sssoooo..... A sad ending, but, Hey! Life still goes on, right? ^_^
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wish I was Yuna....   You're a dark and enigmatic Black Mage!    urlLink   What Final Fantasy X2 Dress Sphere suits you (females)?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, Gosh... How true....   You're too tired to be bothered with smiling,but you're too nice to be really mean when people are annoying you.You look tired,but you at least try to seem happy.    urlLink   What Kind of Smile are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not fair, I was hoping to be night- crawler... :(   You are Jean Grey.    urlLink   Which X-Men movie character are you? (the good guys)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love Switzerland. It is neutral and I love their different and exotic cultures and it is so damn similiar to Singapore! If you had studied social studies, you will know what I mean. ; )    Switzerland  - A neutral power for as long as most can remember, it has avoided war for several centuries. However, it is still considered highly advanced and a global power.    Positives:   Judicial.  Neutrality.  World-Renouned.  Powerful without Force.  Makes Excellent Watches, Etc.    Negatives:   Target of Ridicule.  Constant Struggle to Avoid Conflict.  Target of Criminal Bank Accounts.     urlLink   Which Country of the World are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Cute!! ^__^   I am a drooling baby kitten....**falls over**    urlLink   Which cute or possibly strange kitten are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah! Now, I AM a member of Quizilla. I am so proud! Wait for my quizess...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm... Not very accurate. But I do cuddle my plushie when I go to sleep. But I hate my school- uniform.      You're A School Girl! You may not get the best grades, but you'll always be found sporting your sleek school uniform. You've got school spirit, and lots of it! Pocket PCs and Pocky can be found in your backpack, and you love cute stuffed animals like teddy bears and bunnies!    urlLink   What Type Of Anime Character Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah! *singing* I AM STORM, I AM STORM! YES!   You are Storm!  You are very strong and very protective of those you love.  You are in tune with nature and are very concerned with justice and humanity. Unfortunately, certain apprehensions and fears are very hard for you to overcome, and can often inhibit you when most need to be strong.    urlLink   Which X-Men character are you most like?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I really like night-crawler. Even my Bio textbook has a picture of night-crawler and my school desk too, except it is all taken out(exams). Oh, my night-crawler.... *__*    Your ideal mate is Nightcrawler.  His appearance may be a bit off-putting, but his heart and personality more than make up for it.  He is shy and isn't very sociable and comes off as a bit of a loner (but you'll fix that).  He is also devoted and strong, and he always seems to just *pop* up whenever you need him the most. : )    urlLink   Who Is Your Ideal X-Men 2 Mate? (ladies only)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      YEAH !!!! I am a virgin! Try it, if you dare!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Disney movie! What the HELL are you doing taking this quiz, Goldilocks?! You're not a very sexual person...in fact, you're probably a virgin. You'd be better off trying your hand at voice-overs for a Saturday morning cartoon.    urlLink   What kind of porno would you star in?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Long time no see! I only missed yesterday's blog. My brother was 'fishing' the whole night, lf you play computer games, it will be Jing Yong, a chinese visual computer game where you fight your way through like a swordsmen into caves and stuff like that. Oh, anyway, yesterday I had bio remedial from 3 to 4.30pm. I tell you, I felt so downgraded. My bio teacher was like pointing at us like PIGS "You, stay. You, go!" Those stay, stay back for remedial and that means that you are poor in Bio. But of course, no hard feelings. I just do not like the way my teacher picked up students but anyway she is quite a good teacher though our former teacher went for further studies in overseas. -__- Oh and then when I reached home, I had to rush to the hairdresser where I had a appointment with the hairdresser to rebond my hair. In other words, it means straightening of hair. The process was long but worthwhile, it lasted for 3 hours but the hair will be kept straight for 6 months. Actually, I rebonded my hair when I was in sec 2, that was the time where rebonding was very very popular. Now I think it is cheaper (i will not reveal the price or location :p) But this time, my hair is straighter than before, I am always anti- chemicals, anti- hair- drying, anti- colouring of hair (although I did it a few years back) AND anti- everything that was put on my hair! But why the change? Hmm... I thought my hair was like a birdnest and even if I used the Dove's shampoo (think commercial and ad.), my hair is still like *__* Enough about hair. Today, I had chem practical. And I was doing an experiment on iron(II) oxide reacting with HCl. I am supposed to close the rubber bunk and shake the mixture. Stupidly, I IMMEDIATELY close the bunk. And what happened??? There was a loud "POP" sound, just like a champagne bottle. And all the black solution splashed not on me but everywhere on the table. Jeezz... So much for being ANTI- CHEMICALS. Today, GB girls (sec 3) supposed to set up a mini stall to promote their stalls which will be officially set up after exams in Bishan Junction 8 (all singers and actors will go there to promote their album, etc..) But unfortunately, they forgot to lock up the GB room after taking in or out the items they should be selling, BOOM! Our officer was so angry she gave them a scolding (LOUD!), no, it is scoldingS, with a S. So now the sec 3's could not set up and promote their stall as our officer disallowed and they were black- faced the whole day -__- Well, they already deserved their punishment, so I hope they would be more careful the next time. Jeezzz x2.... Enough x2 of that, had a maths remedial today from 4 to 5.30pm. Yesterday's activities tired me out and it was overlapped and brought forward to today, so adding x2 of stress and tireness. Luckily tomorrow is Vesak day, if not, I will really think of not going to school. Not much activities for tomorrow, but just sort of laze around studying and trying to snatch a moment to confide in here (brother went out AGAIN) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I broke my promise. But this is URGENT! I never celebrate Mother's Day. * A sinister laugh* My whole family never celebrate Mother's Day as 1) Exam period 2) There is no need to 3) There is SARS 4) I loathe (did I spell it correctly?) it! The reasons are reasonable, right? Oh, and if you watch channel U's Ready, Steady, Go!, which is about a competition where two contestants and hosts will go around Singapore's flats to get their items which they need and sponsered by Cold's Storage. A very funny show, the hosts were funny and that adds up the atmosphere. Althought I was able to watch for only 30 min, I was praticularly laughing my head off *Ha Ha*  *_* But I am still very loyal to Channel 5 and 8's shows. *cross my fingers*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My tutor came at about 6.50pm.She was late for about 20 min and my mother was complaining and almost forcing me to call her AGAIN. (Replaying the same scene yeaterday..) My mother had a habit of complaining and kept saying that all tutuion teachers are always like that. They would be punctual for the first few lessons and then arrive very very late... (example above...) Now I am trying to do 1 blog for each day and not talk about exams. I think it is jinxed if I tell all my exams here online. Therefore, I decided to shut my mouth *ZIP* and face the day happily, of course, it is not true as I am having my exam period..... : ( Why the school will not cancel the exams.... *boo hoo*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! It is in the afternoon and RIGHT now my brother is compaining that he is having a temperature of 39 degrees C. Should i believe him or not? Everybody is fussing around him, up to the extent that my mother went to my godmother's house to get the digital thermometer and she even went out early in the morning to buy the strip thermomter (a stip of colours which would turn green if  you press it against your forehead). Naturally, it is the least accurate thrmometer AND the cheapest too ($3). Anyway, now my godmothers are sending fruits for my brother, what to do? He is a boy afterall, the one who can carry the surname and the one who can escape from anything and everything with his SWEET mouth! -__- *bleah* Oh, and just now I had my tution and my teacher was late for 15 minutes and my father (sick with cough) was so angry, he shouted at me to call her. In the end she came in a hurry and she forgot to wear her contact lenses. I thing she is having an exam, she was reading her notes and I predict again that she is in the engineering course or something like that. ^_^ Ta da for now ! ! !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiz.... today's chinese prelims was what I called, HARD. VERY HARD. :~ The comprehension was hard, the cloze passage was hard and the whole paper was hard. I was particulary scratching my head and hair (a few strands did came off *_*). Fortunately, paper 1 was okay. I was able to create a good story in my opinion, but I was short of time. Grrrr....  Oh, I just went out with my family to admiralty (the MRT stop before Woodlands) to have dinner. Actually, we planned to have our dinner at woodlands' causeway point.But my VERY SICK brother was unhappy and decided to have dinner at admiralty. Of course, my parents agreed and all we did was to have dinner and shopped at Popular for my brother's dictionary. In anger, I gobbled up a claypot chicken rice which was quite filling. *burp* And now where is my beloved and sick brother? Upstairs sleeping. Why? Because he had a temperature of 37.5. And my parents dared not sent him to a doctor as the doctor would surely sent him to Tan Tock Seng Hospital and take him as possible SARS case. (SCARY!!!) Served him right for going out and coming back late in the night (between 11 - 12am) AND playing computer games for the whole afternoon for about 6 hours and above. ^_^ Enough of my brother. Oh, I also hope to watch Channelnews asia about the FTA agreement between Bush and PM Goh. I really DO NOT hope they will lift off the ban for chewing gum. I hate chewing gums, I don't care about other countries say about us, as long as our country is still as clean and green as ever. (@_@)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back. I have to. I can't stand staring at my chinese text for the whole night. I am not that studious, ya noe? That's was the reason I dropped my 2 (out of 3) pure science subjects to sub- science, I feel so ordinary now. -__- Anyway, I did not really appreciate the subjects the way my classmates did (they discuss it  everywhere , AND we are not the best sch though WE are the best class, jeezzzz....) Back to SERIOUS business. That's about me!!! *smile*  CCA  : In case u do not know, it is Core Curriculum Activities AND I am in gb (work it out urself again *__*) Have to go, if not I will have to burn the midnight oil. Which is no good and our teachers recommend us to sleep at 8pm. Oooppsss, it IS WAY past 8 already. 0_0
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok... After an hour and a half on the net, I think it is time for me to go.... Miss u lots!!! And lots lots ^___^
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello! I am back! Well, today's school was BORING *yawn*. I mean, all my subjects have 2 periods and each lasting as long as 35 min. Maybe to somebody it is short or vice versa, but I, The Person Who Hates Maths, I REPEAT, HATES MATHS, it really kill mi when I am having 2 periods of maths early in the morning. And unfortunately, I started off late (did I tell u I missed maths when I went 2 e dentist yesterday morning ^_^) and I did all the exercies VERY VERY slowly... Even my partner was "ahead" of mi so many que away. :~ BUT, 1 very good news, I passed my (sub) PHYSICS test. Yeah!!! ^_^ That was the only good news.  THE VERY BAD NEWS: Chinese Prelims 2morrow and I hav only revised sec 4's bk. while the sec 1's bk is on my lap and the rest(sec 2,3)? On my study table, UNTOUCHED. I am begining to fear my chinese prelims although I always did quite well in this subject. What is wrong with me? Arrrggghhhh....... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi there! Its 10.19 pm right here in S'pore. Finished my dinner frm 8.00 to 8.30pm. Normally, I would take 15 min to finish my dinner without braces and now I can take that long. Haiz... It is all worth it if my teeth is straight :~ 1yr and 4 MORE mths to go. Oh, I watched 'SHE SPIES' @ 8.30, it used to be 8pm, u noe? I can tell u, I enjoyed the show tremendously. I mean the ex- con girls can really use their brains, beauty and comedy altogether (like rojak) into 1 VERI good show! I am very impressed. Normally, girls kick ass (asses) would be like Charlie's Angels, THIS will be very fake... I really recommend this show, I always look forward to thur, although there is PE on this day   *pants*   Movies recommended by MI ! ! ! : X- men 2 Why? : What? U dare 2 ask such a que? X-men 2 is better than X-men. The story continues from the first movie. And the movie is packed with A LOT of action. Especially wolverine and Lady Deathstrike. *heart is beating* The movie also has a lot of comedy.  The part between Iceman's father and Wolverine in Iceman's house  (something like that) Father: What do u major in, Professor Logan? Wolverine: *very solemn*  Art. That part was very funny, of course there are others, but I forgot since I watched it on 30th April (VERY EARLY), the day it was first shown in S'pore. Boy, it was FULL house... And it's great that everybody is watching the same pic and @ the same time. *-*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi AGAIN. Trying to laze around and finish off the day as quickly as possible. mum is cooking dinner and I can smell the hot and spicy stingray's aroma coming here. Can't stand it!!! *saliva drooping* => Bio term: It means something about neurones and effector and relay and cerebrum and grey matter AND spinal cord. Oh, to give u more info about moi... * 15 yrs and 9 mths * taking 'O's this yr * currently studying in phs (work out which sch izzit urself) * Birthday: Indonesia's national day (I am not kidding...) * had a 1 yr- old younger than me brother who dosen't look like a year younger than me, get it? * address: Hmm... Do I trust u? * subjects taking RIGHT NOW in sch: 7 (used to be 8, u noe?) *sob sob* * Blah, Blah AND Blah... nothing more to tell u 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Moi again here. Chinese prelims on sat. AND Eng mid- year on mon. *sigh deeply* Who can have a worse month than mi? God? Hmmm... and today was actually a very fine and HUMID *sweats profusely* day and what am I doing? Sitting on the orthodontics' "chair", I can tell u that it is hard and not comfortable and right above u is the damn light. *eyes close, small pupil, circular muscles contract, blah...* And beside u is the dentist all covered in green (GREEN robes, if u noe wat i mean) holding all these wierd tools that look EXACTLY like scissors and other scary- looking stuff. Ok, now u ask mi why in e hell am I doing? Of course, I hav braces and u noe the rest of the story... Jaw IS very sore right now. *eyes blinking* 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Y I hate maths? Hmm... Good question. I hate maths as I keep failing them. There, simple and logical reason. Right? Never got a good grade since when... last year jan. *Laugh*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I FINALLY watched "Charlie's Angels- Full Throttle". Very, Very, nice and interesting. Maybe it will arouse the male's interest. There were a lot of flesh and skin been showed off. But I loved it very much. I watched the 9.50AM time slot ALL ALONE by myself! Yeah! And I thought I went to the wrong theatre as I was the only person and it was actually QUITE scary. But in the end, there were a family or two and some couples. Not many people, but of course, IT IS IN THE MORNING! Oh, I also bought FIRST magazine. It featured Lara Croft- Angeline Jolie. Actually, I bought for the sake of reading "The Twins Effect" but nevertheless it was worth it.....    6 MORE DAYS TILL THE RELEASE OF -+-THE TWINS EFFECT-+-  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changed profile. Now you will know more about MOI!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My whole family watching pirated VCDs. * Heh Heh ~_~ * Currently watching ' I Spy', pathetic movie.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changed my title. Maybe I will like the new version, everything seems ENLARGED! It seems more simpler and as I said before, very, very, sleek.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just now went to check Blogger's new template. Not very sastisfied, decided not to change to any new templates ever, I mean, for the time being....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! NOT VERY familiar with the new version. Very sleek but BORING... Jeeezzz... Anyway, today,  initially , I really want to catch ''Charlies' Angels- Full Throttle'', but I do not have the money, so I can only catch it tomorrow in the morning and try to rush to school in the afternoon. Haiz...    7 MORE DAYS TO -+- THE TWINS EFFECT -+- ......  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       WHAT I DID FOR THE WHOLE OF 1 WEEK....    - On Friday, tried to please my mother so that I can go to the Sentosa's Courage Fund Concert. My brother's friend got free standing tickets.   - Saturday. Finally got to go, went there early in the morning with my brother's  friends. Heh, Heh, I am the oldest, I am the oldest.... But what I was displeased that my brother's friends fooled around at Silso Beach in full clothed. I mean, almost everybody was wearing bikinis and board shorts and except the BB 31st Coy and some organisation, WE DO LOOK WEIRD.... Continue...   - The concert was GREAT! First there was SHIN Band, Elva, Qiu Zhe (??), Fang Fang, Jolin, 5566, 5566's mentor teacher who is about to release his solo album and 1 more whom I can't remember, sorry... But my photos turned out badly. *Boo Hoo* We went there late lah.... Haiz.... All heads, I am only 160cm, ya know.....   - Sunday. Took the NEL all the way to Dobby Ghaut. I mean, from Rumbia (don't ask me, I also did not know there was such a place) in LRT then travelled up (?).... Went to PS but did not enjoyed thoroughly. My brother's tution was at 5pm and the whole family reached there at  2pm. So it was RUSH, RUSH AND RUSH!   So, there is the end of my 1 week journey. Spend the whole of this week lazing around and finishing up homework...     8 MORE DAYS TILL THE RELEASE OF -+- *THE TWINS EFFECT* -+-  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing to talk about. Not even going out with my godmothers, both of them are treating me to watch 'Finding Neemo'. Too bad, not in the mood. Just lazing in the house and thinking death and poly or JC. Man, LIFE SUCKS! Nothing beats it till I am out of school.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Love to eat sushi but my brother loves this more than I do....    You are tamago, which is egg and rice with a band of seaweed to hold it together. You are different, which can be a good thing and a bad thing.    urlLink   What kind of sushi are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tried to register as OZ online game member, *gasp* but have to pay through SMS, not willing to. So let's see what my mother will do when she sees my brother's handphone bill for OZ. Actually, I used to signed up as a trial member when it just started its Singapore online game. It was FREE at that time! Remember? Hang Ten used to sponser it and all their shopping bags are printed with OZ. Haiz... it IS a good game. The characters are nicely dressed and you have to fish to earn money and buy clothes to cover your NEARLY NAKED body.... *laugh* No need to worry, you just go to another virtual world to make friends and the boys there really LOVE talking to girls. What's more? you have a attractive body regardless of male or female, really, very, fun...  --- Uni looks good---   You are Aivilo_Pilut the Uni.  You are my very first neopet.  You are the leader of the pack and the smartest!    urlLink   Which of my Neopets are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What I did on Friday, the 13th.....  DESTINATION: Changi Airport * First, we went to T2, you should know what is that. We were trying to find McDonalds' but only found Burger King. So, we changed out of our school T- shirts and wore our newly- printed Class T- shirts which, I MUST SAY, IT SUCKS.  * After lunch, we went to Swensens and ate Regular Earthquake. Then, we fooled around with their dry ice. I must say that the dry ice was very fun. I LOVE IT! Go and try it! * Later, we went to viewing mall but it turned out to be boring. Not that kind of drama I saw on TV, you know, the parting scene and crying part. *Boo- Hoo* * Then, we went to take the Sky- train and went to T1. Same, boring... And the pics we took did not came out. *Waaahhhhh*  DESTINATION: Tampines  * Actually, nothing much. All we did was to window- shop the whole of Tampines Mall and I went to try the Winnie The Pooh vending machine and got a Eeyore (spelling like that?)  * Then we went to Century Square and went to Delifrance and I spend all my remaining money on a CUP OF TEA! Jeezzz.....  So by the time I went back it was quite late. But nevertheless, I had a great time at least it was not an unlucky day....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Look, I have no time to write much. Bro's away, so computer is like a wreck and my SHOWBIZ programme is coming. Will tell you much more about my trip to Changi Airport, Tampines Mall and Century Square. The photos did not came out pretty well. Like the results though.....    Noon - You are pleasant, friendly, and an overall nice person.  You enjoy the energy and activity of the daytime, and tend to be very productive.    urlLink   When are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's like I have seen so many Angel eggs in almost every CLAMP comic book. ~_~        urlLink Which CLAMP series' random item are you?    Quiz made by  urlLink Let-kun   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HA! Now I have to pay $1 MORE for our teachers' class T- shirt. I ALREADY PAID $5 FOR EVERYTHING AND I AM NOT ATTENDING! Jeezzz.... Sorry, got carried away again. REALLY REALLY, I never like class outing. Hmmm... Now how to find an excuse...... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So lazy that I only did 1 entry for english assigment. Don't feel like going to our class' outing. I DAMN HATE IT AND LOATH IT AND ** IT! Sorry, got carried away. :P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Look's like it is gonna to rain. Want to go to library....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Quite true....   urlLink    Which Part of a Meal Are You? urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I heard it was a sweet and romantic movie......   urlLink    Which Reese Witherspoon are you?  urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is so not TRUE!   urlLink    What's Your Personality? urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I kinda like Sesame Street...   urlLink    Which Kid's TV Character are You? urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmmm....I thought so....   urlLink    Which Flower Are You? urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Who is exactly CHER?   urlLink    Which Clueless Chick are you?  urlLink Find out!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      SWEET !    urlLink      Brought to you by urlLink bunnywunny_~!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dont even know what brand is it. But sounds good...        urlLink  What  kind of clothes should I be wearing?    by  urlLink Evelyn  
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That. Is what I like and want...    YOU ARE ... MYSTERIOUS HERO! (Squall Leonhart from FFVIII [ff8])    urlLink   What Kind of Anime Character Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      As I said before, I WANT TO BE YUNA!    Rinoa    urlLink   What Final Fantasy 8 Character Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dont know, dont care, I dont like disney's princesses    Cinderalla... You love cleaning dont you? Or maybe you are matured and understand life. Or maybe you believe strongly in deep love? Or maybe all? Well, just try not to be so dumb sometimes. You have to be more cruel sometimes.    urlLink   Which disney princess are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man! What a day! I mean it is like I spent 7 hours doing A - maths, 4 exercises and I think 40 over questions in the t/bk. ''_'' Oh, that includes lunch, watching TV shows. I love watching Kids Central. Yeah, call me childish or immature but the shows are all my lost childhood which I never get to enjoy. There was Tintin and Archie's weired mysteries and blah blah.... Oh, there is a show THAT IS MUST watch "Holland Village'' on Channel 8. Yeah, that is the long- winded *yawn* 100 over episodes that stars FAT chen liping and other actors. I watched the 1st episode yesterday. My mother was laughing so hard that she forgot it was dinner time. I am going to watch tonight again...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I am so sweet!    You are a child's kiss.  Completely sweet and innocent and pure. You mean no harm and only love in your sweet kisses.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My friends say I AM THE SUN!    YOU ARE SPRING. Always trying new things, and discovering things about yourself.    urlLink   What Season Are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        -Motherly- You're the motherly type. You love to take care of the one you love, and generally you can be a bit overprotective and possessive, but you know, that isn't always such a bad thing. At least you'll be a good mom in the future.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        You're Red!    urlLink   Which M & M are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went to City Hall from 1pm to 6 'something' pm... Very exhausting and cramps in the legs. -__- What did the group of three innocent sec 4 girls *sinnister laugh* do in City Hall? Ha Ha Ha, Firstly, we went to Suntec and had lunch (had Korean food) at the food court before hunting down the whole of Suntec City. Then, we went to Esplanade and the library.... took photos with a disposable camera and saw three classmates, it is as though we are ''fated'' to meet... And we were like so shocked and aaahhhh..... Oh, we also went to Haggen Dazs to have ice- cream, I odered mango shorbet. Very sweet and nice... ^_^ Lastly, we went to Raffles City and again went around. We did went to MPH and read almost all the comic books and X- MEN.... X- Men's history is so complicated *start singing Avril's Complicated* And then we had 'dinner' at Soup Spoon. Very tasting and delicious.... like the ORANGE spoon A LOT! And I went home after going to the library to borrow TIMES, NG and science magazines for holiday assigment.... Hah! Am I studious or what! I WANT THE HARRY POTTER 5TH BOOK "ORDER OF THE PHONIEX'' can anybody help me order and buy for me? *joking*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Got back report book. Not in the best mood and temper to tell you... -__- Maybe later.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Long time no see! ^_^ These 5 days were HELL to me... Why? Because... every teacher is desperating trying to finish the chapters and topics so that they can catch up due to SARS outbreak.. *Shout Out With Middle Finger: Thanx To You! SARS!* Iwas so exhausted due to these tiring days that I fell sick yesterday. I tell you what happened... The whole night my nose was bleeding from 7 to 9pm plus plus. It was so bloody red and it was my longest nose bleeding period. My family members did not suffer all these except me... Hah!!! My nose has been bleeding since I was small whenever the weather turned very hot and humid or if I stand under the sun for too long...But these few years were okay, judging my four FINE and enjoyable years in GB! And my whole June holidays were filled with GOING BACK school schedule.... -__- Yeah... I know, I should not nag, 'O' Levels are nearing and blah blah blah.... But I am so desolate and SAD :( Never Mind, brother's not back, that's why I can used the com... *Evil Laugh*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I'm back with revenge. I failed my chem again... Now there will be RED mark again on my report card.... Not trying to depress or make  anybody  happy but i felt very tired coz everything time I studied very hard, the results will still be the same... OK, be happy, life's short.... I hope I am eligible to donate blood but I think I can't (they need age 16 and above). The red cross will be coming to our school on 15th August, but my 16th birthday is two days later.      -__- If they can stay for two more days, eeeerrrrmmm, maybe I will try. I have experienced needles pierced into my gums before, so I think thick needles pierced into my skin  should   be fine. (>_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Maybe I can get in the Guiness World Of Records for the fastest person who changes her title within a few days... I watched Gurmit Singh's Small Talk (about small little kids) and was fascinated by his quotes. Of course, majority of it I have used it before. Like ''Love makes the world go round'' and '' Love means never have to say you are sorry'', I have used them all. Now I took it from the show too, "There is no remedy for love, but to love more", ssssoooooo sweet... (^.^)     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Right now, I am eating prawn cracker with my left hand and typing with my right hand.... It is like today so sian and so many tests bombarded at us immediately. Interesting news will be broadcast later....... (=_=) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changed the settings   again  , I took it out from Russell Lee's quote, ''Life Is Vanity Until u Find Wisdom'' I think it is quite true... ^_- (winking expression) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am so sad, I don't feel like coming to school tomorrow, how? . It is like I hate my teachers and classmates.... Today nothing much happened. Except the debating team won and became champions. They will receive $100 ($_$) and a trophy each!!! They beat Commonwealth and will get extra CCA points.... I gonna hate my school 444eeevvveeerrrr....... ---___---
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tulip sounds nice and sweet   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeeeesss, I like beetle cars    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmmmm.......    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Juz popping here before my bro's tution teacher comes. I finally found some of my school's bloggers. YES! Although they are not from the same age, all sec 3's. Haiz... Don't tell me all the sec 4's in our school so hardworking until they never blog?! Or they don't even know what is a blogger??? Anyway, the sec 3's blog are quite interesting and what sould I say, a little on the weird side? All of them are venting their fustrations of their teachers. I am not, coz people will know who am I.... That is so dangerous, I hope the sec 3's will not find out. I juz want my blog to be fun not to be the next conversation in school. Come on, I am still a secodary school girl, what's more can you expect???
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really feel don't like showing off, but I am always very innocent, O.o that's what everybody describe me as... I ate Swesen's Earthquake ice- cream again yesterday.... Not regular but the $32 one. Of course I ate it with my 5 classmates. AND I just ate Strawberry cheesecake ice cream juz now, no wonder I gained weight so fast. (>. EXCITING  shows. I mean, the other participants are also worth watching and they practised very hard. BUT at least show the parade contignent, they learned marching for months and practising their opening- of- umbrellas to form Singapore flag for  months . Spare some thought for them. (>___ 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why Blooger kept repeating my entries??? UUURRGGHHH !!!!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, yesterday night, at 9pm sharp.... Three persons aged 50s, 15 approaching 16 and a 14 year- old boy broke the most terrible law.... THEY WATCHED PIRATED VCDs!!! We watched T3, a bit slanted and not focused, but other than that, I am able to watch and understand the movie. Except, I don't like the ending, it is like X- Men 2, where Jean Grey died just like T 101 died. ... ...  Hiaz... I am supposed to wait for my tution teacher, but where is she? I have not idea... (-_-)ZzZ  Today, Thanksgiving a.k.a Speech Day started at 9 am, I think they are finishing soon... Feel a bit lost, maybe should have gone to watch them....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah, we are approaching the weekend again. -___- Just postphoned my tution to tomorrow. My teacher was late for 1h, (^.^)b I am finally able to watch my x|aO ZhU on Channel U at 8. If I am having tution, I will miss it.... Too bad, I am a HK, Jap, Cartoon and Taiwan Variety Show FREAK!!! Tommorow is our school Thanksgiving Ceremony. Jeezzz, I could have go, either as a parade participant or a class representative, bUt I am shy mah.... (^.^'') But anyway, I will just stay at home and lazed around and study or watch cartoon....  Downloading Rurouni Kenshin Animation.........     urlLink      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Congratulations to my school's choir, *\(^-^)/* they won a Silver in SYF. But I felt sad for the band, ... ... they recieved COP (Certificate Of Participation). My classmates who were in the band cried. It must be very shocking and disappointing for them. they practiced for a long time and always staying in school to practice till night falls. I felt sad for them, I could feel their pain and disappointment. Well, if u fall again, stand up and try to walk again... Life goes on as usual. Even for me, I fell down whenever I failed my exams and I try to stand up, although I am crawling at the moment... It means I am not trying  VERY  hard....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Added Kenshi from Samurai X. The couple look so ccuuutteee together!!!  (^-^) And regarding the pic I put up yesterday, (the old ah ma & ah gong) I think they are booing at somebody instead of exercising.... I was mistaken... (^_^")
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Added Kenshi from Samurai X. The couple look so ccuuutteee together!!!  (^-^) And regarding the pic I put up yesterday, (the 2 old ah ma & ah gong) I think they are booing at somebody instead of exercising.... I was mistaken... (^_^")
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Exercise to keep yourself FIT!!!   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Changed a little  AGAIN   to my settings and info. :P Sorry.... Anyway, I am very happy that the Korean baby girls were separated successfully. After the tragedy, I think Singapore and the doctors need such an encouragement to motivate themselves harder. And what's more? The Korean baby girls are ssssssoooooo kawaii!!! (*_*) They are so fair and chubby. I did not even noticed that they were joined near the spine in the papers until I read the news. So cute, how I wish I was like them (I mean not joined lah!). I was like a boy in my baby photos....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiaz... today got PCCG, and teacher discussed with us about the points to go into JC. He sounded ssssooo confident that all of us were able to go to JC -__- I am unsure if I should go to JC....  Anyway, on a happier tone, today our school gave out lots of prizes. That included 'B' Boys Basketball players and 'B' Girls Volleyball players. Both won and created such a commotion that they gave glory to god bfore and after the match. That's why they won....  The science and maths competition.... -_____- I sat until my legs were numb and 'sleeping soundly' (>_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiaz.... a crockroach was found in my house, as though my house is so unhygenic like that. Jeeezzz... Nowadays my house is attracting tttooo many insects and pests. Four bees and now a large and dark crockroach.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Racial Harmony Day today.... UPSIDE: We need not need to wear costumes. Only a minority, I mean, a few, No, I mean the show- offs (that's better) wore their ethanic costumes. The teachers wore 'attractive' costumes and had a so- called 'fashion parade' where teachers would walk in front of the flag pole and do whatever action they wished to... DOWNSIDE: Well, at least we skipped reading period but had to be forced to buy different types of food from the students' stalls. I bought COLD curry puffs and ate Hokkien Mee, like I like it. -_- Anyway, we were able to skip maths (2 PERIODS!!!) as we had to do feedback form and talk about racial harmony day. I certainly agreed to such a session, not because I could skip maths but racial harmony is very important to Singapore, especially our limited resources. We must rely on human resource and social cohesion to prevent fights or riots, thus, celebrating Racial Harmony Day is very very important....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Racial Harmony Day today.... UPSIDE: We did not need to wear costumes. Only a minority, I mean, a few, No, I mean the show- offs (that's better) wore their ethanic costumes. The teachers wore 'attractive' costumes and had a so- called 'fashion parade' where teachers would walk in front of the flag pole and do whatever action they wished to... DOWNSIDE: Well, at least we skipped reading period but had to be forced to buy different types of food from the students' stalls. I bought COLD curry puffs and ate Hokkien Mee, like I like it. -_- Anyway, we were able to skip maths (2 PERIODS!!!) as we had to do feedback form and talk about racial harmony day. I certainly agreed to such a session, not because I could skip maths but racial harmony is very important to Singapore, especially our limited resources. We must rely on human resource and social cohesion to prevent fights or riots, thus, celebrating Racial Harmony Day is very very important....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Racial Harmony Dat today.... UPSIDE: We did not need to wear costumes. Only a minority, I mean, a few, No, I mean the show- offs (that's better) wore their ethanic costumes. The teachers wore 'attractive' costumes and had a so- called 'fashion parade' where teachers would walk in front of the flag pole and do whatever action they wished to... Well, at least we skipped reading period but had to be forced to buy different types of food from the students' stalls. I bought COLD curry puffs and ate Hokkien Mee, like I like it. -_- Anyway, we were able to skip maths (2 PERIODS!!!) as we had to do feedback form and talk about racial harmony day. I certainly agreed to such a session, not because I could skip maths but racial harmony is very important to Singapore, especially our limited resources. We must rely on human resource and social cohesion to prevent fights or riots, thus, celebrating Racial Harmony Day is very very important....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ate another steamboat at Zheng Fa, that's EIGHT in all so far.... And I played with M1 Funbox and my NEW jap name is Keiji Miyako. Sounds sweet and cute. That is nice... *\(^-^)/*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Nothing much. I almost did nothing except finishing my journal and watching Mary- kate and ashley in action and Lizzie Mcguire. Both are nice and funny shows. And read Sunday Life's comics section. I loved it!!! Then had lunch and watched The Tick. I like The Tick, it is very different from the normal superheroes... I hope I can remember my Neopets password. I forgot and worse, they sent my password to who-knows-where!!! I think it links to my manga as I was quite crazy about it that time and changed reguarly to my title....  How, how HOW?!?! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      YES! YES! YES!!!! (^____^)  You are most like the Summoner Yuna. Although you may seem weak behind your guardians and aeons, it is definetly not the case. You possess the strongest form of determination, and will not give up. You seem to not care about what people think, but it does affect you somewhat on the inside. Happiness may be hard to find for yourself, but making other people happy truly brings out pure joy. You are afraid of the future, but you know what you must do.     urlLink Which Final Fantasy X Character Are You?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made a mistake. Hope everything will be all right... m(_ _)m
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, well, well... today I never stepped out of my house and spent the whole day lazing in house finishing unfinished homework and watching catoon and anime!!! (^-^) I am out of GB and no more waking-up-in-the-morning saturdays, YEAH!!! So, what I watched were Kim Possible, Hercules, Jing Tian Yi and Love Hina! All of them are my favourite shows except Hercules and KP. I just watched it for fun. They were quite funny. Like KP, this episode featured her been engrossed in Animalogy. She was a BLUE FOX and her villian's son was a white throat, (yeah, I don't know how to spell, just the sound is alike to THROAT...) they were perfect SoUlMaTeS... So, hilarious incidents happened. In Hercules, Hercules and his friends were turned back to babies when they were hit by the hOlY wAtEr. They did look kind of cute....  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HERE ARE THE LATEST REPORTS FROM {THE JUNK NEWS}.... Four Bees were spotted at Akiko's beloved nest. FOUR LARGE BEES. With stings too. *scary* (*_*) One was drowned in the toilet bowl, two are making lovey- dovey around the lamp RIGHT above me!!! The other is circuling inside the lamp in the living room, going to be burnt to death.... I am so scared, I was interrupted when I was so- called studying and now, so- called typing......... END OF NEWS
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, change a title, from "~*[If LIFE Is Your Movie...THIS Is Your Movie]*~'' to the curent title. I will change them reguarly, I love phrases and words that have a deep meaning in it... I have also added the Weatherpixie. She is a Japanese girl wearing a kimono. Don't know why they name her a Geisha. A Geisha is an art and I think they should be respected instead of being insulted.... Kawaii!!! I really like the dolls, so cute and darling....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Homework, homework and HOMEWORK!!! Actually my fault... :p Coz I kept forgetting to finish my maths homework, all is like unfinished pieces of work. Hey! Don't get the wrong idea, I very obedient one, ya know.... I will only slag for maths. The other subjects I do it and pass it up at the right time. I so kuai [that means obedient in chinese]. (/^.^)/ *heh, heh, heh...* Anyway, I came home early today . Our school's volleyball team is competing in the finals in Bukit Kombak... Oh! Congratulations to our school's basketball team for winning in the basketball finals. I was like neutral, nothing so proud or happy about.... (-_-)zzz Our school's debating team is next Friday. Hope they win, then maybe our school can be featured in the newspaper. THEN I can show it to all of you. But it is still a IF....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I have add in a site meter. But it is going to start at one visitor. Damn!  (-_-;)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am back again. Put in an animation girl knocking her head everywhere while studying. I am like her. I used to knock my head on the table, and sleep until my hands and legs also go to sleep. That will be very bad and I felt needles pricking my feet. ^_^;;  href="http://petpages.neopets.com/~Cutie_Isaac">  Go to his website, good stuff for you to go and download. Regardless if you are in Neopets or Blogger....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I changed a little in the template. Hope it works *pray pray* m(_ _)M
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      --Went to school --It rained  --Thought P.E will be cancelled --Unfortunately, no. (-_-)zzz --Played badminton. --Sucked at playing.  --Kept running into the puddle. --I GAINED WEIGHT! o_o By 2- 3Kg... Uuuuggghhh  --Had Maths for 2 periods. --Which means 70 min, 1Hr 10Min. >_> --Hate maths (@_@) --Came home --Here I am... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      YES! I at last know where to put in all the HTML codes. It is actually inside the templates area. YES! I am so happy and elated. Hey! It is not everyday stuff you can figure it out without anybody's, I MEAN IT, ANYBODY'S HELP. Not even my computer genius bro. I did it all by myself. But I have to especially thank kao- ani's website. She makes great calendars and clocks, that's why I link her. She is great! Nothing is going to stop me, that include my oral I took in school today... My teacher said "___ (fill in whatever names you want), speak louder" OR "___, widen your vocab and talk more about the picture" -____- ANYWAY, I am trying to improve my settings and lots of interesting stuff. I not only want my blog to be a diary, but also a place to chat and escape from reality for a few hours....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I really loved Archie's Comics. Ya know, on monday, at 5pm, on Kids Central, there is Archie's Weird Mysteries.... I always buy their comics when I have the money (it ranges from $4- $6) And I have quite a lot at home. Mostly Archie's pals and gals comic book. I have to hide it, if not, my father will chop my head before I can say "Let me explain..." At least Archie's pals and gals is worthwhile, you read everybody's stories and interesting way of life. YOU can say I am mad about Archie. They are a break from the reality where there are no such people... But I like Betty, she is so sweet... (0'-'0)    Congratulations, you're like Betty...You are sweet and kind and know what you want, you are mostly full of positive energy. People adore you for your sweet natured self.    urlLink   What Archie Comics Character Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      GB Day... Very sian....(so wierd for me to write in hokkien!) Really! I came at 6.41 am instead of the usual 7.15am in the morning. I was yawning all the way to the parade square and when forming the contingent. The downside was that I had to stand in front. What's worse was that my form teacher kept looking at me as he could not look for my other classmates... *Ggrrrr* The devotion was long, the GB Day speech was long and the announcement was ssssoooo long.... And one of our girls fainted. So embarrassing. I mean, at least squat down, don't fall right onto the ground. It was so loud and at least 4- 5 teachers went to her aid. Jeezz... Nobody was treated like her, ya know... massage by the captain, hot drink and she took off her hat. If any girls faint, we only had water to drink and sit down on the floor. So unfair. I never even once fainted during drill or any event... I really do not know if it is lucky or unfortunate. But I really hope that any uniform groups students, please eat breakfast. If you know you can't tahan without breakfast, PLEASE EAT!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That, is so fake. And sssooooo very fake...    Beauty Queen! aahh you beauty queen you.. all the make up.. and hairspray... and fake boobs! well, at least you are pretty n stuff.. woo hoo.    urlLink   What Kind of Queen Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      If everybody thinks I am a happy- go- lucky person. They are so wrong. I juz read a St Margaret's girl's blog. She relate her uncertain future and her curently 5 subjects. I mean, at least her english is very very good. She gets an A1 or A2, me? Hah! I got a C6, a passing grade. Damn... Ohhh, by the way, ES (Enrolment Shit) is at last over. But so so boring. We were in the chapel yesterday instead of the usual Sunday. And it WAS so boring. We sang, saw the colours, I mean colourful flags... And we ate. But the food was so urgghh, so I never eat much. I later went to PS but again so boring even with my friends... Today, my family and I went to Yum Cha. BUT the service was so bad that after eating a few plates, we went to a coffee shop and enjoyed a cheaper and delicious dim sum. A word of caution, Yum Cha's food or service is not the best. My family and even my relatives said so... Now YOU know....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I almost mistook it for my bro's hp.....    Nokia 6100 is the phone for you. You always do what you are told. You never make mistakes - or atleast you try not to. You get upset easily when what you have plan need to be changed, especially at the last minute.    urlLink   Which Nokia Cellphone is Most Suitable for You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man, I am so vexed and sick. I mean, not sick in terms of illness, but sick and tired of studies. What is worst is that I realised that my school's so- called E- learning portal has recorded my website as I had put in my e- mail. ShIt! I am dead. If ANYBODY inocently clicked to either me or another classmate's website (there are only 2 of us with websites), I am as good as a dead chicken. (;-_-;) I think I have to change the website. Hiazzz.... Oh, can somebody pray for me that I will prevent myself from falling asleep during ES? It will be very tiring and I hate photo- taking session.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *{MY CONDOLENCE TO THE IRAN TWINS, LALEH & LADAN. ALTHOUGH THEY HAVE LEFT, THEIR SPIRITS TO LIVE SEPARATELY WILL BE EMBEDDED DEEP IN OUR HEARTS.... }*  That was the message I have wrote and I hope the Iran twins will be happy in heaven. It is so sad to see the news, everybody was crying and tears as big as diamonds were silently rolling down their cheeks.   Ok, on a much happier tone... I have bought the i- weekly, the chinese magazine that is Mediacorp's NOT Mediaworks. And I bought the cover with Edison and Ah- Sa. They looked so loving. (-_-;) Anyway, the other cover looked cool and mature with Ekin and Ah- kiu. Aaahhh...... I did not have enough money, if not I would have bought both covers. *blush* 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The deepest secret is that I should never have taken this quiz. So Pathetic....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        YOU ARE MARRIED TO A WoODCHUCK!!!    urlLink   what's YOUR deepest secret?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ya, ya, I know...    You are a child's kiss.  Completely sweet and innocent and pure. You mean no harm and only love in your sweet kisses.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanx for the results! That is sssooooo comforting..... -_-   urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Put in a chatter box. Just seeing how it goes before making any changes....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I will be short and quick. - Went to school - Came back from school after a brain- draining session with Maths - Sat at the computer from 6pm till now - Did home work and ate dinner - Sad and depressed. The Iran twins passed away within 1 hour each. Died due to loss of blood. Heard that the Raffles Hospital shares dropped quite a lot. At least they spent 29 years together and lived a fulfilled and meaningful life.... Hope they are happy in heaven.... God Bless Them.... - Right now typing and waiting for the news on the Iran Twins....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Youth day today and not going out to celebrate. -_- My  beloved  brother had requested my mother to buy him a new handphone. And my mother  really  bought him a 6610 Nokia handphone and he is right now beside me playing games with his friends on the hp. And I am still using 8250 Nokia hp. *steam brewing out of my ears* 0_0 But yesterday was very enjoyable and fun for me.... My family and I went to opp. Bugis Junction, a very small Hong Kong Steamboat retaurant. Their service was quite good, even though I spilled my very hot Tom Yam soup on my pants. *Blushing* I really enjoyed it. I recommend this retaurant to all of you. Especially the health- conscious people out there. Their Tom Yam Soup is very spicy and good. And the fee is $15.80 for adults and $12.80 for children below 12. But if you want cheap steamboat, go to Marina Bay. They are famous for steamboats and cheap $12 rating for adults. Except that there is not air- conditioned. So far, I had 2 steamboats at Marina Bay, 2 at my friend's house, 1 at my Grandpa's house and 1 in my very own house and 1 at that HK restaurant. That's 7 steamboats I ate in all.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. Nice picture 2. I am not lost 3. I do no believe in fairies    you're the lost fairy:  you dont know what you are.. you think you're very misunderstood. give people a chance to see the real you, let them know "hey! i'm in the room!"... dont just be the one in the shaded corner with nothing to say.    urlLink   what fairy best fits you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heard cosplayers LOVE to cosplay them... They surely have an interesting sense of fashiooonnn....    Yay! You're intense Kyo! You stand there, hiding behind your hands, staring at whoever's in front of you like you want to eat them!    urlLink   Which Version of Kyo (Dir en Grey) Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changed a little on the settings. No tution tomorrow. *Fist in the air* YES! But have to finish my holiday homework. For your info, tomorrow is YOUTH DAY! But I pity my senior, she starts her poly days tomorrow. On the other hand, she spent 10 months lazing around in her house. No working. Amazing, right? She insisted that she would only work as a secretary BUT never as a fast- food person. And she got c++ for her 'O's. And her pronouncation is very, very, bad. OK, enough about her... Going out later in the afternoon. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tried to include my birthday in the settings. Hope everybody can have a go to guess my birthday.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday, Friday, Independance Day and a day for Akiko to be absent in school with the lamest excuse she said. "I've got a stomach ache". And yesterday there was a celebration for Youth Day! DAMN! Anyway, caught up with HP Bk 5 and managed to finish it at about 6pm during this evening reading from Friday to today. In the morning, I went back to school for  Rehersal  (have to stress that...) For Enrolment Service. JEEZZZ.... Okay, back to the book, then the Enrolment Shit. Harry Potter in this book is, eerrmm, like a little harsh and arragont and hot- tempered. Well, who can blame him if he is kept in the dark and he still did not know about his past. I am very disappointed. The ending was so abrupt, at least revealed what he got for his OWLs, like our 'O' Levels.... Well, his godfather died and I felt no feelings. J. K. Rowling cried after 'killing' him. But Harry Potter should be of course sad and grieving but he should also be relieved that his godfather saved him in order to help Harry Potter to live and in turn, Harry Potter gained more friends and knew his past and his future too, where he have to fight with Dark Lord as only one of them could survive.... HP Bk 6 should be quite thrilling. I have also come to realise that Harry Potter is no romantic guy. He REALLLY did not know what is a girl feeling or thinking. I never like Cho Chang to be with Harry Potter. So, imagined the relief when I read that they broke off. I mean, no hard feelings, Cho Chang deserved a better guy to love and care for her. And Harry Potter needs a girl who really understands his feelings and thoughts. OK, back to ES (short form for enrolment shit) I never put bad words unless I really, really hate that event or particular person. So, think how I hate this 'stuff'. Hah! No parade and the whole morning and afternoon BB and GB were rehersing again and again.... I was so hungry and we still had to recieve the badges. I only recieved 1 badge and not promoted to staff sergent. DAMN! X2 And we still had to stand between the BB boys. Jeezzz... It has been 2- 3 years since we done this " Highly and Dangerous Performance" So that part we spent a lot of time and effort on it.... The singing part was so boring. I never even open my golden mouth. If they ever ask me to sing, which they never, I will tell them I had SORE THROAT! Well, the event is next week and I really dont feel like going. But for the sick of my CCA points, I will grit my teeth filled with braces and do it....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, by the way, I GOT HARRY POTTER 5TH BOOK! Yeah! My godma bought it for me. But I am not prepared to read, I heard it is a bit scary and bloody, somebody died and I heard the comedy was not sufficient. So, I let my brother read it first before handing back to me. Anyway, my english teacher phobited us to read...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I watched '' The Twins Effect''. *in a sing- song voice* Special effects, very GOOD, well, one of the Vampire Hunters died, kind of sad and tears welled up in my eyes. Hey! I am also very sentimental, ya know.... In the end, two vampire hunters became three.... One is a half- vampire, the other is a sentimental vampire, and the other is the sentimental vampire's lover. You try to guess it yourself. I can't reveal too much. It is only the first day.... Oh, halfway through the movie, I rushed to the loo A.K.A the toilet. I can't tahan, bladder was swelling and bloated. So I missed a small part where Jackie Chan fought the vampires. I am so sorry to the audience that I had stepped on their feet. *blushed* I was seated at the back and in the middle, a little difficult and tedious. Sorry again to those audience who read this blog. I was at J8 watching the 4.40pm show. Haiz... A- maths never do and heck it. I am so confused with v-t and x- t graphs and the word problems. And I HATE  sketching  graphs. I mean, you draw will be better, why sketch when the results and answers are easily shown by drawing graphs? Jeezz... Hate A- Maths. Hate 'O' Levels. Hate Life.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Use to like this anime a lot. But lost touch with it since studying in secondary school    Sailor Moon  You are the leader of the Sailor Scouts - but you're also a bit of a klutz! In the end you always seem to make the right decision though - even if you take a long time getting to it!    urlLink   Which Sailor Scout Are You? (With Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why I happen to watch this anime and fell in love with it? It had such a long story... Initially, I went to my Grandpa'a house and was so bored that I went and watched SCV Cable and came upon AXN. And they were having a marathon that showed GALAXY ANGELS for a few hours long with about a few minutes of breaks. I watched from the afternoon till the night and IMMEDIATELY fell in love with their comedy, dirty jokes and sweetness. Although they were in Jap, luckily, the subtitles were in Eng... So end of my summarised story. I am getting quite good at it...     You are mint. You are clever and sensitive. Always thinking of others before yourself.    urlLink   What Galaxy Angel are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tried to download J. K.Rowling at the London Somewhere (?) Hall. Unsuccessful, I am using BroadBand and the result is still so slow. Never mind, I will try later in the night....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, here goes....    2 MORE DAYS TO THE RELEASE OF -+-THE TWINS EFFECT-+-......  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! First day back to school, is like, =_=. I watched Jing Tian Yi (the Jap detective) that night.... Don't like this version of this actor. So thin and the mouth likea beak. -_- But I still like to watch the Jap detective series. I mean, it is like the plot is so scary and the murderer is so unexpected. But their reason is very reasonable. And the story behind their revenge is always a sad one. *sob sob* It always leaves me thinking and treasure my family and close ones.... Anyway, we had a new time table AGAIN. I mean, we have already changed twice and this was the 3rd time.... Oh, I almost forgot today is NCC Day. I was like, came out of the class and shocked to see a big group of army guys and suave guys in white. *_* OK, back to reality. And whats more, Upper Sec were shifted and standing in front and the way the NCC (SEA) commander shouted...  Whoa, So Up Close. I do hope to !forget! that GIRLS BRIGADE DAY IS TWO WEEKS FROM NOW... On the 14th July. Haiz... And our school's GB and BB enrolment is NEXT WEEK. I hate memorising the speech and singing the GB and BB Theme Song AND standing UP and DOWN.... At least there is no parade... This year Sec 1's are so DAMN lucky. I have been enduring the heat for 3 years AND I was not even in the G.O.H. -____- 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bored, Bored, BORED!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK, if anybody wants to leave a message in the Guestbook and cannot access. Please juz type something in the Tagboard, I really appreciate your efforts. Thanks!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      In book, I love his comical and loyalty. In movie, I love his humor and looks. But he is 1 year- old younger than me. *boo hoo*    Rupert Grint/Ron Weasley! *whootwhoot* Go Rupert Grint Fans. I'm one my self ^_^    urlLink   ---Which Harry Potter Actor are You Doomed to be With?---     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love: My pillows, my blogger and errmmm.... I hate: my biase family and education I cry: Just yesterday... I fear: death, really I hope: peace and freedom I sadden: When I am depressed I kill: no one, in reality I talk: myself in my heart I listen: To S.H.E's Superstars I hold: my life I work: anything I need to finish I remember: something, errmm... Whats izzit again? I read: books.... -_______- I breathe: oxygen. What do you expect? I hide: everything in my heart I play: errrmm.... I miss: the things I have lost I touch: my 'mouse' now  I learn: stuff and something like that.... I feel: depressed... I know: everything that needs to be known I say: my mouth is zipped I dream: errrmmm... I have: a lot of stuff. Where should I start first? I want: Super dollfie, Blythe and many stuff... I fall: In Love? nah, never... I wait: for my education to end.... I need: peace and quiet  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      PAST [kindergarten teacher's name] Errrmmm.... [first grade teacher's name] Ermmm x2 [second grade teacher's name] Ermmm x3 [third grade teacher's name] Ermmm x4 [fourth grade teacher's name] Ermmm x5 [fifth grade's teacher's name]  Ermmm x6 [sixth grade's teacher's name] Ermmm x7 [last word spoken] Shit... [last song sung] You Are My SuperStar...  PRESENT [in cd player] S.H.E's Superstars [on feet] Shoeless [under bed] Air, polluting air [what time you got up] 10.20am, lazy   FUTURE [you want to go to] Japan, must learn their language [ideal job] Designer for anything.... [probable job] A teacher [you want to live (place)] An unknown place, quiet and peaceful [number of children you want] none [kind of car] small and kawaii, like volkswagen  CURRENT [mood] depressed, tution [music] S.H.E's Superstars [taste] My morning breakfast [hair] Straight and rebonded a few months ago....  [attire] loose t-shirts and shorts [annoyance] I HAVE TUTION TODAY! [smell] My BO? [longing] Able to free from education... [desktop image] Eyetide's screensaver [fav. music artist] None, very random [toenail color] clear [crush] Hideaki Takizawa, Wong Lee Hom and other boyish- look guys  [time-wasting wish] To be free from education, what crap... [hate] My plump body
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, today is Teachers' Day and it finally was over... *whew* (^o^) The performance, as they said was meant for the teachers. But it think it was meant for the students more. SoNgS and DaNcE repeating over and over again.... I think the only programme the teachers loved was the cutting of the 6kg (that was what they said) cake and we, the graduating classes singing very noisy song up from the top. Jeezz, I know coz I have a auntie who is a primary teacher. She never really like the performance but appreciates it as the students have put in their best. The Power Of Teaching.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I am  so  on the mood to skip school becasuse there is Teachers' Day tomorrow. Not trying to say the teachers suck, it's just that the performance suck. We, the graduating classes have to sing and  surprise  the erm, teachers... And what's more, the song is  so  not matching.... Anyway, at least we are able to release a little bit earlier. Listening to S.H.E's track 7, quite nice and melodious with some rap....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I have 10 min to write before my time is up for my rother to use the com... Nothing much in school today, just trying to finish the weekdays as quickly as possible... And use up my weekends as slowly as possible.... (^0^) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man, I am so damn exhausted. BOTH mentally and physically exhausted.... And my dearest mother wanted me to trade in my new HP to a cheaper one. just because her dearest son wanted a Nokia 7250 too.... *GGGGRRRR* (>- 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ya, I know, I sound weired with the name Gothic in my title. Just experimenting and it is fun to be kind of dark and black for a while...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got a new name, and it is called "Senko". I am so happy. ''Keiji Miyako'', I got it from M1's Funbox, ''papusza'' and ''Akiko'', I got it from a website. Now I have 4 names. I am so happy, Senko sounds nice, like a warrior or fighter... Oh, today, the Love Hina show is so touching. It is like the male character found a doll that can move herself and talk. And conincidentally, the doll belonged to the male character's great grandfather. So, naturally, the doll is attached to the male character. And in the end the doll stopped working, so sad, I mean it is like you seem to know her for a long time, caring and loving her, and she just stopped and everything has ended. Maybe, maybe, the doll will be back when the male character's son or grandson visit her again....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi!Early in the morning(so-called early) I am home alone, sort of. Anyway, I am quite bored. Not interested in X-Men Evolution 2 today, coz something bad is going to happen in this episode. I also never watched Xiao Qian yesterday night. Too tired even though I drank coffee, muz be the cause of tution, espescially chem tution. Mybe watching Kim Possible at noon after that. Want to watch Fabric Of the Nation on Channel News Asia but the speech so long, will watch the news on Channel 8 tonight. Haiz... my block downstairs is building a stage and it is so noisy and afterwards, there will be annoying kids jumping on the stage *BOOM BOOM* My RC sucks. Will also be checking the music store later to see how the S.H.E album looks like....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday, watched A Chinese Ghost Story on Channel U. It can be roughly translated as Qian Niu You Heun (something like that lah). A lot of special effects, cannot really see what the action was about and what was going on. All I knew was that the Star Crossed Lovers were seperated at birth and they met again under very unfavourable conditions and vowed to stay together. Well, the starting point was very touching especially the lead actor talked about how love is all about and he hoped that he never met Xiao Qian before coz it would bring pain to both their hearts. ...>_ very fun * events in my school next week... -__________- (That is the longest frown I have ever made)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, I forgot to announce, I bought the The Dog from McDonalds.... YES! And today was the first day of promotion, I love this kind of feeling. Like you get it first and not anybody else (maybe not in my class..). This feeling will only apply to my Harry Potter movie and books and McDonalds' stuff. BUT never Hello Kitty OR  Finding Nemo.... The Beagle so furry and soft and fits for any sizes of heads (o_0).It is just like a mini cushion, you can carry it around wherever and whenever you are... Gosh, I sounded so much like a advertiser....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah, 1 more day till weekend... Also 1 more day till more homework pile up... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1) If you could get another version of any of your body parts what would you get?  My whole plump and fat body... *ha ha ha*  2) What would you call your debut album?   I hate maths....  3) I'm a magical Fairy, would you like to be a Mermaid, a Princess or a angel?  A princess or either an angel. Coz both are so pure and sweet. Princess is rich while angel is sweet and what can I say? Like AN ANGEL!  4) Whats your favourite thing to do on a Saturday?  Wake up at 10 something. Watched Kids Central show while having breakfast. Watch until 12 something and surf the net till about 2 something while eating lunch. Then watch Love Hina and the Jap show about make-over and cosmetic surgery  5) If you had to banish one ice cream flavour, which one would you ban?  Nutty flavour. They cause me to let out poison gas and stuck onto my teeth... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think I will have at least two red marks in my report card again. Ya, should be like this... Damn...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am sssoooo exhausted. Watched the Fei Ge's show yesterday until 1am something... Ya, I know. i am not much of a night cat, that's why I am dragging my body and mind to school and dragging back a more smelly body and heavier mind  and   a heavier bag home..... Jeeezzz.... So, too tired to talk about how my birthday went. Just to tell you that I am experimenting with my 7250's camera and the photos, I must say, were quite good and professional.... But I cannot activate my GPRS, damn. Thanks to my brother who spent so much on his and my mother got scared already....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       16. Do fish have feelings?  No, I think, if you are going to relate to Finding Nemo. The ans. will be a stronger 'NO'  17. Are you trendy? Nah. But I know what is the latest stuff or fashion...  18. How do you release anger? I don't release, I squeezed into my heart and it bleeds...  19. Where are your second homes?  The net.. *ha ha*  21. What was your favorite toy as a child?  Barbie and lego  22. What class in school do you think is totally useless? The science and maths...  24. Have you ever been on radio or television? -____-  25. Do you have a journal? Dose this blog counts?  26. Do you use sarcasm a lot? No.....  27. Have you ever been in a mosh pit?  ???  28. What do you look for in a guy/girl?  Their character...  29. What are your nicknames? Akiko, papusza, keiji miyako... Wait a minute, isn't that my names?  30. Would you bungee? On a confident day(which is so rare)  31. Do you untie your shoes when you take them off? No, I am so lazy, that's why I spoiled so many so them...  32. What are you worried about right now? Well, my new handphone cost a lot. And my father was not very happy with me. Yyyyaaa, it is always his son clever, his son can have everything....  33. Do you ever wear overalls? No. Not right now...  34. Do you think that you are strong? Both physically and mentally, no.  35. What's your favorite ice cream flavor?  Vanilla and fruity flavours  36. What's your favorite colours?  Orange and happy colours  37. What is your least fav. thing in the world?  No peace in the world, that means war  38. How many wisdom teeth do you have? I  think four, according to my memory from the x- rays last year...   39. Are you in love with anyone?  No.  40. How many people have a crush on you right now?  That will be never one...  41. Who do you miss most right now?  My lost things which I have lost it...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My Birthday and it is also Indonesia's national day. Well, no offense but I just worry that something might happen in Indonesia right now... Who knows? I got a new HANDPHONE! It is 7250 NOT 7250i, -_-. Never mind, at least I got a new one, not a second or hand- me- down handphone from my  beloved  brother. Charging for 9 hours now, and trying to take very pofessional pictures with their built- in camera....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       1. Name  : Same as the below, go read it.  2. Were you named after anyone?  : Ummm... No  3. Do you wish on stars?  I will never be able to see the stars, Singapore is too  bright   4. Which finger is your favorite?  Pinky  5. When did you last cry?  A few days ago...  6. Do you like your handwriting?  Ummm... i can always improve on it  7. Any bad habits?  Too many to fill in here...  9. What is your most embarrassing CD on the shelf?  Aaron Kwok. Don't feel offended coz I bought his cantonese version and I dont UNDERSTAND?!?!   10. If you were another person, would you be friends WITH you?  Ummm. Maybe she 'know' me deep enough  11. Are you a daredevil?   No. And I never even watch daredevil....  12. Have you ever told a secret you swore not to tell?  Oh, LOTS of times  13. Do looks matter?  Sometimes. It depends.  14. Have you ever misused a word and it sounded absolutely stupid?  Always in the blog...  15. Do you think there is a pot of gold at the end of the rainbow?  Well, I think in Singapore, it will never happen. Coz people will go and snatch it, we are just so money- faced... (No Offense) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1.FULL NAME: You really want the full name? Here it goes: Akiko Papusza Keiji Miyako, which one? Up to you... 2. WHAT COLOUR PANTS ARE YOU WEARING? Pale pink 3. WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RIGHT NOW? Chinese food show coming from the TV 4. WHAT ARE THE LAST 4 DIGITS OF YOUR PHONE NUMBER? 2813  5. WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU ATE? --KFC-- 6. IF YOU WERE A CRAYON, WHAT COLOUR WOULD YOU BE? Orange! I love orange!!!   7. LAST PERSON YOU TALKED TO ON THE PHONE? So far, it was my friend yesterday...  8. THE FIRST THING YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE OPPOSITE SEX? Their face???  9. FAVOURITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK Does Tiger Beer count? But I am underaged.. 10. FAVOURITE SPORTS? None. But if I have to choose one, it will be swimming coz I have taken up before...  11. HAIR COLOUR? Black. Will be dying it to copper brown or brown... 12. EYE COLOUR? Brown, I heard there is no such thing as black... 13. SIBLINGS AND THEIR AGES? Haiz... A brother, aged 15 and talking on the phone to his girlfriend and HE IS A BOY!! 14. FAVOURITE MONTHS? August! My birthday! 15. LAST MOVIE YOU WATCHED? The League Of The Extraordinary Gentlemen. *whew, title so long* 16. ARE YOU TOO SHY TO ASK SOMEONE OUT ? Yup. 17. DO U LIKE SUMMER OR WINTER BEST? Winter. My country got no winter leh. 18. HUGS OR KISSES? Hugs. More warmth and cuddly 19. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA? Vanilla. I liked it simple 20. WHAT BOOKS ARE YOU READING? HP 5- FINISHED. Love to read Amazons and Swallows, something like that. it is about sea and sailing, so peaceful... 21. THE FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING? I am going back to ssssllleeeppp....  22. WHAT TYPE OF FLOWER WOULD YOU LIKE TO RECEIVE? Sunflower. Very  BIG   mah...  23. WHAT'S YOUR FAVOURITE CHOC? Anything chocolate will do. I am not that crazy about chocolate....  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I looked left, I met tears, unhappiness and sorrow, I looked right, I was welcomed by hope, choices and confidence, I looked straight, I saw my future uncertain, I looked back, I saw my past tiredness...  Then I remembered it is my BIRTHDAY TOMORROW!!!! I told myself I must never be depressed, at least till after tomorrow.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha! Ha! Ha! I am going amok, crazy, siao.... I have changed over a thousand (Just Kidding) backgrounds. And I finally found this pleasing and nice one. Firstly, I have the CCS, then to other CCSs' wallpaper and then I changed into a car but looked too solemn and dull. Now I have this character from Love Hina, forgot her name, I think she is the girl every time holding the sword or something...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I changed my title again. Adapted from my Eyetide Viewer's screensaver. I love their screensaver, you download it for free and even if you select the free ones (NOT the expensive ones), the pictures are just so beautiful... You can even select one of their pictures to my desktop wallpaper, but you must once in a while go and update it. The picture was taken during the sunset at a seashore, so enchanting and calming to my tense nerves.... Go and download now! ---http://www.eyetide.com/index.jsp---
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate home work..... I want to do my quizzes.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *singing* I HAVE A NEW BACKGROUND, I HAVE A NEW BACKGROUND!!!! YES!!! All thanks to Cutie Issac's premade backgrounds. He actually meant it for neopets' username lookup, but I managed to put it into the template without anybody's help. I AM SO HAPPY!!! (^-^) It's actually very easy to many computer expert but for me, a country girl, I am so happy. The only downside is that Cardcaptor sakura's face is cut and the font is not my desired font and I could not change it. Haizz.... anyway, I am so exhubilant (spelling maybe wrong again)... But please, I am not so girly that I have changed both my background and GB's background to Cardcaptor sakura. It just that I lke CCS a lot and cutie Issac's majority backgrounds are CCS... Happy reading!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sick, sick, sick..... =____= Very tired and sian.... Sure got red marks in report card....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Personal:   Who is your role model:  Errmmm, people who knows how to enjoy life?  Have you ever liked someone you had no chance with:  Ya, in my dreams  Have you ever cried over the opposite sex:  Never  Do you have a "type" of person you always go after:  Errmmm, gothic or lolita kind of image  Ever wanted to get revenge on someone because they hurt you:  Ya, but....  Are you the dumper or dumped:  Dumped, I guess  Rather have a relationship or a "hookup":  None, they suck  Want someone you don't have right now:  Ya, a lot  Ever liked your best guy/girl friend:  NEVER!  Do you want to get married:  Nope  Do you want kids:  Maybe in the future....  What is your favorite part of your physical appearance:  My crooked teeth  What is your favorite part of your emotional being:  Depressed  Are you happy with you:  Nope, never  Are you happy with your life:  Never, hate it   If you could change something in your life right now, what would it be?  My family, friends, education and life 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Social Life:   Best girl friend:  My dolls  Best guy friend:  My male dolls  Boyfriend/Girlfriend:  Nope  If no, current dating partner:  Nobody  Hobbies:  Surfing the net, drawing and ecsaping from reality  Pager:  Handphone, no pager  Are you center of attention or the wallflower:  Wallflower, I am so damn quiet lor  What type automobile do you drive:  I am only sixteen!!!  What type automobile do you wish you drove:  A volkswagen...  Would you rather be with friends or on a date:  I rather be alone...  Where is the best hangout:  In front of the com  Do you have a job:  Nope.  Do you attend church:  I am not a christen!!!  Do you like being around people:  Never 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       In The Last 48 Hours, Have You:   Cried:  In the morning... STRESS  Bought something:  Nope, I am rotting in my house  Gotten sick:  Wish to  Sang:  Too many people  Eaten:  I just have my lunch  Been kissed:  Never  Felt stupid:  Ya, right now, everytime  Wanted to tell someone you loved them:  How I wish...  Met someone new:  On the internet, ya  Moved on:  Huh???  Talk to an ex:  Just a few days ago  Missed an ex:  Never  Talked to someone you have a crush on:  Never. Hiaz....  Had a serious talk:  I never opened my mouth since a three days ago...   Missed someone:  Ya....  Hugged someone:  *^.^*  Fought with your parents:  I screamed at them...  Dreamed about someone you can't be with:  Ya, I have fantasy so many times 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       DO YOU   Color your hair?  I used to, it stayed for quite a long while, Hate It  Have tattoos?:  No, Will never have in the future  Have piercings below the waist?:  Nope, Hate body piercings  Have a boyfriend/girlfriend/both?  Nah... Never  Own a webcam?  I wish to...  Own a thong?:  *blush blush*  Ever get off the damn computer?  Yup,in a few moments' time    HAVE YOU/DO YOU/ARE YOU...   Stolen anything over $50?  Never, I am so innocent  Obsessive?  For my Super Dollfie, cartoon dolls and any dolls related stuff  Panic?  Exams, thats why I hate exams  Anxiety?  Exams too  Depressed?   Everytime, even right now  Suicidal?  Thought of, scared to do it 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       HAVE YOU   Fallen for your best friend:   Never, my friends are females, I am not a lesbian!  Made out with JUST a friend:  Errmmm, so far, no such incidents  Been rejected:  By who? I think never, unless....  Been in love:  Ummmm, maybe in the future  Been in lust?:  Of course, everybody does that  Used someone?:  Sometimes...  Been used:  Sometimes...  Been kissed?: Never *SOB SOB* Done something you regret?:  Once or twice, like a knot in my heart, cannot be untied... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ya, I know, I did it for fun. All of you can get to know me deeper and better. I am addicted to Quizes.... AAAGGGHHH!!!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       WHO:   Makes you laugh the most:   Myself, I LOVE MYSELF!!!  Makes you smile:  Myself again...  Can make you feel better no matter what:  Myself and my blog...  Has A Crush On You:  Nobody, who will love me?  Do You Have A Crush On Someone:  Maybe in the future...  Who Has it easier? Girls or Guys:  The guys! Be it physically or mentally or emotionally    DO YOU EVER:   Sit by the phone waiting for a phone call all night:  I need my beauty sleep!!!   Save AOL conversations:  No, never  Save Emails:  Ya, I have short- term memory   Wish you were someone else:  Lots of times, I have fantasy on that  Wish you were a member of the opposite sex:  Nope, that sounds so cruel and harsh 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       WHAT IS (your favorite):   Your Good Luck Charm:  Anything that has sentimental value with me   Person You Hate Most:  My family...  Best Thing That Has Happened to You this year:  I dropped to sub- science, that is also the worst thing that has happened to me  Color:  Orange  Movie:  I have no idea, but I love comedy plus romantic to be pumped into movie  Juice:  Orange juice  Finger:  Pinky, the cutest...  Ice Cream:  Vanilla, natural's the best  Shoes:  Sports shoes and sandels  Season:  Authum and winter, you cannot experience it right here in Singapore  Breakfast Food:  Eggs and bacon or porridge, I love this kind, no bread please. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       HAVE YOU EVER...   Kissed your cousin:  Nope. I think that suck  Ran away:  How I wish I have the courage...  Pictured your crush naked:  Errrmmm, I want to *^.^*  Broken someone's heart:  Maybe in the future...  Been in love:  I love somebody, but nobody loves me... *wah!!*  Cried when someone died:  In the movie...>_  Wanted someone:  Ya, a lot...  Broken a bone:  Nope, I have calcium!!!  Lied:  In critical times, like real...  Cried in school:  Cried in public in pri schl, secretly in sec sch...  Coke or Pepsi:  Coke  Sprite or 7UP:  Sprite for my ice- cream float, 7UP still manufacturing meh?  Girls or Guys:  Girls, eerrmm, for what?  Flowers or candy:  Candy, last longer...  Tall or Short:  Tall, like model  Pants or Shorts:  Pants, I have ugly legs... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      36. Least favorite color?:  Green  37. Do you value your friends?:  Sometimes....  38. Do you value your family?:  Sometimes again...  39. Do you value your stuff?:  Oh, very, very much...  40. Do you self-mutilate?:  Nope, obviously not  41. Do other people mutilate you?:  Errrmmm, maybe...  42. Have you ever been beaten up before?:  Maybe in the future...  43. Have you ever beaten anyone else up before?:  Maybe in the past...  44. What's your favorite animal?:  A dog, domestic animals...  45. What's your favorite desert?:  Honeydew sago, mostly sweet stuff...   46. How old are you... mentally?:  Smaller than my age, I am so immature...  47. What's your favorite "smiley face"?:  -_-, maybe not that smiley lah...  48. People most often refer to you as:  As quiet as a lamb (O.o)  49. What is your favorite quote?:  Damn, I do not have one, how???  50. What will you do now??:  Finish education and escape reality... Yup, I want to fulfill it... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of these days, ya, I will worship her....     You are "Saint Barbie"    urlLink   Which Mark Ryden Painting Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      21. In what color do you see the world?:  A little orange, blue and red and black...  22. Why?:  Becoz I wan ppl to be happy but war is also going on....  23. How often do you swear?:  Not much... *^_^*  24. How often do you swear at other people?:  A little, not much... ^_-  25. How does this make you feel?:  Relieved and guilty...  26. Are you on some kind of medication?:  Nope, I am very healthy...  27. Do you think you need it?:  I think I need it for depression....  28. Right now, who/what do you feel like hugging?:  My plushie and pillows (^_^)  29. Name 3 songs you'd listen to right now:  jay Chou, Ayumi hamasaki, S Club  30. List 3 people who's voices you'd like to hear right now:  A loved and caring voice, that will be counted as 3...  31. What is your favorite noise?:  Techno?!?  32. What is your favorite word?:  Love  33. What is your favorite color?:  Orange  34. What is your least favorite noise?:  Techno again...  35. Least favorite word?:  All those vulgar and bad words... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      16. Have you ever been hit before?:  Errmmm, face by my father when I was young, but mostly to body area, mother caned me mah...  17. Where were you hit?:  In my own house?  18. By what?:  Bare hands and canes  19. Did it hurt?:  OF COURSE, what did you expect? *ouch*  20. Is the glass half-empty or half-full?:  half- full, muz top up! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      In the morning, between 7.25 am - 10 something am: * Had the usual parade march-in and school song and national anthem * Began to sing the lame songs * Began to give out colours awards that I cannot get *ggrrr* * March past, everybody march like..... -_- * Song was interrupted (what happened?) * Jack Neo came to our school to promote his film, oh, we were going as a whole school to Lido, Orchard to watch Homerun * Media came, pretend, pretend....  In the mid- morning to afternoon: * Able to watch the film after so many hassle and trouble, crossing road, squeezing in MRT, wearing red and white badges  * Quite meaningful and touching, I was so surprised that I never cry.... * Dismissed after the movie ended and we went to PS to eat * Hate the food, wasted so much money * Went back to Orchard becoz I had feelings for it.... Saw not much of our school people, WHERE HAVE THEY GONE!?!  A little tired that's why cut short my exactly 12 hours journey, but I went back home and had my neo print pictures taken, I looked so fierce lor... Haiz, shy, shy... *^_^*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. List in order, your top 5 most desired super-human powers:  able to teleport, run through walls, fly, invisible and a genius (is that a super- human power?)  2. What do you like best about yourself, emotionally?:  able to cry when really, really, really depressed   3. What do you like best about yourself, physically?:  I have beautiful hands? What crap....  4. Do you bathe in the mornings?:  no, unless for GB day, THAT'S ALL...  5. Do you bathe in the evenings?:  I bath in the afternoons, right after school...  6. How many times, in a week, would you say you've washed yourself?:  7 times for bathing and 14 times for washing face or parts of body....  7. Do you flex in the mirror?:  what's that? I think no  8. Do other people find you attractive?:  surely, of course, positvely, nnnnoooo  9. Do you find yourself attractive?:  Nah... -_-  10. List 5 things you hate about yourself:  Plump, flabby arms, uneven teeth, pimpled face and small eyes  11. List 10 things you like about yourself:  eerrmm... Gd Character and so- called a teacher's pet (that adds up to 10 and above :P)  12. List 5 people you care about online: The SD bloggers and the cosplay bloggers, surely that is more than 5 right?  13. List 5 people you care about in real life:  My family, hey! Just nice, 5 persons!  14. Overall, do you love yourself?:  Yup, OF COURSE!  15. Are you more happy, than not?:  I think I am more depressed...     There are at least 35 more que, I will post it at a later date.....  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      NDP EVE TOMORROW!!! YES!!! I love NDP, especially the parade (not the school  -_-) when everybody is working so hard to perform properly and it is especially more meaningful if you have participated in it before. But I kind of hate seeing Stephanie Sun singing this year's NDP song. I think she should not be singing again, let somebody have a chance, girl, you are going to dominate the whole world if you continue and persist. I never get into the colours OR the merit awards, so sad ...>_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      What I have been doing this past few days...   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changed my title  again , *haha* Right now, I am doing three things. Eating, typing and reading... Ya, I know, it is so confusing and tedious. But I will do it just to let my father know I am multi- tasking, if not, he will disallow me to use the comp. Don't know what was wrong with Blogger this afternoon. Almost all other blogs cannot be opened and I spent 20 min trying to open and in vain... Anyway, I am trying to finish my packed dinner, GTG !!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know who is that the character from, COWBOY BEPOP!! And no, I am not a cute kid....    urlLink         Gimme something good!   urlLink Find out what anime character cliche  you are.   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      HI! Came back from Suntec and Little India. First, Suntec. I went to Suntec for the DJs stuff. Whoa... So up- close lor, and the DJs were so funny. That was one of the exhibit. The other one was the FOOD FEISTA, the food was so yum, yum and delicious. I tried the french fries with cheese sauce with my family, then had the penang laska, so spicy!! And then I had the Jollie Bean soya bean mixed with grass jelly, so sweet. And then, again, I had the portuguese tart, so different from egg tarts, I LOVE IT!!! I was so already so full and still my family and I went to Little India, the new shopping mall and had dinner  again . And we went to the shopping market where the suff were cheap, cheap and cheap! And I the Scott Plush Dog, so cute!! But you have to buy at least 2 jumbo tissue. Well, all for the sake of me....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Peach! YUM! YUM!       I took the fruity fruit quiz  made by  urlLink rav-chan    urlLink Check out which fruit you are   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have changed quite a lot to my template, WELCOME.... THE NEW MMMMMMEEEE!!!  (^.^)b
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Maybe   going to Suntec's Radio Deejay don't-know-what performance. That includes FM 93.3, 97.2 AND 95.8 (chinese stations). The contest is that the deejays will be split into two groups, the boys and the girls. SSSOOOO SEXIST!!! Not Fair.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Today read lots, I mean it, LOTS of livejournal's super dollfie's users. I want to log in as a livejournal user. But unless somebody is a friend of the LJ and so- called 'pick me', THEN I can log in as one.... BUT I am still very happy and satisfied as a Blogger user. DON'T KICK ME OUT! I really, really am hoping and wishing and praying for one Super Dollfie doll. The dolls look so nice with the eyes and beautiful face.... You can even customize it through esthetics (something-like-that, spelling maybe wrong), I really want it!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I changed my nickname, no, MY NAME, again... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My new name is AELI!!! ~_-    Your anime name is Aeli!  You're a good little sweetie!  You don't drink, don't do drugs, don't smoke-- You're just an angel!  =)  You're probably a little naive about some things, but that doesn't matter!  People love you because they know you won't lie about them or tell their secrets!!  Go you!    urlLink   What is YOUR Anime Name?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's cool......        urlLink What San-X Character Are You?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I want to cosplay!!! But i neither have the time, experience nor the confident although I almost know who are the 'famous' cosplayers in Singapore and U.S, I freqeuntly visit their websites mah... Hmmm, this schoolgirl costume very, very firmiliar. Fruits Basket? Evangelion? I DON'T KNOW!!       urlLink What Cosplay Type Are You?    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Left Ear listening to: Ayumi Hamasaki's remix Right Ear listening to: The channel 8's variety show My brain is responding to: Whether I am typing a sensible entry or not (O_o) My Heart is responding to: I do not care about anything . My body: I have to sit down, right?  Actually, I am trying a new way to write my entry. You can't always stick to the same hi-today-is-a-boring-day stuff.... -_- But of course, today was a little bit boring with some waste-the-time subjects and I think I will go into hiding.... Coz my friends knew my blog. Yeah, maybe to others it will be cool or popular. But to me, it is a diaster!!! Stupid me. Today I signed in one of my junior's autograph book and I  PROUDLY  -_- wrote my blog's address. UUURRRGGHHH!!!!!! I am as good as a roast duck (very juicy, nice to eat, yum, yum) Anyway, juz came home, I went with my mother and aunty to the Jade Crystal Xiao Long Bao Restaurant (name ssoo lloonnngg) to eat my favourite xiao long bao.... The restaurant is quite small but cosy. And we tried the la mien, I tried the suzchen style with hot hot soup! But it was not that hot or spicy at all. Except it was a little oily with all the peanut oil.... The xiao long bao was excellent, the soup inside the bao was little (all dripped away :p) but sweet. And the drunken chicken was a cold dish but full of wine smell, DELICIOUS!!! But the price ah, haiz.... So expensive, $41 for three persons including GST and +++...... But I always remember this trip as I really love xiao long bao!!??
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ya, I know, I am supposed to be in Hiatus mode but this stupid wedding I had attended just now made me wanted VERY VERY much to vent my anger and fustrations out here, right now! Ok, those civilians who were attending in the Swissotel Merchant Court, listen very carefully here. Coz there was only 1 wedding held there, they should know which couple I am referring to.... The dumb wedding was held from 7.00 to 10.30pm and that dinner only started at 8 something. The wedding sux. All those who attended weddings should know. The standing and watching the couple sssttrrrooollll and waiting for trainees waiter to serve the uuurrrgghhh food and standing up again for photos and the yyyuuummm- ssseeennnnggg...... >_ BELOVED  children to  everybody . His son was abled to study overseas through to UK and his daughter is in the U right now. Seeing them made my nerves go cold and hard. In the past, the 2 cousins of 'mine' were like dolls, mute. Now, they are immature dolls, their hair was like maggi mee and a yellow durian. I mean it may look good on others but not on these 2 ''dolls''.... So what they are graduates, hell to them!  P.S. The above mentioned people and place is real and out of my fustrations and anger, I typed here. Maybe tomorrow I will regret it and apologise. But right now, let me steam and burn.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I am on HIATUS MODE, so don't bother to view here until, maybe, christmas? Ya know, the usual hair-raising and nail-bitting experience is landing on me.... AARRRGGGGH!!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Urrgghh, I am so breathless. I just ate a sussage and a slice of bread. That was my lunch... And I think I almost burnt the whole kitchen, actually I only used the toaster. I could have cooked noodles myself but the stove made a 'click', 'click' sound, and I frightened myself by telling myself over and over again that if I cooked noodles, the whole kitchen would explode. Anyway, back to the toaster. The toaster was so black inside out and the 'door' was spoiled. Well, I have to make do with it. And I can say that I am a lousy toaster girl. Both my sussage and bread were toasted black. Well, partly to blame the toaster itself. *_* Drank cold coffee, could be the cause of stomach weirdness.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Summary from this morning till now... - I woke up at 7am, weird right? For a girl who suppose to sleep late coz today is Teacher's Day.... - Went to Grandfather's house, for breakfast and lunch - Spent the time there sleeping and lazying around... - Had lunch at 12.30pm  - Left Grandfather's house at 1pm with brother - Reached house at about 2pm plus - Tried to put ear stick into my yet- closing ears lobes... - Left side bled, now only 1 stick is sticking out of my right ear lobe. *ouch* - Painted my toe nails metallic pink - Regreted. Maybe should have bought the peach colour - Whatever.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! I am back, temporarily. Becoz I was bored and try to use up more of my time so that I can go to bed earlier.... Ya, kind of lame... (-_-) Anyway, juz update my blog here and introduce all of you to Domuya. Singapore's own Super Dollfie website, shop and forum. *YES!!!* I am so elated! Finally, Singapore had set up a shop that sells SD DOLLS! ^__^ Check out their website ---> http://www.domuya.com and join their forum! Will update more in a few weeks time. Be patient with me coz I will be very free after november for three months... (0^-^0)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ya, I know, it is big, it takes up a lot of space... But I am so desolate. How come, everybody is artistic and I am carefree?!    You're just the happy go-lucky type. You might have your pet peeves, but other than that, you're mainly calm. Blending in with your surroundings, you're the type of person who everyone likes. Usually it's you who cracks jokes at social gatherings - after all, laughter is the best medicine. Sometimes you pretend to be stupid, but in all actuality, you could be the next Einstein.    urlLink   What Type of Soul Do You Have ?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, how true...    A GIRLY-GIRL. You dont have a lot of self-esteem and people are always bringing you down for being sad. What do they know, anyway? You feel like youre too mature for your age and are frustrated by the trend-followers who refuse to accept you because youre not like them. Your virtues: Intelligence, understanding nature, modesty. Your flaws: Lack of social life, inferiority complex, timidity.    urlLink   What kind of girl are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *****DO YOU BELIEVE IN ****** 40. [yourself] Well, at times... 41. [friends] Hmmm... 42. [best friends of the opposite sex] Hmmm.... x2 43. [santa claus] Yup. I believe in him. That's why I love christmas! 44. [tooth fairy] Eeeww. Never again, after watching 'Darkness Falls' 45. [angels] Hmm... Maybe. 46. [ghosts] I hope I will not think that much. But I kinda believe in it... 47. [aliens] Nope. *I hope not* 48. [God] Ya... At times too... *No hard feelings*  *******MORE ABOUT YOU!******* 49. [what are the last four digits of ur phone number] Oh man, not again... 50. [Do you like the person who sent this to you] Actually, I kinda 'steal' it from someone... 51. [how do you eat an Oreo] You bite it and chew? No. I do not duck it inside milk and sing 'Oooorrreeeooo...' 52. [If you were a crayon what color would you be] Orange. Hmm... Maybe black. 53. [Have you ever almost died] Ermmm...  54. [What's the best advice ever given to you] Too many to write it down. Also lazy in the process... *_* 55. [Have you ever won any special award] Nope. How I wish...  56. [Do you like to dance] Nope. I tried Line- Dancing and I was so confused and dizzy that I swear never to dance again. No offence for dance- lovers though. 57. [Worst sickness you've ever had] Having fever and cold and cough all at once in the middle of the night while preparing for two stupid tests and going to school as per normal the next day to take the tests... *ggrrr* 58. [What's the stupidest thing you have ever done] Doing this quiz? *just kidding* 59. [What's the next CD you are going to buy] Maksim at the moment. 60. [What sport you hate the most] Everything, swimming maybe an exceptional... 61. [Place for a dream house] A small cottage by the sea- side... *so unrealistic*  62. [How many kids do you want to have] none. 63. [Have you ever sprained/broken/fractured a bone] Nope. Ermm... So lucky, right?  64. [Who do you tell your dreams to] My blog, but I never remember my dreams much.... 65. [What are you most scared of] Hmmm... Supernatural stuff... 66. [How many tv's do you have in your house] Two.  67. [Do you have your own tv?] Nah...  68. [do you have your own phone line] Nah...x2 69. [do you sleep with a stuffed animal] Stuffed animal. Nope. But I slept with a stuffed doll...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Decided to delete both quizzes I did coz their pictures are just too big! It kind of slowed down the whole process of loading my blog... Man, I hate that... So, into the rubbish bin it went... Mum is killing three crabs if I am not wrong, we are having a crab feast! ^_^ Yee-hahhh! ! !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiaz... Everyday I only have about the whole of afternoon to do my stuff here and MSN... I am not complaining, but I hate to see my  beloved  brother hogging the computer even if he is not in the house! How does he do it? Easy. He is currently obsessed with an online game where he is always in a stupid place with so many people carrying 'steaming pots' on their heads! And then he inserts a cheat code and there, his points increased without him being present, and so does my anger! Okay, enough of ranting on and on... I just surfed Volks's website and they have released two SDs where only the highest bidder on their annual Dolpha Show will receive them. Hiaz...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My current mood is...    I am waiting for Holland Village's last episode! Let's see, 45 minutes more till it starts...The one on the right is my all- time common mood. Similar and alike to all- time favourites list. Don't be confused
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I realised that my blog is running very ssslowlyyy even with my ADSL modem... I think I have to remove some stuff, my Tagboard is the first on the list. Hiaz... What to do? Nobody actually commented much in it and I myself hate to talk inside too... But I have 'sentimental' feelings for it, I am just so confused, so 'mao dun'... Anyway, today was a kind of fulfilling and tiring day. Firstly, I packed my stupid and condensed shelf. There were three 'storeys'. The first was for all my art work and some dusty school files, the second was for my key chains where I kept it in two mooncake boxes (I love recycling!) and the third I put all my childhood belongings and plastic bags, I love plastic bags and Popular plastic bags stand at the majority. Now you may wonder, where this Akiko keep her books and school stuff? I actually put on my study table and it will be a miracle if someone can actually find something among the 'mountians'.... I was sneezing throughout the whole afternoon while tidying up my stuff. My mother even suggested me to wear a mask... Coz I have a 'weak nose'. Ok, back to the shelf. I started about 1pm and just finished, including a 1 hr break to watch 'showbiz'. Now, everything looks more tidy. I even managed to squeeze all my sec 4's books into the shelf... Whew.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Continue from the previous quizes...  21. [scars] Yup. I have one on my forehead. Heard from my parents that I banged against the wall while spinning around...  22. [Height] 160cm... -_- 23. [Do you wear any rings] nope. I do not have the tendancy to care about my image... 24. [What shoes do you wear] I usually wear sandals and slippers. I do have a SKECHERS sports shoe but seldom wear it. It cost a bomb! 25. [drove a car] I under 18 leh... 26. [met someone new] Errmmm... 27. [done laundry] Nope. But I do wash my own bags and pencil cases... Ya, I am weird... 28. [cried] Can you believe it that I cried when True Courage is showing the lady who lose her son during christmas? I never failed to cry when I read this story... 29. [wore a skirt] Nope. Never  30. [How are you today] Ummm... Fine. Trying to find a good layout... 31. [wearing] Pink polka dots 32. [thinking about] Whether I should change my current layout...  33. [What does your hair look like at the moment] Tied up in a pony- tail 34. [What song are you listening to right now] Listening to chinese songs on Y.E.S 93.3FM 35. [What was the last thing you ate and/or drank] I just ate Lor Mee... 36. [How is the weather right now] A little windy and sunny 37. [Last person u talked to on the phone] My friend, less than 5 minutes... :p 38. [watching] I finished watching Showbiz 39. [what time is it] About 4.05pm P.S Pardon the layout. Will change soon...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Helloz! I am back after a great swim during the public holidays, mayve not so great, but at least it was fulfilling... ~_^  Tuesday was a great day, apart from getting a scolding from my mother to get my butt off the bed for a morning swim. I woke up at 7.30am and we delayed and dragged until we can only leave at about 9am... *grrr* Luckily, there were not many people in the swimming complex... *phew* I hate crowds! We went to the deep pool, I have not swam in the middle and baby pool for many years, I kind of cherished the moments... The deep pool, as we know, is deep. Plus I did not touch chlorine water for at least 3 years! At  most the sea water for canoeing during camp... I TOTALLY forgotten my freestyle! I am shocked! Flabbergasted! Should I go into the water twice or once before coming out to breathe? *uurrgghh* And I could only go for 1 lap of breaststroke before my arms called help... At least I could still dived deep into the water and my brother and I dived through 3 adults 'split legs', in better English format, it is legs apart in the water. Hiaz... I better improve my swimming skill, I used to be in the advance level (not bragging but now downgrading myself -_-), now I cannot even finished 1 stupid lap. You want to hear the funny stuff? Here goes... My brother had a kind of a fit. He acted like a kid, stopping the whole family from coming up the water... And we had a so- called fight and I managed to escape. But he was strong and he must have thought I was one of his Indian or Malay friends and particularly dragged me into the water and I cannot continued anymore... It was too embarrassing, I was ducked into the water, and the next minute,  everybody  was looking at us. The old and young. And fortunately I never screamed like a girl supposed to. Anyway, I will go swimming EVERYDAY, that is a promise to slim myself down...      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, the only thing to attract more people or readers is to do quizzes and all these kind of weird questions that they want to know.... Ok, here goes....  1. [What is your full name] My full name is too long- winded. Do not wish to tell. 2. [nickname] Akiko. And I love it!  3. [bday] Indonesia's National Day... 4. [Age] 16 5. [Sex] Female... Weird. 6. [Social Security] ?? 7. [Where were you born] In Singapore, in a hospital.  8. [where you live now] In Singapore, in the east side.... 9. [Zodiac sign] Leo. Ya, I am the leader. 10. [What school do you attend] Errmmm... I have graduated. Next que. 11. [siblings and their ages] 1 brother, 15 12. [do you get along] Currently, he is out. 13. [Pets] Used to have a pair quails. *boo hoo* My Quails... 14. [Righty or Lefty] Right handed 15. [bedtime] About midnight... *yawn* 16. [Hair color] Ooo... I just dyed it copper red... 17. [Eye color] Brown, no such thing as black, right? 18. [Do you wear contacts or glasses] glasses, contacts, is waaayyyy too dangerous and I do not want to carry so much reponsibility. 19. [Do you have any piercings] Yup, on the ears. 20. [tattoos] No way. Never.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Let's continue... Then we hang around at one of the shopping centres... Took Neoprints and cards. *_* Went home at about six. =_=   Saturday  Saturday was like........ Nothing to discuss or talk about. Maybe I should have stayed at home to watch my ''Fa Wan Yi Ren'', my Zhou Chuan Xiong and ''Tian Lun''. Can you believed that I missed 3 shows and 2 of them are last episodes? Just for the sake for going to a stupid dinner... *Grrr* At least I got to watch the Saturday late night show on Channel 8. It was called ''A bite of your apple'' roughly translated from ''Ping Gou Yao Yi Kou'', starring Daniel Chan and Joey. Quite nice and sweet, like an apple. The story is very general and aimed at many people from all walks of life... Daniel and Joey actually were cyber friends but in real life, they are also friends who love each other but were too shy to confess... Haiz... If only I have such a cute and handsome cyber friend. Coz everytime I chat with somebody, it is always friends I know and for a very short time....   Sunday  Ooo... Sunday was better. I went to Expo for the Best Food 2003. I ate a lot and there were also many people... It was like so squeezy and cramped. And I thought I have offended one lady. Never blame her, it WAS very crowded... But I have fun.... ^_^    Monday. Today.  This morning, I went to the library and then proceeded to buy glow- in- the- dark snowflakes to decorate. Lazing in the house till now. I feel kind of uncomfortable writing here... There was a recent news report that youngsters nowadays are crazy about blogs and constantly updating them... I admit I was one of them initially. I was so excited coz this blog is finally your own and you can do whatever you want to do. Then I also realised that I was ''hooked''. So during the most important part of my school life, I tried to stop and went into Hiatus mode with only occasional times to vent my fustrations on something or just to fill up my time... Now I am kind of tired and bored to update here. Maybe I need time to adjust. :P I think I talk too much now, *urgh*, have to stop...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heyz... I am back finally and permanently. Yes! I am kind of distracted coz firstly, I am listening to the Community Chest's Charity Show and on the other hand, I am kind of confused as I have too much stuff to tell to the world. Hmm... Let's see, let me start from Friday onwards.    *Friday*  After I have done what I am supposed to do, I went to my Senior's house. Hiaz... what to do? All my other friends have plans and I also have my ''appointment'' with my Senior... I went to her house in the morning and we hang around till my other friend came over. ---PAUSE---   *My brother is using the com., will update later... See ya*                                         ---END---  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       If you are bent on reading the whole long list, expect many SD this, SD that. Coz I m fanatic about Super Dollfie, like Shirou, my all- time fav and Sweet Dream Lucas, my precious.... If you are not reading the whole thing and just want to 'steal' it and put it in your own website, juz do it... Coz I also stole it from somebody... ^^    1. What did you do in 2003 that you'd never done before?  Getting to know Super Dollfie and finally bleached my hair! ^^  2. Did you keep your new years' resolutions, and will you make more for next year?  I think all my new years' resolutions will never be fulfilled. As for next year, unless somebody ask me to make, if not, I will not be bothered....  3. Did anyone close to you give birth?  Considering my friends' cousin just gave birth to a male baby... So cuuttee!!  4. Did anyone close to you die?  This year? Don't think so...  5. What countries did you visit?  Nearest, Malaysia. Farthest, Korea, Seoul   6. What would you like to have in 2004 that you lacked in 2003?  Able to purchase at least 1 SD. And please, I want a digital camera!!! *wah!*  7. What dates from 2003 will remain etched upon your memory? I think my birthday date, I suppose...  8. What was your biggest achievement of the year?  Finishing what I supposed to finish?  9. What was your biggest failure?  Not able to purchase my fav SD and going to school...  10. Did you suffer illness or injury?  Right now, I am having a flu. And my nose kept bleeding... *Achoo*  11. What was the best thing you bought?  A 7250 phone. It would be the  greatest  thing I have bought IF I have bought a SD....  14. Where did most of your money go?  To my bank, I am saving for my SD....  15. What did you get really, really, really excited about?  SDs!!!  16. What song will always remind you of 2003?  Well, I was listening to Zhou Chuan Xiong's 'Hasayaki'. So that's it.  17. Compared to this time last year, are you: older or wiser?  Older. I want to be young forever!  18. What do you wish you'd done more of?  Creating a website and know how to use flash. Maybe teaching myself how to paint doll's faces....  19. What do you wish you'd done less of? Kept crying for a SD and never purchase one. See, I have done it again...  20. How will you be spending Christmas?  I have spent it and with my friends...  22. Did you fall in love in 2003?  NO. But if you say fall in love with a SD, YES!  23. How many one-night stands? Oh my god, *CENSORED*  24. What was your favorite TV program?  None.   25. Do you hate anyone now that you didn't hate this time last year?  Everything. Coz I am the person who hates everything!  26. What was the best book you read? None. All books are good if they are true...  27. What was your greatest musical discovery? None. I am not musically talented.  28. What did you want and get for christmas?  I got many other stuff worthwhile from my friends. What about my family? We never celebrate Christmas....  29. What did you want and not get for christmas?  I REALLY WANTED A SD! Especially Shirou or Sweet Dream Lucas...  30. What was your favorite film of this year?  Sound of Colors. Never, never expect me to say LOTR:ROTK. Although I love it, I kinda hate it for its long duration... *bladder bursting*  31. What did you do on your birthday, and how old were you?  I did nothing and I am sixteen going on sixty...  32. How would you describe your personal fashion concept in 2003?  Keep the strips going, man!  33. What kept you sane?  SUPER DOLLFIE.... *MY PRECIOUS*  34. Which celebrity/public figure did you fancy the most?  Child actors like the Harry Potter actors and others. Coz they are so rich and famous....  35. What political issue stirred you the most?  The captured of Saddam Hussien....  36. Who did you miss?  I miss my stolen discman.... *WAH!!!*  37. Who was the best new person you met?  Nobody worth writing down...    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ehh, am I seeing things? Why has Blogger switched back to the original one? I was just starting to adjust to the two 'split- tables'.... Well, never mind. I like this better than the latter. ^o^ Just updating here. Have to go back to school tomorrow. Grrr... On the happy end, I will change back my plain template back.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmmm.... Trruuueee....    Uriel: One of the busiest angels, one of prophecy and creativity. Concidered to be represenatative of the sun, and one of the most beautiful archangels ever. Of course that could just be vanity...    urlLink   Which Angel Lays Within You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi to all! Merry Christmas! Today is Thursday, right? I am almost lost in time. Yesterday went to Orchard to look at witless people spraying snow and strings.... Ewww... I hate it and was dirty and sticky all over. I stayed until 12am plus for the countdown and rushed all the way back to the MRT station. Man, I felt sad for all those cleaners out there. They have to clean up the mess after all the celebration.... I ReAlLy HaTe It! Oh yeah, thanks to the stupid necklace I was wearing, now I got rashes all over my neck.... Urrgghh.... Itchy!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoa! Almost a week not posting here! Whoa! *.* During this week and a day, I have watched Lord Of The Rings and Sound Of Colors! Pretty jealous, huh? I watched LOTR with my friends and I am so touched! This is the only film which I would cry so many times. The part where Arwen is going to die and Ewoyn hugging her father.... Hiaz... So sweet and nice! Sound Of Colors was simple and yet sweet. Really, you should all watch it during the Christmas season. Very sweet, the movie felt like honey. It warms you inside out....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       ~* 2 MORE DAYS TILL THE RELEASE OF THE ''SOUND OF COLORS''*~   I finally bought the ''Sound Of Colors'' book! I am so jubilated! Finally. Whew. First time still. I have wrapped it and put it in one corner so that I can read after christmas or read it after watching the movie. Hehe...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       ~* 3 MORE DAYS TILL THE RELEASE OF ''THE SOUND OF COLOURS''*~   Grrr.... I am so infuriated. Vexed. My  clever  brother decided to change the CPU and spent the whole of last night changing. Gee... Now I have to redo my websites and gather everything together again. And NOW Blogger also have to change their whole programme. Urgh! How stupid can I be. All my templates' websites and everything is gone....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       ~*4 MORE DAYS TILL THE RELEASE OF ''THE SOUND OF COLORS''*~   *****Word Association - (1st Thing That Comes To Mind)***** 114. [Rubber Gloves] Rubber trees? Coz they are manufacture from rubber? 115. [Disney Character] I would say Mickey. Ya know the reason... 116. [Fast Food place] I'm Lovin' It.... 117. [Board Game] Monopoly. I have the special 40th anniversery Monopoly. 118. [Rock] I have no idea but I will relate to a rock band... 119. [Blue] The sky. Coz everybody says: ''The Sky Is So Blue Today...'' 120. [Wet] Wet? Hmmm... Water? 121. [Cry] My tears lor... 122. [Peanut Butter] I fart? I hate peanut butter. 123. [Hay] The farm? 124. [Paper] Sissors, paper, stone! 125. [Wood] Termites! Eeekk! 126. [Yellow] Sun. Though, the sun is not really orange. 127. [Laugh] Erm... A person? I don't know. 128. [Ugly] Pactricia Mok. Coz everybody is saying... No offence. She is a good actress! 129. [Happy] A happy smile. Though I don't really like it. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh god, I suddenly had the urge to just use my bank savings to purchase a SD. Preferbably Shirou or Lucas... (~.~) But it is not that easy... Hiaz. How much I want a SD to see him smiling at me when I come home. How I wish I could touch his face, his hair and dress him up and take photos... I just feel so lonely and isolated when everybody has one or your friends do not appreciate your interest... Hiaz. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Congratulations! You're Legolas!    urlLink   Which Lord of the Rings character and personality problem are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I am back from my trip to Malaysia! A little bit tired and boring. I am now going to relate to you on my 5 Days trip... Here goes...   The Coach  The coach  itself  was spacious and cold. The unfortunate part was that it was not the Horse Brand or the one that Moses Lim was advertising... Conclusion: Ok lah   The Driver and Tour Guide  Both of them are Malaysians and speak Hokkien. Which is so fustrating as I myself is weak in Hokkien and majority of the trip they are talking in Hokkien. Man, sometimes I hate the Tour Guide, sometimes not. He is so..... And the driver love to release Karaoke VCDs which features Bikini girls wlking around as if they are the most beautiful people on Earth... Conclusion: Sastifying   The Tour Group  They are a strong group of 24, with many kinds of people form all walks of life. Now let me slowly name them and in detail...   Mr Know- It- All And His Family  Basically, they are weird. The head, Mr Know- It- All was always talking loudly about how he know so much about Malaysia. Grrr. And even the Tour Guide sometimes ignored him. His family has a daughter and girlfriend as all of us were concluding, no, I mean, gosipping.   The Father And Son   Yup. The son is deaf, maybe partly- deaf. Boy, they eat a lot and the boy is trying to see that he is very studious. Reading newspaper early in the morning and writing in his journal  and  bringing a book to read. Grrr... He is trying to show us that he is damn clever and boy, I hate him. I am not jealous or what. Ok, maybe I am....   The Mother And Daughter  This is the older version of the one above. The daughter is obviously not on my good books. She complained and complained and took so long at the St Paul's Church just to take photos... Small eyes fussy girl!   The Hongkes  Sorry, a little rude but that is their common name, right? They consist of two daughters and their mother. Speaking Cantonese throughout the journey, I began to suspect if my mother should also come on the trip to tell them off that Singaporeans CAN talk Canto too!   The Big Family  The loudest and most talkative one at the back of the bus. Three daughters and their parents. Boy, the daughters are really B******. Sorry, but I am in the badest mood when I talk about my group. Yakking throughout the journey in chinese. Even my godmother commented that they must be from China... Haha...   The Indian Family  Actually only the mother is an Indian. Her husband is a chinese, so her three children are Malay- looking. The four of them, abscene of Father eveytime would always treat us some tidbits. But I always reject them. Coz I HATE her youngest son. Good- looking he may be, but boy, he was so hyper- active and talkative. He may be apple in everybody's eyes, but certainly not in mine. Oh, did I tell you that they can speak chinese, that is what make everybody   love  them...   The Photographers  Actually wanted them to be named Husband and Wife. But they are practically taking photos everywhere. And I really mean, EVERYWHERE. Even the most ugly places. Not the toilets. But I envy them, not the persons. It is the camera. It is so nice and sleek. Not the thin kind but that kind which has 3X megapixels, I think. And the zooming part is so whoa! I really want it. Could have steal it, IF it is not against the law and they are always wearing it around their necks...  Now you are wondering now they are only 21, where are the remaining 3? Yup, that's me and my 2 godmothers. I will not relate my 5 day trip right now. Maybe even forever. I want to keep it personal. If not, what if somebody from the Tour Group reads it? I will be dead. At least they can suspect but will never be certain. And if I continued onwards, I will be sprouting all the vulgarities right now... Yeah, I really don't like the Tour.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Don't really like this character. I everytime call it burnt bread...        urlLink What San-X Character Are You?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did I say I like Maison Ikkoku? I love the artist's drawing of every single detail!        urlLink What Anime Art Style Are You?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      *****Preference***** 105. [Sleep on your back, stomach or side] Normally I sleep on my side, but the next morning, I am on my back... 106. [Adidas, Nike, or Reeboks] Nike is nice... 107. [Croutons or Bacon Bits] I do not go for Western food or brands. 108. [2 doors or 4 (on a car)] 2 doors. Smaller and cute! 109. [Bridges or Tunnels] Bridges. Coz, Londen Bridge is falling down... falling down... 110. [One pillow or two?] 1. But I really prefer 2 so that I can hug one of them... 111. [Salt or butter flavored popcorn] Butter. Salt dehydrates my throat.  112. [Fizzy or still water] Still water. Fizzy? Burp! 113. [Red wine or white wine] Red Wine. Do you know it helps to prevent cancer? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      AT LAST! I was able to borrow Hello Kitty magazine after days of waiting! But I managed to borrow 2 only, and one of them, I have already borrowed a few months back... Maybe I should buy Hello Kitty instead of borrowing. At least I can say it is mine and look after it well. Not like some readers who went and glued the pages together and cut out some cute pictures they want. It is so damn outrageous! Down to these people! If I really like a particular picture, I don't cut it out, I will photcopy it at Toa Payoh Library where they provide Colour Photocopy service. Hiaz... Library Books are for all to share and care, not to conquer it and say it is yours. Anyway, I managed to found one particular picture in the H.K. magazine and it is similar to my blog's wallpaper! The H.K. don in a blue gown with her crown. So gorgeous! It cost about 5000 Yen for a large one, which is about S$75. Whoa! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Morpheus    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      90. [Root Beer or Dr. Pepper] Root Beer. Coz I don't know what is Dr. Pepper! 91. [vanilla or chocolate] Vanilla. In terms of ice- cream flavour... 92. [Love or lust] Love. Lust is juz so... 93. [silver or gold] Silver. But I love gold. 94. [Have you ever gone skinny dipping] Nope.  95. [What's your favorite color] Orange. 96. [What's your favorite band/singer] Ermm... Let's see. Since I just bought Hang Ten clothes and SHIN band is advertising them. Then, it is SHIN. 97. [What do you dream about] Ooops. I cannot remember. 98. [Favorite song] Varies. Cannot be so specfic lah. 99. [Do you like to sing in the shower] How to sing when the water keep splashing into your mouth? I just cannot figure it out? 100. [Had an imaginary friend] When I was small. 101. [Wanted to "hook up" with a friend] No Way! 102. [Cried during a movie] Ermm... Disney's The Kid which I watched recently made me cry... 103. [Had a crush on a teacher] Nope.  104. [What is the first thing you think about when you wake up in the morning] Can I go back to sleep? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      70. [Are you shy] Ya. Very introvert. Everybody says that about me.  71. [Are you outgoing] In the net, Online, ya. 72. [Who is the loudest friend you have] An ex- pirmary school friend. Nothing much to talk about it.  73. [Who is the quietest friend you have] I will have to admit, it is I myself.  74. [Who looks the worst in the morning] Family members? It has to be me and my brother. Both of us just look so different from our usual looks in the morning, right after waking up. 75. [Who's the messiest eater] Definately, not me. 76. [Who's the slowest eater] Not me again. But if you ask me a few years back, it is my brother. 77. [Who's the bossiest] Not me. Maybe me. 78. [Who is the 'mom' outta your friends] My senior, it is very obvious when we are having steamboat. 79. [who are the top 3 hottest guys/girls u know] None. We are the geeks. *haha* 80. [who's the weirdest] Me? 81. [who is the funniest] Not me. My humour can only be activated for just a few minutes.  82. [who do you go to for advice] Sometimes my family. But usually I seek from books myself.   83. [who do you think about most when you're not happy] My school. Bascially, they are the ones who make me so unhappy... 84. [who do you cry with] Nobody.  85. [what's the best feeling in the world] Being alive and still breathing.  86. [when's the last time you cried] Yesterday. When I was reading a comic book. Ya. 87. [is cheerleading a sport] If you are able to sweat. Ya, it is a sport.  88. [How many licks does it take to get to the center of a tootsie pop] Dumb que. 89. [Which came first the chicken or the egg] Egg. Or maybe it is the chicken? Egg?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh Yeah! Today is the Chingay parade! I am actually half excited and half anxious about it. Although I am not going to peek a view of the procession... Coz I am still stuck in my stupid job until tomorrow. I just cannot believe it! I am just a part- time girl and I am slogging away like a dog already! I only have 1 DAY of rest for the whole of this week! And... Hiaz... Cannot reveal too much! *Grrrr* The excited feeling is that my workplace is so near to Orchard and you will feel excited too if you are there thinking ''I am so near to be in the camera!'' sort of thing in your head... The anxious part is that they have blocked the road for Chingay to process on. And I do not wish to see myself stuck in a bus with hundreds of other 'sufferers' looking at nothing but each other faces.... But fear not! Coz my father is going to fetch me home, hehe! Like yesterday the roads were already blocked for the Chingay reherdsal and I kinda forced my father to fetch me home too. Ain't I evil? I guessed its because Jacky Chan is present. But my auntie said is because half of the participants are foreigners... Hmmm!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh, I feel so happy and carefree.... ( Although I don't think I am such an angel... ^_~)    You are one of the few out there whose wings are truly  ANGELIC . Selfless, powerful, and divine, you are one blessed with a certain cosmic grace. You are unequalled in peacefulness, love, and beauty. As a Being of Light your wings are massive and a soft white or silver. Countless feathers grace them and radiate the light within you for all the world to see. You are a defender, protector, and caretaker. Comforter of the weak and forgiver of the wrong, chances are you are taken advantage of once in awhile, maybe quite often. But your innocence and wisdom sees the good in everyone and so this mistreatment does not make you colder. Merciful to the extreme, you will try to help misguided souls find themselves and peace. However not all Angelics allow themselves to be gotten the better of - the Seraphim for example will be driven to fighting for the sake of Justice and protection of those less powerful. Congratulations - and don't ever change - the world needs more people like you.    urlLink   *~*~*Claim Your Wings - Pics and Long Answers*~*~*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi there people! I have changed the template to this layout, taaddaahh! Nice? I downloaded it from Blogskin. Didn't know it was that easy. Hehe. But this layout is kinda nice and warm. Although I think millions of people out there are using this layout too... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I cannot believe it! Cutie_Isaac's graphics site is gone and replaced by his neopet! Arrgghhh! I need his site to survive, to live on....*exageratting* Now I have to go and download 'skins' from 'BlogSkin', oh god. I do not want to be a copy cat. But I think I have to, haiz.... Work tomorrow and in the morning. I just cannot drag myself out of the bed at 5.30 am in the wee hours of the morning! It's just not me! And I don't wake up at this hour to go to school too... What to do.... I need the money to purchase my SD or AI. Having second thoughts to buy a smaller doll. Like the Petite Angel- Gabriel from Custom house...  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, a little quicky update on my life and before I abandon this blog to recieve 'hongbao'.... Nothing much but just bought 5566's 2nd album, 'Zhi Ai'! I was early, I was able to get the poster, it looked quite nice and cool, a winter look picture. Listening to Track no. 5, 'Bounce', very catchy and nice. Very different from the 1st album where there were many pop songs, now there are ballads and a little R&B and they surely have matured through their songs. They even have one song written by Toro, ex-member from Energy, 'For You', very slow and sweet. I heard the members of 5566 love this song very much. I think I have kinda take a fancy on Toro, his hair is nice, so does the songs he sang for his debut drama... Ooops, too much pop. Now I will insert a survey to fill up the blanks... Here goes!   who do you wanna   kill: No one physical in particular. Everybody deserve a little chance and love... Whoa, suddenly I have became so forgiving! talk to: My friends, they are so busy with their school life. Actually one did called me in the afternoon to meet up with her to shop for clothes. But I was short of money after purchasing 5566 and topping up my money. Hiaz... kiss: Nobody in particular too. Coz I am wearing braces and looked so hideous, haha!   favorites   food: Nothing really in paricular. But Tarimisu came first on my mind, although I have only eaten once. cd: None. As long I like it, that will be ok. But I kinda like Ayumi's ballads coz it is very slow and sweet... Maybe my all- time favourite. candy: Anything that doesn't stick to my teeth... animal: Dogs are fine. I used to have a pair of Quails.  song: Pop, ya, I know. It harms you, dehydrates and kill your brains. But it liven up my mood! vegetable: No all time favs. But if you give me vegetables, I eat. fruit: Same as veg...   right now   clothes: A greyish Snoppy (really from the Snoppy shop) shirt and a pair of blue shorts. Talk about color co-ordination... mood: Awake. Just had a nap for 1 1/2 hour. make-up: None. I am in my house leh. But if I am out, I will normally put a little lip gloss over lip balm coz my mouth cracked a lot. It also helps to add a little more glossy- look. That's all. smell: Nothing. I never sweat nor came out from a bath. It's like just there. refreshment: Water and sometimes some swet drinks like honey water, Qoo packet drink or syrup with water... Am I too simple? worried: Like the money I will be getting for CNY and what exactly I should wear coz I only have two new blouses and no more new clothes... hair: Longer but not straighter any more *boo hoo* annoyed at: My stomach, cramps... *Ouch* song: 5566's Boyfriend, very nice... *dreamy look*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have been engrossed in LiveJournal for too long. So, now I will update in Blogger. Did nothing much today, not even going outside to buy New Year cards or even design one for my friend coz I only have her full address... Ok, so I just surf the net until my brother comes home and snatch it to play his Jin Yong. Haiz, I must stop complaining and ranting on and on. Hmm... Today I have decided on a spur of interest to research about FF X-2... Ya, I know, it is oudated, so long already. But I am like that, so I went to their costume changes and was amazed by their so many costume changes. Cool! Oh, did I say I never play before any Final Fantasy games or ANY online or PS or anything that requires a stupid joystick? I played a Super Mario game once, on PS with my cousin and guess what? I burst out crying and my hands sweated like a waterfall. I always, never fail to sweat and get excited when playing virtual games. Haiz.... That's why I am not that close to my cousins as they are all boys. Plus, we are having a family gathering this Saturday. But I cannot go coz work disallows me to do so. I am actually quite happy. Wonder they ever read my blog or not? Hmm.... Oh gosh, I can actually lead from a game so far away... Ok, back to FF X-2. I actually like their costumes a lot, that was why I was attracted to the game. But never played before. I love is their 'Songtress' costume, including Rikku and Paine. Very cool. Not forgetting their 'White Mage' costume... And their '1000 Words' and 'Real Emotion'. Ooo, just so cool. If I can cosplay, I will do one of their costume and acting as Paine. Coz she look so fierce and her hair is the shortest and I  think  the easiest to style. Yuna's hair is fine. But her hair requires a 'ironing' hair kit, ya know what I mean. And dying my hair to brown is so boring. I don't mind changing to Paine's ash- grey color.  Gatsby  has that color... Hehe! But providing first I know how to make and design clothes.... Ok, enough of FF X-2. Now, I shall talk about Fatal Frame 2, another FF. FF 2 is scary and colder. Two twins with sixth sense investigating a huanted village is so way scary... Argh. I also never play the game before, I was again attracted by the twins' innocent looks and great outfit. Then I visited their official website with fear and it was ok lah in the end. I really LOVE their outfit. I will try to design the braver sister's (forgot the name ^^). Coz she is wearing pants. Haha. Their clothes are also very lacy and figure-hugging... Oh, how I love their clothes...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       are you  obsessed with anything: Yup. SDs!!! Shriou and Lucas... Hehe!  happy in life: Will if I can have Shriou/Lucas, a digital camera, a laptop, my own website and... Ya, I am actually not very happy with my life...  forgetful: Well, I sometimes do forget to return my borrowed books...  loving: Loving? To who and whom in particular? Well, I will be loving to all non- living things...   smart: Hmmm... On certain subjects in gerneral...  lazy: Right now?  patient: Ohhh, people say I am very, very patient...   last person you  phoned: Phoned ah? I think was my aunty who called me...   hugged: Nobody physical in particular...  instant messaged: SMS? I think it was my mom... Ya.  yelled at: Oh, it must be my brother... It will be him forever.  broke your heart: Oh, as in in love? Nope. Hope not in the future...  kissed: Nah...  went out with: My family? Ya, I am kinda a boring person at heart...  laughed with: Myself in front of the computer screen... Haha! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ya, I am very bored. Well, at least I update.   full name: Akiko Papusza (Actually that is my nickname lah! Oh god, I think I am using Singlish too much!)  also known as: Ya, Akiko...  asian name: Erm... I kinda don't like my asian name. But my asian name has 3 characters with 9 strokes, 6 strokes and 9 strokes... Guess.  birthdate: 17th August... Yup, Indonesia's National Day   zodiac sign: A Leo. This is dumb que.    residence: Singapore, where else?  siblings: 1. And nothing much to talk about him   hair color: A little golden but very light. Not like all those Ah Beng out there!   eye color: Brown. I wish to change it to a lighter color...   hobbies: Updating blogs, drawing and drooling over SD... It is exactly the same as my Hobby page in Friendster...   last time you  talked on the phone: Oh, a few minutes ago. My aunt called.  ate candy: A few hours ago. But it is not candy, but a sugarless sweet...   went out late: On christmas eve day... Actually it should be on New Year's Day. But everybody was too tired and went home... -__-   got sick: A few weeks ago. After my trip to the Malaysia. *-*    do you  smoke: No. And never. Down to these people!  do drugs: As I said. Never. I rather spend my money wisely on other stuff like SD.... Hehe...   eat a lot: I used to. Have the 'Kiasu' character. But trying to cut down...   get good grades: At times... -___-   drink: Of course! We need 70% of water in our body... Those who never drink are.... Like I heard of this guy who chewed 2 BIG pills without drinking water even after swallowing... Talk about kissing him... YUCK!   sleep with stuffed animals: Ya. I need comfort from them sometimes...   remember your first love: Erm... I think I do not have a first love...   believe in god: At times, when I am really depressed.   pray: At times too. When I feel very spiritual.  have any piercings: At my ears, nowhere else.  have any tattoos: No way!  have any bad habits: Ermm... Like eating my vegetables first before consuming other food?   have a job: Ya. A part- time. Very stressful and kinda scary. No more elaboration.   like candles: I like beautiful ones that doesn't have smell and that are big in size...   believe in fate: Ya, sometimes when I cannot get the things I want... Face it, that's fate. Everbody has the same thoughts, right?   believe in love: Sometimes when I read stories where love conquers all...   want to get married: No. Not right now... Maybe later.   want to have children: No. Maybe. No. I just want to carry babies but don't want to carry the burden of taking care and be responsible.   how many: But I will acknowledge my SDs or MSDs as my 'children' in the near future. At least have three... Then I will be so, so happy!!!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I stole it from a survey in LJ... And it is a must that the que be answered in lyrics form... But I am neither a Beetles or Dolly Parton fan.... So I will just answered in words and ya, I am very bored and desperate to do something...   1.) Are you male or female?:  Bascially, I am a female and nope, no operation done on me except that I wore braces to straighten my stupid and crooked teeth...  2.) Describe your neighborhood:  Right now it is peaceful except for the people playing basketball downstairs and there was a quarrel going on next door...   3.) How do you look?: I look regular and a little on the plump side.I admit I do look a little like Jap. or Korea. But I really look normal...  4.) If you could say something to the person you like/love, what would it be?: I hope we will be together till the end of the world... I never took it out from a song and really, I won't tell my love like that! So eeewwweee....  5.) Where do you wish you were right now? I really want to go to Japan and absorb in the spring atmospehere... Hiaz....    6.) What would you say to your best friend?: My good old Buddy!   7.) Any words of wisdom: Knowledge is Power?! I not good at talking words of wisdom...  8.) What do you wish you were doing right now?: Grabbing a SD and keep taking photos with a digital camera...  9.) What do you think of drugs and alcohol?: It is a sin and nobody must ever indulged in it. Whoever does it is stupid! But drinking a little beer or wine at certain times are ok lah...  10.) If you could say one thing to your enemy, what would it be?: The fight is on, I won, admit you are defeated!   11.) What do you usually do on Friday nights?: Hmmm.... Actually, nothing. Just watched TV and update blogs... And of course, sleep.  12.) Are you for world peace?: Of course! Can't you even see how choatic the world has became! World peace, I Love You!  13.) What do you think about school?: Ermm... Study till you drop dead... And rot to death...   14.) How do you feel right now?: I felt so oily and fat, cause I am sitting down and not exercising to slim myself down...  15.) Any closing words?: Ya, this survey really should be answered in lyrics form....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I just came back from outside within 1 hour. Don't know why, but I kinda felt tired and 'sian', so went home after buying my lunch and nail polish. Just had lunch and realized that cup noodles really taste different from packet noodles. I had Korean noodles and felt so fat and sick. I actually wanted to slim down but now I only managed to bleach my hair and ya, I only really managed to bleach my hair... *Geezzz* Must go and save up money to purchase Shirou/Lucas.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I know I haven't updated for quite a few days. Kinda busy, ya know. Nope, I am not going, no, not AbLe to go to JC.... *Sheesh* Juz very busy with my personal life. I am finally admitted to Livejournal! YES! But that means I have to update both journals. But Blogger will be my first piority. LJ is too complicated and tedious. I think I need at least half a year to sort out my template and fonts (it is still in Times New Roman, Man, I hate that font). Plus LJ is so 'ma fan', must do this, do that, to impress people so that you are accepted as a friend. But why I still join even I know it is so troublesome? Easy. The simple reason is that it is FUN! But as I say, Blogger is still my first and foremost....  P.S By the way, have you notice that my blog is just too PINK? I also noticed it, scrollbar, the background, EVERYTHING! But please try to be patient with me, ok? Especially the male species out there.... *hehe* 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ----------------FAVORITES------------------  -- Shampoo: Dove. Gives a nice, rich smell... -- Color: Orange. No doubt about it. -- Day/Night: Night. Coz that's when the fun begins! -- Summer/Winter: Winter. I love cold and snow! -- Lace or Satin: Hm, lace. But I will refer it as gothic/lolita, not that lacy lingerie... -- Fave Food: So hard to choose. But i can't live without noodles. Must at least eat one bowl a day.... ^.^ -- Fave Movies: Harry Potter and those that doesn't rely on too much graphics... -- Fave sport: Swimming. But I am certainly slacking and detoriating. -- Fave sports stars: None. Coz if I like them, they are not sports stars, they are idols.  ----------------RIGHT NOW------------------  -- Wearing: Big, baggy 'My Melody' t-shirt.  -- Drinking: Coco plus milk powder... Weird but sweet. -- Thinking about: My stupid job which is about to begin in a few hours time. Grrr... -_____- -- Listening to: 933 Y.E.S station playing some husky male voice whom I don't know who.  ---------------IN THE LAST 24 HRS------------------   -- Cried: No. But the last time I cried was watching 'Moulin Rouge', I cried at the last scene when Satin died... *boo hoo* -- Worn jeans: Ya, later for work. Damn, I really hate wearing jeans or long pants. I prefer khakis or shorts. -- Met someone new online: Last 24 hrs? No. My brother and mom were using the com. -- Done laundry: No. Enough. -- Drove a car: No. But I really want to.  -- Talked on the phone: Just. I think my brother's tution teacher called. Don't like him at all.  ---------------DO YOU BELIEVE IN--------------  -- Yourself: Ya. Who can you trust then? -- Your friends: At some point. -- Santa Claus: No. I was brought up to believe in Santa Claus appearing in TV and movies, not in reality. Unless you count the one at the department store who looks so fake. And no, I don't sit on their lap. -__- -- Tooth Fairy: Not after watching ''Darkness Falls''. I really used to believe in her. Put the tooth under the pillow but of course, no money or coin. -- Destiny/Fate: Sometimes. You sometimes need to believe to live on and survive, ain't I right? -- Angels: Oh, I still believe faithfully up till now. Don't ask me why. -- Ghosts: Ya. Don't ask me why too. -- UFO's: Hmmm... Not really. -- God: At times. When you really need someone spirtual to guide you...  --------FRIENDS AND LIFE------------------  -- Do you ever wish you had another name?: Ya. I was thinking if I had a different name... Will people still make fun of my name or just leave me alone? Hmm... -- Do you have a girlfriend/boyfriend?: For a hundred over times, no. -- Do you like anyone?: Like? Ya, my parents, my friends, and those who treat me well, really treat me well... -- Which one of your friends acts the most like you?: In reality, not really. Everbody has his/her own personality or character. But  none  acts like me when I got crazy over SD/AI... -- Are you close to any family member?: Close ah? How close? I'm close to my aunt coz she is at home 24h everyday. My parents? We don't even get past 10 sentences... -- Who do you hang around the most?: The computer. Coz I can know everything without 'hanging around'.... Duh.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man, I love this ''Sephiroth'' character from Advent Children though I have never played FFVII, the game before... I hope my future SD can look like that. Long silver hair with that sinister smile and ooo, so tight clothing... But in another way, I kinda like ''cloud'' character. Spiky, blond hair with his famous sword. Alamak, now these characters are hot! Visit  urlLink http://www.adventchildren.net/           
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am relating to Elva's 'Cappucinno'....     You're a Cappicinno!  urlLink   What Kind of Coffee are You?   brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have got to stop my mom from buying the wrong coffee packet. She bought 2 in 1 instead of 3 in 1... Have got back my coffee habit again, headache and restlessness... I NEED COFFEE!!! *Rushing off to make coffee* Hmmm.... Black coffee...  ------------IN THE PAST MONTH HAVE YOU-------------- -- Drank alcohol: Drank Ice Wine a few weeks ago... And got a sore throat a few days later.... But oooo... So rich and yet so simple... -- Smoke(d): Never. And I hate somkers! -- Done a drug: Drugs? Consume nothing unless the doctor tell me so... -- Have Sex: -___- No....  -- Made Out: Yuck, no! -- Gone to the mall: Ya, yesterday morning... -- Eaten sushi: A few months ago, but I have eaten Udon instant and Korean spicy noodles. Oooo! -- Been on stage: Not for many years already... And I will really avoid it at all course -- Gone skating: Nah... -- Made homemade cookies: When I was much younger. Made Brownies from my Girl Guide Book. And taste quite good! -- Been in love: Hmmm.... Nope. -- Dyed your hair: Bleach, to be exact. But nothing better to do. -- Stolen anything: Ermm... No. But I used to take all those small little cute keychains from bags... But now I will save up and purchase. Stealing no good.  -----------------HAVE YOU EVER------------------  -- Flown on a plane: Ya. Few years ago to Hong Kong. And I really hate my trip to Australia, it was terrible. My ears were almost on the verge of bursting! So now I will always chew a sweet when the plane is about to take off or land... -- Missed school because it was raining?: Nope. Lame, lame, lame excuse. -- Told a guy/girl that you liked them?: Nah. -- Cried during a Movie?: Recently. During LOTR:ROTK, I was very emotional that day... --Ever thought an animated character was hot: Oh yes, I thought the female characters are hot. Whereas the male part, I do not regard them as 'hot', but handsome, kawaii. Male SDs are hot though. -- Cut your hair: No, not now. I want to have longer hair.... -- Had crush on a teacher?: Erm...  -- Played a game that required removal of clothing?: Hmm... Swimming? Coz you must strip to your swim suit? *-* -- Gotten beaten up: Ya, my brother when we were young. Now, my brother gets beaten up by god knows who.... -- Been in a fight: Physically? My brother and I. Emotionally, ya, my parents, of course. -- Shoplifted: No. And I hate to talk about this.  -----------------THE FUTURE------------------  -- Age you hope to be married: In the future. Or maybe not. -- Numbers and Names of Children: I am certainly not contributing to the government.... -- Describe your Dream Wedding: Simple. Wedding at the beach. White and royal.  -- How do you want to die?: Peaceful sleep... -- What do you want to be when you grow up?: Some job I love to be.  -- What country would you most like to visit?: Japan and the whole of Australia. I have only been to Perth and Channel 8 has been showing all the good destinations at Australia...  -----------------OPPOSITE SEX------------------  (I do not have one, this is my ideal person..) -- Best eye/hair color: A little golden and spiky hair style... Haha! -- Short or long hair: Sometimes I wish for long hair. It shows the mysterious character of the person. *Have been watching too many vampire shows and comic books* -- Best height: The average kind will do. -- Best weight: Do not have a exact weight enquiry. -- Best first date location: Somewhere cooling and peaceful BUT not that kind that is quiet and eerie... -- Best first kiss location: Hmmm... haven't thought of it, so distant...  -----------------NUMBER OF-----------------  -- Number of girl/boyfriends you've had: 0 Haha, this is certainly a touchy que! -- Number of drugs taken illegally: Zero. -- Number of people I could trust with my life: In actual fact. None. I can only trust my life to myself or sometimes god... -- Number of CDs that I own: 20++ I only started to buy CDs when I was 14. Hehe! That includes some of my brother's techno cds. -- Number of piercings: 2. One on each side of my ear. But I am really hoping for 2 more, if I do not have a sensitive ear or scare of piercing.... -- Number of tattoos: None. And I advise people never to DIY, my brother did it and his pattern was so stupid and the method he used was so damn disgusting! Yuck! --Number of times my name has appeared in the newspaper?: None. Similar name, have a few. But it is so rare! -- Number of scars on my body: Many. The most obvious one and maybe the first one I got was a 1 cm long scar when I banged my head against the wall when I was about 3 years old. Long story. I remembered I fainted in the car when my parents were rushing me to the hospital... My mom said that I screamed so loudly that everybody outside the theatre could heard my screams. How I got the scar? My mom said I was dancing around like a mad girl and bang!  -- Number of things in my past that I regret: Oh, many, countless! *Rushing off to eat chinese version of Onde Onde (It is orange in color)*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      -----------------INFORMATION------------ -- Name: Akiko. The most commonly used name on the net... -- Birthdate: Indonesia's National Day. -- Birthplace: In Singapore, where else? -- Current: The living room, I smell eggs and stupid 'Bengay' -__- -- Eye Color: Brown.  -- Hair Color: Light golden on the surface.... -- Righty or Lefty: Right-handed. And my brother is a lefty who has left the house... -- Zodiac Sign: Leo. And I certainly have no leadership qualities, duh. -- Innie or Outtie: What's that? I think I am 'innie' as in introvert?  -----------------DESCRIBE------------------   -- Your heritage: Heritage? I am Hokkien, pure chinese. -- The shoes you wore today: Sports shoes with mismatched shoelaces and pattern. -- Your eyes: Wearing spectacles. Opting to wear contact lenses in the near future... -- Your weakness: Being shy and ya, shy, shy, shy.... -- Your fears: Of ghosts? And making careless and stupid mistakes which I did that often... *o* -- What you want to achieve: Wisdom and power. That's a little untrue, but most importantly, freedom.  -----------------WHAT IS------------------  -- Your thoughts first waking up: What time is it? I am going back to sleep... *yawn* -- The first feature you notice in the opposite sex: The hair? Hehe... -- Your best physical feature: Actually to be truthful, none. -- Your bedtime: 12-12.30am -- Your greatest accomplishment: Able to earn money but not physically touching it? That's torture and painful. And working for FREE!! *grrrr*  -- Your most missed memory: Playing paper lantern during mooncake festival... My parents thought it was childish of me to play and it also conincided with the exams...  -----------------YOU PREFER------------------  -- Pepsi or coke: Coke, I think. But I hate gaseous drinks.... -- McDonald's or Burger King: McDonald for its family feeling... But I love Burger King for their cheese cake. Yum, yum! -- Single or group dates: Group dates are safer and fun.... -- Adidas or Nike: Adidas. But I love Nike's ads. Very unique. -- Chocolate or vanilla: Vanilla. Chocolate, when only my craving starts... -- Cappuccino or coffee: Cappuccino. But I usually drink coffee when I am going to drop to sleep. -- Bras or Panties: Both are underwears and essential for a lady... I have no special favours for both of them...  -----------------DO YOU------------------  -- Smoke: No thanx. I hate smokers! -- Curse: When I am in anxiety and irritated... =_= -- Take a shower everyday: Ya. I have to. It's a habit.  -- Have a crush?: Now? Naaahhh. I have been facing too many women and approaching middle-aged but still think they are young, man. -- Who are they: In my workplace. Sometimes, it really get into me to grow up quickly to understand what the heck they are talking about?! -- Do you think you've been in love?: Love? Nope. Lust? Yuck! -- Want to go to college: Well, at times. When you are surrounded by many college people.... -- Like high school: Nahhh.... -- Want to get married: Thinking how the government is trying to make working adults be in love. It has made me think of marriage as a walk into my grave.... -- Type w/ your fingers on the right keys: Nope. I have to look at them... Mom said it is not the good way to do that... Well, how cares? As long as you can type out a good report... -- Get motion sickness: Not for a long time... -- Think you're attractive: Heck. No. -- Get along with your parents: Damn. Not really. -- Like thunderstorms: In school, especially P.E. times....  -- Play an instrument: None. And I mean it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     Can you believe it? Jolin's new costume and song 'Pirate' is so cool and unique! You should all go and listen, very unique and special. And I just love her outfit, especially the female outfit. The male outfit is like a mini copy of Johnny Depp character in 'Pirates Of The Carribean'. But I heard that Jolin had to wear three layers of skirt for the female outfit, not forgetting the corset. Whoa! But Jolin looked really dainty and sweet. I just love her curls. I am going to curl my ends when my shoulder-length hair grows longer. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hehe! A little html code I am trying to do. Let me see if it works. ("o")  I kinda like the side-by-side look. You really cannot differentiate the two sisters. But gosh, they are pretty. I must learn how to draw them. Ya.   urlLink     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Newspaper report said that youngsters nowadays are very 'into' internet chatrooms and getting abused becoz of this. I thought this was so long ago... But the new thingy that is taking we teenagers over the storm is 'Friendster' (I have linked it at the bottom of my blog. Scroll down and enter to 'Friendster'). That's true. Coz I am a little crazy over this new programme. But I am a little introvert, so not many friends or testimoniels. But ok. The downside of 'Friendster' is that it runs very slow at times and runs like a bullet at very rare times. But I heard that the management will look into it. And I have not made new friends so far, just found many ex- primary school friends. Well, I have to just keep looking... (".) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know, finally know how to create simple html codes for small graphics. That's cool. And this means I can put in pictures I like and of course linking back to the owners' web site. I have included Dodo's Watermelon  urlLink   and Tifa's Strawberry  urlLink  . They are cute and kawaii! Oh, and before this, I have visited quite a few CHOBITS website. Mostly Anime. And gosh, how vast the difference between anime and manga. Anime version of CHOBITS is more conservative and funnier with many twists. While manga is more depressed where the male character wonders alot about Chii and all that. Weird huh? I will try to put in a small screen cap when I have the time and free. Off for dinner! Ciao!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's official! I have purchased the last volume of CHOBITS Book! And that was Volume 2. Funny is it? Why my last book wasn't vol. 8? Coz I first read CHOBITS was Vol. 3 and the last was Vol. 2... So that means I read Vol. 3 then 5, 6, 7, 8 and then jumped back to 4, 1, 2... Ya, I am a weirdo. Like right now I have two speakers at my computer blasting techno music... Thanks to my  brother . *Grrr* Oh, and 1 Book cost $6 nett. And 8 books together cost about $48. Whoa, I am sure a big spender. ^o~ Ya, I admit, CHOBITS is a little R(A) kinda comic. But this is the only trick to lure those Japanese readers, right? Anyway, initially, I was a little shock by the graphics, but reading repeatedly had made it a small thing. At least it is not as bad as the 'Eechi' or 'Hentai' kinda stuff (No offence). I think.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did I mention that my brother got a sore eye? I felt so angry and happy in a way. Angry coz he was so stupid to get into a fight. Happy because it served him right. Haha. I felt so evil....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink http://www.us.playstation.com/Content/games/SCUS-97266/ogs/    You really have to browse, no, read through thoroughly this website! It is so cool! The newest Playstaion game where it can be played along side the PCs (that's me!)! And the CGs are certainly more detailed and precise. Now nearing to something about people versus monsters. And as usual, the evil are after something and the heroes are after the monsters and so on... But what is so kawaii and stunning are the characters! The Humes, are the most human- being like while I love the so cute Tarutaru! Their hair, face and height just made me want to run and grab them, emtionally... Haha! Everything is cool, I recommend everybody to view the short clip in the main website. I felt like I was viewing a movie where you just have the urge to play the game. Now, this is what I call online game! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did a little house-keeping... Update on my 'update box', LiveJournal and included 1 link... This Princess Diane's is an illustration website, I accidentally clicked on the link, of course stupidly thought that it would be about THE Princess Diane... But her website was filled with sweet, sweet and cute pictures of a little girl she drew. Very kawaii! I always have a thing for this kind of cute, cute stuff although I admit I don't look like one who will carry cute key chains or draw these icons. That's really not me. But I love the little girl and the hostess's love for everything. But a caution for non-chinese browers, you must download a chinese sofeware, if not you can't really read what exactly is going on. But her icons are in English, so it is easy to browse. *Running off to check on my more websites...*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A very general update on what I did during the whole of the March holidays... Hehe! Actually a little boring, but what the heck... I AM boring!  M O N D A Y - Slack, slack and slack. Coz I was tyring to relax after my stressful day at my workplace. Sunday was a disaster! But... I went out with my friends to celebrate her early birthday! Did nothing much but walk around from Little India to Bugis to Suntec. I even lied to my parents that I did not go for the Food And Beverage Fair 2004, they would be so crushed! But I had lots of fun there, good food and free/cheap stuff. Conclusion? It was a tiring but very fun day. And full too.  T U E S D A Y  - I really need a day of breather, I even let my mother help me to return my library books.... *~* So never went out. Drool over SDs, again... And just basically mope around the house. Even my aunty wanted to invite me out to shop, but I rejected her...  W E D N E S D A Y - Same and exactly like Tuesday. Coz I was too lazy, ya, call me a pig. My father also began to be very anxious about my postings results. I wasn't. I was trying to explain to him that it would be relaeased at Sat. He said, check, check, no harm checking. Darn.  T H U R S D A Y - Went out with my friends again. This time to Jurong East for the LOTR Exhibit. The so-called ''Only Venue In Asia''... Well, having to pay $16 for the entry ticket was a heartache, but it was certainly an eye-opener. I didn't know that the crew behind the movie were so hard-working and precise. I began to admire Alan Lee's drawings and sketches. And they even have the 'Armour Corridor'' where all the armour costumes were so, whoa! It was like the soldiers were standing right in front of you, facing you with the strong, cold looks... The costumes were breatheless! Especially, Galadriel's dress, so stunning! And, and Legolas's costume, Arwen's and Aragon! Eeek! The digital effects and make-up sections were so cool and informative. I actually cannot believe that behind the orcs and scary guys, they are actually extras in that costumes. Whoa! Oops, shouldn't leak out too much of information. But no cameras were allowed, so not pics. The souviners section was a let- down though. All the prices of the rings were kinda steep and so, fake, well. Everybody who loves LOTR should go and visit to be blown away. Though, the air-con was a little cold and the exhibit was a little dark... :p  F R I D A Y - Went back to work... *Yawn*  S A T U R D A Y - Went to purchase my MSD Mary at Domuya a few hours ago. So happy! *\^o^/* Although I will be seeing her only after three weeks, but I AM SO ELATED! YES! And I was posted to a JC, science stream. Yeah. And my ex- cca got first in their competition. Ya! Congrats! Today is certainly a fulfilling day! Haha!  S U N D A Y - Although Sunday will be tomorrow, I betta I can tell you what is going to happen tomorrow. Work, work and work. And maybe going out to have dinner with my family later...  END.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Suppose to go out today to Dobby Ghaut's Spotlight to purchase some buttons and lace ribbons. I want to decorate my bag into something lolita and sweet. My bag cannot be a Gothic kinda bag coz it is not black or dark. But I can always buy a few metres of leather skins or something like that... Hmmm.... Interesting thought, but this is project no. 2... Project no. 1 is to finish my cross-stitch pencil case. I bought it last year and ya, have been slacking to finish it. And I am short of one of the color strings, don't know how I am able to finish the string so fast within a small pattern. And the pattern was simple and easy. Not like those big cross-stitch pattern, where you have to use different stitching patterns into so, so, small holes.... I am certainly slacking throughout the whole week. But by the way, I am nearing my target to get doll. Very possibly a MSD. Then maybe I will purchase a petite AI or infant. They look so cute! Or maybe a ''Who's that girl?'' doll, they certainly have nice anime eyes... But first, have to rush to check my savings.... *running, running....*  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      R A N D O M In the morning I am: Exhausted and in need for a fresh air.... Hate Smokers! all i need is: Money and freedom. Please? *~* love is: Something you need to recieve and feel and believe it at least once in a lifetime. *I think I saw a halo above my head...* i dream about: I obviously cannot remember it. I don't really remember my dreams that vivdly. Although I always remember nightmares...  o p p o s i t e  s e x  what do you notice first: Face and Hair. Ya, I am a sucker for hair and good character. last person you slow danced with: Nobody. I guess I have never slow danced before....  worst question to ask: So.... How old are you? When are you getting your results? Duh, I don't need all these kind and *thoughtful* questions to know me, ya know. who do you have a crush on: SDs! My Lucas! I really can drool over it. who has a crush on you: I think nobody physically in particular. Hehe!  d o  y o u  e v e r  wish you were a member of the opposite sex?: Actually, yes. I do. I actually wish how life is for the boys with no PMS or any pimples or BO or make up to worry about... *Chasing after a boy for answers* wish you were younger: Ya. I wish I am forever young. Yup. cried because someone said something to you?: Who never? That person must be an angel or just deaf and dumb to do anything.  N u m b e r  of guys ive kissed: Never. Zero. of continents i have lived in: ''Bo'', Hokkien for nothing. of tight friends: ''Tight''? As in? I have a few very good friends, but not tight. Is this question leading to another? of cds i own: 20++  of scars on my body: Around less than 10 visible scars. And numerous ''unseen' scars... Adding up to together will be at least 20++  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hehe, I was eyeing at a FFX-2 Album at HMV. It was priced at $19+ which includes 'Real Emotion' and '1000 Words'. I am really looking forward to purchasing the album. And I will try to pursuade my parents to go to the IT Show 2004 at Suntec to buy at least a digital camera. I am eyeing the Panasonic DMC-FX1 or an Olympus. But price- wise, Olympus is only $399+ while the panasonic is $649 (=~=). But Panasonic features more like the famous Macro function and many white balance settings. Olympus has more megapixels and 'Super Macro'... But first, my quiz....     i n f o r m a t i o n  1. name: Akiko, the one who always hates everything in the world. 2. single or taken: Single. Hm, I don't like the word 'taken', sounds so low. Like those that are 'untaken' are the unlucky ones. I tell you, no. We are not! I am happy as a single even if it means I will be a single forever. 3. sex: Female. I have a very pure mind and concept. Don't lead me into the wrong path. 4. siblings: 1  5. hair color: Lightish brown. Ya, I did mentioned before I like a coffee downpour girl.  6. eye color: Brown. Dull color. 7. shoe size: A petite 5, or is it a 6?   8. height: 160cm. And will never grow up again.  r e l a t i o n s h i p s  1. who are your best friends?: My sec school friends. What about my pri. school? I was too miserable to remember. 2. do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?: No. That's kinda sad, right?   f a s h i o n s t u f f  1. where is your favorite place to shop: The nearer to my home, the better. Ya, I hate to travel far. Or places I am firmiliar with. Ya, I hate to lost my way.    2. any tattoos or piercings: Tattoos, nah. Piercings? My ear lobes. That's it.  s p e c i f i c s  1. do you do drugs?: No. I am not sick. Stop cursing me. 2. what kind of shampoo do you use?: Dove. I am going to swtich to the Pantene's 'Lose Hair Control' or something like that. Coz my hair keeps falling. Ooops, there goes another strand of hair again.  3. what are you most scared of?: Nowadays, I will say I am scared of getting a sucky job that pays low and you must see other people's 'faces' every time... Man, I hate that! 5. who is the last person that called you?: One of my friends, she was anxious about her project or something like that. 6. where do you want to get married?: Somwhere that is simple, quick, good food, good music, good air conditioner. And no, it is not a church. Sounds like a restaurant... That will do.   7. how many buddies are online right now?: 6 right now. It's the low peak of the hour... 8. what would you change about yourself?: My physical looks foremost. Then, maybe my character or attitude. My father always says I have an attitude problem, ya, I have, especially to him.  f a v o r i t e s  1. colors: orange and white. But I hope my future room will be painted deep pink oround the four walls and then a thick line of orange across the room. Ceiling will be white. Coz it helps to 'expand' the room.  2. food: Noodles, noodles and Japanese food. 3. boys names: Oooo. I love this question. Lucas, first. Coz I love Lucas SD, regardless if it is 1st or 3rd edition. Second, Harry. I like this name for a long time. Because SM Lee's christian name is Harry. And of course, Harry Potter. Both characters are brave! Shiro is also a nice name. 4. girls names: Sylvie, also taken form a limited edition female SD. And boy, she is a beauty. And also Freya and Alda (something like that, I translated from the chinese words) from Chobits. 5. subjects in school: Arts. No specific favourite subjects. 6. animals: Dogs and hamsters and rabbits. I like those, their movement are so cute! 7. sports: swimming. I am lazy, so I did nothing much but just walking around...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Paine   urlLink   Which Final Fantasy X-2 character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Did twice again. And that's my future, being dark and quiet. But.... I LIKE IT! I have always love Paine! Her hair and everything. But I kinda don't agree with her skull badge. Her costume is fun and cool, so is her sword. Did I mention that I bleached my hair again? Now to Ash Brown color from Gatsby, thanx to my brother who volunteered to streak my hair. My hair looked like coffee stain all over it. (*o*) He said he wanted that color coz he can pass it off to his DM that that is his 'natural' color. And please, his March holiday is just next week and my mother promised him that he can color his hair any way he likes for next week, duh! He just won't listen. Oh and that means I am putting ammonia and hydrogen peroxide and other too difficult chemical terms to type in here, to name a few. You can always go and glance at the side of any Gatsby hair dye box. It's all stated on there, Jap. people are real honest guys... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am in a bad mood. I say it again, I am in a bad mood. So the below survey maybe a little, not me. But reassured that there is no vulgarities, I have removed it some ques that involved in that.  The Basics  Name: Akiko...  Age: 17 going on 40... Gender: Female, no, I just had my sex operation... *whistling* Hey Babe! Location: Somewhere in the eastern part of Singapore. Are you stalking me? Looks: Short, plump and dark. In other words, I look like shit.   Social Life  What kind of school do you go to?: Very smart question. And I am smart enough not to answer. How many friends do you have at school: Surprisingly, less than 5.  How often are you online: Everyday, IF my brother is not hogging the computer and when I am not exhausted from my work.  How many friends do you have online: 5. At max.  Have a crush/obbsession/stalkee: Nah. But I was hoping for either one of the three... Ya, I am desperate to fall into the sea of love. Care to share his/her name: Blah, blah, blah.... Also, would you like to tell us why you crush/obbsess/stalk them: I am desperate? =o= Finally, is this person a friend or just someone you admire from a distance: I hope, my future 'admiree' will be someone I am not too close to know anything about me. *banging head against the wall*   Which of your friends is...  The Purest: Me. Duh. Most Devilish: Devilish? I don't hang around with the wolves or foxes... Most Perverted: Ah ha! 'She' will know who I am referring to... The Smartest: God and forever your parents. The Funniest: Everyone of my friends has a sense of humor, you just have to know when to capture the laughing gas. Convinced They'll Get You In The Sack Someday?: No. Friends do not get you in the sack. Even if they do, I will also never realise it. So, next que!  The News Buff: Me!  The Insane One: Not me! And What Word Describes You, If None Of These Work: Weird-girl-who-hates-everything....   Word Association  Hungry: No. Air in my stomach... Uncomfortable.... Posted: Ya, I posted a cheque this morning.... Water: Sweating. I am sweating profusely right now. *bangs the old fan again* Chips: Potato. See. Potato and Chips, gets Potato Chips, get it? Cow: Meat. And I was not allowed to eat beef ever since the mad cow disease... But now and then I still consume.... Single: Me. I am single... ARRGH: What the heck is the problem? I have heard too much 'ARRGH!' for one day! ARRGH!  Ducks: Beijing Peking Duck. Yum Yum! Puppies: Cute and cute! Red Hot: Chillies. Oooo, hot!   Have You Ever  Drank: water and drinks, right? Ya, of course. Smoke: No. Never. *Holding out axe to kill smokers in sight* Snogged Someone: Ewww. Nope. Done drugs: Nope. Done Karaeoke: With my relatives and boring. Coz they were all belting out old, hokkien songs.... My brother and I went to the bowling alley and pool table instead. Gone into a chat just to annoy people: Hmmm.... Sometimes, in IRC, and go to God-knows-where channel to vent my fustrations.... Hehe! Filled out a survey with bullshit answers: Did once. And never again. But don't mind doing again to get the kick out of it. Swore in front of your mother/father: No. Behind their backs... Who never? Contemplated a huge road trip with friends just for shits and giggles: I am not going to be the next Britney to do Crossroads. But I really don't mind. Had dreams involving your internet friends: Nah, I always cannot remember my dreams. *Baging head against wall repeatedly....* Screamed random things at people while in a moving vehicle: In my father's car while he is fetching me to my workplace. I will complain and make everybody listen to what I say. Ya, I am very forceful when it comes to venting my fusrations. Written a song: Not really. But if you pay me, I can write a song nobody wishes to listen and leave you alone. Ya, that includes your parents....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      TODAY IS GOTH DAY! Hehe, not really but this entry is all about goth! First, quiz.... I did it twice and got the same results! Am I doomed to be so dark and black?   Atelier Boz: You've got real class!  You're Gothic/Lolita because it is an expression of yourself, not because it is an expression of your friend's self.  You do have a tendency to be a bit of a downer, though.   urlLink   Which Gothic Lolita Fashion House Is For You?!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Next.... Names.... urlLink http://www.necroticobsession.com/gothname.html  Haha.... This website can generate your Goth Name! And mine is 'Innocence Lost'', so funny! I have not lose my innocence yet... Worth going, just for fun lah!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Reopening of  urlLink http://www.volks.co.jp/en/index.aspx , browsed through already. A little confused and weird. Their introduction to every dolls or other areas is so, so... accurate and precise. And they really aim to satisfiy every customer. So many sweet and dreamy wordings.... I felt I have stepped into a child's heaven, everything is so perfect and dreamy.... But I am not buying these stuff online... My parents are very strict about buying online goods. They cannot trust online sites. Hiaz... I just have to keep looking!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink http://www.ff12.com/   *laughs* I am really contradicting myself again! Playstation has featured another Final Fantasy online game, FF 12. And of course, it is newer than FF 11 and better image quality and very, very detailed structures of 'buildings' and airships. I like it, this time, not focusing or drooling over the characters, but the structures of airships and the view. Though I must say the characters are certainly cooler and nicer- looking. But no cute, cute characters. Just more skin are exposed and more realistic features. Too bad, it is going to be released only next year, 2005. Hmmm... Just a thought though. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Gold or silver : I am actually a 'gold' kinda person... My horoscope metal is gold. But in reality, silver seems pure, to me. ~.^  What was the last film you saw at the movies? : "Fantasia" or something like that. It features TWINS, Jordan Chen, and others. I watched it during New Year's eve. Oh, did I tell you I am not really a sucker for movie? I will only watch my fav "Harry Potter"... (drools)  Favorite cartoon/anime? : Anime ah.... I have not watch anime for a long time already, neither do I watch cartoons... Oh! I remembered! I watched "Black Jack" a few weeks ago at Arts Central. "Black Jack" is not really a anime, right? But I really love to watch! It is always late in the night because of it's not very "suitable rating" for kids. Ya, I will be looking out for "Black Jack" comics...  What did you have for breakfast this morning? : Nothing. I rushed out for my dental appointment and later went out with my friends for breakfast cum lunch. So I took wanton noodles.  Who would you love being locked in a room with? : As in human being? Nobody in particular. But I really love to lock in with Doremon coz it has everything I need and want! Ya, there was this incident and joke about Doremon we had this afternoon. Haha!  Could you live without your computer? : Not really. But I can live without it for a few days. But not forever! 0_o  Would you color your hair? : Yes, I have already colored my hair already. So far, so good. No Discipline Master tailing me or asking me to dye back. But in the future, I better leave it to the hairstylists....  Could you ever get off the computer? : Ha, I am very good at it! Give me half an hour, and I will automactically get off. Unlike my brother, he will take more than an hour to get off after playing his RPG the whole night.... -__-  How many people are on your buddy list? : 47 in all. 6 close friends and remaining are all classmates. No cousins or relatives.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ah... Finally able to blog something in Blogger. The previous post was a pic of my MSD Mary, Natsumi. As you already know, or I have already realised myself, I fanatic about dolls. Ha! So a real close-up pic of her. Whew! Thanx for Hello! Oh, the holidays are coming, but I cannot damn feel the holiday spirit. Urgh. My progress report sounded quite badly and negatively. And yes, I still loathe maths. What's the problem if you are quiet? I am very confused... Hmmm... I shouldn't have go to school today, ya know. I could have stayed at home and slack. I missed my friends a lot. Yesterday, we went out for dinner and everything was so fun and we just laughed and teased and well, just had fun! I am currently in the school library rambling nonsense, and students around me are surprisingly, rushing for their powerpoint presentation. Whoa, no wonder I cannot feel the holiday spirit...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Natsumi!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Downloaded Hello! So it will be easier for me to upload pictures. So cool, and fast. Really. I have taken this pic (at the profile) from the Jap Volks website, she is a One off Model. Meaning: Only one kind of doll in this world, and it is only available for the Jap residents. She is a beauty! Initially, I have uploaded a pic of SD13 Michael, he is actually dressed in black gothic outfit and painted in very, red lipstick. I actually prefer Michael pic to this current Nana pic. But, I fear that I will scare off everybody, letting them think that SDs are so scary. NO! They are not! SDs are really, very beautiful dolls created by skillful artists. Hiaz... Better not start a war here, hehe! So enjoy my blog and await for more ramblings of my daily life. To see more pics of my MSD in the future (coming very soon), you will have to visit LiveJournal... Edit: Haha! Changed back the profile pic to my MSD-Marie, Natsumi. I think this pic made her look more mature. But it was not taken by me, I took it again from Volks website. ^ ^
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! Blogger is so cool! The new Blogger is certainly sleeker and much, much more faster... Ya, I know, this has been ages already, but let me gush over first, please? Ooops, sorry for the long wait for whoever has been waiting patiently to see if I have any updates. Yes, I have finally realised that Windows XP made my blog look like a rubbish dump. I used to use Windows 98, but I have since 'upgraded' to Windows XP. For the few months I'm not here, I have totally given up on this blog, becoz of the codes. But now, I will just stick to the templates that Blogger has. Hope it works and my blog will look much more neater. ^^ I was in LiveJournal for the past few months and have made many friends who also love SDs and AI. SDs is known as Super Dollfie. Oh, did I ever mentioned that I have purchased a MSD-Mini Super Dllfie? Her name is called Natsumi. Very sweet and pretty. So, I will just end here, if you wish to read my LJ, feel free to browse, it's more stable down there in terms of LJ structure and entries. I may need a little more time adjusting to this new Blogger. Oh, and Happy 1st birthday to my blog, it is 1 year old plus plus already. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>