<Blog>

<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Step Up Day? WTF?]  Yeah, the eighth graders come up to my school on monday. Woohoo. That means we get a bunch of snot-nosed losers who idolize FRESHMEN. God, that's stupid. Next thing on the agenda: Something reeks. I'm in CAD class, and something form the area of the moron clump smells like decomposition. I think the had some school breakfast or something. And finally, I think that Biology  blows . Why? Because I've been up until almost 11pm every night this week making a project for the class. I have to make a "Portfolio containing your best works from the semester". BS. In this portfolio, I need to collect a bunch of work from the semester, and write a letter from someone I don't know to another person I don't know. Why? How the hell am I supposed to know? I'm out.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Blow Me]  Ya know what? I don't give a fuck what you think about this page. If you don't like it, go ahead and blow me. I made this page as a web journal, not to make fun of people, or to try to win friends on the internet. So, like I said, I don't care what you think about me OR my blog.
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Ben is nuts]  Uhh I think Ben is nuts. He just made a picture in DataCAD that had a little guy with a gun next to his head. Now, this would've been all nice and cool except he had a little section of text that said "I'm going to shoot myself" in very very bad writing. Duncan has made him black as well. I'm out.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Erm...No dice]  Well. After a long weekend of playing around in my house (building stuff) I still have *gasp* no computer. (*sigh*) I had some trouble this weekend. In the parking lot for BJ's, I almost hit a guy who decided to park within three inches of me. Moron. Last Friday was Martin Sargent's last day on the ScreenSavers! :*( He has a new show on Monday to Thursday at 2300, on TechTv, so check it out. It's really weird...think Tom Green + Computer. I saw a segment where Martin went to the International Gourmet Kitchen Appliances Show in LA. Do you know why he went there? That's right. To get a blender! Oh yes, a blender. He went through the convention for about an hour to find the most badass blender there, and my oh my did he find a kickass blender! It was the PowerBlend 5000 from Kitchenaid, and it was a military-grade crusher-blender-pureer-killing machine. Check out Unscrewed at 2300 (That's 11pm for you military-impared ones) on TechTv. Well, I'm almost done with my house now. We have the plumbing in, and will have water by next weekend (yay!). After that, all we need to do is finish the electrical boxes then we can hang the drywall, lay down careting, and then do the finish work. I'll update some other time.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Home, Sweet Home]  I'm at home, on my brother's computer. Not quite as slow as the school computers, but almost there compared to my race car-puter. I checked out the stuff from the view of a computer on another resolution (the school computers have it locked on 1024x768), and I noticed that my posts section is...small. I tried to remedy this, but I don't have the patience to do that right now, so I'll do it on Tuesday during CAD class >:). Err...It's Friday, like I said before, and David is going to come up tonight, so maybe I'll get my puter back fomr the shop, which I have found, is where it  has been hiding since last Thursday. But, I'm a little bored. All week,I have been watching shows like  Silent Mobius  on  urlLink TechTv  and the  ScreenSavers , also on  urlLink TechTv , but the content has...stagnated. (*sigh*) This is getting to be a little annoying, working on such a slow computer, soooo cloooose to where mine was just eight days ago...I feel like I  need  to play Natural Selection! >.>  Ah well. Later.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Out with the old...]  OK here's the deal. New Template and the tagboard *finally* works. I know I've been saying that I was gonna fix it all week, but I finally did, so TAG! I think I am the only one who tagged (keys doesn't count, he's too short :P). Duncan and Ben are still playing with  urlLink Terragen,  a terrain generator, which takes FOREVER on the school computers. Oh well. Umm. It's Friday, and suprisingly, I didn't see Matt yesterday, so I couldn't scream things almost like "Happy Birthday" at him. But it's Friday, and since it is Friday, I'm not gonna do any work in CAD class. Hey--doesn't that sound like Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,  and  Thursday too? I think I may be seeing a pattern here. Ben is going to be a narcileptic now, just to see whether the teacher, Mr Duquette notices. I wonder if he does... Over the past few weeks, I have acquired more and more students from Duquette-san, and I have been teaching them the masterful art of Visual Reality.
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Boring]  Here it is. May 22. A.K.A. Late Arrival day. That means that I get at school at 830 and I wait until about 945 until CAD starts, so I can continue playing games, though on another computer in another room. You may be noticing that I cannot spell the word necessary correctly, as Ben has pointed out many times. The problem is, I cannot spell long words for shit and I don't care if you tell me, got it Ben? Good. Another idiot is near me. This seems to be a pattern...thenever I go into the CAD room, an idiot comes to meet me. Hmmm.... Jimmy the Fish is next to me ranting...this reminds me of the Ranting Swede from the show  Sheep in the Big City  from the Cartoon Network. Silly Jimmy... Seth is next to me on his laptop, which I was just playing Unreal Tournament 2003 (if you haven't heard of it, the site is  urlLink here ) on (and pwning, just so you know). But, since it was Seth's computer, I let someone else have a chance to get pwned (this is where the moron comes in). Anyways...I'm out.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Slow?]  Well. I WAS going to write about how slow this computer is, but for some reason, while I was showing someone how to do something, Duncan thought it was nessicairy to delete my post. I'm a little pissed off right now.
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Negative on Duquette?]  Today, my CAD teacher, Mr Duquette is out. Instead, we have one of the coolest subs in the school, Mr Ben Hill. Mr Hill does stuf to make him cool, and I'm not sure what that stuff is yet, because I've only had him as a teacher for one or two classes. Anyway. About 30 seconds after I typed the last sentence on my last post, my friend came in and told me that his mom was going to give us a ride instead of him going to get his car. Later, though we went to the store and came back to school to get working papers (hmmm maybe I should get those today...), and all of this was in his car! W007 M0nt3 C4|2l0!!1  :) I'll update again later if I feel it is nessicairy, or if I just have nothing to do.
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Waiting...]  By now, you may have realized that I am waiting for something. It turns out that this somethign may be my Tag-Board to work. I got it to be on the page, but...it's a little high for my taste. In this update, I'm going to try to fix that up for my own state of mind (haha!). But, alas, I am waiting instead for my ride home. I was told by my friend that I could get a ride with him because he got lisence today (did I spell that right?). So, he was going to pick me up in his brand spanking new '98 Monte Carlo LS (whoohoo), but, at 15:30, he still isnt here, and it is a about an hour after school ended. LOL! After I got done typing that last sentence, his mom just pulled into the school traffic circle thingy, which happens to be right in front of me. Aight, I'm going to try to fix that annoying thing on the tag board. Later y'all.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [WTF?]  Now, you may be thinking, why did he use that inappropriate phrase? I assure you that it was not supposed to offend anyone, except maybe Ben Perkins...but that is beside the point ;-). I'm writing to y'all from CAD class, and the reason is because...my PC at home has been, well...misplaced. I'm not sure why or how, but: One day it was there and the next day it wasn't. If you can assist me in finding it, please drop me an email. Wait. Scratch that. No computer = No Email. You may be asking "How are you updating your Blog, then?" Well, rest assured, I have my ways. Uhh. I'm gonna try to get a TaggitBoard up for you all to drop one-liners on, and maybe some NIALL quotes (NIALL is a Non-Intelligent Language Learner, the A means something, but I'm not sure what that is). Another Language bot is the Jibble Applet Bot, located  urlLink Here . I'm not sure where NIALL is right now, but the JibbleBot is cool because you can see how it actually maps its language.  Well. Later.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Once Again]   Again, idiocy confounds me.  But off of that, I would like to say that today is a good day. First of all, most of my classmates are off on a fieldtrip, so in two of my classes, we won't be doing anything at all! In the other two classes, we don't do any work at all anyways, so it don't matter. :) Oh ya, I only have four classes.  I'm sitting in 3D Art class right now, typing on a SLOW computer while I should be doing my monster project >:). About that, the blog for it is at  urlLink This Blog .  Check it out in a few days, and I should have updated it at least once.    Furthermore, today is good because the Matrix: Reloaded comes out today :-D. Check it out at   urlLink The official Site   Erm, for now, I don't have anything else to tell y'all, so I'm off.  Later.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Idiocy Confounds Me]   ...What should I write about? I have a flaming moron near me and I'm not sure what his problem is...for some reason, he just stands there screaming at me and other people, for no reason whatsoever. Oh well.   Another note, I'm about to make fun of people. I'm sitting here in CAD class, and I guess I've inherited a protege (*sigh*) from the teacher. The thing is, this kid can't hold his own for crap. Yesterday, for example, I told him how to do the same thing about twelve times before giving up. Needless to say, I'm a little annoyed by him.   Another Idiot that I can't stand is Senator Fritz. For some reason, he thinks that people need to have their computers all equal and with "Trusted Parts." These "trusted" parts have special chips on them that allow the Trusted Computer Platform Agency to know what you do at all times. They will log your keytappings, and they will be able to remotely scan your computer and delete any files they don't like, such as music, "Innapropriate" games (GTA III for example), and any pirated stuff on your computer (music, games, videos, etc).   Oh ya, speaking of idiocy, check out my friend's blogs:  urlLink Dismantled Intentions  and  urlLink Monochromatic Existence    I'll update later. 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Where was I?]  This week, I have been taking some time off.I just didn't feel like posting. But, I have things to tell anyone who reads this. First: I keep getting people telling me that they don't like this page. I have a question for those people: Why do you read it then? If you don't like my page or the way I run it, stop coming back and shut up! I'm not going to change the layout, the subjects, or my tone for anyone or anything. Next: This is the last week the Seniors are at my school. This is saddening because I have quite a few Senior friends. I didn't notice this until yesterday when they were in the Auditorium at school, and they were playing pictures from the past year on the big screen thingy. Now, I coulda taken this fine, except they were playing the song "I Will Always Love You" by Whitney Houston, I think (Don't even think of tagging or emailing me about me being wrong, because I will immediately delete them). Now this song is very saddening, plus someone played it at my Dad's funeral reception, so it makes me depressed almost every time I hear it. Anyways, I saw my friend Jeremy for what could be the last time today. I'm moving about 40 miles from my current home, and since Jeremy is a Senior, he will be going to Rochester Academy next year. Combine these two, and you'll understand that I may not be able to talk to him other than in emails or at F.I.R.S.T. competitions that he gets to come to, if my team goes to the ones he goes to. Enough of the saddening stuff. Wait. I don't have much else to say. Oh ya...I am Neo from the Matrix:   You are Neo, from "The Matrix." You display a perfect fusion of heroism and compassion.    urlLink   What Matrix Persona Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Try that out, it's pretty cool.  Oh well. Later.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Uhm ya...about that...]  Yup. I wasn't here yesterday. Orthodontist appointment. Then I went to our computer shop for about six hours. After that, I went to my new house then home. I don't feel like doing anything today, so I won't.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Must...Have...Computer...]  It's only been about a week since my last entry. I'm on tongiht to update all my stuff and check my email, maybe even talk to my estranged friends (estranged = disconnected from me). I haven't  talked to my friend Jeremy since school let out...maybe I should email him...later... I'm starting to wish I had a computer at this point, because I've been out of the loop, and all of my friends have gone out and done stuff without me even knowing! *Sighs* That, and NS 2.0 comes out in about 9 days...but who's counting? Work (I should tell you about it huh) ...work is starting to be...uhh...traumatizing. The little girl (I told y'all about her) thinks that I'm her boyfriend now, and tells all her friends so. Why can't I get the girls I actually want? This confuses me severely. *Sighs again* With nothing really to tell you other than that, I'm off to check on my friend's blogs.  G'Night y'all.  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Long Time No See]  Hey all. Unless you're completely retarded, you might have guessed that I haven't posted in about.... 40 days; but who's counting?. This is because I haven't had time! Believe it or not, I actually have a job and after work, I go to my new house to work on it. Fun Fun Fun. Sadly, I haven't even had time for girls, like my friend Bonsai on  urlLink DisInt . He seems to be having a little trouble with his lady-friend, but I hope it works out well for him. Seriously. Hey shut up! What's up with this world...no one ever believes a sincere comment because of all the negative and sarcastic remarks that get thrown around. Sheesh. Anyway. NS 2.0 comes out July 31. (*Is excited*) Back to work...I work at a summer camp and we go around the state to swim and play around in all the state parks on monday, tuesday, thursday, and friday. On wednesday, we go somewhere special, like a museum or roller skating. I've met a bunch of people and reunited with a couple old friends (all counselors), and I'm afraid that one little girl "likes" me too much. I'm not lying...she follows me around and trys to show off to me and she's just weird around me. Ok off of that... I'm still sad that I haven't even  talked  to a girl my age (out of work and offline) for about a month now. *Sighs* I'm hoping to hook up with my friends and go to Hooters (Fa'Tony...ahem!) but to no avail, as my mom has been in the hospital twice in the past three weeks, and is there as I write this post. Back to girls. I  really really really  wish I knew one who liked me on more than a friendship or professional level. I think I'm compatable, at least, but all the girls just act like I'm the nice guy they's just like to "be friends" with. *Sighs twice* I'll never understand girls, but then again...who will? *Sighs again for good measure* I don't have much else to say tonight, so if you wanna talk to me, my contact info is on the side, and my AIM is wolfhoundNH. Bye  --Clash
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Whoa...Halloween]  It's been a loooong time since I updated, huh? I bet y'all thought I was dead. Unfortunately for you I'm still here, just fell asleep for a long time...nah I lied I was just a little busy. I have a question: Why is it that the nicest people tend to be the ones that live the loneliest lives out? I mean Bill Gates, the purest form of evil is happily married, but a person like me, who is nice to everyone he sees is seen as a loner, no matter what he tries to get the attention of the girls that he likes? It confuses me to no end. If you asked anyone I know, they would say that I have never done anything to make them dislike me (Even Bonsai who ritually and regularly tries to bring my self-esteem lower than it already is). Does anyone out there know why this happens? I surely don't. Whatever. To whine a bit more, I have noticed that all of my friends have a very close friend of the opposite sex...even the punk-geek ones. Monochrome has this really nice girl named Chelsea, Bonsai has a girl named Talia (who may not exist because I've never seen her), Keys had a girlfriend until just recently, but I'm sure that he can get another if he tried. So that leaves me. The last girlfriend I had was in the summer, and we broke it off after being "together" for about 3 weeks since she "Didn't want to have a strained long-distance relationship." Bah fuck. Last night Monochrome told me that a girl at school liked me, and though I was skeptical, I went along with it for a while. Today she didn't even say "Hi" to me. Once again: Bah Fuck. On another point, I have CAD again next semester (that is, after the second week of January). This means I'll be updating a lot more by then. More on updates: Bonsai has moved to  urlLink his own blog . This means that you probably won't see a lot of him on DisInt. Keys has pretty much left DisInt alone altogether so you won't see a lot of him there either. Monochrome is still at his old blog,  urlLink here . If you feel the need to, update your bookmarks as necessary. I'll be changing the blog links as well to match this new development. One more thing: I think I'm going to change my handle to Raine. It sounds cooler than Clash.  That's about all for now. 'Night.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Blah...]  Blah. I'm in one of my pissed-off depressed moods tonight, so I'm just gonna not post at all other than this one sentence.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Car Car Car Car Car Car Car...]  After work, I went to dinner at Friendly's. In my car! No, it isn't a really big thing for most people out there, but I just got a new car (mentioned in previous posts), and I drove it around Concord and my neighborhood. I  really  love this car a lot. My mom filled it up with gas before she went to Market Basket, and it took less than $10 lol.  I've been training at work, and today I was put with a weird guy named Matt. He's a little slow, I'd say. He liked to repeat his strange sayings (none of which were about the job), and took his time with, well, pretty much everything we did. Whatever.  Today we watched some of Saving Private Ryan in History. Good movie.  Very  good movie. After I'd read the material backgrounding the scenes we watched, I had the strangest desire to play  urlLink Day of Defeat , and I found out tonight that I'm pretty good at being a Sargent/Unteroffizer/Sargent Major. I'm also not too shabby in the Sniper/Marksman/[German Sniper] class. Anything with an automatic non-rifle or a scope, I'm pretty good with, especially in close quarters (not the scope on that part, more the sub machine gun). I went 57/21 with a score of 42 in one round. (Not too bad for someone who'd never played before, eh?) I'm not sure how they award points, but I think it's based on your kill to deaths ratio.  Oh ya--just in case you've noticed typos or things that don't make sense, I'll never go back to change a post other than to make it legible, so I'll never have to be accused of changing information, and I'll not have ot forget things that were important to me at a certain point in my life. If this happens to come back and bite me in the ass, so be it.  Hmmmm....Nothin' else to say tonight.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Five little words]  It's funny how five little words can make you feel so weird. On Thursday, I realized how much I really liked Darcie when she said to my friend "I do like you, Jon." Funny, huh?  I've moved on though. Why? Because I got a car! It's a 2000 Daewoo Nubria, fully loaded with only 43,000 miles on it. I got it for $3,650 (USD). It gets about 35 miles per gallon, and it has a lot of vertical headroom. I like it. The only thing I don't like about it is that it's an automatic :(. Oh well, you can't get everything, huh?  urlLink Here  is a picture of a car that looks just like it, just more expensive. The guy that I bought it from doesn't have a license to sell cars that have been in accidents, so I know its clean. He's going to have it inspected and make sure that everything is good on it before I can take it from his lot, so I know it'll be in good working order. I drove it, so I know it runs. I'm happy. Guess what else I have to tell you? I got a job at Market Basket! Yay! I'll be starting tonarrow at 3:30 and I'll be getting $7.00/hr. It's not much, but it's $7.00/hr that I wasn't making before, plus it gives me something constructive to do in the afternoons. A bunch of my friends work there too, so it can't be horrible or anything, plus if I need a day or a few off, I just ask my boss a week in advance and he'll put it in the schedule. Yay! That's about all I have to post tonight. Later, y'all.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [I'm not too sure right now]  I'm very confused...but more on that later. First off, I went to the mall today and *bought* four games, and two were even for the computer!   -Enter the Matrix-No explaination needed   -Diablo II Expansion-The downloaded one didn't work online   -Jet Grind Radio-Pretty Colors+Cel Shading+Spraypainting stuff=Good   -Rogue Squadron 64-X Wing+Little men running on the ground=Fun >:}  Why am I so confused, you may be asking. I'll tell you after this. After we went to see the Matrix, Janelle and I went to Borders, the coolest book store evar. I bought a deck of Tarot Cards and I'm in the process of learning to Read them for myself. But That's not why I'm so confused. You see, there are a few people who think that I "like" Darcie. I'm pretty sure that I told myself that I wasn't going to let myself or anyone else down again for a while, but the people who have asked me aren't the most intuitive folks that I know, so there  must  be some reason that they think what they do. I don't know if there is a blatant "sign" or something, but I really don't know why three people who barely know wach other have come toward me saying this. It's funny...less than three weeks ago, I was so desperate for a close girl friend that I was feeling dejected after being dropped so many times before. Now, when people are saying that they think I "like" someone, I don't give it any real thought at all. It's not that I don't like Darcie. She's one of the most wonderful people I know: Smart, funny, incredibly deep eyes, and she's nice to everyone, not to mention fun to just talk to. Is it that I think I'm not good enough for anyone? Could be. Or maybe I'm just so lost in my own mind that I don't know what it is that I know and what I don't know. The Tarot give you guidance, much like the Oracle in the Matrix. This morning I gave myself a general guidance reading, and it said that I would have to make a very important decision reguarding a close friend of mine. The decision, the cards said would change my entire mentality from mysterious or cold to open, free, or lost. Could this friend be Darcie? Is this choice to be one way or another, or could it be for me to decide whether I really do have feelings for her? One of the reasons that I haven't had a real girlfriend for, well, ever, is that I'm afraid of alienating my friends from myself. I feel that if I tell a girl that I have feelings for her, which she cannot return that I will lose her as a friend because I can't be near her by choice. I guess it ends up, again, with me feeling inadequate or just having a Victim Mentality, which the Tarot described to me in another form of a reading I practiced with today. I was told that I am someone that people look to as a regulating force, that I am generally not prone to spontenuity, but I was also told that I am also prone to said Victim Mentality, which I am. I feel that I am not quite enough for my friends, or, well, anyone so I pretend to be someone that I am not to make them seem like they need me to just do what I do so that they can be themselves. I modify my personality to what fits the mood of others to balance them, and I have become good at this with practice. I may lose her as my friend for saying this, but it is possible that I do "like" Darcie. When I talk to her, I don't try to be "The Regulator" like with the rest of my friends. I just say what is on my mind, and what I feel, and it seem to fit. I have a feeling inside me that this could be the last post I do feeling like I do, and it very well might be. If Darcie reads this, I will either become closer to her, and she to I, or I may lose her forever. Either way, if she sees this post, I will never be the same, and neither will this blog. This may have been a struggle for you to finish reading, but I thank you for taking the time to do so.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [I just want peace]  Haven't seen Revolutions? See it.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Neo, you are the One.]  Guess what? On Wednesday, The Matrix: Revolutions came out. So, my friends and I are going to see it tonight (booyea). The only problem is, its just the normal crew :(. Darcie isn't going, Chelsea isn't going to be there, and FaTony won't be going either! What's with that? Anyways...I finished downloading a while bunch of stuff last night:      -1984: Ingsoc+BB=doubleplusungood      -MechWarrior 4 Mercenaries: Beep Beep vrrrr shoom! BAM!      -Diablo II Expansion: Lord of Destruction: Ba'al=weird name for a demon  What else? Today we had a sub in History. Guess who? It was Knowlton! Yes, for the second day in one week, we've had the Knowltonator as a sub. That's  really  cool. Knowlton is the strangest person that I know, and he's a great sub. When we're done our work, he starts some philosophical discussion with us. Today, we didn't have time because we watched the West Wing episode from Wednesday, but the last time we had him as sub, we talked about how girls are wearing things that they shouldn't be, and how guys are wearing things that a couple years ago would make them be called gay (run-on). To end this post, I'd like to say that Ryan Gallant of Pembroke, New Hampshire is a complete and utter moron (see side pane for more details).
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Nooooooostril!]  I just talked to my friend Jeremy a minute ago. He's a cool guy, though a little strange. He has *big* nostrils, so we call him Nostril. I don't have a lot to update on today, so I'll just cut it off at that.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Just like the one-winged dove sings a song, sounds like she's singin']  Hmm... Today: I woke up to my computer crapping out. Last night I left it on to run Norton, and it found 80 infected files! Yay! So, after that happened, Norton cleverly deleted the files and my computer didnt like that for some reason. Nevertheless, it was making its funny little noises this morning for a little bit. School was funny though. Functions was dull until we went to a presentation on respect. After that presentation, with all of its flashy pictures, I felt like buying a case of Pepsi...wonder why? Chemistry was, as usual, very, very, very boring. We went on for a little bit about chemicals and then talked a little more about chemicals and then talked about some weird bridge building contest where you use popsicle sticks to build a bridge to span a 30" gap. It seems that my class is going to watch the competition for some reason...iunno why since we're a chemistry class and it's a physics project. Whatever. English was actually semi-fun today. We kept working on those stupid words that I talked about before, and I just copied off of Allison's paper today (since we were working together ;) ;) lol). We talked for a bit and then in the second part of class we talked again until Dunlea made us watch a video on Langston Hughes, which I *proudly* slept through :). History wasn't as good as yesterday. We talked about our candidates for the Final Exam project, and then we talked about Allison's  scary  story she wrote using some '20's era words that Gleason gave us (*shudders*). Afterwards, we talked about the reading from  "A Problem from Hell": America in the Age of Genocide" , at which point he just gave us some questions to answer. Monochrome and I worked with the rest of the people in our row, including Darcie, Chelsea, and a few scary girls named Michelle, Christina, Jessica, June, and the rage-fueled one: Mary. Somehow, I ended up telling everyone in the group the story of how Monochrome burned his chin on some pizza--obviously  completely  off topic, but whatever. In the end of the class, we were talking about the  best  movie evar,  urlLink Donnie Darko . Though it makes no sense at all the first time you watch it, it is major deep stuff after you've seen it twice. I  highly  recommend it to everyone who reads this page...and by every one I mean all one lol. After I got back from school, Monochrome IMed me and started talking about how he can't get Chelsea, who just doesn't seem to want a boyfriend at this point. I have to admire him, though, because he's persistent. What else has happened today? Not too much to be honest. Right now, I'm listening to the best psychadelic rock band ever: Pink Floyd, and I'm feeling a little tripped out :P. Ahh, The Wall r00ls. For today's first survey:   Your element is Earth. I hate to say it but you are down to earth. Stubborn and loyal. You tend to want to nurture others and you are the one person friends always come to for awnsers. Without people like you others would be flying over the edge because, whether you know it or not you keep a steady beat to your life and will end up where you want to in the end. There is a sureness about you that is hard to match that draws people to you. No matter what happens the Earth keeps turning.    urlLink   What's your element     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    ...and:   Miyu -- Now that you know which anime vampire you are, why don't you  urlLink  Click Here  to become one!    urlLink   If you were an anime vampire, who would you be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     I think that's about all for this afternoon's post.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Liff?]  I just finished watching Monty Python's "The Meaning of Life." While I was watching it, I was burning it onto a few CDs for my friends (don't tell lol). One of these friends was Chelsea...and while I was burning it, I realized that she may not like this film, as it happens to be written by a group of sexist English men. I'm almost afraid to give her the CD tomarrow in case she would be offended, as if she is, I may lose a friend in her...What to do? Aight, that's all for now...no wait...it's not. I changed the color of the scrolly-bar on the right side of the window (for IE4+ and NS6). Now,  that's  all.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Updates galore!]  Hey...It's me again. I just thought that I should show you some of the updates I've collected. I found a really cool website that lets you have free tracking on your website, as well as a free guestbook. Why is it so cool? Because I didn't have to code any of it myself, and since I'm lazy that is good for me. I just got a hit counter and a guest book, both at the bottom of the page. I'm not sure whether I'll get anything else, but for now, that's all. I'll update later then.  Guess what? My vampire name is Driretlan: Driretlan is your Vampire name. You are a witty Vampire with a certain style that others are drawn to. To use your new Vampire name and become a Vampire, go here: www.life-blood.vze.com     urlLink What is your Vampire name?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    And I'm most closely related to the song "Sweet Dreams  by the Eurythmics:   "Sweet Dreams" (by Eurythmics) Sweet dreams are made of this Who am I to disagree? Travel the world and the seven seas Everybody's looking for something Some of them want to use you Some of them want to get used by you Some of them want to abuse you Some of them want to be abused    urlLink   Which 80's Song Fits You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    ...Aaaaand for those people who just happen to be fans of me: You won't die. God will take you up to Heaven without having to taste the bitterness of death, just like Elijah and FDR.  http://spartacus007.tblog.com  Political Satire http://www.LiberalClassic.com  Buy unique pro- Liberty apparel, bumper stickers and books!     urlLink How Will You Die?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Finally, I'm loneliness...who woulda thunk it?   You represent... loneliness. Always alone and always sad about it... unlike angst, you don't have to look for a reason to be miserable.  You want to be in the company of people but aren't sure how to act when you're with them.  Sometimes you have to make an effort.  You can't always wait for others to come to you.    urlLink   What feeling do you represent?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    That's about all for now I think.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       [Somebody's got a case of the Mondays...]  Well it's Monday. Whoopee. Today I started feeling like crap. My alarm didn't go off, and I woke up late, and on top of that I didn't get toeat anything. At school  didn't finish my Functions homework, so the teacher was being a douche about that, and in Homeroom, I found out that everyone failed the summer reading tests. Second block wasn't so bad, I did a test then went to the library and drew baaad pictures of the Banshee vehicle from Halo. Afterwards, the day picked up a little when the girl mentioned in the last post started a convo with me ( :-D ). We did some stupid thing matching literary terms to stories or something like that. It was stupid and boring, so I talked to Monochrome for the whole period :). By History, there was about 12 people in the class, so we just hung out mainly. Monochrome and I talked to the girls the are at the next table over, Darcie and Chelsea. Allison is also around and we talk to her too. Darcie is nice, she's tall with dark hair. We have an ongoing joke that she is a stripper becasue when we are bored in History, we draw pictures of pretty much random stuff and have the random stuff fight between them. I was brought into one of these battles by Monochrome, and Darcie drew a stripper who "Distracted Jake." In the end of this paper conflict, Darcie wrote "She wins," to which Monochrome wrote "Who? The stripper or Darcie?" and Darcie wrote: The stripper, 'cuz it's Darcie." I guess you had to be there. Moving on, Chelsea is short and a little over-obsessed with her pet donkey. Note: This Chelsea is not to be confused with my slutty ex-girlfriend Chelsea who just happens to be short as well. She's cool though. Oh ya, if you didn't catch that part, from  urlLink his blog  Monochrome is like in love with her (lol). Nevertheless, she's a nice person. Allison is...well...Republican to the max. She is obsessed with George Bush in a scary way. She has some strange theories about what the world should be and why it should be like that. One of these theories is that some people just don't deserve rights. She flat-out said this on the second day of our discussion of  women's rights . Now, why would a woman say these things about women's rights? Seriously, how can someone like that who thinks that anyone who is a Democrat should be lynched say that people shouldn't get equal rights? I'm not sure and I probably will never know either. Oh, ya...I came to a startling conclusion today. Fat girls shouldn't be allowed to wear thongs and short skirts, especially if they are planning on standing near a stairwell. I was walking up to History class today and I determined this by experiencing it, which made Darcie, Chelsea, and Allison laugh hysterically when I said that to them. They're evil to the max. After school let out, I went down to get my birth certificate back from the Driver's Education instructor. I had to wait like twenty minutes and I missed my ride which I wasn't too happy about. I got a ride from my friend Mike, though and here I am, telling you about the amazing day I've had and such. In a couple of weeks, I may be going to MIT for a program called ESP Splash, which sounds really cool. The deal is, you go to MIT for two days to attend 16 hours of seminars on various things. It cheap, too...like $30 to do the whole thing. Though it doesn't give you any college credits, it  does  make you look really good to colleges that you apply to, which is ?ber cool (like the umlov'd U?).  I think that's about all for now, I'll try to update again soon.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Happy...ThanksgivingChristmasNewYearValentine'sDay...That went by fast.]  Yeah I just didn't feel like posting at all for the past...well couple months. Not much has happened in these months. Just before Thanksgiving I went to MIT for an annual set of seminars and stuff to make us more cultured...culture? Mmmm...yogurt... Meet the Candidates Night at school was productive back in December. That was the UberProject that Gleason assigned to us, never knowing how big it ended up being. We went to Applebee's afterwards and everyone acted drunk. Christmas was cool, I got a bunch of stuff for my car and it's all pimped out now. I got TireFlys. light-up dice, cathode tubes for the inside, and a bunch of other stuff too. Brothar got Xbox and a bunch of games from me, and that collection is growing weekly. New Year's was ok...had to work, so I was really tired and never watched that accursed ball drop. Whatever. After new Year's I had to do Fiscal Inventory, so everyone at the store was there for hours and hours :(. New Classes started a little after New Year's (Spanish, CAD/Free Block, French, Trig.), and with the New Year means new FIRST game. check it out at www.usfirst.org . My friend Brandon and I are working on an animation for it this year, and we had one almost done until his hard drive died. D.I.E.D., as in RIP. can't even access it as a slave. So we have to make a much more Spartan animation than we had planned. The rest of January was alright, and my boss Mr. Davis just left the store like last week to work at a store closer to his house. His replacement (Mr. Beaky lol) looks just like him. Scary, non? I've gotten a few compliments from the higher-ups at work saying I'm a good worker and stuff like that. I got my first promotion today...that means that instead of wearing a red "trainee's" apron, I have a blue "bagger's" apron. I really wanna move to Dairy, Produce, Meat, Grocery...somewhere but the front end, as it sucks. The robot is sexy this year. Check it out on the chiefDelphi forums... I dont' remember the exact URL but just search for Team 134 Robot at www.chiefdelphi.com and you'll see it on the top of the list. ignore the idiot's comments. Seth burned me a copy of the media form my old computer (before it crashed), and the 16 files that I wanted on the 4 cds he burned (about 2.4 GB) were the only 16 that didn't burn correctly. That's just my luck these days. I'm addicted to anime now, especially the "really sad for Americans to like" animes, like Azumanga Daioh and Chobits ;'( *tear*. I think my favorite, though, is Last Exile. Head on over to the MegaTokyo forums and there is a board where you can post your favorite animes and why. I guess that's all that there is to post about tonight. If I feel like I missed anything at all, you know I'll post it, whether you wanna hear it or not.  --Raine
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [The American Reality]  You've all heard it, the tale of someone starting a multibillion dollar software company in their garage, or someone who designs a special bike for people who only have use of their arms. These people end up making millions of dollars and becoming famous. It's called the American Dream, isn't it? The American Dream is that noble cause that everyone is supposed to follow, that "Work hard and anyone, even you make a name for yourself" philosophy that everyone has.  The truth is that the American Dream is just that, a dream. Like almost every dream, this one is unattainable. The American Dream is a false philosophy. No matter how hard you work, there's a great possibility that you will be left behind in the wake of the people who will step on you to move up.  In this country, the hardest workers are usually the ones who are continually left behind. Take a look at the class of people called "Blue Collar." These are the good ol' boys, the coal miners, the farmers, and the people who put in a good day's work every day, and collect a modest paycheck at the end of the week. You look at the "White Collar" folks, and you'll see a great contrast. The rich people are getting richer, and they're doing less and less work. People in the top of the big companies that make everything "easier" for us are the ones that mainly just sit at home and watch TV, or just go out and play golf on their own private course on one of their islands in the Carribean. They are the lazy ones that make humanity so incredibly disgusting. Yes, it is easier to find the bad points in people than the good ones, but when you look at people as a hole, you won't see the good ones that hold up the rest of them. No, you'll only see the "creme de la creme," the ones who are standing on top of everyone else.  So, where's all this going? Where is this rant on the unfairness of American life headed? This isn't a post that I just ran off. I've been thinking about this for quite some time now, and the only way I can think of educating the masses is through my writing. All I'm trying to say is that it matters none whether you work yourself to the bone or just fuck off your whole life, you'll end up under six feet of dirt anyway.  Bottom Line:  The American Dream: Work hard and you can make your dreams come true. The American Reality: Work hard and get left behind and stepped upon your whole life.   
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [chin up, dipshit]  Last night, before I went to sleep, I got a peptalk from Ben. The last words that he said to me are the title for tonight's blog post. Today, wehn I woke up, I remembered him telling me this and for some reason it stayed in my mins all through school and afterwards too. Most of the time I wouldn't have given it a second thought if Ben called me a dipshit--it happens almost hourly--but for this one instance, I just couldn't forget about it. And for some reason, it was this one thought that got me through the day. I don't quite know why, but I guess it was Ben that made me feel a lot better. I guess it was a kick in the ass that I needed more than anything. When we were talking, it suddenly came across me that, yes, my problem was pretty tough for me, but there are people out there who have it much worse off that I ever have. I don't know any, but they're probably out there somewhere. I guess "I still want to be good friends" means Laura doesn't want to talk to me anymore. It's her loss. Tomorrow night we're having a LAN party at Seth's house. Everyone is invited, as we're pretty resourceful when we need to get stuff. Seth is going to boost a few tables from work if he needs to, and last time they made a table out of computer cases. Ben uses laptops as mousepads, and we use Seth's little brother to vent any gamerage we build up. He's one angry little freshman, so it won't do any harm to make him a little more mad, will it? Today was the start of the Track and Field team's season, so I went to the meeting. I don't know if I can work and do track at the same time... Ordered my class ring today too. $159.64 at Wally World--you can tell by the .64 at the end (not .99 or .95, but .64)--compared to $350.00 for the same one... Nothing else of note happened today, so I guess I'm off to that magical land called sleep.    The Lost Soul    urlLink   What sign of the Black Zodiac are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    --Jake
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Why I Think God Hates Me]  While I was at work today I realized that there are quite a few times in my life where God has demonstrated how much he doesn't like me. Here are a few examples: --Age 0: I was born 6 weeks early with severe jaundice, I nearly died. --Age 3: I accidently ingested half of a cup of antifreeze. I almost died. --Age 7: I stepped on a stud bracket, severing a major artery in my foot and nearly bled to death. --Age 9: I was hit by a truck, completely demolishing my new bike. I stayed in the hospital's ICU for a week, then had nearly a year of rehabilitory therapy. With a major concussion, punctured lung, and broken pelvis, I wasn't in very good shape. I've never been as good at running since, and I have arthritis in my knee as well. --Age 10: My dad died of a heart attack just after leading my soccer team to a 2nd place in the town's tournament. --Age 13: Sami, my first girlfriend ditches me for another guy (23 days). My mom marries John Miner, one of the worst decisions she has made to date. --Age 14: Deanna, my second girlfriend refuses to talk to me (16 days). I still haven't found out why. Kathy, my third girlfriend dumps me the day before my 15th birthday (26 days). --Age 15: Chelsea, my fourth girlfriend, and a girl I had a crush on for almost a year, tells me that she's been cheating on me and dumps me at a school dance (6 days--and yes, she  did  cheat on me in 6 days). I meet Laura, and she starts going out with a close friend of mine, Matt. By the end of the summer, my girlfriend Sarah decides she doesn't want to risk drifting away from me during the school year and dumps me. --Age 16: I reconnect with Laura and we start dating. Three days later, she tells me that she "just isn't ready for another boyfriend," though she was the one that wanted me to ask her out. If the rest of my life is as bad as the first 16 years, I think I may want out. I have deduced that God hates me because, as you may be able to pick out from the events listed above, nearly every time I am really happy, or I start to get happy, something happens to put a quick end to that. What do you think? Comment if you wish--that's why I put that comment collector up.
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [A Big Ball of Suck]  That's about what my life is at this point. I got dumped (again) this afternoon, and I'm not feeling too good. I've been thinking a lot though. About girls, about my life, and about me. I've come to realize that pretty much everything I've ever sone just ends up hurting me in the end. Letting my feelings open up to anyone has nearly killed me more than once, but I still let it happen, over and over again. They say it's a sign of stupidity, doing the same thing over and over, expecting different results with each new try. I may have to agree with them, because I have to be really stupid to let myself get hurt over and over doing the same things over and over. At most, three people read this blog, including myself, and Ben, who just reads it to make fun of me, so I'm pretty sure I know just about everyone who has read it before. You all know that I'm not perfect, but I'd consider myself a nice person, though I must not be good enough for anyone out there. Sure, they all say things, like "I really like you, but now's not the time for me, " or the ever-popular "I think we should just be friends from now on." What these really mean is that the girl has gotten sick of me and they want to get rid of me as quickly and as easily as possible for them to. I know from experience--five girls in less than two years. But this time is different. Yes, I've been through being dumped plenty of times, but this time hurts me more than any of the others. I don't know if it's the fact that I made a new record of a three day relationship that makes it hurt so much, or the fact that she creid for an hour when she realized she didn't like me anymore. I have a major guilt complex and I feel responsible for a lot of things. Tonight, though, I realized that even though I've done some really stupid stuff over the years, I actually made a girl cry today. A girl I care for, no less. It makes me feel just a little more like a reject just knowing this, and I don't know if I can handle knowing that I made a girl cry just by being me. I've been told that this isn't my fault, that I'm a good person, every piece of crap that anyone can pull out of their ass to try and make me feel better. I can't help but think, though, that it's a little weird for so many girls that I know and like to be at fault for broken relationships. I mean: five girls dumped me after going out for less than a month! Am I that annoying? Probably. I tell everyone that I know what I think, when I think it--and no matter how stupid I feel afterwards, I've never taken anything I say back. You'll notice that I leave each and every post up on this blog, untouched, other than to correct grammatical or typographical errors. Sometimes, I think some really stupid stuff, and this evening was no exception. A lot of things went through my mind tonight, thoughts about hurting myself, thoughts of just giving up altogether on life, and thoughts of flat-out going crazy. But then I realized that I was being selfish. This was as hard on Laura as it was on me--if not worse--and it would only make it worse for her if I did something stupid because of it. I still like her and there's nothing that could ever change that, and I will never do anything that would hurt her. I've seen it before, but never really understood the feeling that people get when they are in love. I wonder if this is it? I still care very much for her and I am willing to wait until the end of the world for her if that's how long it will take.
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [breakups suck]  fuck the world
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [I am not an atomic playboy.]  Bleh. It's all crappy outside, I've got a cold, and Laura says she's sick. I hate winter. A lot. No. More than that. A ton. Today has sucked so far, and to top it all off, I have to go to work in an hour. Ugh. It's tuesday, so *hopefully* it won't be too busy at the Basket tonight. I stopped by last night after I dropped Laura off at her house and it wasn't too bad in there, and usually tuesday is a calm night becuase everyone is out of money (like me). Yarg. I don't have a whole lat I can do in an hour, so I'm just sitting here listening to Bassic's Daydreamer CD. He released it a little more than a year ago for free download off his website, so I got it. Then, he started charging for it and coincidentaly I had to reformat my hard drive soon after. So I backed up all my media to Seth's computer and He just burned me the CD again. *yay* Bassic is awesome. I love his EI song. A lot. Eh. Nothing else to write about at the moment. --Jake
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ["Well, that was interesting"]  Just got back from the movies a little bit ago. Went to see Starsky and Hutch with Laura, and that's the first thing the said after the movie was over. I get the feeling she didn't like the movie too much. Personally, I didn't think it was all that great either, but it was worth it because of the company.
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Duct Tape Use #125: Toilet Seat Cover]  I can't seem to understand it, but there was been one thing that all of my thoghts have revolved around for the past couple of days. Whether I'm cleaning my car, as I did this morning, or I'm at work cleaning up the mess of Ranch Dressing someone decided to leave in the middle of an aisle, there has been one thing on my mind: Whitesnake. lol, no, not Whitesnake. It's been Laura, my girlfriend. Yes, believe it or not, I am going out with someone, like I said in my last post. And unlike some other people I know, we aren't the kind of couple that bases our relationship on lust (at least not yet :P). There's no way that  can explain why I like her as much as I do. She's smart, she's funny, and she's really pretty too. How she ended up liking  me,  of all people, I'll never know. I sit here in my computer chair, in front of my computer screen, trying to hear the music from my headphones over the blenderlike noises coming from my computer, and no matter what is going on, I just can't seem to stop thinking about her. My one fear at this point is that we'll grow apart like she and Matt did. Yes, Matt, her last boyfriend (I think), and one of my close friends. I don't konw why I've done it, but I broke one of my personal rules by dating my friend's ex. No, it's not like she's his property or anything, but I just usually don't make it a habit to do this. I haven't talked to him since the morning before Laura and I started going out, but I can't help but wonder how he feels about all this. *le sigh* I just hope he isn't too mad...
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [New Blogger Posting Method]  "I should be updating more often." Sorry about that. Today was the last day of our FIRST competition. It was held at the Verizon Wireless Arena in Manchester, New Hampshire. We locals just call it the Verizon. Well last year we placed "42nd out of 42 teams" as Mr Kelly said to the newscaster interviewing him. Today we were in the third place alliance. Woot. Even more interesting than the competition is the award that we won. Ryan Cummings, our programmer, made one of the best efforts I've ever seen or make this robot work. This year he programmed eight different types of codes and constructed a program box to load each of them before each match. For his efforts, we got the Leadership in Programming Award, a very high honor. Just as his luck happens to fall, he left early last night to go to his friend's house. Better than that, I got Woodie Flowers to take one of my bandanas. It took some trying, but it eventually worked out well. I told him to take it and he said "Well, I don't think I can take that, but how about you sign my shirt?" Eventually, I got him to take the bandana. No big deal, right? Well you don't know Woodie Flowers, then. He usually refuses to take things from students because he feels too modest, like we're better than him. Whatever. Even better than that, Over the past three days, I got much closer to my friend Laura. So close, in fact, that we started going out. :) Guess that's all for now. Later. --Jake
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Why?]  Tell me why the worst things always happen to the best of people. I have a friend who is one of the most amazing people I know was let down, and now she just wants to give everything up. I don't know what to do to help her because I don't know how. It hurts just talking to her though, because I don't want to see her sad. As many times as I've been dumped, I know how much someone can hurt another person, but I still can't help but hurt for her, and now pains me more than any time when I've been dumped myself. I value my friends and family more than anything I have or will ever own, and when one of them is hurt, I don't care about anything that is going on in my own life, just theirs. As much as I want to, I just can't help her though. Nothing is restricting me except my inability to console her. I don't know what else to write but that if she reads this I want her to know that no matter what happens, I'll always be here for her. Always.
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [What's Wrong With Me?]  Don't answer that. Well, it's been 2 whole days since I last posted, so I decided to post some since I don't have a whole lot else to do tonight. A guy at work told me tonight that I need to get a girlfriend. I wish it were that easy for me. Fuck, I can't even talk to most girls out there, let alone ask one out. Fuck, man. Talking to people makes me feel even worse sometimes. I've been talking to some of the girls I know about stuff that's been going on in our lives. I talked to one of my friends one night until early in the morning because she's been having a hard time with her ex, and I was up all night with her one time just talking. There's a lot of stuff that we talk about and I really wish I could help her more than I can. On another note, I've been talking to one of my close friends a lot and I can't think about anything but her sometimes. Why? On top of all the other shit in my life, I'm probably going to screw up one of the best relationships I've ever had by going crazy over a girl. Go me. On a lighter note, Pat is going to St. Paul's this summer to study Artificial Intelligence. I asked if that is just because he went there last year, or if it's another program altogether. If I can, I want to go next year. I was so bummed out because the didn't invite me for this year, and every time I talk to Steph or Pat they make me feel even worse because they both went last year. Hope I can go, though. That would kick some major portions of ass.
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [A day of many feats]  Today was second block final, but I didn't have one so I just hung out at home until the review for third block. After that I came home and cleaned out my car because it needed to be done. Went to the movies with Steph and afterwards we went to the mall and I got some snazzy new swag. Got two shirts and a pair of shorts at Old Navy and then went to Electronics Boutique where I got Harvest Moon for GBA and then to Hot Topic where I got a John Deere shirt and a new watch. I was just about out of money at that point so we just headed over to Steph's so she could show me all her neat stuff. At about 8 we went to Pat's to go swimming and then we got cold so we went inside and I got ignored for a couple hours. Big suprise there. I'm cool with it, though, happens all the time. Just about everywhere I go with more than one other person, I get left out. I guess I can't do much about it. I think it's in other people's nature to just ignore me unless they want something. So I'm sitting here trying to think of something to do, and I realized that I haven't updated my blog in a while, and since today was sooooo amusing I figured I'd dump some of my shit thoughts in here. I wrote a song too. Yay. It's called The Sun Goes Down. Enjoy the First Draft.  I'm so sick of pretending That I'm not what I am Tired of feeling Nothing like I truely am The world thinks im not who I really am Free, light, not distant from all we are  And it all falls apart After he sun goes down I lose myself When the sun goes down I can't keep control And in the end, the sun goes down  When im out there I look like anyone else Happy, normal, independent But when I'm not in the open The real me comes out  And it all falls apart After he sun goes down I lose myself When the sun goes down I can't keep control And in the end, the sun goes down  The sun goes down On me, on you, on everything we know I get lost in the darkness No one to help me get out Of this prison I am locked up in  And it all falls apart After he sun goes down I lose myself When the sun goes down I can't keep control And in the end, the sun goes down  And it all falls apart After he sun goes down I lose myself When the sun goes down I can't keep control And in the end, the sun goes down  (The Sun goes down...)
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [What is this?]  I don't know what it is, but I'm more open with one person I've known for less than three months than I am with people I have known for my whole life. Why?
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Hello.com]  Just got this neat little application from  urlLink here  that lets me post pictures onto my blog, so all of you get to see my ugly mug. Cool, eh?
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me trying to smile, though I am exhausted.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me, exhausted&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Heehee]  Just started taking some quizzes randomly in Quizilla again.  Which swear am I?   your fuck.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    I like that one.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [When it all goes to hell]  Ever see a kid grow up? Do you know how much difference one year can make for a 12 year old? I do. Working at a summer camp you realize how fast kids really grow up and how much they can change in a short amount of time. Last year was the first year I really worked for a camp. I tell ya, there were quite a few problems, but for the most part it was great. I got to know 140 of the greatest people on the planet. Some of them I wanted to strangle daily, but I would still give my life in an instant for any of them. This year, a lot of the kids came back from last year and I was both suprised and saddened by the changes that they went through in the year they had been gone. First of all, there is one girl, named Katie. She was the most energetic little girl I had ever seen last year and at the beginning of the summer I was thinking to myself "We have quite a handful this year." She turned out to be one of the best campers I would ever know. So this year when she was in my group again I was excited thinking that it would be another great summer with her. I was wrong. In one year, she had turned into a sweet little girl into a girl on the verge of  begging  for sex. She acts like a porn star and has gotten into more than one fight over boys. Know what the worst part is? She's 9 years old. NINE. How the fuck does that kind of transformation happen to a nine year old? Second, there is another kid in my group, named Bryce. He was, like Katie, relatively well behaved and very energetic. Now, though he's mopey all the time and disrespectful toward everyone, as well as very whiney. Someone told me that his brother molested him. Another girl at the camp, Jess, was the best kid I could know last year. She's the worst one in camp though. Today her group went up north to a science center and went for a hike on some trails. She crouched down for a rest. Now this wouldn't be so bad, but she likes to wear short shorts. On top of this, she didn't wear any panties, so just about everyone saw just about everything. Added to that, she's going to a hotel room with her "friend" tonight. Who brings a 13 year old to a hotel on a Tuesday night for one night?  I just don't know anymore. I know that phrase is the most commonly used one in this blog, but God dammit I'm pissed off. Boss Lady Elaine says that I can't do anything to try to intervene or I will lose my job. I can't take this. I mean, how does this happen? These are just the three stories I heard today alone. Three kids, all of which were good kids no more than a year ago, and now they're all jumping into a handbasket. What is someone supposed to do?
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Mexico]  Steve called me about 2 weeks ago and said that I'm going to Mexico with him in February. I&nbsp;think that's pretty cool.&nbsp;I mean how often does someone get to go to Mexico? Well. It's an all-expenses paid resprt so I'm just gonna hang by the ocean and drink expensive drinks and stuff. Yesterday was Alex's birthday. She's 15 now. In her words: "Wahoo." Wish I could talk to get more, but she isn't online much&nbsp;anymore. Work kinda sucks now. I quit Market Basket, but summer camp is pretty bad though. The Renaissance Project gave up control of the camp since their grant ran out, so the Boys and Girls Club too over and has pissed more than just me off since then. I mean, even kids are mad about what's happening. I don't think it's good when the camp overseer spends more time yelling at kids than making sure she's presentable. She comes in a half hour late and sits down to put stamps on her wedding invitations...only to scream at one of the nicest girls I know because she didn't wear a camp shirt that day. What a fucking bitch. Now when I related that little episode it seemed like it was only a one-time thing. Not at all. Elaine doesn't come in unless she really feels like it. When she does, she's always late. One day she left to go to the Boys and Girls Club in Concord (20 minutes from the main camp base) and was gone all day. Turns out she wasn't at the Boys and Girls Club for more than a half hour before she left.&nbsp;We never did find out where she was or why it took her all day to go there. Then there's Steve. That guy creeps me out. He comes in the first day and tells the kids to call him Smiley. Now I wouldn't mind it if that were a name they made up for him, but it's just a little weird for a 26 year old guy to tell 8 year olds to call him Smiley. Then he starts holding hands with the kids. Not even only the girls, either. Later, he brings in flourescent pink fishnet arm covers and tells some of the boys to wear them. And all through this he is bringing in Spongebob Squarepants lanyards that are grimey and gross, and telling kids to wear them around their necks. I think he gets off from little kids looking like gay men. Speaking of Steve and gay men, he asked like 4 people to go to the "3on3 Gay Lounge" in Manchester. That just creeped me out. I was sort of offended that he would ask me about that, too. I don't know. Something needs to be done about him, and soon. &nbsp; --Jake 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [The Bender]  Well I just uploaded like 15 pictures that I had sitting on my harddrive because I was trying to make a picture for my Blogger profile show up. So why the 15 random pictures? I have a short attention span. Enjoy them, though as more are certain to come. Most likely theme for the next batch: DDR stuff.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I love playing with my Bawls. They are blue and nubbed, and they will keep you up all night long, if used correctly.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My superior driving skills hung our robot (134) on some other one...809 or some weird number like that...psht.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me in my Super Pimp hat.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ryan learning that I sweated in his boots all day.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ryan showing everyone his boots that I sweated in all day.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    It's true, you know. You don't have to sleep.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ahh...sweet sustinence.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me at 4am. I am SO more awake than you.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A nice shot from the Basin.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another nice shot I took at the Basin.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [The Sex Game]  Nothing big today, just wanted to post that Friday night I went to a LAN party at Brandon's. Not too great a LAN. Seth's are better. Got a Gmail Account last week. jake.gallagher@gmail.com if you feel like emailing me there. Yesterday we went up to the lake and played DDR at the arcade and then went to another, bigger arcade and played there. After that we went to the beach and played around in some kayaks. Quite an eventful weekend. Right now, I'm playing "The Sex Game" with Genia. She seems to like it. It's one of those This or That kind of games...You can probably get the rest. Tomorrow is when parking stickers get on sale at school. Seth is coming over early and we're heading up there to purchase them. Yay. Later, all.
    
</post>


</Blog>