<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many Londoners often ask themselves: Why is the  urlLink District Line  called the District Line? London is not divided into districts, but into parishes and Boroughs. Other than the line, nothing in London is called a District.  This line of thinking is based on a misconception. The line's name stems not from district meaning "area", but from an Italian banking family called the di'Stricti. The di'Stricti came to London in 1841 and in the 1860s provided much of the funding for the early Distict line, which was promptly name in honour of them - once that name had been anglicised.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Green Park was once home to the world’s only rodent cemetry, where gerbils owned by the younger members of the Royal Family are interred. Among the more famous names buried there is Mr Carrots, one of George III’s earliest pets, who once amazed courtiers by changing his own bedding.  The cemetry was closed to the public in 1968, when it was overrun by rats. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      15th-century London was filled with unusual diversions ranging from stoat kickboxing to locking 12 of the most stupid people who could be found in a house together for 12 weeks and then watching them through the windows. But one of the strangest pastimes was "the running of the hills".  This odd sport was introduced to the city by European merchants. It involved gathering a crowd of people at the bottom of one of London's many hills - Primrose Hill was said to be popular - and then running up it in as tight a formation as possible. The first contestants to reach the top then had to immediately come to a dead halt, hoping that those behind them would run into their backs and fall over. The person who knocked over as many people as possible won a yard of ale. Injuries scored extra points.  Sadly, this charming part of our heritage lost popularity and faded into its history, but is still practised on the continent. To this day, European visitors to the capital will attempt re-enactments by stopping dead still at the top of Tube escalators and pretending to read maps.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This Isn't Londoner  urlLink Alex Wiltshire  has contributed this fascinating fact. It has been mildly edited.   Tufnell Park was controversially renamed after the Spinal Tap character Nigel Tufnell by the then Labour MP for the area, Bob Tree, in 1987. It was his reaction against its original name - Tebbit's Village. you can still see the remnants of scratched graffiti of phalluses on bikes on the walls of the tube station, references to Norman Tebbit's infamous quote on unemployment. Ironically, though  urlLink Norman Tebbit  had no relation to the original name, the Tebbit of Tebbit's Village, who was the major landowner and developer of the area in the mid-1800s, invented the inner tube for the penny farthing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When it was first opened in December 1906, the Piccadilly Line only had one stop - at Finsbury Park. It was an immediate financial failure, and almost went out of business altogether. However, investors poured in more cash and an extension to Barons Court was completed by 1909.   Still, it was used by almost no one, so in 1912 the decision was taken to update the timetable to include stations other than Finsbury Park.  Even then, it lost money heavily until it was decided to build stations along the stretch between Finsbury Park and Baron's Court, bring the total number of stops from two to fifteen. While some investors claimed this would decrease train speed, but common sense prevailed and the work was completed by 1915.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      75 Beak Street, Soho, is now a slightly mad Bistro, but until 1861 it was the home of Doctor Bleasdale's Temperance Vomitorium, the last of the great Emetic Cults. It is believed that these mysterious establishments sprang from the coffee-house culture of the 18th century, specifically after an ill-fated experiment with pig's milk at an establishment in Cheapside had unexpectedly explosive and colourful side-effects.   By Victoria's reign, Emetic Cults had risen in tandem with the Temperance movement, in that they encouraged abstinence by permitting patrons to drink until the inevitable occurred.  urlLink Dickens  mentions them in Dombey and Son:   The next morning, refreshed after a visit to Bleasdale's purging-house the previous evening, Dombey again returned his attention to the matter of Paul and Florence ...  Sadly, by 1855 these unusual establishments had fallen from favour and by 1860 only Bleasdale's remained. On the centenary of its closure in 1963, Westminster council attempted to re-establish it, only to fail when three aldermen were hospitalised.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a common misconception that the name  urlLink Elephant & Castle  is a corruption of "Infanta de Castilla". This isn't true: it actually stems from the words "Bellephron and castor oil". In Greek mythology, the hero Bellephron trained the winged horse Pegasus by walking it around the roundabout now taken up by the lumpen Faraday memorial.  Where the castor oil bit comes from is uncertain. Possibly one of them had an upset stomach at the time.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While the conversion of the Bankside power station into the  urlLink Tate Modern  was being planned, another, far more secret, set of negotiations was taking place on the other side of the Thames.  This was because in 1998 it was proposed by a Belgian consortium that the  urlLink Tate Britain  (then the  urlLink Tate Gallery ) be converted into a gas-fired power station. Although Westminster council liked the idea, it ultimately foundered on a dispute over employee parking.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An integral part of the 1980s plan to regenerate the Docklands east of London was the construction of an  urlLink elevated light railway network  covering the area. In 1986 government ministers issued tenders to establish who should be given the job of building this railway, and imagine their surprise when the winning bid came from  urlLink Hornby !  Construction went ahead, and to this day the  urlLink Docklands Light Railway  remains the largest model railway system in the world, controlled from a  urlLink state-of-the-art network centre  at Poplar.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Netto Ockwell was born in a disease-ridden swamp south of the Thames in 863 ( urlLink map ). He rose to prominence in 885 after his shirt fell apart during a drinking competition and he preached a fiery sermon on the spot about the importance of low-cost clothes.  Despite having no religious training from the church, or indeed any training at all, he rapidly acquired a following thanks to his vehement and often expletive-laden sermons in the area - mostly on no particular subject other than the audience being "fuckers", which was believed to be an imprecation against the sin of fornication - and his habit of falling into a deep meditative trance at about 8pm every evening until noon the next day. Thanks to his diminutive stature, he acquired the nickname "Little Ockwell" ("Lidl Ockwell" in old English).  Reports of his demise vary. Some of his more ardent supporters claim he was burned at the stake by the church for heresy. Others claim he set himself on fire demonstrating one of the cheap lighters he was attempting to sell. All accounts agree, however, that he miraculously exploded and was consumed by flames within seconds - possibly a byproduct of the enormous quantity of lamp oil he drank.  Although he was never officially beatified by the Vatican, the area became known as "Saint Ockwell's". This became "St. Ockwell" in 1705, and by 1840 was commonly abbreviated to "Stockwell", the name it bears today.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The pedestrian subway systems under Marble Arch, the north side of Blackfriars Bridge and the southern end of Tottenham Court road were designed and built by the Ministry of Works in the Spring of 1940. Their intention was to confuse and demoralise as much of an invading enemy army as they could - it was estimated that as many as five Wehrmacht divisions could be tied down and destroyed by attrition in each system by a force as small as eight Evening Standard vendors.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This site was created on 3 June 2004 as the web's first, best and only* source of completely untrue - indeed, made-up and unfactual - facts and information about London, The World's Greatest City*.  urlLink Its creator  originally planned an Encyclopedia Errata of untrue facts about things in general, to counter the rising tide of accuracy and diligence on the internet*, only to realise upon being permitted access to the British Library's fabled Mythomaniacal Archive* that the vast bulk of interesting material therein was about London*, his home city.  This database will be updated hourly* and by September 2004 will contain more than 600,000 entries*.   *Might not be true. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wren wasn't the only one to have grand designs for this fair city. In 1951 architect and intellectual Thaddeus Roshanak unveiled his new for a rebuilt London to a breathless crowd in Methodist Central Hall. Roshanak was an arch-modernist and his plan displayed the clear influence of Le Corbusier's  urlLink Plan Voisin  for Paris, but was far, far more radical.  Under Plan Thaddeus, Central London from Ludgate to Bayswater and from Charing Cross to Regent's Park would be demolished. In its place would rise a new, modern city of gleaming white towers and broad, straight avenues. The railway stations would be combined into a new 72-platform central station, linked by tram to  urlLink Paddington Airport , where Oxford Circus now is.  So far, so predictably Corbusier-style. But Roshanak's genius went further. None of his new streets would have corners, which he despised, and would thus only run east-west. Pedestrian traffic would be carried by looping travelators arranged in a stylised form of the  urlLink coat of arms of the Royal Institute of British Architects . In a nod to the city's destroyed heritage, the 40-storey residential and business tower blocks of the centre would be thatched. The central station would only accomodate inbound trains in order to promote tourism. And the new city would be entirely nuclear-powered, with each flat and office having its own reactor.  Understandably, the radical plan met with a mixed response. The National Trust called it "barbaric". The Royal Fine Arts Commission wanted to know if it was "some kind of sick joke". Malcolm Muggeridge praised its "excellent benches". And the  Evening Standard  was so horrified it refused to come out for four days.  In the end, Roshanak lost his fight for the plan and it was consigned to the dustbin of history. Intensely disillusioned, Roshanak quit architecture and became a freelance mermaid.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a common misconception that time constraints and greedy developers confounded  urlLink Christopher Wren 's plan for the rebuilding of London after the 1666 Great Fire ( urlLink here ). This is not true.  The real story is rather more mysterious. After hearing that the city fathers were minded to approve his grandiose plans, Wren went on a terrific all-night drinking session with Robert Hooke. After drinking some twelve pints of Old Vituvius Ale - which he and Hawksmoor arranged into the secret twelve-cornered hexagon of the Masonic God Jabulon (or something) - he passed out and rolled under the table.  When the next day came, he awoke to discover not only that he was late for the meeting that would formally endorse his plan, but also that Hooke had spilt beer all over it. The ink was running quite badly, but there was no time to do it again, so Wren attempted to fill in the gaps and repair it while on the way to Westminster.  A combination of the rubble-strewn streets and an attack of the morning-after shakes meant his new version of the plan possessed few of the clean, crisp lines of the original. Nevertheless, his plan was approved and  urlLink remains the basic layout  of the city of London today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This isn't Londoner  urlLink Pom du Cap  writes:   Cleopatra's needle is a well known landmark on the north bank of the Thames near the Embankment tube station. What is less well known is how it got its name. Some speculate that it is because of its pointed shape, but the truth is more interesting. The obelisk was presented as a gift to London in the 19th century by the rulers of Egypt, who were less than impressed with Britain's foreign policies of the time. They decided to get their own back in two ways. The first was to make a great show of presenting the monument to the British High Commissioner in Egypt, but then to make it Britain's problem to get the thing back to these shores. The transport by boat, and the subsequent erection took months, cost the British authorities a small fortune, and produced no end of problems. The second thing the Egyptians did was to cover the needle in hieroglyphics, which of course the Londoners could not read. Years later it transpired that the etchings translated as rude jibes at Queen Victoria, and the British in general.  When this story got out, the Londoners started to refer to the monument as "Cleopatra's Needle". The Egyptian queen had of course been dead for a while by this stage, but the combination of her name and the word "needle", taken colloquially to mean wind up or irritate just seemed to fit, and the name stuck. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's still 1998 in the London Borough of Newham. The reason for this rather odd fact stems from the  urlLink calendar reforms of 1752 ; as part of a political compromise to adopt the Gregorian calendar, the burghers of Newham were given the right to ratify every new year's calendar before it came into force.  This ratification proceeded like clockwork for more than 200 years, with the new calendars passing into local law on the nod. However, the debate over the endorsement of 1999's calendar proved to be unexpectedly contentious as the affair became entangled with a dispute over the funding of the Millennium celebrations. The ensuing deadlock has yet to be broken, although a meeting scheduled for December the 2027th 1998 may provide a breakthrough.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Elgin Marbles may be the most notable example, but as the Director of the British Museum says in  urlLink this article : "The range of the British Museum's collections is truly worldwide." So, what other  booty   plunder   spoils of conquest  disputed cultural treasures can be found in the museum's hallowed halls?  *  The contents of the original Parthenon gift shop, including a wide selection of postcards  *  A Hittite frieze depicting what is believed to be the first ever game of  urlLink Twister   *  Ayer's Roll, stolen from Australia in 1802  *  Fourteen tonnes of pieces of the True Cross  *  The mummified feet of  urlLink St Ockwell   *  Bangalore's tram network  *  Former Swiss Finance Minister Otto Stich
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Planning permission for the  urlLink London Eye  runs out next year. Remarkably, it's been suggested that this great tourist attraction and adornment to the London skyline might have to be taken down forever, or maybe re-erected elsewhere. So what are the other options?  *  Wheel to be accelerated slowly until it dismantles itself  *  Easyjet to take over sponsorship from BA; ticket prices will drop to £1 but the view will be of Luton  *  Dismantled and re-erected horizontally on top of the Telecom tower to act as a giant merry-go-round  *  Dismantled; pods converted into pedaloes and set afloat in Thames  *  Dismantled and put into storage for 994 years so that it can be re-erected on the same spot and fail to turn on December 31st 2999  *  The wheel will be unhooked from its spindle and, thus freed, will roll around the country solving mysteries and avenging wrongs  *  How about this: Despite its popularity, dismantled in an act of bureaucratic vandalism, put into storage, much of it melted down and turned into ashtrays, then re-erected on the same spot 55 years later after a popular campaign? Yeah, right,  urlLink that'll never happen .
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Inspired by the success of the  urlLink Barnes Wetland Centre , where disused reservoirs were converted into a haven for bird life, London authorities are planning a follow-up. The London Desertorium, planned for a nine-acre former civil service car park in Balham, will recreate a desert ecology a mere stone’s throw from the city centre.  When completed, a process requiring 19,000 tonnes of sand and rock, the Desertorium will simulate the 40 degree celsius noon temperatures of the world's most extreme deserts with the aid of a series of powerful arc lamps. It will  be stocked with all the exotic flora and fauna one would expect to find in a desert, including camels, venomous snakes and black widow spiders, scorpions, stinkbugs, praying mantises, vultures and rampaging Berber tribesmen.   Bring the family! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All of London's dogs are owned by the same company. Amalgamated Canine Industries was founded when the dog population of the city was nationalised under the Attlee government in 1948, and its holdings were leased back to the pooches' former owners. Since then, this company has, in various forms, regulated all dog activity in the capital.  However, it was not always successful. Inefficiencies and strikes in the late 1970s plagued ACI, and ultimately led to some dogs going as much as three days without walkies. Hampstead Heath was littered with unreturned sticks, and the Minister for Employment struck out at some of those involved, claiming "I have found many to be not very good boys at all".  In 1987, Thatcher privatised ACI in order to improve its competitiveness, and in 2001 the company rebranded as ProCanis.  On a related topic, it's interesting to note that, although they operate on a freelance basis, the squirrels of St James's Park are unionised. This makes them the third most organised group of animals in London after dogs and wombles. Wombles do not have their own union, but most are members of Unison, the public service union.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Government's solution to London's chronic housing shortage is to expand the city to the east. However, a lot of people don't really like the idea of living in east London. To tackle this image problem, the Deputy Prime Minister has proposed the "rebranding" of certain districts to make them sound more attractive. &nbsp; For the first time, TiL can exclusively reveal what the new names will be. &nbsp; Dagenham --> "MoTown" Barking --> "Thames Riviera" Poplar --> "Popular" West Ham --> "Parma Ham" Deptford --> "Prudenceford" Mudchute --> "Chelsea East" Blackwall --> "Domeview" Stratford --> "Stratford upon Avon" Canning Town --> "Candem Town" Beckton --> "Beckham" Woolwich Dockyard --> "Marlowe Marina" Rainham --> "Sunnytown" &nbsp; And so on. A vast improvement, I think we can all agree. &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mayor Ken is to  urlLink take over London's railways . What will this mean?   * Old Routemasters to be used as spare carriages on congested lines   * Now the Mayor's office has King's Cross, Marylebone, Fenchurch Street  and  Euston stations, it can charge everyone who uses them £200   * Prince's Risborough, Luton and the other outlying commuter areas are to be reclassified as "Lesser London"   * Trains now liable for congestion charge   * "Normal" service to be renamed "wonderful" service   * "Integration" of train, Tube and bus services mean that delays will be harmonised across the system as soon as scientists have developed a way to cause buses to suffer signal failures. Similarly, commuters will be pleased to hear that strikes will now be synchronised across all three services   * Birmingham next on Ken's list   * By 2008, railways will demonstrate the same level of improvement that the Tube has since 2000. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From 1928 to 1968, there was an international airport near Paddington station. As the closest airport to the West End, it was extremely popular, handling more than 30,000 customers a day.  This is depite the fact that, because Paddington International was in the middle of an extremely built-up area, planes had to taxi into the terminal from Northolt, travelling down the Westway.  The airport had to close in 1968 because the wider wingspans of modern planes could no longer handle the turning into Harrow Road.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As a lifelong inhabitant of the royal borough of Haringey, I am often asked why the name of the borough is spelt as above while the neighbourhood that stretches from Manor House to Wood Green is called Harringay.  The answer is somewhat unexpected: the extra r and a are a tribute to the Egyptian sun god Ra, who has been worshipped in the Green Lanes area for at least 6000 years. His temple is now the car park at the McDonald’s DriveThru but Ra’s followers still meet on the first Monday of every month at Johnny English Potatoes and Melons under the railway bridge. To join the congregation, just go to the counter and ask for Tut.   Contributed by CS.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. The gig will use enough cabling to stretch all the way to Paul Simon's home town of Pydehark, New Jersey.   2. A brace of specially trained stunt condors has been shipped in from Argentina and will be released for the closing chorus of "El Condor Pasa".   3. Art Garfunkel's rider includes a handbag-sized can of Charles Worthington No More Frizz hairspray, a 500ml bottle of Body Shop Vitamin E Body Lotion and a copy of the 12th edition of Chambers Guide to the Legal Profession.  4. Diana, Princess of Wales, is known to have been a big fan of Watership Down and psychics believe there is a 95% chance that, if the duo play "Bright Eyes" at midnight tonight, her spirit will appear floating above the memorial water feature that was recently erected in her memory.  5. Other celebrity visitors tonight will include Euan Blair, Salman Rushdie and H from Steps.  6. Peter Gabriel will come on towards the end of the gig to do some backing vocals in that yelpy way he has of singing.  7. One of the few things that Art and Paul have in common nowadays is that they both suffer from hay fever, so the park's grass has had to be temporarily removed and replaced with astro-turf.  8. Rumours that Paul and Art can't stand to be around each other these days are totally untrue: in fact, they will share a trailer and will doubtless be keen to continue the game of chess they have been playing since 1972.  9. Paul Simon is, in fact, two inches taller than Art Garfunkel, but a clause in their contracts dating back to 1959 (when the duo were a skiffle act called Simofunkel) states that Art will not perform unless wearing stilts.  10. The auto-tuner used by Paul Simon's guitar technician was confiscated at US customs because apparently its case can easily be dissambled and turned into a lethal terrorist weapon powered by the chemicals used to scent the moist towelettes offered to passengers in first class on Virgin planes. Luckily, however, the canary used by the crew to detect poison gas leaks has been found to chirrup a perfect A and tonight, this will be used to tune Paul's guitar.   Contributed by  urlLink Fizzwhizz . 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This isn't London has been inundated by two emails from  urlLink Fizzwhizz  and CS. Here they are ...    Four killings and a film deal   Quentin Tarantino's most recent films were originally to be called Kilburn 1 and Kilburn 2,  writes Fizzwhizz . They were to be set in the eponymous north London suburb and featured an angry housewife's attempts to get revenge on the man who sold her a jar of gefilte fish so dodgy that it gave her husband a bad stomach upset and left him unable to attend his own daughter's wedding. The Lucy Liu character was originally to have been a comedy Indian grandmother played by Meera Syal; Bill was to have been a self-conscious upper-class fop played by Hugh Grant.   However it was decided to move the setting to America and increase the martial-arts content of the movie after studio executives became concerned that a gentle ensemble comedy would not afford sufficient opportunities for a video-game follow-up.    Taxloss responds: I heard a similar rumour. Apparently the posters were to be based on the traffic markings on West End Lane,  urlLink an influence that can still be seen .     “Of course, this is nothing like the food we had at the Medicis”   The first Italian restaurant in London opened almost 300 years before the creation of the Italian state, in 1582,  writes SC . Its proprietor was one Carlo Ghiradino, who had left his mother’s house at the tender age of 41 to bring the secrets of her kitchen to a wider audience.   He set up shop on Dogspit Lane, in the heart of the capital’s epicurean district. He could not forget home entirely, though, and honoured the tiny city-state from which he came – Tremestino (turn left at Piedmont and please drive carefully) – by covering his wooden tables with its distinctive red-and-white checked flag.   Before long, Carlo was the toast of Elizabethan London and his humble hostelry echoed to the sounds of fashionable diners exclaiming: “I remember this place when it was actually run by Italians” and “Of course, your actual Tuscan fisherman will eat something entirely different”. Soon, Ghiradino was able to enhance his décor with miniatures in oils depicting himself welcoming celebrities of the day such as Sir Walter Raleigh, Kit Marlowe and, on one memorable occasion, Queen Elizabeth herself. It was reported that she did not like the gnocchi.   Ghiradino was truly the city’s first celebrity chef, but his fame did not last. After being falsely accused of being a Venetian spy – a rumour first spread by a jealous member of the Worshipful Company of Gammon Fashioners – he was imprisoned in the tower. On 17 April 1587, he was doused in boiling olive oil and flash-fried with garlic before an audience of jeering Londoners. His last, agonised, words were: “No, you must  tear  the basil.”    Thanks, guys!  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Mayor's office is apparently planning to follow the Congestion Charge with a similar scheme to cut down on overcrowding at the city's more popular begging sites.  Prime pitches such as around the Hungerford Bridge, along the South Bank and near mainline stations including King's Cross and Victoria will be marked with a large B surrounded by a red circle. Use of them will cost £5 a day.  A well-placed source told TiL: "What do you mean it's an outrageous abuse of power? We're perfectly within our rights. This scheme will raise thousands, thousands I tell you. Thousands! Folk music concerts in Trafalgar Square don't pay for themselves, you know. Now get out of my office."
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heavy German bombing during the Blitz actually  increased  property prices in Walthamstow.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This site was featured on the  urlLink Guardian Unlimited Weblog  yesterday, and as a result traffic to this site has increased a bit. About 7000%. Anyway, as a result I've made some changes; you can now see  urlLink my profile , which has an email address for this site and is throbbingly dull, and (hopefully) leave comments even if you don't have a blogger account (or something).  I only mention this because I welcome feedback and also maybe submissions, although I haven't really thought that part through.  Normal service will now be resumed. Over and out.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      London’s smallest minority is Mr Uighr Denala, the city’s only representative of the Tamlyk people from a distant corner of the blasted tundra of Siberia. He is also the editor of  Hnk Tamlyku  (“Hey, Tamlyks”), the capital’s only Tamlyk-language newspaper, and lead DJ of its sister radio station ?Ulk Temo Prghu? (“Is there anyone out there?”).
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mayor Ken Livingstone’s  scheme to rid Trafalgar Square of pigeons  has been extremely successful. So where have all the pigeons gone?   34% 	KFP  29% 	Guest presenter slot on Newsnight Review  15% 	Always wanted to visit Venice  8% 	Suing pedicurist  7% 	Writing memoirs  3% 	That infuriating tea advert  2% 	Auditioning for remake of  The Birds , plotting revenge. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Worshipful Company of Stanners, a  urlLink livery company , was founded in 1321 to recognise a form of civic official unique to London. "Stanners" were - and still are - licensed to make arrests, practice as a doctor, conduct weddings, advise on astrological issues, divine for wells, issue financial advice, hunt deer within city limits and sell pamphlets and newspapers.  In order to provide these services to the general populace, they stand in little kiosks around the city - generally near Tube stations - and announce themselves by shouting: "Stanner! Stanner!"
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many Londoners and visitors to London often express their horror and disbelief that it can take London Underground  urlLink more than three years to repair an escalator  and that escalators are so often out of order at stations such as Notting Hill Gate, Brixton and Bank-Monument.  In fact, the reasons for these long interruptions are believed to be similar to the reason  urlLink unused Tube stations are mothballed  - so that the government can use them secretly.  For instance, the third escalator at Brixton has been out of commission for years simply to provide a discreet ministerial “fast lane” for government officials visiting the  urlLink Fridge nightclub . And the semi-permanent malfunctions of the escalators at Bank-Monument are actually part of a clandestine government initiative to keep the Square Mile’s office workers in peak physical condition in the event of a national emergency.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Moquette" is the robust, deep-pile material used to cover the seats on the London Underground and on London buses.   For many years these seats were simple wooden benches. When the decision was made to upgrade to padded seats, the Royal Geographical Society despatched explorers to points throughout the British Empire to find a material tough enough to withstand the rears of thousands of Londoners.  The breakthrough was made by Sir Magnus Larchwood in south-west Africa. In 1923 he discovered a species called the moquette (a relation of the  urlLink meerkat ) that had checked fur in a variety of striking colours, notably orange, purple, blue and brown. A trade in the moquette was set up and Tubes were furbished with their hides.   Sadly, such was the demand for moquette skins that the native population quickly dwindled. The ranks of this noble beast were further eroded after the second world war when they fell prey to Wrigley's Disease, a malady spread by discarded chewing gum. The last moquette died in captivity at the Royal College of Fashion in 1974 during a desperate attempt to equip the new Jubilee Line.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This isn't London  is not merely intended to be the ultimate reference guide; the author also has frankly misguided ambitions about creating a community of those dedicated to unearthing untrue, misleading and plainly wrong trivia about this great city.  With this in mind, I present the first "Open Post". I'll run one of these when an item of  Arcana Londiniumensis  exhausts even my considerable scholarly powers.  Let's set off with this: can anyone tell me the origin of "Gorblimey Trousers", as mentioned in the stirring Cockney Ballad  urlLink My Old Man's a Dustman ?  urlLink Old Moore  once mentioned that they were imbued with mystical powers. Any thoughts? Comment below.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      London's famous A To Z street guide was first serialised in Blackwoods magazine in the 1930s. Its evocative renderings of the London of the time were an instant hit, but many found the plot lacking and characterisation almost non-existent.  In the story, the heroic Kensal Rise travels from left to right in straight lines across London attempting to visit every street, an epic quest that takes him from Neasden to Grove Park. It was often compared to James Joyce's  urlLink  Ulysses  , mostly in the sense of "nothing at all like  Ulysses ".  It was adapted for radio in 1936 but did not travel well, and was taken off the air after Page 62 (Earl's Court, Fulham and Parson's Green).  In 1946 it was discovered that German strategist had been using the map that accompanied the full text as a street guide to London while planning the invasion of Britain. The publishers thought they might be onto a winner and, taking a risk, released the map separately. It was an instant hit and still sells strongly today.  For the author of this site, however, nothing quite beats the original eight volumes of leatherbound fiction. Although they can be a little unwieldy on the Tube, they do provide something to read during delays and also, crucially, do not include the Elephant and Castle shopping centre (TiL  passim ).
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Traffic has been an abiding bugbear of Londoners since Roman times. As  Fetlock's London Chronyk  pointed out in 1475:   "The Streetes doe so heave Wyth carts and theyr beastes of Laboyr that this Chronykler wasse layte for his worke agayne and didde gette a Ryght ticking-off fromme the Manyger of his Line; and suche is the heaving of the Beastes that their Dirt and Manyure does mayke manye a Pedestryan heave also."   In recent times, though, much of the motorists' ire has been directed at Traffic Wardens, who issue fines to illegally parked motorists. With these custodians of the yellow line again heavily in the news, we revisit the three most extreme cases of wardens overstepping the mark:  1. Parking services had to be suspended for three weeks in Islington in 1994 after it emerged that wardens were ticketing items of street furniture including bollards, benches and street lamps. While the council approved of the wardens' zeal and creativity, it found it self-defeating to end up paying the fines itself.  2. A 1990 plan to force drivers in the borough of Wandsworth to carry a warden in the front passenger seat of their cars at all times, believed to be the "final solution" to traffic violations, was abandoned after an "extremely successful" pilot because it cost too much.  3. Haringey council's innovative and more cost-effective policy of summarily executing errant motorists was scrapped in 1999 after three years of operation because of the escalating problem of abandoned vehicles and health and safety concerns. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      London has been the venue for many pioneering public health schemes over the years, ranging from  urlLink John Snow's work to identify the causes of Cholera  to  urlLink Bazalgette's construction of the sewer system . But for every breakthrough in public health, there have been numerous horrible failures. Here we list the top 10.  10.  Typhoid: Nature's Beautician for Healthy Skin.  Pamphlet, 1871.  9.  Dr Feniloe's Radium and Lead Cutlery.  Withdrawn 1894.  8.  Barking Spa.  Renamed "Northern Outfall Sewage Works", 1904.  7.  The Killer In Your Home: Why Privies Belong At The Bottom Of The Garden.  Book, first and only edition dated 1922.  6.  Lawnmower Repairs For The Under-Fives.  Book, pulped 1971.  5.  Botulicks.  Popular frozen-milk snack until 1959.  4.  Our Friend Anthrax.  Government film produced 1952, shown twice.  3  AIDS: It'll Probably Go Away By Itself.  Pamphlet, withdrawn 1982.  2.  The Daily Mail.  Various stories including "New Asylum Seeker Breast Cancer Threat to House Prices", "Flirting: The Cancer Connection" and "Did Nostradamus Predict BSE Using The Bible Code?", 1971-2004 and on.  1.  The Rat Diet.  Controversial nutrition advice until 1348.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The current controversy over whether  urlLink murders have been inspired by violent films or computer games  is nothing new. In fact, similar debates have been raging in London for almost 2000 years.  In Roman London, this controversy first reared its head after the unveiling of a new mosaic of the fall of Carthage at the forum. Its depiction of the violence inflicted on the stricken city was said to be graphic, and within a week a man was found two street away cut into half-inch squares. The mosaic was swiftly covered up.  Another notable instance was the infamous furore that surrounded the growing popularity of  urlLink magic lantern picture shows  in the 1830s. At one particular establishment - Messrs Lagrange And Their Coloured Light Amazeum - a show entitled "Mrs X Walks Her Dogs" is believed to have sparked a craze for dog ownership - a harmless enough pursuit, you might think, until you consider that the show ran as an unending loop and thus led to several cases of exhaustion and The Vapours.  Indeed the Lagranges' establishment seems to have courted controversy. A showing entitled "The Wronged Customer Wreaks His Bloody Revenge" was accused of directly leading to the Umbrella Salesmen Massacre of 1839. The Lagranges hotly contested this claim, but undermined their case by following The Wronged Customer with an attraction called "The Satisfied Customer Gives The Lagrange Brothers All Their Money".  We shall not linger long on the Punch & Judy killings of the 1890s but to say that the culprit was almost certainly a man in a crocodile suit rather than an actual crocodile, all shows at the time carried clear warnings that that was  not  the way to do it, and that the murderer's modus operandi led directly to important safety laws that finally banned the inclusion of six-inch nails and lead shot in sausages.  On a related note,  the world’s first clockwork orange  was shown at the Great Exhibition in 1851. The spring-driven geared citrus could be an orange at three different speeds, easily adjustable by switch, and only needed winding every four hours. It was a popular success, easily outselling Stevenson’s Patent Steam-Piston Pear, which had a tendency to overheat.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From 1880 on, open-air vertical lidos were very popular in London. Requiring little more than some water, a tiled surface and a large diving platform to erect, they sprang up across the city and attracted great crowds.  The largest and most lavish was in St John's Wood. The Wellington Road Vertical Swimming Ponds and Spa was centred around a 45 feet-high cube of freestanding water that visitors could dive into from the tallest diving platform in the world or walk into at ground level. But you had to be careful once inside, because a nasty fall could result if you fell out of the side.  It was, of course, most popular in summer, when people could pay their penny and just stroll in for a refreshing dip, but it froze into a solid block of ice in winter. Nevertheless, it could still be seen surrounded by small children, either because their tongues were stuck to it or, in the bitter winter of 1948, because they were admiring the lithe body of Walter Samuels, who loved the lido so much that he refused to come out and had to wait until the spring thaw of 1949.  Unfortunately, the growing popularity of "baths" or "pools" eroded the visitor-base of the vertical lidos and one by one they closed. The Wellington Road was the last, and only closed in 1957 after it was found to breach section 1.1a of the new planning act, "Gravity: Compliance with". But even today you can meet people who'll tell up they regularly "swam up the Wellington".
     
    
</post>


</Blog>