<Blog>


<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear all, i am back from South Africa.. jus for those that still think i'm there and want me to say good nite to animals.... bah... haha..  Well, overall a very good trip. Was kept safe by God's grace. But South Africa's not as dangerous as everyone thinks. Just dun go to those places that you're not supposed to. For example, the settlements... But then again, there are people that go on tours to these settlements. Wassup wif that man? People are living like that and others are goin in to gawk like the stupid tourists that they are. They deserve to be robbed.   Had my first game of golf over there too. Can ya&nbsp;imagine?? No handicap and trying to negotiate a South African course. That was the end of me man. It wasn't so much golf as it was cross-country for me. Hit the ball - run to the bushes - hit the ball - run to the trees. Think i spent more time in the vegetation than on the green. Who sez u dun get much exercise? People who want to play golf and exercise should follow me.... jus suck at it... hahah  Also noticed that the SIA safety video is on helluva irritating. You kinda like settle into&nbsp; the "comfy" airline seat, that squeezes ur kidneys and back to a funny shape, turn on the movie that you watched halfway on the trip there before they took away your head phones, then they decide to screen the damn thing at the most exciting part. One particularly interesting part was when they said to "use the light and whistle on the life jacket to GET ATTENTION." Can ya imagine if some attention seeking kid got that? OMG... i would like kill myself before he got warmed up. He would jus run up to u and blow the whistle and blind u with that strobing light on his jacket.   hehe...ok...if u guys would like some pics, once again, they are available at  urlLink http://photos.yahoo.com/akeldama09  . Enjoy ok? Anything dunno, jus leave a comment below here and i'll answer. Mark does professional consultation. F.O.C   Special mention to Wes for that amazing slip of the tongue on Saturday. Sexual Immortality!! Awriteeeee!! hahahaha 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear all, here is my last blog before i set off for the foreign land of South Africa... alittle scary if ya ask me, but then again, so is Little India..... kidding!!!!!! hahahah.... pls pray for our safety as we venture into the unknown....  &nbsp; Just had convocation yesterday too... alot of comments. first they give us this small-ass room to change in. It can hardly fit fifty people and they expect 400+ of us to squeeze inside to robe up. It should be called a knee-to-elbow-to-face room rather than a robing room, as such was the situation. After we manged to suqeeze our feet past our face into the robe, they made us wait around for dunno how long before the professors and deans started to make their way in. Now, watz the deal with the pace at which they walk down the stiairs?? I understand that there' nice elevator music and all to accompnay their entrance but then again, to be walking at a rate of 2cm/ hr is ridiulous. The ceremony hadn't started and i was already falling asleep... not good. &nbsp; So thruout the ceremony, i was reading my book until it came to my name. So i got up and made my way across the auditorium and lined up. Was telling myself not to cock this up........but then again........ that wouldn't be me rite??? Soooo, as the story goes, i made my way across the stage all confidently to receive my "empty NTU cert thingie". stuck out hand to shake the Dean's one and jacked him in the nuts.......... &nbsp; &nbsp; Nahhhh.. i'm jus kidding... hahaha.. wat happened was that i shook his hand, then raised my other hand to hold the cert thingie. But alas, i made a parallax error and did not grasp the thingie properly... soooooo, my 12 dollar photo of me has me holding thin air while my beautiful smile pretends there's nothing wrong... great... i cant wait for them to send me the photo in 6 weeks time.... bah... &nbsp; Notice everyone is particularly frenly during the after-convocation party. No request for a photo is turned down... Photos here and there, and everywhere else. My eyes had those patches where u cant see anything beocz of the flashes after a while. Better still, we dressed up our compatriots who were late for their ceremony...  &nbsp; I know itz kinda cheesy but i haf to thank me mom and dad for putting me thru uni man... and thanx for coming down to the ceremony Jamie!! She came down all the way even tho she was tired from the trip back from Bangkok.... hee.... really appreciated dear... &nbsp; all rite.. thatz all for me now... i'll try and think of some stuff to blog when i get back from SA... haha... u can check out the convo fotos at the usual photo website...heh.... take care ya'll!! &nbsp; Clownz signing off!! &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, wasssuppp pple?? Anything changed between sunday and now? Doubt so rite? haha...watched Mean Girls... can ya believe that? Watched it with a guy some more... felt strangely vulnerable all thruout the show... hmmmmmz. Anywayz, not a veri funny show lah... thot it would haf been funnier actually. Turned out to be pretty predictable. but i think the girls will still like it lah.. Dun think it will dethrone legend like Legally Blonde tho.. hahaha..  letz see wat nonsense i can think up today. Oh yeah, there shd be a shopping survival guide for guys.. here's some pointers i can think off.   1. When u first step into the shop, quickly scan around for a place to sit.  If there are people already on the seat/ couch, try to sidle up to them and make space for ur rump. Slowly move your ass inch by inch, before proudly proclaiming the seat as urs.  2. If there are no seats, do not dispair. Seats do not have to be a legitimate chair or couch. Empty display tables are welcome also. For example, in Zara there are those metallic steps that the salesgirls use to reach high places. These can be sat on too. If the salesgirl is using it, simply push her off and sae the customer is always right.   3. Amusement is another way of survival. Proceed to check out wat other people are trying. If you are lucky, you might bump into a few aunties. These are especially interesting. Usually they will be trying something totally not suited for their age or that resembles tableclothes/ curtains. If you are super lucky, they will jio their friends to wear the same thing as them. Remember to ask ur gf to look at this point in time. Share the joy.   4.  Stoning is another option. But it justs makes u look like a junkie.  5. When the gf is trying on stuff, try to gather with the other men. It makes it look like they are trying to fall in in threes. U know, when they all stand outside the fitting room, with plastic bags and handbags in their hands, which are held together in a "v" shape, in front of their bodies. If u are realy bored, conduct an inspection by walking in front of them, stopping ocasionally to chat with one and telling the next one to stand easy. Ask at least one why he never Kiwi his boots.  Here are some DO NOTS:  1. DO NOT browse thru the clothing. These are not for MEN!! Pls proceed to the Men's department before browsing. I know it rubs off but pls show some restraint.  2. DO NOT clean ur fingers on the clothes. U might get caught. I should know....  3. DO NOT bring drinks into the Taka Zara. The security uncle is damn on. He will ask u to drink outside. He did not like it when i told him i'm drinking Coke, not Outside.   4. DO NOT tell other women to get a size larger.  5. DO NOT check out the stuff that you bought a while back while on the move. Neither should you read a magazine while one the move. You will end up telling another lady that "That looks very nice honey". If u are damn suay, it will be an auntie in a tablecloth.   6. DO NOT react when there is a tranny browsing. You have seen one before, you do not haf to risk life and limb to see one at this particular moment.   Wellll, thatz all i haf for now...letz see if i can think up more things for the next few days... heh....Btw Jamie's back... yeayyyy!!! hahahaha 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Would ya believe it! The dreaded chalet is finally over... i sae dreaded becoz everyone had so much fun and nobody would feel like working on Monday. Alrite guys, hands up all those that found Chris severely entertaining... i see u, i see u, i see u....hahaha... Bond, Christopher Bond... "zero! zero! seven! Pom! Arrrgh!!"....  This is an entry from my former blog:   Question : Why do they have showers and taps at the same time? The kind where u gotta pull the "thing" at the top of the tap to activate the shower?? Wat the hell? Do u know how difficult it is to take a shower..... shampoo ur head, turn the tap on, wash ur feet instead.  soiap ur body, turn the tap on, wash ur feet again.  By the end of it i had pretty clean feet. Sheesh.  Got smarter on the 2nd day tho....soaped and shampooed and washed my face (and feet) all at once. Take that u damn tap.   This is an entry for my current blog:  Alrite, wassup wif them chalet toilets. Last year i had problems getting myself clean. This year too!!! Was all ready to get my bath, since i was feeling like a post it note. So, i go to that spooky "The Eye" toilet out on the balcony and happily get ready for it. AFTER i get into the bath tub and turn on the tap, i realise that the "thing" as mentioned above in spoilt!! !@#$%$%&*@ That totally made my day man. But the other part of my mind told me that the marginal utilities of getting dressed again and going to another toilet was lower than just staying there. So i tried to pull that measly lever and activate the shower head. No success there. In the end, i was left squatting in the bath tub, splashing water at myself wif my hands!! I actually thot i was a samsui woman.... To add insult to injury, a coupla ants come along and decide to bite my toes..... Def not a good bath. I haf no "yuan fen" wif chalet baths...  Ok...enuff from me... go look at the pics... they tell a story by themselves...heh
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesss itz me!! Back in the bloggin industry...figure i have so much time now that i'll do something. Here's my social commentary on how the world and how much amusement i can derive from it.  Hey!! Portugal's into the finals... that's like how not cool. They played well lah...but i dunno...i haf something against them.. Dunno wat it is tho...maybe itz becoz i got indigestion from eating portugese eggtarts last time.  So wah! the chalet is like in 2 days time! How exciting is that? Ok, for those that will at the chalet for the first time, lemme break it down for u.. *all rite stop! Hammer time!*. The people at the chalet will usually be grouped in a few categories. The "swimmers", the cardists, the alchohol deprived and the ignorant. Now, the  swimmers  will be doin a special version of the breaststroke. Dun ask me whether got pool or not. You will find out when u're there. The  cardist  will engage in harmless games like heart attack and snap...... rite..... The alchohol deprived will be doin their fair share of tasting certain concoctions that Wesley makes up. (PS This is not for the faint stomached) and the  ignorant  sit around downstairs and watch tv. That's basically it.  Hey, will Larry and Angie be there? Doubt so rite? How many of ya were at the wedding?? Mad fun man. Sorry Laine, u had to be in Aust. Hahahaha... We had the pre-finale of the Bachelor going on there. For those of you that dunno, the finalists are Jamie (my gf) and Sharon (Jame's gf). Maggie (Chris' WIFE) was unfortunately eliminated in last week's episode. When interviewed, Maggie said "I never really liked him anyway. Those 2 girls are just in it for the money...." Jamie Yap seems to be the hottest item out there these days. Eligible financial banker-analyst-like-thing job.  No wonder he got chosen to be on The Bachelor :Singapore version. (Pls refer to http://photos.yahoo.com/akeldama09 for pics.) Btw, i feel ripped off. The menu said we were gonna haf chinese tea after dessert. I DIDN'T GET ANY CHINESE TEA. YC and Irene, you better make sure we get our chinese tea if the menu sez so....  OMg....u can tell i'm really bored can ya? haha... btw, interesting note...i'd rather watch mean girls than spiderman 2..... is someting wrong wif me???   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I know he passed away... but this is too funny to not share... hahahahahahha&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just watched Bad Boys 2 again... while watching, i got really pissed at them pple who borrowed my discs and never return!! GIMME BACK MY STUFF YOU PPLE!!! ARRRGHH!! hahahaha..  Went for dinner yesterday at this coffee shop in Commonwealth. The food was good but i have to comment on the drinks auntie. You try and try to get her attention but itz like she's on coke or something (Coke... hahaah... she's a drinks auntie... i jus realised i made a corny) Wellll, when u finally get her attention, she jerks a little, macam she jus snapped outta a dream. Then she starts on her journey towards you. I tell you..... by the time she gets to you, you have almost died of thirst. Wah lau!! She walked at the same speed as them professors at the convocation man i tell you.  Anyone watched SG idol? That lemon tree guy looked possessed man. Scary. Well, as long as he wasn't possessed by the spirit of that stripper. i dunno. I'm still skeptical about SG idol. We'll see how it develops in the coming weeks. The good ones were really good tho. I liked that girl that dressed like an auntie. She has a happy voice. But i must say! The judges are jus pissing me off!! Kauz. They think they damn witty, making comments at every bad auditioner. Trying to be like Cowell lah.... at least Cowell doesn't do it at every opportunity. Goodness.....  Ok.... here are a few songs for u people to go download and listen.  Mark's Recommendations!!  1. Terror Squad - Lean Back 2. Lloyd Banks - We on Fire 3. Maroon 5 - Sunday Morning 4. Los Lonely Boys - Nobody Else 5. Sugarcult - Memory  Hehe... jus a little music something... maybe i'll keep this up.... qutie fun,...macam music critic hor? hahahahah....  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello helloooo... tis me again. heh heh... jus received word that my blog is appreciated!! That's u Liz!! Special shoutout to my fans! I'd like to thank my dog, cat and fish.  Aha! Take that u sappy bloggers who write abt every detail in their sad sad lives. Nobody wants to hear how u damaged ur cuticle when u were dieting to fit into that mini pink dress that is 5 sizes too small!!! ahahahaha...  Anywayz, DnD is approaching rite? For hall 3 at least lah.. heard that itz at Meritus Mandarin. Whoa... rite smack in the middle of Orchard huh? hopefully the drunkards wun get too far when the whole event is over.  Went back to play for MPE week something something.. no idea wat it was.. jus knew i'd get paid.. hahaha.. so we played our 2 songs and got outta there. It sucked but we didnt care... nobody was noticing anywayz... hahaha.. all i remember was that there were a lotta China people around. All wanting that free goodie bag... and free macs!  Well, i'm too lazt to think of new stuff, so here's something from my old blog.   OK..here goes...new games to play during OC      1. Cpt Durian   2. Team fortress with super soaker.... fire extinguisher is bonus weapon   3. bungee jumping from N4   4. "Steal the exam paper" - to be played in 5th week of school   5. Initation Sprint   6. Chug the Beer      Haf u thot of some games that we play? like the cross lines games at the bball court? I think it'd be more fun if we had our own rules, without telling the station master. For example, who can put the most catchers out of commission by stepping on their toes...hiakz...fun!How abt going ard trying to scare the monsters on monster hunt instead? haha...(nobody leak this out ya hear??!!! haha...)      Or that thing on the soapy canvass...spend the better part of ur time trying to push people down rather than retriving the dang ping pong balls. They're so darn small anyway.....screw them..letz haf fun making people fall...crush a few of them balls on the way b4 they disqualify u.      war games...spend ur time wallowing in the mud making oinking noises...freak the freshies out.      Mini olympiads.....wear your best olympic get up and start to warm up...tell the freshies they better wear shoes and drink lotsa water to avoid cramps. "Dun wanna end up like the last batch. Dehydration's a bitch"      Sentosa...climb to the top of the two towers and shout across "For the glory of Sauron!! I claim this tower in Sauron's name!!" Proceed to jump off into the ocean.      On the last nite, wake everyobdy up and claim itz gonna rain soon...rush them off into the tents, then proceed to take all the space u want on the porch.      Sentosa beach games. Run straight into the sea and continue running out with half closed eyes....keep yawning. Peridically turn back to shout "C'mon team!"      Ice breakers...intro urself as Tan Chee Hong. Observe eyes growing wider....then claim itz a joke and ur real name is Lim Jiak Sai.      Eat the polo sweet everytime it comes round. Yum....then squat down and pretend to look for the sweet under the couch.       Announce that u are the king cockroach during the "cockroach chicken monkey' game. Bestow kinghthood on other cockroaches and cower in fear when u see a chicken. Immediately transform into a cock and claim the chicken as your mate.      OC rox....  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    myself and the big thing i picked outta my nose&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today jus had a family dinner at my haus. Most entertaining. It was for my grandmother's birthday. Well, for one, once everyone was into the house, it was chaos. Instructions were being flung left rite and center for people to move around, do this and do that... the kids were so confused that one of my cousins was jus spinning in a circle..... kidding.. haha.. But there were so many conflicting instructions that it was fun to see people trying to get all of them..  "Go get the plates from the kitchen." "Also, get wash them!" "Then get the forks and spoons..." "The forks and spoons are already on the table, get the meat!" "Make sure the meat is on a clean plate."  I ended up washing the meat and placed it on a dirty plate... jus to spite them all... muahahaha...  Also, i noticed that the older u are, u get to do anything u want. Like my grand dad, he was done and he was like "Ok, i'm done, i'm outta here."  So my mom was like "no you're not...Sit down and chat wif us leh. I'm not done eating yet"  And he was like "I'm done... you're not done... so YOU sit here and eat. I'm goin to watch TV." WAhahahaha..... I wanna be like that when i get old.   "Granddad! Letz go to the museum!!"  "Museum?? The museum is for pussies. Screw the museum."  "Granddad! U said a bad word!! I'm telling mommy!!"  "Dun tell on me ya little brat!! I'll kill ya!! " hahahahaha.... wat fun   After dinner, when everyone was duly satisfied, we all split into our various haunts. Some into the tv room, some jus lounging at the sofa. So my bro, my cousin and i struck up a little bet, to bet on who fell asleep first. The hot favourites were my grandpa, and my uncle. My grandpa usually slept early, so he was in the running. My uncle had unfortunately plonked himself onto a very comfortable reclining chair so he too was chosen. In the end, none of them won becoz my grandpa wanted to go home. bah.... no winners there.  But still, it proves my point that family dinners are very entertaining. They are nowhere near as boring as you would think. You jus need to find entertainment in the rite places. heh heh... 
    
</post>


</Blog>