<Blog>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      >>  urlLink [Chapter 2 - The Disease]  >>  urlLink [Chapter 3 - The Sweet Legacy]     Copyright 2003     All characters in these chronicles are real, and any resemblance to any living person, is entirely intentional and purely marked by full consciousness of the nature and effects of the events being chronicled.     It's no longer a question of staying healthy. It's a question of finding a sickness you like."    - Jackie Mason, US Comedian    December 29, 2002 - 5:45 am IST   I woke up, almost startled, and it took me a few seconds to realize that Gulf Air flight GF-52 was preparing for landing at Mumbai's Chhatrapati Shivaji International Airport. I was experiencing a throbbing headache for almost half of the 30-hour long journey from Denver, Colorado to Mumbai and was tired like never before, with stop-overs at New Jersey, London-Heathrow, Abu Dhabi and Bahrain, the last one being just a technical stop. Now you know, 'long journey' will perhaps be an understatement. This was the most grueling journey of my life and just never seemed to end. I hate air travel, yes I do. Not that I am someone who has done a lot of flying-around-the-world thing, but whatever little I have traveled by air, I just did not take a liking to it. The continuous high-pitched whine of the aircraft engine (perhaps more appropriately associated with a jet propeller engine) makes me numb after a while, and my efforts of finding solace (maybe 'comfort' is a more decent word) with typical on-the-plane activities like listening to music and reading, usually prove unsuccessful. Not that there is really anything else to do except for smiling (I am not a 'talker') at fellow passengers and peering through the small windows for brief glimpses of the outer space which initially seems to draw your attention, but as you move on, drives you to boredom. Worse, the 7 of us from Colorado State, who were traveling on the same leg throughout, from Denver to Mumbai, were spread out on the plane, as we did not manage to get the seats booked together. So our plans of having whatever little fun we could with each other's company were already busted.  I still spent most of my time listening to Dire Straits and Mark Knopfler solos - my newly found craze for Classic/Progressive Rock, thanks to my dear cousin Shailesh, alias Bhushan -  urlLink http://bhush.tripod.com , and affectionately called 'Big B', who first introduced me to his music. Many thanks also go to Siddharth, a.k.a. Sid -  urlLink http://hawkeyejo.blogspot.com , good friend and roommate at CSU, for allowing me to access his MK collection! As they say, Sachin Tendulkar is God's gift to Cricket or God Himself, and I guess Knopfler, the 'Sultan of Swing', draws similar comparisons when it comes to Classic Rock. Interesting fact being that, Sachin himself is a tremendous fan of Knopfler! The man is God when it comes to guitar playing. The guy is phenomenal. I am not a connoisseur of Music or Guitars, but my hats off to him! Nikhil, a college friend of mine in India who plays the guitar, and is a 'jammer' himself, once said that if you learn the guitar chords (what they call as 'chord progression'), understanding and appreciating Knopfler's amazing work becomes even more obvious. As a matter of fact, Bhush and I share very common music interests and he was also the one who hooked me onto another GOD, of Indian music this time, none other than ARR (A.R. Rahman), some 10 years ago. I do not wish to digress too much, so I intend to write separately on ARR and Knopfler sometime later.  I had managed to get very little sleep in the past 30 hours of a physically and mentally taxing journey. Now, that perhaps could be an overstatement. Here I was, on the way to my home country, for the most awaited one-month's vacation of my lifetime, and there was really nothing I could crib about.  We got off the plane at Mumbai with an immense sense of relief, and fortunately, it took just 30 minutes for immigration, baggage claim and customs clearance; unusual scenes at a place, which is teeming with people all year round. My patience had already been tested to the limit in the last 30 hours and last minute hiccups with customs/baggage would have made matters worse. It was smooth sailing (or should I say 'flying'!) for us, when it came to these 'worst fears' associated with air travel. Pheeew!  Once outside the terminal, I instantly spotted my mom and my dad and waved. This wasn't exactly true with them. They spotted me mostly because of my 'CSU' t-shirt, and according to them (especially my mom), I was almost unrecognizable. Ofcourse, they attributed this to what they thought as unimaginable weight loss. And although this was true, I wasn't even aware of the fact that I looked shockingly different from my old self, when I had left for USA 18 months ago. Since my parents were the first and only people who were seeing me after such a long gap, they were obviously alarmed at my physical condition. To be frank, I guess I looked pathetic and completely worn out. I do recall friends at CSU saying that I looked much leaner of late, but their reaction was not really as serious as my parents'. Understandably so, since my parents met me after a span of 18 months, and they noticed the change more easily than my friends who were used to seeing me everyday. We pushed off for Pune; I was thrilled to be back in my homeland, but completely unaware of the fact that I would be in for a rude shock the coming New Year.   Here, I would like to add something, which my dad revealed to me later, after I was diagnosed. My dad has been a Type-II diabetic for the last decade or so (more on the technicalities of diabetes later), and he was well experienced to sense that something was wrong with me. An hour or two after we met at the terminal and were in the car on our way to Pune, he was the only one conscious of the fact that I drank two big bottles of water (almost 3 litres) in the space of an hour. Drinking water in such proportions is not only unusual for any person (perhaps true with very few people in extreme cases, as in sportspersons who constantly consume fluids to keep themselves hydrated), but my dad's fear that I might have 'diabetes' grew even more, when my weight loss was backed up by my 'unquenchable thirst' and the 'dry mouth' syndrome. He kept mum about his feelings during that time, and must have hoped that eventually he would be wrong.   December 30, 2002   The first couple of days (December 29-30) were pretty busy, meeting family and friends, answering phone calls, and catching up on some well deserved rest and sleep. By this time, my apparent weight loss and worn out looks had become the focal point of my conversation with anybody who met with me in person. In spite of the fact that this 'issue' grabbed so much attention, I (and others around me) was/were, still absolutely unprepared for what was in store a day later. I shrugged off this issue most of the times.  The truth of the matter was that I had lost a whopping 20 pounds within the last 6 months, more precisely, starting June 2002, from whatever analysis and comparison I could draw from my photographs before June and after June, and I had no fundamental explanation as to why this had happened. Another fact that was hard to be not noticed for all of us was the frequent runs to the bathroom that I made. Again, something which I now find surprising myself, I was the least bothered about this in the last 6 months, and like the other two symptoms (thirst and weight loss), I was completely ignorant of the fact that I urinated once every hour. I am not sure if this was the case every day, since June, but in the past three months during the Fall semester, I can recall myself waking up thrice in the night regularly to urinate. Drinking bottles and bottles of water (and then urinating) became a routine thing for me, and I even remember having a laugh or two on this, with my friends. Worse, I had even joked once, that I might have diabetes. Diabetes runs in our family, and I was aware of some of the symptoms associated with it. Ignorance is bliss was my motto for a while, and since I felt perfectly fit otherwise, I did not even care to discuss these things with my parents on the phone. I kept telling them that I never felt better ever in my whole life and was doing alright.  	 In reality, my pancreas was losing its fight inside my body over these months. (Note: I plan to discuss all the gory details of diabetes in the next few chapters, so forgive me if some things seem unclear at this point). The beta cells or islet cells (also called the 'Islets of Langerhans', named after Paul Langerhans who discovered them), which produce the hormone 'insulin' in the pancreas were battling to survive against my body's immune system.  urlLink Merriam-Webster  defines an immune system as: 'the bodily system that protects the body from foreign substances, cells, and tissues by producing the immune response '. In short, the immune system, which normally battles to keep us alive and healthy, was instead, gradually destroying and wiping out the islet cells that produce insulin, the hormone essential for converting sugar, carbohydrates, starches and other food into energy (metabolism) needed for daily life. The  urlLink American Diabetes Association (ADA)  describes insulin as the hormone that "unlocks" the cells of the body, allowing glucose to enter and fuel them. I was a victim of all the 'classic' symptoms of Insulin-Dependent Diabetes Mellitus.  In the meanwhile, my dad's fear grew more into concern and impatience and he suggested that I check my blood glucose levels using his glucometer, before I go see our family doctor. A glucometer is a device used to measure a person's blood glucose levels, and my dad used it to check his own sugars once in a while. Glucometers are still not very well prevalent in India; my cousin, Milind, had brought one for my dad from the US a few years ago. It's an extremely convenient device (these days more of a 'smart' blood glucose monitoring system) to check one's blood sugars at home, without having to visit laboratories to submit blood samples, and then (anxiously) wait for the results. Glucometers give results within seconds, and moreover, do not compromise for accuracy. More on glucometers later... The only thing that turns people off when they see a glucometer is the idea of pricking your fingers for a blood sample. Now, this is actually a much better option, than getting a blood sample using a painful needle and syringe, since these lancing devices use a thin needle to prick (or lance, as they call it), and most important, the person can use it on his/her own, independently, without somebody else drawing the blood for you. This particular glucometer was pretty obsolete by current standards, and did have a fairly thick needle as compared to the one that I use at present. But since I had seen my dad regularly using it, I had no intentions of making a fuss about pricking myself. The seriousness of my symptoms was starting to bother me too, and I thought about getting over with everything once and for all. This was really no big deal, I thought; perhaps only because I had no idea I would have to do this atleast 3 to 4 times a day in the coming months (and maybe for the rest of my life), which I must say does get painful at times, and if not painful, extremely frustrating.  I pricked, drew the blood sample from the tip of my finger with utmost difficulty (a case of cold fingers I guess), dabbed it onto the meter's test strip, and inserted the strip into the device. I remember very clearly, my mom, dad and me, staring at the glucometer for almost 20-25 seconds, which seemed like a lifetime, and I could sense the tension in the air. To our dismay, the glucometer showed an 'Error'. I tried using another blood sample using a different test strip, but the result was the same! However, when we consulted the glucometer manual, we concluded that the reason for the error was nothing but a blood sugar level so high, that the glucometer went out of range!  Although we failed to get an exact blood sugar reading, I was pretty much a confirmed unofficial 'diabetic'. It took me a while to really understand what was happening. There was a short span of time when nobody spoke. The rest of the evening and night was a time spent in long discussions with my family, and the only thing left to do now, on our part, was to visit my family doctor and get a confirmed official diagnosis. There was still a feeling that we would be proved wrong, that my case would turn out into something called 'Pre-Diabetes' (temporary high blood sugar levels which can be brought to normal again). I was myself ready to accept the fact that I might go on some medication for a few days, and things would be back to normal once again.   December 31, 2002   Early morning, my dad and I set off to visit Dr. Anand Gokhale, our family doctor for the past 30 odd years. For Nulkars, Dr. Gokhale is someone who is not just a doctor; the mere mention of his name in the Nulkar household is enough for us to be rid of any sickness in this world.  There are two standard blood tests that are generally carried out to test for diabetes:    I) Fasting Plasma Glucose:   The fasting plasma glucose test is the most preferred way to diagnose diabetes and requires atleast 8 hours of overnight fasting. A single blood sample was drawn at the doctor's clinic and sent to the laboratory for results. Normal fasting plasma glucose levels are between 70 and 110 milligrams per deciliter (mg/dl).   II) Oral Glucose Tolerance Test (GTT):   This test is performed after the fasting plasma glucose test. I was given 75 grams of glucose in a sweet tasting liquid (or water). One or more blood samples are then taken two to three hours after this test. The morning of the test, a person should not eat, smoke or drink coffee/tea, and should be in a fairly healthy condition (no cold or flu). The oral glucose tolerance test measures blood glucose levels several times over a period of 2-3 hours. In a person without diabetes, the glucose levels rise and then fall quickly. In someone with diabetes, glucose levels rise higher than normal and fail to come back down as fast. A person is said to have a normal response when the 2-hour glucose level is less than 140 mg/dl, and all values between 0 and 2 hours are less than 200 mg/dl. In my case only one single blood sample was taken, 2 hours after the GTT.  By the time I left for home at 11:30, I was utterly famished. Incidentally, another common symptom of a Type-I patient is increased hunger. I did experience uncontrollable hunger at times; but it did not reach alarming proportions like the other symptoms did.   I was supposed to know the test results by evening, and could hardly wait. In the evening, Dr. Gokhale had bad news for me. My results came as a shocker for everyone, including Dr. Gokhale. My Fasting Plasma Glucose was 260, and the GTT was 340, way higher than anybody expected. (That explained why the glucometer conked off the previous day; I was definitely above 400, atleast!!). There was no doubting the fact that I had developed chronic diabetes, and this was a classic case of Hyperglycemia (the technical term for high blood sugar).  Although I was prepared for the worst, it took some time to sink in when the news actually hit me. Things had happened fairly quickly over the last couple days, and for me it was impossible to fathom what exactly had gone wrong. I tried to think and piece together all the information I had. Like any other patient who is newly diagnosed with a disease/sickness, I was dumbfounded.  In spite of tremendous research on Diabetes - its causes, symptoms, and treatment, doctors still are unable to confirm whether a diagnosis is Type-I or Type-II with these initial results, unless a person suffers from many other serious complications, in which case definite conclusions can be immediately drawn. Before going into details about the types of diabetes in later chapters, for now, simply put: a Type-I patient is insulin-dependent, i.e. he/she needs insulin externally (shots or pump) in order to survive, whereas a Type-II patient can be treated by taking oral pills to control the blood sugar. Since an insulin treatment is considered 'intensive', and has its own initial risk factors, Dr. Gokhale decided to begin with a short 10-day treatment by prescribing some oral pills for me. In the 10 days to follow, if the pills worked in controlling my sugar to normal levels, then I would essentially fall in the category of 90% of diabetics who are Type-II patients. Eventually I would learn that the pills had absolutely no effect in controlling my blood sugar.   January 10, 2003   On January 10, exactly 10 days after I went on oral pills, I was officially diagnosed as a Type-I patient. This was again, based on the blood sugar tests done on the glucometer. Following were the exact readings I got on the three days prior to my confirmation as an Insulin-Dependent Diabetic.  January 08 - Random Test: 372 January 09 - Fasting Plasma Glucose: 237 January 10 - Post Breakfast (2 hours after breakfast): 378 January 10 - Post Prandial (2 hours post-lunch): 277  The results showed that the pills did nothing to achieve any sort of control, not even the slightest of improvements in my condition. The reason being that pills work only in the presence of insulin in the body, even if there's a small amount. The fact that the pills failed was proof enough that my pancreas produced no insulin, or extremely insignificant amounts of insulin, which the pills could not use.  In the meanwhile I underwent several other tests, to check if my diabetes had caused any other physical complications. This is important, simply because prolonged high sugars if gone un-noticed, may result in life threatening long term complications, and it was essential that I undergo a through medical examination. The history indicated that my diabetes was actually 6 to 8 months old, assuming that was the period when I began suffering all the symptoms, and hence this exam became even more important. Most of the tests fortunately turned out to be normal, namely: Sonography of the pancreas, ECG or Electric Cardio Gram test (detection and diagnosis of heart abnormalities that measures electrical potentials on the body surface and generates a record of the electrical currents associated with heart muscle activity), Kidney and urine tests and a whole lot of others, which can only be understood by medical technicians or doctors. However I had a close call with two other tests. My case was borderline, or slightly over the normal mark, on the 'Thyroid' test, luckily not alarming. And when I did an eye-check up at Dr. Sachin Kale's clinic, I found out that the spherical distance of my right eye had increased from -3.25 to -4.0, and the left eye's distance had gone up from -3.25 to -3.50. Even though my fundus (the part of the eye opposite the pupil) was normal, I was at a stage wherein another few months of high sugar could have resulted in possible retinal damage, a common diabetes complication in older patients. For the time being, I was fortunate to have left the clinic with nothing but a slightly thicker pair of glass lenses! :)    In a sense, when I look back, I think I was extremely lucky to have got diagnosed at the right time. I cannot imagine the physical complications I would have experienced if my condition had gone un-noticed in the USA, i.e. if I had not planned my India trip in January. The creepiest thought that immediately came to my mind when I slowly began to learn about diabetes and its complications was about a condition called as 'Diabetic Ketoacidosis'. Ketones are the acids or toxins that build up in blood, produced when blood glucose rises in the absence of insulin. Large amounts of ketones in the blood can cause a life-threatening problem called diabetic ketoacidosis (DKA). DKA IS A MEDICAL EMERGENCY, a serious condition that can lead to diabetic coma (passing out for a long time) or even death. I know a person who had sugar levels above 600, and at one point, found it difficult even to recognize people! Ketoacidosis may happen to people with Type-I diabetes. Ketones can poison the body. They are a warning sign that your diabetes is out of control. Ketones mean your body is burning fat to get energy. My urine tests did not indicate ketones, but that could have been just the beginning of why I was losing weight even though I was eating much more than normal; I was essentially burning all of my fat!  Moderate or large amounts of ketones in the urine are dangerous. They upset the chemical balance of the blood. Ketoacidosis usually develops slowly, but when vomiting occurs continuously, it may turn serious in a matter of hours. The other symptoms generally are: increased thirst/dry mouth, frequent urination, tiredness, dry/flushed skin, nausea/vomiting/abdominal or stomach pains, hard time breathing, paying attention or utter confusion. I was already experiencing half of the above symptoms. I also realized that the harsh winter in the USA had added to my dry skin problem even though it never bothered me, and as for tiredness, I remember having a hard time concentrating during my classes at times; even dozed off on occasions. In the end, managed to perform well though! ;) Moreover, I am still bewildered as to why I considered myself 'fit as a fiddle' even after knowing these symptoms.   To me, whatever happened during those first two weeks in India seemed a miracle, nothing short of a bad dream, a bad dream that would eventually change a lot of things for me, albeit positively. Those two weeks were nothing but sleepless nights and frustrating days at the doctors' clinic, and spent largely over 'Diabetes Education & Awareness' as well as with retrospection.  In the next chapter I plan to discuss more details about Diabetes and the beginning of my new life as an IDDM patient.  >>  urlLink [Chapter 2 - The Disease]  >>  urlLink [Chapter 3 - The Sweet Legacy] 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Artist: Dire Straits/Mark Knopfler Album: On Every Street, 1991   Well it's a strange old game - you learn it slow  One step forward and it's back to go  You're standing on the throttle  You're standing on the breaks  In the groove 'til you make a mistake  Sometimes you're the windshield  Sometimes you're the bug  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're a fool in love  Sometimes you're the louisville slugger  Sometimes you're the ball  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're going to lose it all  You gotta know happy - you gotta know glad  Because you're gonna know lonely  And you're gonna know bad  When you're rippin' and a ridin'  And you're coming on strong  You start slippin' and slidin'  And it all goes wrong because  Sometimes you're the windshield  Sometimes you're the bug  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're a fool in love  Sometimes you're the louisville slugger baby  Sometimes you're the ball  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're going to lose it all  One day you got the glory  One day you got none  One day you're a diamond  And then you're a stone  Everything can change  In the blink of an eye  So let the good times roll  Before we say goodbye, because  Sometimes you're the windshield  Sometimes you're the bug  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're a fool in love  Sometimes you're the louisville slugger baby  Sometimes you're the ball  Sometimes it all comes together baby  Sometimes you're going to lose it all
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had an amazing game of Badminton yesterday. We are a group of 4-5 students here, who indulge in the game atleast 4 days a  week at CSU's Recreation Center. As "graduate" students ;) although we do not get a chance to play much during the regular  semesters, we make it a point to play during the summer. And yesterday turned out to be a fabulous day of badminton for us.  Me and my doubles partner/friend, Sachin, lost the first game to Vivek and Ninad pretty easily (15-5 I guess). We seemed down  and out in the first one, mostly because of a lot of unforced errors on our part, and we tend to fire late. :) The second  game though, was vastly in contrast to the first one. With deft touches, deceptive drop shots and some hard kills, we sent  our opponents packing with a score of 15-6 in our favour. Important, Sachin and I got our hand-eye co-ordination going really  well. You need really fast reflexes and a strong wrist action to play badminton and although this sounds "technical matter",  its true. I love playing doubles, as a team, it sort of fires me up. I hate to lose when it comes to playing a sport, and I  use this to motivate myself, even if these are friendly games where nothing is at stake. Now this might sound funny, the fact  that games like these needing "motivation" in the first place! :) But when it comes to some things which I really know I am  fairly good at, I make it a point to go down fighting, and badminton is one such instance. It actually hurts me when I lose,  and those who have played with me, know that I get very vocal, nothing to worry about, but just venting my anger. :)  I used to be a doubles partner with my roommate and friend Rohit last summer, but this time around, I've got Sachin as my  partner, and fortunately for both of us, we seem to be clicking well together. Its important to adapt to a certain style of  play in doubles, either each player controls one side of the court (left/right style), OR one player controls the net game  (more about defence) and the other plays the role of the more attacking player right from the word go, from the back of the  court (offense). Sachin and I play the defence-offense game and for both of us it comes naturally, from whatever experience  we have had before. However, I must say we are still playing using the old badminton laws. According to recently made new  laws, the match consists of best-of 5 games, with players needing 7 points and not 15 to win each game, true for both men's  and women's matches. This law, I guess, was changed so as to make each game last for a shorter time, (and perhaps faster),  and thereby increase the public's interest in the game.  The third game between us turned out a humdinger. :) There were a lot of ups and downs for both teams. We initially had the  balance tilted in our favour, with a 5 point lead. But Vivek and Ninad played some good shots to level the points, and from  then on we just couldn't bounce back. We eventually lost by a whisker, as the game went into a 17-pointer (17-15). But the  game was special in terms of the huge amount of rallies we had and everybody gave it their best shot. We decided to play the  fourth and final game as an 11-pointer instead of 15. We had to pull this one off to make it a 2-2 out of 4 games; we were  trailing 1-2 after 3 games. Again, this was a tremendous game in terms of the rallying and the vast range of shots we managed  to play. Nobody was giving up. The score stood 10-8 in our favour and we just needed 1 point to close it. After that, took  place some really high quality shots from all of us. The most wonderful aspect about badminton, that is perhaps not present  in any other game, is that you have to earn points on your own service. You never gain a point (even if you "win" the point),  if your opponents are serving. The score read 10-8 for almost 5 to 6 service exchanges and somehow nobody could gain the  upper hand during that time. But finally, we got lucky, as Ninad netted a forehand. We were glad to make it a "2 games all"  contest, but more than winning, it was one of the finest and the most satisfying game of badminton we had in a long time.  Personally, I was happy with my fitness level, and an increased stamina in general (Hehe...I sound like a pro at the All  England Championship from the Padukone Academy!!). :) Same time last year, was different, badminton tired me out in one  single evening, the tiredness being probably related to diabetes. Things have changed this time. I could have even slugged it  out for another 4 games, if someone asked me to! (I keep talking about diabetes again and again, might be irritating!, but I  hope I can start my chronicle dispatches soon).   Badminton is one game that I not only enjoy playing a lot, but I consider myself pretty good at it! :) In fact I regret not  taking it seriously during my college days in Pune. I have been playing since the last 5 to 6 years. During my undergraduate  years at the Modern College, in Pune, we used to play in the WIE Complex owned by the college's Progressive Education  Society. A few years back, WIE was a famous sports complex in Pune, which hosted National Games' badminton matches. It still  is one of the premier places for badminton in the city, but I am not sure if it still hosts the big games. I was extremely  fortunate to have played on the wooden courts of WIE for 3 straight years, for free! (Yeah, at WIE that's important!!). :) I  haven't seen wooden courts like those at WIE anywhere else, although I am sure there should be quite a few sports complexes  in Pune by now, sporting even better standards.  We were a bunch of enthusiastic folks who never missed an opportunity to spend a couple of hours at WIE atleast 5 days a  week. At one point, we ate, slept and dreamt badminton, such was the craziness. Most of the folks in our group, including me,  learnt the game all by ourselves, in those three years, by practicing for long hours. Initially, we played simply for fun.  But it did not take much to realize that we were getting pretty competitive amongst ourselves, and soon were involved in  serious games, and not just to while away our evenings (and at times early mornings) at the courts. One reason for the  competitiveness was that most of us were good at racket games. I was myself a pretty decent Table Tennis player in  school,having played the inter-school matches for a year. Its a different story altogether, that I had really no impressive  records to prove that I was decent, but it was a strong self-belief :) I was a typical Indian kid during that time (perhaps  things have changed now for Indian kids taking up sports). Never took sports seriously, inspite of the fact that I might have  been able to make some money out of it, if not a career! :) I have seen many of my friends who were good at particular  sports, but academics always held the upper hand for us. Also, WIE hosted a lot of national badminton camps with top players  like Gopichand, Rajeev Bagga, Manjusha Pawangadkar etc. We learnt a few tricks in the trade watching them play some  breathtaking badminton. Modern College too had a large pool of really good players. I had managed to grab a spot in the  college team but never played in the inter-university games. My only decent achievement was a runner-up in the singles final  of the college matches and the winner in doubles. But these were fairly easy games, and it was nowhere near state or national  level badminton.   Anyways, I hope we have another smashing game of badminton today!  I get the feeling, my blog here sounds more like a sports correspondent writing about Pros on the tour or about player  profiles or the like. But I guess I just love to write, and that's what blogging is all about. :)
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had never been to an American, rather, a Christian wedding before. Saturday, June 14th, gave me the opportunity. I had been invited to the wedding of Shaun and Carrie. Shaun, a fellow Computer Science student at CSU (who recently graduated), and I have been good friends ever since I came to CSU, nearly two years ago. Shaun is a Type-I diabetic himself, and he was the first person I talked to (apart from my family) when I was diagnosed on January 1, 2003. We became more close friends in the last 6 months. He is one of the nicest blokes I have ever met in my life. He graduated in May with a BS in Computer Science, whereas Carrie too graduated on the same day (that's neat!), with a BA in Music. Moreover, Carrie is a Ayurvedic Medicine practitioner as well as a Yoga Instructor. I was really looking forward to their wedding, and I am glad I was able to attend it yesterday. Incidentally, this was the very first wedding of a friend of mine, which I have attended. This is kind of interesting... Ketaki, another close friend at CSU, got married a few months back (the day when I landed in Pune from USA), but I could not attend her actual "wedding" and managed to make it to the reception for only a few minutes; so Ketaki, you do not qualify as the "first" one here. :)   The wedding was at Trinity Methodist Church at 2:15 pm, in Denver, CO, which is a 75-90 minute drive from Fort Collins. We (myself and some of Shaun's friends) arrived at the church around 30 minutes before the start of the ceremony. When we stepped inside the church, I quickly realized that I was the odd one out; I looked partly lost and partly in awe of the church and the surroundings. The scene was straight out of Hollywood and previously experienced only in movies and read about in books. However, I tried my best to look good. In the morning I wasn't sure exactly what would be appropriate to wear for the wedding. One of Shaun's friends told me that dressing up is not a big deal for an American wedding, unless they have explicit dress-code mentioned in the invitations, and he even said that there will be some people who will dress formally, while some would prefer to remain fairly casual. In the end, I guess I made the right decision to wear my suit, when I saw that almost everybody was dressed to perfection. Another reason for me being kind of lost, was that I was perhaps the only "single" guy out there, if one decided to leave the kids out, and assuming that all the pairs of "ladies & gentlemen" were actual 'couples'. Man, there cannot be a better wake up call! :D. This conclusion about being single was based on the fact that when we entered the church (in a queue), everyone was supposed to sign the guest book (elaborate!!), and after signing up and getting a handout of the marriage ceremony from the attendants, we had to go ahead and grab a seat for ourselves; and I observed that everybody who went ahead, except for me, went as a pair, escorting themselves :). The church seemed quite HUGE, atleast for me, and I have no idea how big they normally are. But  considering that this was right in the middle of downtown Denver, and that Shaun/Carrie's family had reserved this place a year ago, I guessed that this church should be really busy all year round. I did not waste time in clicking my camera away to glory for the church pictures, as they do not allow you to take pictures during the ceremony and I had no idea what was in store after it would be over.  The ceremony began with the "Processional", which is a hymn or other selection piece played or sung during the church procession (during the arrival of the bride, groom, and others), at the beginning of the service or ceremony in this case. The Processional was arranged for organ by Daniel Jones and was called as "Sinfonia and Toccata (L'Orfeo) Monteverdi". So far as I understood, Monteverdi is the name of the original Composer, and the rest is the name of the piece. :) It did create a very typical church atmosphere, and the classical music felt pretty good.  Shaun, the Groom, arrived first in the direction facing us (we were seated), which to me seemed not readily noticeable. (We entered through what I will call as the balcony, like in a cinema house). The Groom was the only person who arrived facing us, while all others arrived through the doors behind us. Don't know if this had some sort of significance. Next came the "Ring Bearer", one of Carrie's cousins - a cute little boy carrying the wedding ring (who was understandably confused and overwhelmed but was happy to grab the attention of the 200 people gathered). He was followed by two little 'Flower Girls', also Carrie's cousins, who spread rose petals on the white carpet for the Bride to walk on later. Then came the six Bridesmaids (cousins and friends of Carrie) and the six Groomsmen (friends of Shaun, brother of Carrie), in pairs. Again, I am not sure if the number six has a significance, or whether it depends on every wedding. (I have a lot of questions for Shaun, when I meet him next). Next to follow was the pair of Maid of Honor (college friend of Carrie) and Best Man (college friend of Shaun). All Bridesmaids and Groomsmen were dressed in the same fashion. Finally, Carrie, the Bride, wearing an amazing white wedding gown, was ushered in onto the white silk carpet laid down earlier. Well, I don't think I can describe the wedding gown here :p :), but it was stunning, and it only has to be seen in person if you have to realize its beauty. Carrie was the Cinderella of the hour.  The hour long ceremony that followed can briefly be described (in order) as follows:  - Call to Worship, by the wedding officiant - Meaning of Marriage, by the wedding officiant - Reading of Sonnet 116, Shakespeare, by Carrie's uncle - Statements of Intent - Blessings of the Couple - Reading of 1 Corinthians 13:4-13 (??), by Carrie's friend  :) - Vows (a short speech prepared by Shaun and Carrie themselves) - Exchange of Rings - Lighting of Unity Candle - "Sing to Me" a beautiful, original song, with guitar accompaniment, composed and performed by Carrie's friend for their wedding. - Prayer of Blessings - Lord's Prayer - Pronouncement of Marriage - Introduction - Recessional  (a hymn or musical piece that accompanies the exit of the clergy  and choir after a service or ceremony).  Most of the ceremony's proceedings were easy to follow and were explained in simple English :), although for me, its hard to describe them in writing, but hopefully you will get a fair idea from what I have posted.  And then, after the ceremony got over, it was time for the photo shoot. I again helped myself to a few pictures of the bride and groom.   Immediately following the wedding ceremony was the reception at The Pinnacle Club just across the street from the church. The reception was held on the topmost (38th) floor of this really tall building, I guess owned by Qwest, the phone company. The view from the top was spectacular. Denver's downtown might not be comparable to some of the other US cities on the East/West coast, but the building did provide a fantastic view of the other sky scrapers, and the Rocky Mountains in the background. Truly, the Rockies are the jewels of Colorado and the USA! Prior to the dinner, we hanged about around the bar and the guest room where everybody sipped on their drinks and had snacks, and mingled with other guests/friends.  The dinner thing was somewhat new to me. We had to pick individual cards that had our names written on it, plus the table number, and then that was to be our dinner table (elaborate, once again!!). From what I observed, there were 8 people assigned to one table. Again, the entire setup was Hollywood style, everything was set in perfection, very plush. At one point of time, it looked like I was at the Oscars..whee! :)) Dinner was shrimp cocktail, spinach salad, veggie lasagna, chicken in garlic mustard sauce, desserts,...and I-dont-recall-what-else. :) After the dinner, came the fun part. The couple cut their huge wedding cake, and everybody made a toast to them and their family members. A band played live music, and Shaun & Carrie danced to some romantic as well as foot-tapping numbers, amidst loud cheer from everybody. They did a great job! Other dances which followed were made up of pairs: father-daughter, son-mother, son--mother-in-law, daughter--father-in-law (and I guess every other combination). :) One of Shaun's friends mentioned to me that this was a really unique wedding, in terms of the magnitude of family members from both sides of the bride and groom, and that was great to see. It turned out to be a one big united family eventually. In the meanwhile, all the guests were in a party mood, and for the next 45 minutes, everybody was on the dance floor, yes, including me. :) However, after shaking a leg or two, I was back at my table, pondering over the fact that if anybody ever makes me dance during my reception, I would have to pull up my socks for sure (another wake up call for yours truly!!) :D. In between, there were short speeches from the Maid of Honor, the Best Man, and the fathers of Shaun and Carrie, a proud moment for them. I guess the party must have continued well into the night...I took some more pictures and it was almost time to go...  Shaun and Carrie make a great couple. Congratulations and Best Wishes to them!  Inside Story :p: They flew to Tanzania, Africa, for their honeymoon today. They will summit Mt. Kilimanjaro, the highest peak in Africa, which is close to 20,000 feet. I can't wait to hear from Shaun about their summit experience! Now that's the way to do it!
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      In the last couple of months, I have managed to catch up with my long lost hobby of reading some good fiction and non-fiction. When I plan to do serious reading, I can be a voracious reader. :) Of late, I have not really done that, but anyways...  If I have to choose between party hopping at the best hangout in town/watching a hit movie at a cool cinema house AND reading something interesting, I have no doubt I would go for the latter.  Coming back to the point, here are some non-fiction books that I recommend reading:  1. "It's Not About the Bike: My Journey Back to Life" by Lance Armstrong, 4-time winner of Tour De France  This is an out and out inspirational story about Lance's fight with cancer and how he overcame all odds to compete and win the greatest bicycle race in the world.  I was myself able to draw a fair bit of inspiration. :) Here is Amazon's review that best describes the book: "People around the world have found inspiration in the story of Lance Armstrong--a world-class athlete nearly struck down by cancer, only to recover and win the Tour de France, the multiday bicycle race famous for its grueling intensity. Armstrong is a thoroughgoingTexan jock, and the changes brought to his life by his illness are startling and powerful, but he's just not interested in wearing a hero suit. While his vocabulary is a bit on the he-man side (highest compliment to his wife: "she's a stud"), his actions will melt the most hard-bitten souls: a cancer foundation and benefit bike ride, his astonishing commitment to training that got him past countless hurdles, loyalty to the people and corporations that never gave up on him. There's serious medical detail here, which may not be for the faint of heart; from chemo to surgical procedures to his wife's in vitro fertilization, you won't be spared a single x-ray, IV drip, or unfortunate side effect. Athletes and coaches everywhere will benefit from the same extraordinary detail provided about his training sessions--every aching tendon, every rainy afternoon, and every small triumph during his long recovery is here in living color. It's Not About the Bike is the perfect title for this book about life, death, illness, family, setbacks, and triumphs, but not especially about the bike."  The next couple of books are related to mountaineering. My newly found craze and fascination for the subject was in a way responsible as to why I chose to read these books. The interesting fact about these books is that all are true and highly gripping stories, written and explained with intricate details. Morevoer, one does not need to have any knowledge about mountaineering to read them. Especially, the first book by Krakauer is quite amazing!  2. "Into Thin Air: A Personal Account of the Mount Everest Disaster" by Jon Krakauer.  Amazon's Review: Into Thin Air is a riveting first-hand account of a catastrophic expedition up Mount Everest. In March 1996, Outside magazine sent veteran journalist and seasoned climber Jon Krakauer on an expedition led by celebrated Everest guide Rob Hall. Despite the expertise of Hall and the other leaders, by the end of summit day eight people were dead. Krakauer's book is at once the story of the ill-fated adventure and an analysis of the factors leading up to its tragic end. Written within months of the events it chronicles, Into Thin Air clearly evokes the majestic Everest landscape. As the journey up the mountain progresses, Krakauer puts it in context by recalling the triumphs and perils of other Everest trips throughout history. The author's own anguish over what happened on the mountain is palpable as he leads readers to ponder timeless questions."  3.  "Epic: Stories of Survival from the World's Highest Peaks" - by Jon Krakauer, Greg Child (Contributor), Stephan Venables, Art    Davidson, David Roberts, Alfred Lansing, Eric Conger (Narrator), Rick Adamson (Narrator), Graeme Malcolm, Alan Sklar (Reader), Clint Willis (Editor), Stephen Venables.  Amazon's Review: "Some of the most exciting and harrowing mountaineering events ever chronicled are collected in Epic. From Jon Krakauer's solo ascent of Devil's Thumb in Alaska to John Climaco's account of being threatened by a homicidal Pakistani army officer in the Himalayas, these are stories of survival in nature's most inhospitable places."  The final two recommended reads are actually Marathi books. :) I used to read a lot of Marathi during my school and early college days. And I bought this one during my recent trip to India. Even if there might be English editions of these books, if you like reading Marathi, I can guarantee that English versions won't have the same punch as the Marathi ones.  4. "Shreeman Yogi" by Ranjit Desai.  This famous book is a bible in itself, with more than 1000 pages dedicated to Shivaji, the founder of the Maratha Empire in the mid-1600s. The book contains an absolutely fabulous description of the 1600s Maratha history, and includes every detail related to the birth, life and death of the great warrior. I hope I can finish reading this book sometime; it is so HUGE, the history is so complex, I am hardly half way into it at this point. But its worth it!!  5. "Panchavanna Kotinche Balee" by Gopal Godse.  This is a book written by the brother of Nathuram Godse, who assassinated Mahatma Gandhi. Gopal himself was one of the conspirators in Gandhi's assassination. The book is all about why and how the Godse brothers killed Mahatama Gandhi and also contains a long draft written by Nathuram himself, explaining his stance in the assassination. I chose this book plainly out of curiosity to know more about the the reasons and the plot behind the killing. I did not read this from a point of view of an Anti-Gandhi or a For-Gandhi (I prefer to act neutral when it comes to discussing politics). But anyways, it makes for an interesting read. I must say that some of the stuff described is pretty hard to comprehend, not only because of the high quality of Marathi used :), but also because of some of the historical ambiguities and controversial descriptions. Again, being history, that is bound to happen.  Happy Reading, folks!
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Namaskaar! A warm welcome to my new Heavenly Abode. :) Here I am, joining the blogger bandwagon. My purpose for creating this blog is not necessarily to write day in and day out or perhaps not even week in and week out, as most people like to do. But for the time being my short term goal is to put up what I would like to call as "My Diabetes Chronicles".  It has been a little less than 6 months since I was diagnosed with IDDM (Insulin Dependent Diabetes Mellitus), commonly known as Type-I Diabetes. Before I was diagnosed with diabetes, I was never a serious writer, but I have always had a habit of writing notes and maintaining a scratch pad (my version of a "diary"), although my frequent laziness to jot down my thoughts on paper did not allow me to get into any kind of routine writing. However, the last 6 months have changed this. Almost every single day as a diabetic has been pretty much unforgettable, and I have made it a point to record every minute detail that I have experienced and been through as a diabetes patient. At the risk of sounding overly emotional, my chronicles have helped me put some things into perspective and this has changed my life for the better. Through my chronicles, I hope to describe my experiences as a diabetic - both good and bad, some painful and agonizing moments, but which eventually led to a pretty successful achievement, and an immense feeling of self satisfaction, that surpassed every other feeling. My story would perhaps not be a whole lot different from fellow young adults who have also been recently diagnosed with diabetes. But personally, as silly as it may sound, diabetes has been a blessing in disguise for me. And nevertheless, there have been a lot of positive outcomes.  I guess, that is enough writing for this introductory blog. Keep checking this space, for my chronicle dispatches/archives.
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Watched "The Pirates of the Caribbean" on Sunday. Without doubt its my favorite movie of this year so far. Nope, no Khalid Mohammad talk and movie reviews today. I have seen three Hollywood movies on the big screen in the last three months. This feat HAS to go in the record books for me! I ain't no movie buff, but looks like times are changing. I think this was my first Johnny Depp movie. Didn't have the slightest of ideas that he was SO good (is he?). Yeah, impressed! The movie has amazing performances and in fact it was much better than I actually expected.  Another week begins, and work beckons (hmm not exactly). Have to make up lost ground on the work front in the last few days. The heat is on full throttle. Lethargy is creeping in. The summer is killing me. It went upto 103 the other day in FoCo, and 108 in Greeley.  Ye re ye re pavsaa...
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is nothing short of a dream come true. I can hardly believe I'll be going to the 2003 United States Grand Prix at Indianapolis, Indiana. I could not sleep well yesterday, I am still bleary-eyed. My eternal dream of watching a Formula One Race, Live, has finally turned into reality, and am I on cloud nine! The roar of those 800 BHP engines as they go from 0 to 300 kph within seconds (simply the greatest sound on this planet), the smell of the slick rubber thanks to the Bridgestones and the Michelins burning against the tarmac, a Ferrari and a McLaren driving in a perfect slipstream, the 7 second pit stops, those breathtaking passing manoeuvres, the chicanes and the spoon curves, the pit babes (whoa), and finally Schumi's trademark leap in the air on the podium followed by the burst of champagne; Aaah - its a heady feeling (forget the champagne) - I think I already see myself at the race, and as you know, I have even gone ahead and predicted the winner! And if the race itself was not enough, I also hope to be a part of the screaming and waving Tifosi. Tifosi (Italian for "to be a fan of") is a large group of die-hard Ferrari fans, and I suppose they are sorta similar to the Barmy Army, the fans of the English Cricket Team who follow the team everywhere they go. On second thoughts, I believe, Tifosi is also associated with Soccer, so its not really a Barmy Army, something not exclusive to F1, its just "Italian" perhaps. Not that I expect a lot of Tifosi at a US GP; for that I'll have to dream another dream - of going to the Italian GP at Monza someday. But I am gonna paint myself "Scarlet Red" and root for the Scuderia anyways!  To top it all, this is probably the closest championship in the past few years, with atleast 6 drivers competing for the world champion honors. The Prancing Horse looks formidable as ever, but BMW Williams is looking in great shape especially with the unpredictable duo of Montoya and Schumacher Junior, and then the Woking oufit - Ron Dennis, Adrian Newey, DC and Kimi are capable of delivering the goods anytime. The US GP is the penultimate race before the drivers and the engineers have their final tasks cut out at the Japanese GP at Suzuka, and in all probability it looks like it will all go down to the wire at Japan. This could make the visit to Indianapolis even more special, drivers competing for points and places, and I expect a lot of surprises, even if they aren't pleasant.  I hope Ferrari reserve their best for Indianapolis. Good Luck Schuey, Rubens, Todt, and Brawn! - but since I got to be politically correct, may the best driver and team win!  I can hardly wait...it does not get better than this.  I'll sign off with a Knopfler classic - it has racing as the main theme. Can somebody please ask Bernie Ecclestone to make this an official song of Formula One Racing? Okay, forget the fact that its not really "Formula One" type. But is there a better one that I don't know of?   SPEEDWAY AT NAZARETH    Artist: Mark Knopfler     Album: Sailing To Philadelphia     After two thousand came two thousand and one To be the new champions we were there for to run From springtime in Arizona 'til the fall in Monterey And the raceways were the battlefields and we fought 'em all the way  Was at Phoenix in the morning I had a wake-up call She went around without a warning put me in the wall I drove Long Beach, California with three cracked vertebrae And we went on to Indianapolis, Indiana in May  Well the Brickyard's there to crucify anyone who will not learn I climbed the mountain to qualify went flat through the turns But I was down in the might-have-beens and an old pal good as died And I sat down in Gasoline Alley and I cried  Well we were in at the kill again on the Milwaukee Mile And in June up in Michigan we were robbed at Belle Isle Then it was on the Portland, Oregon for the G.I. Joe And I'd blown off almost everyone when my motor let go  New England, Ontario we died in the dirt Those walls from mid-Ohio to Toronto they hurt So we came to Road America where we burned up the lake But at the speedway at Nazareth I made no mistake 
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love automobiles, cars rather, have always liked them ever since I was a toddler (atleast that's what family members tell me). Call it some kind of fetish acitvity or whatever, but it didnt take long for me to rip open every hood and bonnet of my toy cars, and frisk out every minute part of the little assembly that they were made up of. Hell no! I was no budding engineer, and fortunately my parents quickly realized that there were no "creative" or "innovative" intentions and urges behind playing a bit of havoc with my toys; but "destructive" in the absolute sense of the word! Well, my friends would vouch that I still haven't changed! The so called destructive nature still remains one of the essential factors in my life, but then I have mellowed down quite a bit, and would probably break a few glasses and mugs in the kitchen (Excuse me dear Joshi brothers), not more than that, certainly not cars!   This fear of my childhood habits was constantly ringing in my mind, as I ventured out today, to get behind the steering wheel of a real car, the very first time in my life. I find it highly surprising myself, that I did not care to learn driving a four wheeler to this day, given the fact about my passion for cars, not exactly cars in general, but atleast considering an avid F1 Racing fan that I am. But honestly, I couldnt have got any lazier. If it had not been for my temporary instruction permit (that will expire soon in a month or so), I would have probably never thought of seriously learning driving, when that's one thing that probably sits somewhere between the top 3 list of "To-Do" acitivties for anybody who wants to get to the United States. I think I always wanted to drive a car, unlike those who prefer to be navigators and enjoy being driven around, and it seemed exciting watching others around me hopping into the driver's seat and driving long distances with consummate ease. Somehow, I was never hell-bent upon learning to drive (and driving to learn!). Driving will probably join the list of quite a few other things which seem to happen late with me...a pretty late start, but a start anyways. "Shubasya Shigram" as we call it in Aamcha Marathi.  Yes, its an immense relief, finally, to have broken my own shackles, and taken the first step towards driving a four wheeler. Hurrah! I not only managed to steer clear of destroying anything on the roads, I think I did a fairly decent job as a rookie driver. Well obviously I was taken to a neighborhood where I could not really get any chance of destroying anything in my path, as nothing came in my way and my driving, except for some wierd intermittent mental illusions of cars flying past me that I had on occasions (no, my sugars were perfectly normal)! Having said that, I am in no way tooting my own "horn" (Haha...pun very much intended...but you know what, I actually did bang the horn once, and the instructor next to me almost jumped in his seat!!). I suppose, I have quite a long way to go before I can master the steering wheel. I started off well, almost got over confident to be frank and messed with many of the driving basics. For a few minutes, I lost my composure, and I was all over the place. I tried to appear as if I was unflappable, but in vain. I kicked myself and gradually regained my lost balance.   I had BIG problems when it came to manoeuvring the turns, especially where you stop at STOP signs and make turns. I managed to get the 90 degree turns correct only once or twice (although not really "copy book" stuff). The most intriguing thing I practically found out was how people can manage to turn well and accelerate even better, both at the same times!!? Its like accelerating and turning in a fairly swift, steady yet calm motion, just as you apply butter to bread in one neat stroke (Wow, is that really a good way to compare..??..I doubt, but forgive my spontaineity once more). I flunked on this part of my driving. When I thought I managed to accelerate pretty well on sharp turns/curves, I either achieved an "understeer" or "oversteer" because of lack of good control on the steering (Yeah, Yeah - Wait till you hear more F1 "lingo" in my future blogs!). And then on occasions I managed to hit the kerbs extremely well ("smooth turns" that is), but then either went too hard on the pedal or so slow that my car barely crawled out of the turn. It was a Plymouth by the way, very nice car; old one, but seemed to tug along nicely. My top speed for the day was 35, when the limit was 25, and if not for my instructor calming me down continously, my sudden surge of adrenalin would have been responsible for not only some destruction, but also a ticket on the way home for me. I wish I had the chance to check my sugars during one of these "surges". I can bet my glucometer would have conked off!  As with many rookie drivers, I made the mistake of "fighting" the car, trying and pushing too hard at times, when all I needed to do was to be more laidbackish in my driving...do the simple things right. Its tough though, I don't think driving is that simple, as to manage to relax in your very first driving lessons; its like any other art, easy to understand theoretically, but try to put it into practice and you know how it becomes a different ball game altogether. I learnt one big lesson - more than "driving", its about controlling the vehicle. I would love to try a stick shift, but I can already see how much efforts I would have to put in to master the manual transmission, the late learner that I call myself. I am very much optimistic though, and the future does not look bad. Driving's addictive. I did not want to get out of the car even after an hour of toil under the opressive Colorado heat.  Overall, I was inconsistent but after an hour of twists and turns, I emerged out of the car alive and well and was pretty satisfied with my early lessons.  Just you wait till I buy a car for myself someday...I am gonna HIT the road or what!  I DO NOT BELIEVE all the Schumachers, Coulthards, and Montoyas driving at speeds of 300 kph with a killer g-force of upto 6 or 7g. These men are UNREAL, they are DOWNRIGHT CRAZY; they must be robots, I bet they cannot drive! It just seems humanely impossible to me. If I have the audacity to talk of under and over steering at 25 mph, care to spare a thought for these men, driving a 600 kilogram, 800 BHP and 3000 CC machine, that goes 0 to 60 in the blink of any eye (under 3 seconds); with  seemingly ridiculous ease?!
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      In the past few months, I have tried to keenly observe myself deep within, and have managed to put a lot of efforts into putting a lot of things into perspective; the things I do, the things I talk, the things I read, the things I hear and listen to; well - absolutely whatever that can practically stimulate (and stretch) my thought processes. No, if you thought I have just finished reading one of those American "self-help" and "self-mastery" books, you are wrong. No way am I doing this to make myself a better person, as you know, I already am! Jokes apart, whether my efforts directly or indirectly affect my personality or not, is not much of my concern, but the point here is that the mere "thought" of "thinking" sort of gives me the kicks! I cannot imagine the oh so precious minutes and hours I have lost in my life due to this "mental preoccupation" of mine. My personal feeling is that a lot of people who consider themselves fortunate enough to have known me better, seem to think that I "think" too much. And lo behold! If you happen to be the one who felt the same, you can consider yourself pretty much bang on target with your "thoughts" about me.  Thinking has become a routine way of life, sometimes helping me solve umpteen daily problems, but which also happens to be an easy way out for me to distract myself from doing other routine activities. A perfect example of late is the precious time I have spent "thinking" about music and about the books I am reading, some of the time which I could have very well utilized to do some useful research as a computer scientist (!?), atleast for the benefit of mankind (read: my adviser), if not for myself. Yes, the phrase "thinking about music" and not just listening, is one that I have recently coined for myself. Before you get a chance to read about my my ever-growing musical manias in one of my future blogs, you will perhaps want to (unfortunately) tread your way through torturous blogs like these. Seriously speaking, if I could write something so spontaneously, then it has to be this particular blog. Partly, because I am done with my "research" deadline for tonight, and since the near future looks exciting on the research front, I am unashamedly hitting the keyboard hard and subjecting folks to endless torture. I am repeatedly asking myself: Did I ever get so spontaneous?..Not Really, Not that I remember! *Sighs* - I wish I could write my exams even half as spontaneously as this blog and that too, without too much "thinking". Alas! Okay, I promise to take it easy. And agreed! I also sound a tad "philosophical" here, atleast the initial part of this blog appears to be like it, or whatever purists wish to call it. But that ain't quite true, even though I see a few raised eye-brows already.  I have begun reading Ayn Rand stuff of late ("The Fountainhead" to be specific), but hold on; give me a few more weeks before you and I start discussing objectivity and philosophy (in case you are interested, that is). When it comes to Rand's carefully carved out yet immensely strong characters, I do not wish to take the risk and jump the gun too soon and offer my expert comments and opinions yet. I have to admit though, that it's a terrific read; the first couple hundred pages have been one of the best I have ever put my hands (and mind) on. Rand's style is not only highly unique but considering the timeline of the book (1942?), it is even more spellbinding. It has to be read with a certain frame of mind though, only then will it appeal to the reader in an appropriate way. Again, the word "appropriate" is so delicate here. I have talked to quite a few people, who have read this book long before I even knew such a book existed, and everybody seems to have contrasting opinions. And my friend, therein lies the secret! I know of no book which holds so much substance in the characters it potrays. And the mere fact that this so called "substance", appeals differently to different people, is interesting in itself! This is no "what-will-happen-next" kind of novel. I do not have the exact words as yet to really categorize and sum up the book in a nice way (talk about "spontaniety"!!), but as of now, I can make some of my claims anyways. It looks like poeple either tend to appreciate this book a LOT (to the extent of it being HIGHLY INFLUENTIAL, to say the least), or they feel its almost TRASHY (to the extent that people seem to lose their basic thirst for "reading" books after reading it)!. Now both seem to be extremes for me. But since the book is enough fodder for my "thinking" grey cells, I still love it, nevertheless. Again, Rand's writing is special, in the sense that the book actually gained more recognition and popularity in the modern times, from whatever I hear and understand. That's because even though it was written in the old times, it identifies itself with the present so well. It almost seems like Ayn Rand is prophesying how future generations of mankind will come into existence, even though fiction works like these are more or less on the unrealistic side. Rand writes these different shades of characters and leaves the readers themselves to interpret them. To me, the way she describes her "philosophy" through her characters, without actually making the reader get into the "theory of philosophy", is awesome. Since the reader is free to draw his/her own conclusions, (and could perhaps essentially carve out his/her own philosophy through the book), it makes for a truly wonderful read.  One thing's for sure. You will most probably yearn for your pillow and hit the bed pretty soon, if you begin reading this after a long hard day at work. (*Sheepish grin* - 'cause I did, after reading the Intro!). But the stubborn reader that I am, I'm glad I diligently stuck to the book.  I have just realized that I have missed my dinner insulin shot tonight - *Kicks himself*. Research, followed by Blogging, backed up by my concept of "thinking", can be a deadly combination. And if I continue my spontaneous writings like today, without disciplining myself and my diet, I might soon need an insulin drip or something, to keep myself aware of this hormonal need. But since I can proudly thump my chest and say that "Diabetes meri mutthi mein hain", I need not be alarmed. I almost forgot that I am happily neglecting my series of diabetes chronicles. Its time I posted the second chapter.  Didn't a Santa or Banta someone Singh write when asked about the past tense of the word 'think': "I thought, I thought, I thought and then I wrote 'thunk'"!...?  So much for the torture...
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      No, these aren't really my words (although it feels great to be back from a brief two week hiatus and typing away to glory once again). Its the T-850 (a.k.a. Terminator) - Arnold Schwarzenegger in "Terminator 3: Rise Of The Machines", released last week, and Part III in the "Terminator" movie series, which to me, revolutionized sci-fi flicks years ago; the first time in 1984 ("The Terminator"), and then the quite unforgettable Part II in 1991 ("Terminator 2: Judgement Day"). A lot has changed in these 20 years, EXCEPT for Arnold - the cyborg action hero, the man, the machine, the terminator.  A guy who wins hands down when it comes to delivering (or call it blurting out) these words with the most stone-faced of expressions you will ever see, and muscles taut to the extent that they make a cracking noise everytime he speaks (and make no mistake, it does not look ridiculous for Arnold, as it does for all those Akshay Kumars and Sunil Shettys). Wait, this is just the bonus package that comes along with (arguably) the best male physique on this planet. If God (or "Human Resistance" to put in James Cameron's words! :)) created Terminator in 2064 (or was it 2032?), it would be a reincarnation of Arnold himself, there is not even a hint of doubt. Arnold is not the one who simply physically towers above everybody else, but there is this amazing streak of ruthlessness and sheer dominance in the way he moves, the way he talks, the way he holds those seemingly toy rocket launchers in his iron hands, the way he puts on his goggles, the way he rides his other toys (read: all the Harley Davidsons, Sports cars, Vans/SUVs and Firetrucks), the way his CPU listens to commands and he in turn interprets them in words, the list goes on...and there's definitely a lot of "muscle" in all that he does (yeah, pun intended).   In contrast, the Terminatrix (a.k.a. T-X: Kristanna Loken) seems like a chick model in reality, only to be converted to an unstoppable mean machine on screen, albeit pretty successfully, I would say! Fortunately, the makers of Terminator have not done anything drastically different from the plot of the original Terminator movies, as opposed to "The Matrix Reloaded" folks who did helluva lot to increase the complexity of the plot and make die-hard viewers/fans spend sleepless nights pondering over mysterious "oracles", until perhaps Part III unravels the secret mystery in November 2003. :) Well, in reality, there are no comparisons to draw between the two movies; each is a great one to watch on the big screen on its own. But the truth is that Terminator is a pretty much no-nonsense movie, you do not need to apply your sci-fi skills or make your grey cells work harder. You do not need to worry about who wrote the "source code" and how, the gory details behind the emergence of the "matrix" and all those hard and soft(ware) abstracts, no matter how hunky-dory eventually they may be! Even better, perhaps, Terminator doesn't even have any out-of-the-world revolutionary visual effects if you compare it to its Part II predecessor. I know, nobody would have complained if they would have come up with better computer wizardry, but Terminator scores well in the sense that it does not stray away from the basic plot: Machines vs. Human Resistance, although in the practical sense of the movie, it's still a battle between - One highly sophisticated and potent machine Vs. Another, less sophisticated (but-who-cares!) machine. Terminator does not potray irrelevant and ludicrous emotional outbursts, unwarranted average-american love and sex scenes, and the run-of-the-mill action/violence, some of which unfortunately even the Reloaded guys could not resist to show in their Part II adventure. Neither is the movie stretched w.r.t the playing time, nor in terms of the overall storyline. The entire length of the movie has a nice consistent flow to it, its neat!  Agreed, any discerning eye will find a few glaring erroneous bugs in this movie too, one notably being the car/truck chase involving the Terminators, Mr. John Connor (Nick Stahl) and one Miss. Kate Brewster (Claire Danes). As much as you will get lost in this amazing chase (drive safely when you go home after the movie!), which can be second only to the freeway chase of Reloaded, (really, no room for comparisons again), it is mind boggling to see both Connor and Brewster escaping the T-X "unscathed" (Brewster's hair and skin is in flawless condition even after the most horrifying of rides you can experience sitting in the back of a rickety old truck!...atleast Connor is shown to be hobbling...they could have asked Brewster to do the same! :p;) ). But C'mon! Spare a thought...there is a lot more to this movie than just finding faults over this particular incident, and sci-fi flicks like these deserve to have some loop-holes!  I refrain from writing complete movie reviews. Yahoo, IMDB et al already do it for you, and they are good enough.    urlLink http://movies.yahoo.com/movies/feature/terminator.html   urlLink http://us.imdb.com/Title?0181852   But don't go by reviews if you are a Terminator fan. Don't even waste a moment; go and watch it on the big screen!  . . . .  And then, apart from a memorable trip to the Water World in Denver on the 4th of July, nothing special to mention about for now.  Let me get back to some research activities...;) Bientot!
      
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        >>  urlLink [Chapter 3 - The Sweet Legacy]     Copyright 2003     All characters in these chronicles are real, and any resemblance to any living person, is entirely intentional and purely marked by full consciousness of the nature and effects of the events being chronicled.     "Diseases are the tax on pleasures"    - John Ray 1627-1705, British Naturalist    January 10, 2003   The day I began my life as an IDDM patient will be unforgettable. Although Dr. Gokhale almost confirmed me as a Type-I diabetic, he, more than anybody else, still had every reason to believe that it was important for me to consult a specialist doctor, specifically speaking - an  urlLink endocrinologist . He referred me to Dr. Shrirang Godbole, an endocrinologist sub-specializing in diabetes mellitus. Things had to be done quickly if I were to bring my blood glucose levels under control, and if that wasnt easy enough a task initially for a newly-diagnosed patient, there was more pressure to follow - I had only 15 more days with me before I was to leave for Colorado, and this is practically very little time to receive any form of diabetes education, leave alone grasping every bit of it and acting accordingly to get your sugars down.  I spent close to 4 hours with Dr. Godbole, and without a hint of over-exaggeration, it was the toughest tte--tte with a doctor I have ever had. First of all, he did not waste much time in declaring me a Type-I patient, based on all the medical information I provided, and that effectively put to rest any more speculations on the type of diabetes I was suffering from. In a sense, I was almost relieved; there were no more shades of doubt. I can still recollect, although a bit vaguely, the first few statements that Dr. Godbole made. There was no affectation in his voice; he seemed to me, to be one of those doctors who usually do not mince words to state the obvious medical facts. There was a subtle ruthlessness with which he diagnosed me; he spoke with utter non-chalance, but displayed panache and supreme confidence at the same time. I remember him asking me - Do you wish to live the next 15 years?. As rhetorical as a question this may seem, I still had to blurt out a Yes, (I believe I was expected to), and considering my emotional state of mind during that period of time, those words stung me alright. Here comes the taskmaster..., I thought.  The next few hours were like sitting through a crash course in one single go; the course primarily dealing with imparting whatever little diabetes education and awareness that was possible in the short time, and then mentally preparing me for the possible big hurdles ahead as an IDDM patient, especially since in a matter of 15 days I was to start dealing with it all by myself, independently, in an environment pretty much alien to me. I had no time to experiment with different forms of treatment, which I would have normally undergone, if not for my trip back to the USA on the 25th, and an insulin intensive treatment was the only form of survival. Fortunately, I wasn't really a novice when it comes to knowing about diabetes; it pretty much runs in our family and I had a fair idea about the complications. The fact that I call this as fortunate wasn't much of a comforting factor at that point of time, but I was certainly not short of resources (in the form of close family members and friends) who would help me to tackle this disease. My side of the conversation with Dr. Godbole was quite shamefully, limited only to frequent head-nodding, and an occasionally interspersed Yes and No. I was not only expected to admit that I understood every word the doctor spoke, but also throw questions at him. The hardest part to grasp was the  urlLink Time Activity Profiles  of insulin  which I would realize later on, was an extremely important aspect in case of Type-I patients to effectively achieve safe levels of blood glucose, and a fact, which if not understood well, could play havoc with your sugars -  urlLink Hypoglycaemia  (or Hypoglycemia) being a prime example. A time activity profile indicates how and at what time insulin starts acting in your body to control your sugars, based on when you deliver yourself an insulin shot, how much you deliver, and the type of insulin you are using. It appeared that there was far too information to know and awfully less time to think over it or discuss it with others. If I am asked to summarize what I learnt in those tense moments at the clinic, I would hardly be able to answer. Nevertheless, I was brainstormed on all the ABCs: diets, exercise, insulin (the buzz word for a Type-I), and taking care 24 hours a day - 7 days a week, plus a host of other encyclopedic information and terms pertaining to diabetes.  I left the clinic in a daze with another sleepless night awaiting me.   January 11, 2003   I was prescribed the premixed  urlLink Humulin 70/30 insulin , manufactured by  urlLink Eli Lilly and Co.  using  urlLink recombinant DNA technology (rDNA) . All I can say is hats off to the biochemistry.  I had to administer two shots daily, one before breakfast in the morning (22 units), and one before dinner at night (14 units). A person from Eli Lilly came home to demonstrate the use of the  urlLink Insulin Pen . The pen is a truly remarkable advancement for delivering insulin and gone are the days when people had no option but to resort to painful ways of delivering a shot using a syringe and a vial. The lighweight, pocket-sized, disposable pens come prefilled with insulin and use a fine needle. The pens function almost similar to fountain pens filled with ink. Once you master the technique of delivering shots all by yourself, it is virtually painless.  The morning of January 11, I prepared myself for the first insulin shot of my life. Although the propsect of administering a shot on your own is not the most welcoming, having seen my dad doing it every day for quite a few years, I tried to stay calm. The shot has to be delivered in the subcutaneous layer (and not intra-veinous or intra-muscular), either on the abdomen, thighs or arms. I dialed the dose of 22 units on the pen, but hesitated when I pinched whatever little skin/flesh I had on my abdomen. After a momentary case of nerves and shakiness, I gathered my might and injected the needle, pushed the plunger, felt the 22 units surge under the flesh, released the skin, held the needle for 10 more seconds and then removed it. That's the way you do it, and surprisingly, I did it perfect the first time. Better still, there was absolutely no pain. Easy, I thought. But not quite. This was only occasion #1. The problem when you initially deliver shots if you are insulin-dependent, is that you have lost lots of weight, fat that is. Finding an appropriate place on your body (a fleshy area) for the shot is a job in itself. Its easy to make a mistake, and inject in a vein or an area close to a vein. Moreover, the injection site needs to be roated at all times, because injecting at the same spot repeatedly, causes tissue damage. I realized that I was quickly running out of areas with enough fat on my body, and experiencing pain thus became a routine, almost a necessity for getting accustomed to more pain. And then delivering a near perfect shot is impossible at all times, what with nerves and shakiness adding to the woes in the first couple of weeks. I still run out of injection sites on my body, but then pain is the last thing I worry about. As a matter of fact, after close to 8 months of injections twice a day, and making almost 500 tiny little holes in the skin, each of 29-gauge thickness, pain is really not a feeling anymore. Quite amusing, isn't it?    Insulin for Dummies     Disclaimer: I provide this information only for the insanely curious. This information might not be 100% accurate and is solely based on my knowledge and understanding. Although I am a self-confessed and self-proclaimed doctor for my diabetes, I would advise you to be your own doctor with yours, and not base any critical decisions on my write ups. Adjusting the dose of insulin is no child's play and you don't want to regret until its too late.   70/30 in simple terms means combining or mixing two types of insulin and using it as one, to control blood sugars over a longer period of time (generally over 12 to 15 hours). The 70% component (human insulin isophane suspension) is a cloudy/milky suspension and is the intermediate-acting insulin, whereas the 30% component (human insulin injection) is a clear liquid and serves as the short-acting insulin. The two are in a premixed form and appear uniformly cloudy similar to skimmed milk.     Short-Acting or The 30% Component   The onset of the short-acting insulin begins 30 minutes after the shot is delivered, which means it takes 30 minutes for the 30% component to start working. Technically speaking, short-acting insulin enters the blood stream within 30 to 45 minutes. For those who wonder why I insist on eating a meal (breakfast/dinner) 30 minutes after injecting myself, this explains why. The peak action is observed between 2 to 3 hours, which is when the insulin has its strongest effect. Thus the 30% component controls my post-breakfast blood glucose. It generally stays effective for a duration of 3 to 6 hours.     Intermediate-Acting or The 70% Component   In case of the 70% component, the onset of action is 2 to 4 hours, i.e. the intermediate-acting insulin enters the blood stream within 2 to 4 hours. It reaches its peak anytime between 4 to 10 hours after the injection. Now this explains how the 70% controls my post-prandial (post-lunch) sugars, since I have my lunch 4 to 5 hours after delivering the shot (or say 4 hours after breakfast), and that is when its peak action starts. And since intermediate-acting insulin stays effective for 10 to 16 hours, it also controls my blood sugars in the evening (supper), until dinner. By the time I take my dinner, the morning insulin dose has almost lost all its effect, and hence the need for another shot pre-dinner to control my post-dinner as well as night time and early morning sugars. But since more than half the time between dinner and breakfast next morning, is spent sleeping, I needed a lesser dose (14 units). And whereas the morning dose covered my three meals: breakfast, lunch, as well as supper; the pre-dinner dose would have to cover only one meal (dinner).  Although these time activity ranges seem too wide, they have been based on clinical trials and prove that insulin time activity profiles show large variations with respect to the intensity and timing. Hence the peak action and effectiveness for a person using the same insulin could be entirely different. These variations are based on the amount of dose, site of injection, the person's physical activity, temperature etc. There is an interesting bit of fact about diabetics facing serious medical problems if they spend a lot of time in hot tubs or saunas or if they indulge in excessive physical activity with an incorrect insulin dose and insufficient amount of food intake. I quote a paragraph from an article that was recently published on the  urlLink American Diabetes Association  website:   When your whole body gets overheated, your heart tries to increase the blood flow to your skin to get rid of some of the extra heat you have absorbed from the water or steam. If you use insulin to control your diabetes, you may find that this increased blood flow to the fat (where you inject your insulin) increases the rate at which the insulin is absorbed. So a dose of a longer-acting insulin that is intended to last throughout the night will be absorbed much more rapidly. This causes low blood sugars during the hours after you get out of the tub.     Grappling with the Hypo and the Hyper    Insulin successfully brought my blood sugars down to acceptable levels, if not in the desired range at all times. I had to grapple with once in a while high sugars (hyper) as well as low sugars (hypo). I checked my blood sugars using the glucometer on January 13, the first time since I went on insulin. My Fasting sugar level in the morning read a perfectly normal 79. Was I thrilled? There was no doubt that insulin WOULD work, it HAD to; but to get to know the exact results is even better. It's like getting a stamp of approval, and indicated that I was on the right track. But before I got a chance to celebrate an early victory, I fared poorly in the post-lunch test on the same day. My sugar read 319, and I was back to my usual ritual of retrospection. Did I get my diet wrong? Did I administer the correct dose? I did not really press my panic buttons, and after consulting my doctors, I was told that the body may react unusually during the first few days until it adapts itself to the insulin, a man-made chemical, literally. The body's natural reaction is to ring alarm bells when it finds something un-natural in its system. In my case the un-natural substance was Humulin 70/30, and the body doesn't care the least, even if it's been processed using rDNA technology! Its job is to fight any intruder in its system. The alarm bells first appeared in the form of a mild headache, and when pain killers proved worthless I could do nothing but wait, till the throbbing headache died down automatically about 3 days later. Those restless days and nights would be etched forever in memory.  If the human body is a miracle, a supernatural, at times inexplicable phenomenon, then its an understated fact. Try churning up any adjectives in the English language that are synonymous to the ones I have described, and they would probably still fail to sum up how the human body really is! When I run out of real good adjectives I usually tend to bring God into the picture. The human body is God! How's that? Nope, I don't think that's a satisfying explanation, so I won't play with this anymore.  Within 4 days, my body seemed to have realized that Eli Lilly's Humulin 70/30 didn't mean any harm at all, and the best (if not the safest) bet for all the countless cells, molecules and organs was to accept and welcome this frequent visitor. Does it get more amusing?  Along with frequent bouts of high sugars (theoretically not exactly hyper), I had a couple of scary moments when I went low on my sugar levels. The first few experiences of hypoglycemia (low blood sugars) are terrible, but I consider them as experiences worth learning from, if you have to be prepared to face tougher situations and complications involving diabetes. Twice, it was real hypoglycemia, whereas on one occasion it was about my mind games, a false alarm, but creepy anyways.  Once, I woke up at 2:30 am in the middle of the night, with a cold sweat all over my body and feeling shaky, dizzy and weak, with a slight piloerection (erection of the hair), and in a confused state of mind. All classic symptoms of hypoglycemia. The symptoms do not look serious at first glance, but a prolonged condition (for say 30-45 minutes) can prove utterly dangerous. It was a real wake up call so to speak. However, within minutes, I grabbed some sugar and glucose biscuits, and was back to normal. Hypoglycemia is alright if you are able to react quickly and help yourself or if you have somebody around who knows how to treat it. The second hypo occurred during the daytime, 2 to 3 hours after I took my morning breakfast and although even with similar symptoms it appeared less dangerous, my sugar level read a meagre 56. I cannot recall why it occurred after eating my morning meal, but I assume it to be one of those weird things associated with diabetes that are impossible to explain scientifically or even practically. Hypoglycemia cannot get more treacherous if you have an atrociously low sugar but still hardly feel hypoglycemic. It's like being in a state of hypo without actually feeling it, and then by the time you feel it, you might not have any time to react, because of damage to the brain and the nerves. The brain ceases to function like normal. The speed with which this occurs is quite unbelieveable, and I say this from experience. Theoretically, a sugar level below 40 can be fatal, depending on how strong the individual is, although I have read about people bouncing back alive and well from levels as low as 20. Sounds almost unreal more than scary, but is true alright. People with diabetes for many years can develop something called as Hypoglycemia Unawareness, and its the worse thing to happen. A person loses consciousness without even knowing that his/her blood sugars are dropping. Perhaps the only way to treat this is by quickly delivering a Glucagon shot on time. Glucagon injection instantly raises sugar levels if the person is unable to swallow food.  During the case of the false alarm, which was more of a psychological hypo, I again woke up sometime in the night with a cold sweat. I checked my sugar instantly, and although I do not have it on record, it was well withing normal. Hypoglycemia was freaking me out and it was almost playing on my mind all the time, like a nightmare, robbing me of a good night's sleep. I felt jittery for no genuine reasons. It was a paranoia of some kind.    The Tax on Simple Pleasures    Diabetes put enormous pressure on me in the last 15 days I spent in India. I tried to hide it, but it became more or less apparent. I spent countless sessions with family members, discussing every issue related to the disease, read diabetes books, and tried to keep myself upbreast of diabetes news and information. I was hoping to give myself a break from sitting in front of a computer during these 3 weeks, but I wasn't to be spared. The Internet, obviously, happened to have a wealth of information on diabetes, and I began digging deep. I indugled in numerous chat sessions with my good friend Shaun, himself a Type-I diabetic here in Colorado, in order to get a feel of life as a diabetic in the United States, and without his help and tremendous support, things wouldn't have worked out so smoothly here for me. I spent most of the evenings with friends, and although I had quite a few reunions with old pals, I hated myself for not being as cheerful as I would have liked to be with them. I hated when people came to visit me, instead of me visiting them. My mind wandered towards the prospect of facing tougher hurdles as a student and a diabetic, all by myself, at Colorado State. Nightmares continued. Following a strict diet plan was adding fuel to fire. I would have loved to help myself with home-made delicacies and sweets and paying a visit to all the popular food joints in Pune, but I managed some leeway very rarely. The ups and downs in sugar levels didn't help, and that forced me to cut down on a lot of food.  Instead of the vacation serving as a well-deserved break from the gruelling semesters at CSU, I spent most of my time thinking about what the next semester would have in store for me. I was swamped with information on diabetes, but wasn't exactly high on confidence when I tried to apply it to my own benefit.    On the Road Ahead...    Believe me, hypoglycemia is horrifying, and learning insulin time activity profiles to utmost perfection is perhaps the first and the most vital step to avoid one. It took me months to figure out how my body adjusted to the type of insulin I was on, and also to unravel the somewhat mysterious pattern of how and when daily acitivites and meals affected my blood sugar levels. Understanding your diabetes on your own and taking actions accordingly is a painstaking and extremely frustrating process but its one of the things that I have probably done better than anything else at any point in my life. I had no idea that living in the United States as a diabetic would be an enitrely different ballgame when compared to how I tried to tackle it in India for the few days I spent there on vacation. The difference lies culturally, technologically, financially, apart from the obvious huge gap in the general lifestyle and eating habits. Arguably the biggest factor is the difference in diabetes care and treatment in both countries, especially for IDDM patients. After 3.5 weeks of perhaps not-the-best-of vacations in Pune, India, I was all set to be my own doctor in Fort Collins, Colorado.   Sure, more Testing times lay ahead for me!    >>  urlLink [Chapter 3 - The Sweet Legacy] 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is not really worth a blog. But before I publish Chapter 2 of my Diabetes Chronicles, thought of a real quick post. I am working on the next chapter, a little bit everyday, and won't release it till I polish it. I think I am getting in a rut with my writing; pardon my audacity if you will, to call this as my "writing" in the first place, but nevertheless. I get the feeling that my spontaneity is affecting my writing, so to speak, so I plan to write and re-write and re-write till I give up. (Sid, I am trying to take a leaf out of your books, so get ready to share the blame if I fail in my quests). I think I am trying to make my blogs sound more like "my writing", rather than just day-in-day-out posts, although I don't guarantee that "more careful" writings will ever make me lose my spontaneity or will make my future blogs any better reads. But an effort's being made to try and develop a style here. I have to admit, blogging has sort of whetted my appetite for writing, a hobby that I sometimes regret not having taken seriously, years ago.  I tried to Bend it like Beckham on Saturday, while playing soccer at the University Village Olympics (!!). I think even Sid did. And we ended up cooling our heels, literally! We both twisted our feet badly, in almost the same exact manner, just a different leg. Worse, as a team of soccer novices, compared to our opponents - yours truly shamefully being the #1 novice - we were thrashed in the final by some well seasoned players. Well, we played just two matches, and although we won the first - technically a semifinal - the final was the soundest thrashing I have ever received in any form of a game I have ever played. I think I seem to care about the most insignificant of games I have ever played, and then a sport like soccer, which I don't even remember playing since passing out of school. Could barely walk for half a day and the pain was excruciating. I better stick to badminton.  And then, I invited Shaun and Carrie for dinner on Sunday. Spent almost the whole day/afternoon cleaning and cooking. To top it all, my destructive nature, which happened to be on an indefinite break, HAD to creep up at the wrong time. I made some last minute groceries in the afternoon and as soon as I started making Ras Malai, spilled the boiling half n half milk. Time to mop and clean more, and then another quick rush to the grocery to get another half n half. By 5 pm, the alarms went off (not really), and dinner was ready. Made Pav Bhaji, Veg Biryani, Ras Malai and Salad ("Koshimbir", really). The rest of the evening was a "gappa" session with Shaun and Carrie, hearing stories about their honeymoon trip to Mt. Kilimanjaro/Tanzania, and watching their huge collection of trip pictures and video clippings. There cannot be a better honeymoon, and I can't wait for mine to happen.  It's Monday; the weekend exhaustion is starting to show up at the wrong time - for a change, not getting enough of sleep is neither the reason nor the excuse. I have no other option but to gear up for another impending research meeting.
      
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      "The mathematics are simple. The problem is Michael Schumacher." - Jonathan Legard, BBC Motor Racing Correspondent.  I could not help myself with a chuckle when I read that. If I am asked to preview the United States Grand Prix at Indianapolis next Sunday in less than 10 words, then I won't hesitate even a second to pick Jonathan's statement. It aptly sums up the whole situation leading up to the race at Indy. Now, any F1 fanatic will know that it wouldn't be a great idea to start an argument with Mr. Legard on his statement; those who wish to, can do so at their own peril. For those who aren't sure, the problem is not about arguing with Mr. Legard, the problem IS (and perhaps HAS always been) Michael Schumacher - the 5 time world champion, gunning for his 6th crown, and to me, quite easily, the greatest human being to have got his act behind the wheel of a Formula One Car, so very right!   What more can I say about this guy...I have been watching him race since the last 11 years, seen each and every pit stop and passing manoeuvre he has made, right from his Benetton Renault days. Alas, after I came to the US in 2001, F1 has been limited more to reading and following on the WWW, rather than spending a Sunday afternoon/evening watching 22 drivers hitting the tarmac (whoa!). Watching a race from the stands and being close to the deafening but equally beautiful sound of the 19,000 rpm engines has been one of my top 5 dreams since I began following the sport in my 7th grade. So hooked was I onto F1 during those days, I spent weekends not only watching the qualifying and race day activities, but I even went to the extent of jotting down excerpts from the live commentary sessions on Star Sports, and systematically archiving all the technicalities and trivias associated with my favorite teams.  If I am excited about going to Indy, its a grossly understated fact. Its an inexplicable feeling. If that itself was not enough, the championship this year has been hotly contested like never before in the last 20 years; I believe, the last time three drivers were gunning for the crown (by the end of the last few races that is), was in 1983. And although the problem is Schuey, all I can hope is that I (or Mr. Legard for that matter), don't get to eat our words after the race on Sunday; the competition is thoroughly intense this time around. Schuey could very well be the 6-time world champion on September 29th, or he could be down and out as far as the race for the championship goes, or we could have another 3-way tussle in the final race at Suzuka, Japan. Almost anything could happen and it depends on how the three drivers score points, and make things easier or worse for each other at Suzuka. For now, the only thing I can do is chew my nails. But let's face the truth, if Shane Warne had literal nightmares about Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar smashing him out of cricket grounds for huge sixes, the cocky Mr. Montoya would be feeling something pretty similar. Mathematics and endless ifs and buts about the race predictions are too simple; the vital element so to speak, in today's racing, is none other than Schumacher and his Ferrari. This man and this car could be ruthlessly reliable on their day, and there have been a lot of "these" days in the last few years, leaving other teams and drivers dumbstruck. I won't get a better opportunity to watch a F1 race. Considering Schuey has hardly disappointed his fans in the last 4 years, I can quite proudly say that there's a high probability of me getting to see HISTORY in the making at Indy. Trivia: Schuey would be the ONLY driver to win 6 crowns after Juan Manuel Fangio, who won 5.  To quote a Navjyot Singh Sidhuism, it will be nothing short of: "Taking the cake with a red cherry on top".  P.S.: Whether or not I get to eat the cake with the cherry (and probably share it with you if you want), the Indy Trip Diary will be posted for sure.
      
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoever derived that well-known albeit now-cliched phrase - " Records are meant to be broken" , wasn't exactly joking. The way modern day sportstars are sending the record books tumbling (Michael Schumacher, Sachin Tendulkar, Matthew Hayden, Lance Armstrong to name a few), a record has become a feat destined to be erased from the annals of sport sooner or later. No sooner have we dealt with all the statistical interpretations of this 'r'-word, we force ourselves to possibly ponder over another banal argument. Is Player 'X' (or Team 'X') the  Greatest  ever? Or is Player 'A'  Greater  than Player 'B'? Commonplace remarks like these are being made and used so often, that no wonder, any arguments associated with it eventually become completely threadbare.  If you are someone who reads the online version of  urlLink The Times of India , you will understand what I am saying. Here comes a pathetic newspaper which (quite unfortunately) markets itself as the  World's #1 English Daily . True, the TOI is still the #1 newspaper, and calling it the World's #1 is certainly better than say, calling New York Yankees as one of the  World's top  baseball teams, if you know what I mean. But I am not entirely sure whether TOI is really the #1 "read" newspaper or simply the #1 "viewed" newspaper. To stretch this further, of late, I sincerely believe that TOI is synonymous to crappy journalism at its very best. Folks at TOI barely manage to do "sound" reporting once in a while, forget about finding a nice column or two once in a week on their webpages. All they are able to churn out is entertainment, and mostly celluloid trash relating to kissing scenes and hot gossip in bollywood. The fact that the stuff TOI sells is actually "sellable" is itself a tad unfortunate. If you compare TOI with the other distinguishable Indian daily -  urlLink The Indian Express , you'll perhaps get a better idea. Ofcourse, I have no plans to canvass for IE in the future, as I am not a big reader of IE either. But from whatever little I read and could make out, IE does seem to have a far better journalistic approach towards current affairs and general reporting. I suppose, gone are those days when the daily morning cup of chai deserved to be sipped only if you had the TOI pages spread in front of you.  I get the feeling that the only person who might not complain about TOI is our very own little master, cricketing genius - Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar. The astounding amount of coverage and attention (in any "web-compatible" form you could think of) that the wonder boy from Mumbai gets from this daily, would probably put to shame even the British newspapers, tabloids and paparazzi when they report about their beloved Princess Diana. If the name "Sachin" literally becomes a religion in the years to come, I am quite sure TOI would have a major hand in doing that. The paper manages to shower endless praise on Tendlya; they keep elevating him to higher pedestals, if religion as a pedestal was not high enough (what a thought!), and then they don't waste much time in playing down his achievements or actions either; its like being hypocritical. Let it be anything, absolutely  anything  happening in world cricket, there  has  to be atleast one page dedicated to this God, irrespective of the fact that he has nothing to do with what happened. It irritates me, not because Sachin does not deserve encomiums, but the fact is that this God needs to be worshipped and left alone; he really does, he certainly deserves it more than he deserves never-ending eulogies and comparisons between him and the current/past cricketers. The media is prying all the time, waiting to pounce on every opportunity. One article talked about Steve Waugh's association with Udayan in Calcutta, a charitable organisation that houses children of leprosy afflicted parents, and then it talked about what Sachin did with his million bucks (rather what he  did not ), in comparion to Steve's charity work. If Sachin earns billions, why should not he have the right to use it for selfish motives? He serves not only Team India, but every citizen of India. It's simple math. If a billion people were to pay "a rupee" to Sachin for the indescribable joy that he gives them when he bats, wouldn't that amount to an income of a billion? Okay, this might be some warped theory of mine, but I think it makes sense (atleast to me). If Sachin makes the Sensex go berserk, and manages to directly affect the sentiments and emotions of billions in India, this seems fair and  logical  (if not exactly pragmatic) to me! Matthew Hayden was the epitome of murderous frenzy when he smashed 380 against Zimbabwe at Perth. Shouldn't Hayden take a bow for that? Not exactly, we don't care about that, the only thing we care is why doesn't apna Sachin score triple hundreds? Isn't it high time he scored real BIG? Even before 24 hours had passed by after Hayden's world record, one of the top TOI headlines read: "Is Sachin still the best?". Pray, why can't this chap ever get a break?  Why are we so preoccupied with labels like  The Greatest ? Call it venting my anger on TOI (and their fetish for Sachin), or call it being opinionated for no genuine reasons, I realize that many a times I am myself unable to resist similar temptations of comparing sportstars. People will say there is very little point in finding a reasonable and rational answer to finding  The One  great, amongst all. Different eras, different rules of the game, different opponents, different equipment renders, the argument gradually gets redundant. Although I am not as paranoid as TOI about indulging in these debates, I think there is an enticing aspect about drawing comparions, dissecting sportstars, (their achievements that is), and analysing them. Is Michael Schumacher the greatest driver ever? Is Tendulkar the greatest batsman? Or was it Bradman, Gavaskar, Waugh? Again, as rotten as these arguments get day by day, I would be the first one to admit that they are lip-smacking all the same. After returning from my Indy trip, I spent a week exchanging healthy emails with a friend of mine, on the greatness factor in F1 Racing; a topic that has been hotly discussed in the last couple of years since Schumacher and Ferrari began their dominance in F1, and more so after Schumacher won a record sixth title this year. Obviously, the heated discussions were on Schumacher and whether he is the greatest. I won't get into more details though, since if you happen to be the one who is aware of my writing capabilities, you would know that Blogger.com would have to increase their disk space in case I plan to publish a transcript of all the emails out here. The discussion was truly healthy though, and I guess the final outcome of the debate was pretty much a stalemate!  Personally speaking, I have a different perception of judging a player's  greatness . People have different criteria for judging the greatness of a player, criteria that they use to separate men from mere mortals in a sport. So let me put forth before you, my own reasoned commentary. Since this is already turning out to be a  BIG BLOG  that I've been writing and re-writing the last 3 weeks, I thought I might as well write my tuppence worth on some sporting greats. I believe that deciding Sachin's greatness is a bit tougher than someone like Schumacher, Armstrong, or Pete Sampras.  1. The 5-time Tour De France champion Lance Armstrong has probably the easiest of cases. This man bounced back from the brink of death after being diagnosed with advanced testicular cancer that spread into his lungs and brain, but still went on to win the intensely grueling bicycle race on this planet, not once, not twice, but five times in a row (99-03). A feat perhaps unmatched in any other sport. If people still fail to consider him as the greatest, then I am sorry to say, but they are either deaf, dumb or blind or they have a severe Anti-American xenophobia of some sorts.   2. With Schumacher its not as easy, but I guess its not as hard as determining Sachin's case. Schumi too, has every record in the bag, but I always felt statistics can be misleading. I rate Schumi as the greatest driver ever, not because of his record breaking feats and championship wins, but because he is a tremendous driver even otherwise. The man who brought Benetton and Ferrari to winning ways when they were almost down in the dumps speaks volumes of his skills. This man doesn't need a good car like most other drivers do. Even Minardi's Paul Stoddart was impressed after watching him in one of his own two-seater cars, with Schumi behind the wheel. Stoddart described Schumi's driving as truly exceptional after the German posted lap times within a second of their normal single-seater F1 cars. The Benetton team (now re-tagged as Renault) never enjoyed success before or after Schumi's four-year spell with them from 1991-5 before he moved on to join a struggling Ferrari outfit. The rest, is history. Under Schumacher, Ferrari dominated like no other racing team, ever. But then Schumacher has been a far too controversial figure than Armstrong, and they say he didn't have stiff competition over the last few years, and that he got lucky on most occasions (the last two arguments being as ridiculous as they can get). What would have happened if he was in a lesser car, or if any one driver amongst Hill, Villenueve, Hakkinen, Coulthard, Montoya, and Raikkonen were to be driving for Ferrari, as Schumi's teammate? Interesting questions, for which nobody has answers, which is why his greatness will always be questioned.  3. I have a controversial opinion about Pistol Pete. To me, he is  not  the greatest tennis player. He has also been described as the most invincible player ever, but I saw him being invincible only on the hallowed grass of Wimbledon. He was never invincible on any other surface, although he did manage to give a  perception  of invincibility. I am not sure which player I would rate as the greatest all-round player in tennis; but the name of Andre Agassi comes to my mind instantly. I came up with my own theory (again), to compare Sampras and Agassi. Suppose that Wimbledon was to have a surface like clay instead of grass. Considering Sampras' poor record on clay, would he be even anywhere close to being called as the greatest? The chances of him winning on Wimbledon clay would be close to nil. Since Agassi won all grandslams - be it clay, grass, hard-court, rebound-ace, cement, and what not, even if you change Wimbledon to clay or a French Open to a grass surface, Agassi's chances of winning won't lessen, unlike Sampras. My notion of a great tennis player is someone who can play equally well everywhere. After watching Agassi's tennis, he could even play on glass! Having said that, I have no intentions whatsoever of downplaying Pete's achievements.  4. Sachin's case is tough. But for me, he will always remain as the  greatest . A few years ago, when Sachin was in the most pristine form of his batting career, they started comparing him with Sir Don, notably after Bradman himself showered accolades on his batsmanship. Sachin without doubt, will break every record in cricket (are there many more left except for Hayden's test record and Anwar's one day record?). The biggest road-block for Sachin on the way to becoming the greatest is the number of matches he has won for India single-handedly, compared to Waugh. In a team sport like cricket, this statistic is a benchmark for purists to comment on greatness. Sachin would never win as many matches for India as Waugh did for Australia; in fact the way Rahul The Wall Dravid is going these days, he stands a better chance of scoring BIG for the country. But I never use this criteria for judging his greatness. On any given day, Sachin is head and shoulders above the rest when it comes to simply "batting". Alas, if only he could use it to win more matches. Its my perception, that nobody comes even close to the repertoire of shots this man has. The difference is that someone like Steve Waugh has fewer shots but still goes on to win matches. And although that is great in itself, I see Sachin with a completely different view. When Sachin plays his trademark straight drive with the full face of his willow towards the umpire, it wouldn't be a farce to say that this man makes my day; a fact equally true with most of his other shots. There is unfathomable joy when I watch him bat - be it destroying the opposition or playing defensive; even the way he braces himself for the next ball, the way he holds his 4-pound willow and takes guard. There is artistry, a magical wizardry to his batting. The mere sight of Sachin stepping down the wicket, or going on the backfoot or hooking or pulling or cutting or driving or simply tapping the ball, is the most beautiful thing to watch on a cricket ground. No other batsman gives the same amount of cricketing pleasure. Those who did not watch Sachin's exploits at Sharjah against Australia in 1996 in the final two matches, should consider themselves as not having lived a better life. Those including me who saw him that day, were priviledged to watch something out of the ordinary unfold from the depths of heaven and descend on mother earth as a cricket innings that will never be forgotten till I breathe my last. (Call it a coincidence or whatever, I clearly recall a desert hurricane during one of those matches causing the match to stop for a while. Sachin almost symbolized that hurricane, whoa!). And then we experienced another slice of that similar heaven when Sachin demolished Shoaib Akhtar and Pakistan in the 2003 world cup match, as well as some of the other teams in the WC matches. Furious, incessant sledging was going on during the Pakistan game. The pandemonium this guy created when he blasted the Pakis with majestic ease will be etched forever in memory. The match proved a canter, and Akhtar had to eat his own four letter words. It seems Sachin could not sleep well for 13 days before the game vs. Pakistan. How could one forget the leg-side six (flick) off Andy Caddick against England? Poor old Caddick. I would not even dream of becoming a bowler if I have to face this little man. Sachin has to his credit a lot of under-rated test match centuries. Centuries which I have seen on tv, and for which I would have given more money than watching a double or a triple century from Lara or Hayden or Richards. Remember his 110 at Perth (1992?) in Australia as a 20 year old kid? The fastest pitch on this planet, against the Aussie battering ram of Merv Hughes and Craig McDermott? His 169 in South Africa when Allan Donald and Co. were throwing perfume balls (with Azhar at the other end)? (Note: "Perfume balls" was a phrase used for the WestIndies in the Michael Holding and Joel Garner era, when the Windies' bowlers ruled cricket. They bowled at lightning fast speeds with an akward length and line. The balls whizzed past so close to the nose of the batsman, that he could "smell" the ball.) And then the mockery he made of Warney when the Aussies toured in 1997, dancing down the wicket outside the leg stump and employing extraordinary tactics on dusty tracks to negate the huge spin and whack the greatest turner of the ball out of the grounds, and moreover, to add salt to wound, leaving him with nothing but nightmares of every shot he played! Some of his other test hundreds like his first century at Old Trafford against England and his 136 against Pakistan at Chennai (pity we lost him at the end thereby losing the test), and his ton at Melbourne in 1999 against McGrath, Lee, Fleming and Warne will also remain memorable. Not many centuries have produced a result in India's favor, and therein lies the unfortunate statistic! Didn't I say before, statistics could be misleading? SO true with someone like Sachin. Bradman might have played on worse, uncovered pitches in his days, but did he play 10 different teams at 50 different venues all year round, with the pressure of a billion people against him? I have had a first-hand experience of watching an India-Sri Lanka match at the Wankhede stadium (Independence cup), and believe me, it takes much more than guts and resolve and determination to play and perform well in front of a raging 50K capacity crowd. . . . Sachin Tendulkar, thanks a zillion. I don't care whether you win matches for India, whether you score a triple ton or not. My life is certainly better because of you. Thank you for opting to play cricket and for the  to-hell-with-college  approach, and thanks to your parents to have not objected. Thank you for all the honors of seeing you bat all these years.
      
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      After my Indy visit, quite a few people have asked me to write on my F1 experience; to publish a dream-come-true report of the race, as well as a personal journalistic write-up on Schumacher's "Greatness", after watching some truly scintillating racing.  It took me a while for the F1 hangover to die down, to get over the post-race exhilaration. I haven't had enough time to think and write my version of the Indy diary. Not having enough time is not the greatest of excuses I can think of (even if it means trying to hide my own disappointment). First of all, no excuse can really cure the feeling of disappointment. Secondly, in order to write on an experience as dream-come-true as this one, merely having "spare" time on a weekend hardly makes things in favor of writing. Take for instance the last couple of Sundays. On both occasions, I planned on making a head-start towards writing the report. Going through what I call as "A blogger's labor pains", I laboriously spent a couple hours on each of those Sundays, trying to "key"-down my thoughts. Not that I thought it would be easy. I was perfectly aware that going about writing a first-hand report of Indy would be well-nigh difficult. It was a four-hour struggle that involved establishing a connection between the thoughts in my mind and using the keys on the keyboard to express those thoughts. But there's been a relatively quick change of opinion; "quick" because four hours of giving a shot at writing a pretty detailed story is perhaps not as painstaking as it seems (for someone who enjoys writing more than talking), and even if it  is  painstaking, it ideally shouldn't lead to a "I-give-up" reaction. You guessed it, that is what I've  exactly  managed to do after my tryst with self-tooted journalism! I always want to let my writing do the talking (tongue seriously in cheek), a (somewhat proud) fact which some of my close friends know quite well. However, I  have  to conclude that writing this stuff is well-nigh impossible for me, and nobody can make me change this opinion. Here is a flowchart of my activities in those hours:  1. Start with a few carefully and laboriously chosen words and/or sentences and type them. 2. Hit the backspace key at the exact instant where you are about to end your sentence and finish with a period. (Time for labor pains to crop up). 3. Keep hitting the backspace key until you erase the whole sentence, forcing yourself to think and re-think and re-type. 4. Go into the "re-examination" mode with a sip of hot coffee. (Coffee acts as a narcotic and seems to ease the pains a bit for me). 5. Go to Step 1.  Sheer agony is all I can say. If not for a phone call that broke the flow for 45 minutes, this 5-step process could've easily turned into an infinite loop.  When I finally slumped into my chair and was all set to bang my head against the keyboard, I recalled my friend Karthika saying - "Life gets tough when you try to express greatness through mere words...". It's a sign that I am perhaps better off being a  computer scientist  (a much more respectable word these days, even if all it means is being a  computer science major ). Isn't life  already  tough enough!?!
      
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Song Title:  Vellai Pookal (lyrics' interpretations coming soon)  Movie (Tamil):   urlLink Kannathil Muthamittal  (2002)  Music/Vocals:  A.R. Rahman  Lyrics:  Vairamuthu   Pros I:  A.R. Rahman, but obviously.  Pros II:  Vocals + bass/acoustic guitars + flute - percussions = an utterly, unbelieveably beautiful and haunting melody.  Cons:  Sleeplessness.   VeLLai PookaL ulagam engum malarhavae kizhiyum Bhoomi amaidhikaaga vidihavae manmel manjal veluchcham vizhuhavae malarae sombal muRiththu ezhuhavae kuzhanthai vizhikattumae Thaayin katha kathappil ulagam vidiyattumae piLLayin sirumugha siRippil (VeLLai)  katrin perisaiyil mazhai paadum paadangalum oru maunam poal inbam tarumooOO koadi keertanamum kavi koartha vaarthaiygalum thuLi kaNNer poal arththam  tharumo (VeLLai)  yengu ser kuzhanthai than kaigal neetidumo angu thondrayo koLLai nilavae enghu manidha Inam poar oyinthu sayinthidumo angu koovadho veLLai kuyilae (VeLLai) 
      
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        A Bit of History     urlLink Dire Straits , who are they? A Classic Rock band that was formed in the late 70s, consisting of  urlLink Mark Knopfler  as the composer, producer and lead musician on lead/rhythm guitars, vocals; his brother  urlLink David Knopfler  on rhythm guitars, Pick Withers on drums, and John Illsley on bass. I say Classic Rock merely for saying it. After all, genres are just interpretations. Morever, in reality, only the first three or four Straits albums can be categorized as Classic Rock. The band broke sometime in the 90s when Knopfler went solo. For many Straits fans, Dire Straits was nothing but another name for Mark Knopfler, who with his legendary guitaring, made it a one-man show. And although Straits was, and will always remain essentially  MK , the equation holds true because of the fact that Knopfler overrode everyone in the band; all others were puppets. In fact the names of all four appear only on their first two albums,  urlLink Dire Straits  and  urlLink Communique . David doesn't appear on  urlLink Making Movies  and  urlLink Love Over Gold , their next two albums, (although it somehow seemed he was a part of Making Movies too), whereas Pick Withers left the band after the fourth album, since he wanted to do more  serious  music. Both were hugely talented in their own domains. According to hardcore Straits followers, the truth was that David was always a better musician than Mark, even though Mark was a better guitarist. Straits sounds beautiful because of initially David Knopfler's rhythm guitars and Pick Withers' drums. When they left, the sound changed, the guitars changed. Straits never became as profound as someone like  urlLink Pink Floyd , a real travesty. When I started with Straits, I thought I might as well hear all their stuff, and to date I have almost their entire collection. Why move the mine when you've find the gold? Really, there is no other sound in music like Dire Straits, the guitaring is totally unique, one can't even compare or find similar bands. That's a problem in a way, as a friend said:  "After you finish hearing all of it, you can't have anything else which is similar!" . Paradoxically speaking, Straits is instant gratification which somehow lasts long!  Mark Knopfler was the guy who told the sound crew at concerts to  "keep the sound low so that people can talk to each other".  The sound crew said  "Dude, you are a rock star man".  A  urlLink picture  of MK is incomplete without his headband, and his famous  red  urlLink strat  , which he unfortunately stopped playing, after the fourth album; the clean, electric strat. Guitarists say that MK's talent is recognisable more if one is a guitarist, otherwise the beauty of his solos are lost on you, they just  sound nice . MK was known more of a  guitarist's guitarist , as opposed to someone like  urlLink Santana  who is more of a  people's guitarist . MK has been criticised many times for writing stuff that only guitarists will appreciate, even though his work still is easy and simple enough for people to  like  and doesnt get too complex with structures and patterns. MK was inspired by  urlLink Bob Dylan , who, to many, was the father of Classic Rock. Recently I heard one of Dylan's songs. Without doubt, in Sultans of Swing, MK sounds very much like Dylan. The talkback style is extremely vintage, and although MK's vocals were never extraordinary, they were fitting enough. Lately, MK not only sings, he croons, notably in his 2002 solo album -  urlLink The Ragpickers Dream . Gone are those long solo sessions. Instead its more of  singing , even though the subtle licks still remain. With  urlLink Golden Heart , his second solo album, his music exhibited a combination of country-ish, irish/celtic pop and rock. Its boring, since its too much oldies music. The strat is nowhere to be seen.  Knopfler is one of the few guitarists in rock who plays primarily with fingers. His guitar sounds like  many , even though in reality its just  one , since finger-plucking is equivalent to having four  urlLink plectrums  (or picks). To my knowledge, most other rock solos are with a plectrum. If one tries to combine and learn both its hard to be good enough to play the solos. The art of finger-plucking or playing  only  with fingers, turns the guitar into a totally different instrument. MK plays it like a piano. The thumb gives the base, the fingers give melody, at the same time! Knopfler can never play as fast as most other rock legends, but its just a choice one makes, of beauty vs. speed. So far as I understand, plectrum gets mechanical, though it has its beautiful points too. With a plec one can attack strings, something that is not possible with fingers because fingers run only in one direction whereas a plec runs in both directions. Knopfler rarely goes speedy, its all about the  subtle feel . And then he sacrifices the lightning speed a plectrum gives, by making it up with  urlLink pulloffs and hammers . If you follow his music closely, his stuff has nice progressions and bridges, some lovely transitions. The uniqueness lies in the fact that he bends more than one string at a time. Most of the time, there are simultaneous bends on many strings, and the intensity of bend on each string is different. I talked to a couple of serious guitarist friends and they said that MK is nice and melodious, but not outrageously progressive, not too risky. Plays a  safe  style of guitar. Of course, any good guitarist worth his salt can play with fingers, but Knopfler goes way way ahead of that. Listen closely to some of his numbers, and you will see the fillers in between the leads. The fillers come from the same guitar, he's just plucking away subconsciously. Leads are conscious, the subconscious fillers are the awesome part. They are spontaneous, and that's the secret!    urlLink DIRE STRAITS (The Album)    Their first self-titled album in 1978 is perhaps their least popular of all, from the masses point of view, although ask any fervent Straits fan and they'll tell you that it is vintage Straits. My favorite album. The album picks up with the song  Down to the Waterline . It is the most awesome way to start liking Straits. Their first release. Lovely chords. David Knopfler strikes them just at the right time to complement the lyrics. Hardcore Dire Straits. The best lineup you could ever get. A legendary introductory song. Unbelieveable riffs, a complex bridge, and serious crazy  urlLink damping . Guitarists bend one string at time, Knopfler usually bends two or three at a time. Its tabla on a guitar, sounds like a tabla! - Just before  "Sweet surrender on the quayside..." . The foghorn sound at the start of waterline is a guitar too. Knopfler did it on his guitar, but its not audible on ordinary speakers. Its one of those fancy tricks that he did only during vintage days, later on, he got too mature to do that stuff. And then ofcourse, Straits' baby so to speak, the song -  Sultans of Swing . An outright breezy number, Sultans was originally written for acoustic, but the leads came out properly on a fender strat. It has some tremendous pulloffs and hammers, and MK seems to be doing relatively little with his right hand. But its a pity that Straits is known only for Sultans in the masses - its my least favorite song from the album. There is some equally great if not better guitaring in  Setting me up  and  Southbound again . In southbound there's a continous rhythm guitar going on, its faint, but constant. And then Six blade knife; only one word to describe that song -  subtlety . There are some amazing nuances and subtleties in this song which normal speakers fail to capture properly. The licks/riffs are all  urlLink harmonics . MK plays the guitar such that the fundamental frequency of the string is muffled, but the smaller vibrations of the string  continue resonating. The guitar fades away, reappears, fades again...extremely subtle variations, lot of multiple bends. Throughout the song he's scratching on the guitar. Totally maddening effects.     urlLink MAKING MOVIES    Their third album has two wonderfully composed songs.  Romeo and Juliet  and  Skateaway . The first one is a beautiful ballad. Sweet, soothing guitar. Skateaway happens to be one of his complex compositions. Very fine guitar interludes backed up by equally good drumming.    urlLink LOVE OVER GOLD    Their fourth album, Love Over Gold contains even more beautiful Dylan-esque songs. Knopfler almosts sounds like Dylan. It contains another legendary intro song called  Telegraph Road , which is a 15 minute number containing three great solos. It has an interesting bit of history associated with it which you can find  urlLink here . The album is hugely underrated. Has only 5 songs but the band spent a year on it and labelled it as their most ambitious project. This album has Alan Clark on the keyboards and Hal Lindes on the rhythm guitar for the first time. The entire album has an atmospheric feel to it.  Private Investigations ,  Love Over Gold  and  It Never Rains  are the other three picks. If waterline had a tabla on a guitar, in It Never Rains, MK's guitar sounds as if it is  singing . All songs have truly incredible solos.    urlLink ALCHEMY    I haven't heard all of Alchemy but have checked a couple songs from it. An album that doesnt sound as catchy since it is live, but the atmosphere is worth it.  "Not a pick in site" , is how they advertised Alchemy. And sure enough, there were no plectrums to be found anywhere. Knopfler threw one into the crowd just before the concert and started some finger control exercises driving the crowd mad. Then he stretched his hands out, relaxed, and started playing  Once upon a time in the west  all by himself. They say that it was the first live album which wasn't edited after recording. You will find the band actually making mistakes while they played!    urlLink BROTHERS IN ARMS    The album that rocketed Straits to popularity. They got commercialized. My least favorite album. In fact it is not at all trademark Straits. It has a few good numbers such as  So far away  and  Brothers in arms , but lacks the punch and the vintage style. Songs like  Money for nothing  and  Walk of life  were big hits. But those are nothing but nursery pop when you look back at the original Straits.    urlLink ON EVERY STREET    The last of the Straits' albums. Again, very experimental. Not exactly vintage, but still in a class of its own! MK used a gibson style guitar for this. Starts of well with  Calling Elvis . Good rhythm.  On every street  has a short but good solo. A lot of the songs in this album too are very ambient and atmospheric, very haunting.  You and your friend  and  Iron hand  have typical finger-plucking. I already talked about  The Bug  and  Ticket to Heaven . Probably my pick of the album is  Planet of New Orleans . The song is supposed to have wierd, complex chords. Great sax and guitar combo.    urlLink SULTANS OF SWING: THE VERY BEST OF DIRE STRAITS    Again, an album that was compiled for the box office. Doesn't contain much of the vintage works. But has a lovely, (live) song called  Local Hero . Just MK and his guitar. The last song of the album but which probably deserves a better rating.    urlLink SAILING TO PHILADELPHIA   and   urlLink GOLDEN HEART    Sailing is an exceptionally phenomenal solo album, and I am running out of space, time, words,  and energy to dissect any more of his songs. Golden Heart on the other hand was nothing too spectacular, although it has its fair share of good songs like the  Golden Heart  and one called  Vic and Ray . More celtic than any other album.    urlLink NECK AND NECK    Not a Dire Straits' album, but has MK and  urlLink Chet Atkins  going crazy on guitars. Its a guitar jugalbandi in Indian terms. It has a piece called  I'll see u in my dreams , which is only guitar. The album is proper country guitaring, serious guitar picking. Chet Atkins, himself a country guitarist and a legend in his own right, taught Knopfler. It has some slow numbers here and there, but in between are some unbelievable and long guitar jams. The first guitar solo of the first song -  Poor boy blues , MK just  takes off  into the first solo.    Summing up my longest blog    From what I gather, what MK/Straits does is inspire people to start learning guitar, which is the most amusing thing. I wouldn't have learnt guitar otherwise. In fact I keep hearing from people that one good thing Straits does to you, is when you are through with it (which is a hard thing in itself); in a few years, one is prepared for much more complex music, which otherwise is not as easy to understand/like. Straits has a typical sound which if you like, you will like most of it.  Getting into Straits is a smooth ride like none other. I will perhaps never enjoy any other band so much. People tell me that Straits will educate me, as a favor to me. By the time I am through with it, I'll understand  urlLink chord progressions . Its a slow process, and if one is not obsessed about a band, one doesn't take the trouble to understand it. Its infinitely complex. You derive something out of it, only after you listen more and more to it. Eventually a day comes when you listen and know what each instrument is doing exactly. To put this in computer lingo, its all about parallel processing; equalizing mentally. For instance when to have the drums and guitar  UP , bass  DOWN , rhythm  UP ......  Whatever you say, I'll be indebted to Mark Knopfler for the rest of my life.
      
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       I can see what you're looking to find in the smile on my face In my peace of mind, in my state of grace . . I got my ticket to heaven and everlasting life I got a ride all the way to paradise   -  urlLink Ticket to Heaven , by  urlLink Dire Straits/Mark Knopfler   The song might be too idealistic for some musical tastes, but nevertheless, has stunningly beautiful lyrics. Its even more beautifully composed, and when you complement this with Mark Knopfler's awesomely clean, laidback, and completely distortion free guitaring, it really is a ride to paradise.  The time was December 2002. As I look back with nostalgia, it has been the most smoothest musical ride of my life. My cousin  urlLink Bhushan , suggested I check out some of the Mark Knopfler solo albums -  urlLink Sailing to Philadelphia  and  urlLink Golden Heart . Bhush has a tremendous flair for music and is adept at playing keyboards as well as with programming and arranging music. I usually take his recommendations pretty seriously and we usually end up hitting the same note, so far as musical interests are concerned. Here at CSU,  urlLink Sid  was already familiar with MK and Straits, and thanks to him, I was initially able to check out some of their collection. It didn't take me long to get hooked onto Knopfler and Straits. I always loved the sound of the guitar, but then this was an entirely different sound, completely unheard of before.   The rest is history. Guitar soon became an intense obsession and I decided to take a beginner level instructional guitar class at CSU this Fall. With MK and Straits, inspiration and motivation came easily, and I picked an acoustic Alvarez guitar to start strumming away. My immediate goal was to learn the guitar in order to play some Dire Straits riff, forget the fact that I fortunately figured out very early that it takes atleast a year to play even the most easiest of songs with the slightest of clinical precision. The obvious difficult part was putting inspiration and motivation into practice. And thus I began the frustrating journey, perhaps none more frustrating than learning a string instrument like the guitar; where fingers hurt and cramp, words such as  inspiration  and  motivation  become a thing of the past and are replaced by words like  loss of interest  and  utter boredom . It is easy to put down a guitar after 10 minutes of frantic fret-play. Another phrase that I take credit for coining. You begin to wonder if the entire process is worth going through. However, to quote MK's lines from  urlLink The Bug  -  "Its a strange old game you learn it slow..."  - given your continous zest and passion, you will eventually find the process worth it. And what better than to actually be able to play the songs of the band that became the very reason you took this ride! I can say with atleast some degree of self-satisfaction that I was able to play  urlLink Ticket to Heaven  in the last couple of days. One thing's for sure; at this stage  playing  is rather a glorified word for  scratching , but I know I'll get there one day.  I am still unqualified to dedicate an entire blog to discuss my own guitaring in detail. So let us leave this for another day, a day when I can probably boast of playing some more serious stuff. The section  My EADGBE  in the sidebar contains links to songs that I am playing on my guitar these days.  But it sure is high time I dedicated a blog to the guitar God who fuelled this passion in the first place. I have been guilty of writing excessively long blogs in the past, and MK deserves an entire space to himself. Check the sequel to this blog  urlLink here .
      
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's what  urlLink The Matrix Revolutions  is. A classic example of a trilogy that became legendary with Part I -  urlLink The Matrix , quite disappointing after the sequel -  urlLink The Matrix Reloaded , and without doubt, an  urlLink absolute disaster  after Part III.  However, even after two hours of great atrocity watching Part III, I am not sure how Matrix still appeals to the  philosophical  minds, so much so that I now hear it deals with Hindu Philosophy (seems that the song that plays in the end credits of Part III are sanskrit shlokas), in addition to Christianity (you betcha, starring Neo as Christ "The One").  Check some expert comments  urlLink here .  If this philosophy crap was all that the Wachowski brothers wanted to put forth before the audience, then as a Matrix fan, I certainly need better philosophy lessons than The Matrix Revolutions.  Everything that has a beginning has an end. Thanks to the Wachowski brothers for ending these systemic anomalies once and for all.
      
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's  urlLink Miss Harper Lee  bowling and flooring me with her famous novel -  urlLink To Kill A Mockingbird . What a book this is. Its been a long time since I have picked a book and voraciously devoured half of it in one go. Not that its of biblical proportions anyways. But just for the record,  urlLink Fountainhead , for me, holds the dubious distinction of being the book with the least number of pages to have been read in the first sitting - I dozed off after the introduction/preface, cursing  urlLink Ayn Rand . On the other hand, I might also hold the rare distinction (c'mon, not  exactly  dubious this time) of actually finishing that 700-odd page epic after three months of diligent reading, and inspite of cursing the author initially.  Getting back to the mockingbird, I don't know why I am reading this at the age of 24. On second thoughts, I wouldn't have understood much of it in my teens anyways, although as it has always happened with me and my books, most people seem to have read it long back, making me wonder if my reading abilities in my teens were ordinary or what.  If ever writing could be subtle yet so powerful, that too using real-world, almost everyday characters, then MockingBird should be a classic example. This is really a literature masterpiece. Post-mockingbird, I have already set my eyes on welcoming the new year with  urlLink Catcher in the Rye  and  urlLink Catch 22 , two books which people are known to go ga-ga about.   2003 has been a great year for me considering I managed to do some big reading. Fountainhead,  urlLink Shreeman Yogi  (which is simply a must, must Marathi read; all of 1100-odd pages, my longest one ever and took me a whopping 6 months to finish), and lots others. I also have another Marathi book,  urlLink Panipat , waiting on my bookshelf to be picked up. Then there's  urlLink Douglas Adams ,  urlLink Aldous Huxley ,  urlLink Existentialism ...the saga should continue...welcome 2004!
      
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
             Copyright 2003     All characters in these chronicles are real, and any resemblance to any living person, is entirely intentional and purely marked by full consciousness of the nature and effects of the events being chronicled.     "Son, I have just passed on a sweet legacy to you"    - My Dad, Uday K. Nulkar, after I was diagnosed with IDDM    Preface   As I await the results of yet another quarterly  urlLink Hemoglobin A1C  test (or the glycosylated hemoglobin), and a few others next week, my mind is rewinding itself to the events that occured a year ago. Come December 31, 2003 and it would be my first Diabetes Anniversary. Life has absolutely zipped by since December 31, 2002. At times, days and nights have seemed long, but a year seems way too short.  "It was all happening..." , to quote Bill Lawry's Aussie drawl on Channel Nine.  Feels tremendous to be alive and kicking, and I am looking forward to another year to zip by just the same. After my second A1C test at the beginning of the Fall of 2003, Dr. Russell Risma at CSU's  urlLink Hartshorn Health Center  looked at me with a smiling approval and asked,  "Atul, are you sure you are a diabetic?" . As much as that was friendly banter, I wish I could have responded with a pompous proclamation of a  "No" . Pausing briefly, he added in his characterstic humorous tone:  "I am not sure if my own A1C level is as good as that" . That, simply put, was the final seal of approval.  Whether they are academic grades or results for diabetes lab tests, I still seem to experience the same feeling of trepidation, even though at the same time, I feel confident about my third A1C being just as good as the first two. Ofcourse, there are a bunch of other tests to pass - like the  urlLink lipid profile , and a couple others to do with the kidney and the thyroid. There's no reason why the butterfly-shaped glands or the bean-shaped organs should be a source of worry, but a bit anxious I am, anyhow. My eyes have a different story to tell though, as a slight blurry vision suggests that I might have to adorn myself with a thicker pair of lenses. Or maybe thinner, if optimism sounds better.  I woke up today, and I hated to see a new day dawn. Might seem unusual for a morning person who likes to catch a glimpse of the first rays of the soothing Colorado sun in these bitter cold days of winter. I hated to do the daily morning routine. The chore, which starts with a big yawn that welcomes the new day, followed by the gradual slipping-out-of-the-bed thing, trudging towards the bathroom to brush and pee, and then getting back besides the bed only to thrust that seemingly godforsaken insulin pen inside my belly. I have done that for about 340-odd days every morning, now. And I just could not prepare myself to inject today, although eventually sanity prevailed, and I did inject. Over these 340-odd days, taking shots twice a day has been literally a routine,  and I mean , "a routine". Initially it used to be:  "Hi there, I am taking a shot for my diabetes" . Slowly but surely it changed to:  "Hi there, I am taking a shot" . It was similar to any other daily chore such as brushing your teeth. Today was a bit different. I had a fleeting glimpse of frustration and depression getting the better of me. If its fairly easy to get into that so-called routine, its even more easy to loose the grip on it. This was followed by visions of me devouring candy bars and chocolates one night, when it was time for the cravings to get the better of me. Yes, that actually did happen sometime last summer, only to find my fasting glucose levels in the morning sky-rocketing. I still have a hearty laugh when I recollect those desperate moments.   I tried to overcome my frustration by letting myself know of the good work that I had been doing all these months. My mind wasn't ready yet. "Yes, but can I continue doing the good work for say, 10 or 20 more years down the road?". I imagined myself going through that same godforsaken routine for the next 20 years, and I laughed again.   Maybe I should just stop worrying about my future worries.    ~ The End of the Chronicles Series ~       
      
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The  urlLink Indian summer's  getting hotter, just when the  urlLink Kangaroos  thought it was already over at  urlLink Brisbane .  urlLink The Wall  not only batted and fielded like GOD, but He, and a Very Very Special  urlLink Laxman  ensured that Houdini will never be heard of again in cricketing parlance.   Two articles that instantly impressed me: 1. Samit Bal's beautiful piece on  urlLink the celebration of orthodoxy .  2. Amit Varma's  urlLink Wisden archive  on two cricketing gods, written not so long ago.  We have seen  urlLink Dada Ganguly  successfully dancing to the tune of chin music. We have seen Rahul Dravid erecting the Great Wall of India. We have seen why VVS is poetry in motion. We have even seen the  urlLink Bombay Duck  learning to fly ( urlLink plagiarized from Cricinfo ) . . .!  But its not over yet. Its the calm before the storm. If you've read  urlLink this blog , you'll guess that I already have visions of another of those  slices of heaven . Its imminent, and it  will  descend onto mother earth.  Sure, we are waiting.
      
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was hoping to continue the series of diabetes chronicles, but looks like they have to stop sometime, and the time has come. Writing these chronicles has been a memorable journey, and they are as indelible as the actual journey itself. I am less motivated than before to continue writing the series, and its partly because I've moved on with diabetes. What better than to end on a good note.  Rest assured, efforts will still be on to maintain the heavenliness of this abode.  Thanks for stopping by, and for the comments, ofcourse.   It was I who was The hourglass And the sands of time like Shattering glass went past me Like a tunnel to the sea  -  urlLink Stevie Nicks / urlLink Fleetwood Mac 
      
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A.R. Rahman is back, and he's back with the greatest bang possible. His latest score for M.F. Hussain's  Meenaxi - A Tale of 3 Cities , is an outright stunner. A peach of an album. Inspite of a poor quality audio, I have been completely blown away in the first listening. This is a rare occurrence, given the fact that I've been an ARR devotee for the last decade or so. And by devotee I  do  mean, following almost each and every piece he has composed, and not simply his commercially hit music.   ARR's stuff is something which always needs a careful ear; it takes quite a few listenings on a decent set of ear phones, until the music grows on you and until you really begin to appreciate the nuances and subtleties. On numerous occasions I have found myself being absolutely disappointed after the first listening session, only to come back later and find something extra special about it. In fact there are a number of examples of his musical scores, which failed to take off at the box office, only because they werent for the masses (even though any genre of music these days is essentially targeted and marketed only for the bucks and the mass appeal). 1947 Earth is a classic example that comes to my mind. Without any hint of doubt, I would rate that as one of his top 10 compositions.  Frankly speaking, I have been drifting away from ARR since the last two or three years, not only in the quest of some good Classic and Bluesy British Rock, but admittedly, Rahman too hasn't produced anything spectacular after  Lagaan . I don't count  Saathiya , because its a parallelized version from his original compositions in Tamil, from Mani Ratnam's  Alai Payuthey , released way before  Saathiya  hit Bollywood. Sure, he did have some great succeess in the Tamil industry, with movies like  Kannathil Muthamittal  and the highly experimental rocker -  Boys . But the journey in Bollywood hasn't exactly been a joy ride.  Tehzeeb , another recent release was forgettable by ARR standards, except for a couple good ghazals.  Lakeer  was also practically a  flop , although again, die hard fans should know that Lakeer's score was taken from his Tamil works; from the film  Rhythm , where Rahman had originally composed five songs depicting each of the five elements -  Water, Wind, Earth (Land), Sky, and Fire . The Tamil score is sensational, and I am at pains to understand why Rahman has to parallelize his score for Bollywood, just about for  any  movie. It just doesn't sound and feel the same in Hindi;  Saathiya  being an exception. In the ARR fans community, talks have been going on, as to how and why ARR has lost his lustre, which though true to a certain extent, isn't anything alarming. Personally, I felt ARR was experimenting too much, to the point where his music did sound monotonous and completely out of sorts (okay, maybe I  should  say crappy!). This is like comparing Sachin Tendulkar's batting. Not so long ago, Sachin's batting was not only a spectacle, it was something people would discuss, analyze and scrutinize for years. Things have changed a bit after the arrival of the Gangulys, Dravids and Laxmans and after his own loss of form. ARR hasn't really been threatened by competition in that sense, but of late, his music hardly warrants any dissection and expert commentary like before. ARR himself agreed that he was concentrating more on expanding his horizons - notably with his score for the Oscar nominated Chinese film -  Warriors of Heaven and Earth  and his work on the theatrical version of  The Lord of the Rings . Having said that, Warriors is a masterpiece in itself, even though I have only heard mere snippets. I believe it could easily send Hollywood composers on the run.  With  Meenaxi , ARR is at his very best once again, and has managed to create music that has  "Vintage ARR"  inscribed on it, if ever such a thing could be possible. Mind you, the sound and feel are vintage, since its more or less the familiar  "ARR sound"  that you'll hear, but paradoxically speaking, at the same time, that doesn't take away the lingering freshness of the music. Everything fits perfectly. Not even one song is anything short of a  great piece . These are strong words to say after only my first musical experience of Meenaxi, but then I am not rambling either. ARR's forte - the soaring vocals/harmonies, the typical steady ambient bass and strings, the beautiful haunting flute and violin interludes, the carefully constructed synth pieces and fillers, and ofcourse Sivamani - the meastro of Indian percussion, with his heady mix of instruments ...  every  iota of his music is back! The orchestration, the sound arrangement, the entire feel of Meenaxi is pure, vintage, classy Rahman. Meaningful lyrics and poetry (for a change), always a welcome prospect in Bollywood, are a breath of fresh air too! Looks like recording in a London studio has also helped a lot, not that his Panchattan Inn in Chennai would be anything less.   Yeh Rishta  - The album begins with this song, having a nice and soothing solo entrance piece. It kicks off on a lovely, dreamy note. Debutant Reena Bharadwaj, another super ARR-find, supplies amazing vocals. The integration of tabla-like synthesized drum beats and strings by John Themis, along with some peaceful sounds of flowing water add that extra bit of flavor. Seems that Rahman requested Reena to give an audition in his studio apartment in London and ended up recording the scratch version in his kitchen.  Chinnamma Chilakkamma  - The second number is an interesting piece, and has western beats on a traditional south indian folk rendition. The song almost takes you into melody music of the 50s/60s with some oldies style flute pieces, but then changes pace nicely to the tune of some creative electric drumming. Just notice how Sukhwinder Singh lends unusual smooth vocals to this telugu folk song, very unlike his usual high pitched notes; especially when he sings the line -  "Zindagi khayal ..." , altering the electric drumming to a peaceful transition of synth, bass and (possibly) violin interlude. Maddenning effects!  Do Kadam Aur Sahi  - This track is perhaps the pick of the album. Sonu Nigams rendition should rank as one of his best. The atmospheric and spatial synth sound creates a symmetric rhythm that is an ARR hallmark. If you listen carefully, it also has a short acoustic guitar lick, although faint, but  so  appropriately mixed. This is one aspect I am impressed with, of late. Since Kannathil, ARR uses a lot more strings (acoustic guitars) in addition to his more well-known flamenco-style guitaring. There's even a continous rhythm violin (almost like a rhythm guitar) going on in the background. Subtle fillers create a deep and rich sound, creating a tremendous intensity, almost giving it a divine feel.  Dhuan Dhuan  - Its Asha Bhosles turn to walk away with a major credit for the fourth song. She is past her 70s, but no other lady on earth has a voice as seductive and painful yet silky and smooth as Ashas. Contains some heavy percussive beats on a hindustani-classical base as well as additional grooves by James Asher, and is one of those hardcore ARR songs that is here to stay for years to come.  Rang Hai  - The fifth track might take more time to appreciate. Its not instantly catchy, but incorporates a great Rajasthani folk rhythm for Hossam Ramzys heavy percussion/drums. Alka Yagnik is on lead vocals, as always holding her own, and Dellinda, a Lebanese singer, provides additional vocals for the western style rendition.  Noor-Un-Ala-Noor  - A sufi qawwali written by M.F. Hussain, this is an instant winner. Sung by Ustad Murtaza Khan and Ustad Qadir Khan, this one has everything that a classic qawwali song should have. Flowing harmonium, traditional fast-paced tabla beats and great alaaps and swaras. A virtuoso performance!  Cyclists Rhythm   If anybody in Indian contemporary music can get creative and innovative, then it has to be ARR. What an instrumental piece this is. Naveen Kumar on the flute (Raag Hansadhwani?) and Sivamani on percussions. It reminds me a bit of  Taals   Beat of Passion , but is not plain percussion as in  Taal . This piece is supposedly filmed for a scene in the movie where the actress Tabu is caught in the street amidst bicycles. It begins with the chiming of bicycle bells and drums in the background, which then leads into a short flute masterpiece, then back to the bells, and then finally the bells fading off into speedy and thunderous drumming by Sivamani.  Potters Village   Another, very different instrumental track to wind up the album; this one has a distinct middle eastern, arabic touch to it, with Johns prominent guitar and Hossams drums. With great use of instruments, this too is a treat for the ears.  All said and done, Meenaxi is an album with a complex set of compositions by Rahman after a really long time, rather than just popular music dished out for radio hits. Its proper music, in its entirety, given that you allow yourself some extra bit of ear-time for it.   The good old times are back. Slip on those decent set of ear phones and let the music take you over.  My life's better because of ARR. Let the mania prevail...
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sitting in my stuffy little cube inside the Computer Science department here at CSU, sometimes leads me to meandering thoughts about anything and nothing in particular (no, the last five words have nothing to do with the  urlLink Eclipse  project and its punch line). At times, the cube can act as a perfect place for convoluted minds to drift away deeper into their labryinth of dreams or to indulge in serious surreal activities. Not that I know of anybody else here who feels the same about this place. But Room 200 sure has that distint eerieness, especially when most of the folks here are known to go about their business in their own quiet manner. I almost hear faint whispers of people gossiping -  "Psst Psst...Man is a social animal, but this guy Atul never is...!" . Hey hey, no qualms about that. I am happily reconciled with kuo, my linux box. Whereas the room is on the quiescent side - the silence broken only by the harsh ringing of a phone or a hearty but equally loud burst of laughter - it does play host to a myriad of odours ranging from caramel coffee, hot chocolate, cinnamon tea and roasted turkey to exotic french perfumes and scented candles, and also to some ephemeral scents that you probably don't want to smell.  These days, a surreal activity for me is a dose of caffeine backed up by Pink Floyd's essentially psychedelic and trippy dreamscapes rocking in the background. What an ambience, this creates. I wonder how Pink Floyd's music feels when you get doped and become  comfortably numb , in Floydian terminology. Yeah right, they'll say. But then according to common belief isn't it always the thought that matters?! Well, maybe it doesn't matter in this case, or on the flip side it probably matters too much!  I was almost reduced to tears when some of Floyd's music started growing on me. Here's one great piece...   Ticking away the moments that make up a dull day You fritter and waste the hours in an offhand way. Kicking around on a piece of ground in your home town Waiting for someone or something to show you the way.  Tired of lying in the sunshine staying home to watch the rain. You are young and life is long and there is time to kill today. And then one day you find ten years have got behind you. No one told you when to run, you missed the starting gun.  So you run and you run to catch up with the sun but it's sinking Racing around to come up behind you again. The sun is the same in a relative way but you're older, Shorter of breath and one day closer to death.  Every year is getting shorter never seem to find the time. Plans that either come to naught or half a page of scribbled lines Hanging on in quiet desperation is the English way The time is gone, the song is over, Thought I'd something more to say.   - Time,  urlLink Dark Side Of The Moon   
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "Theory is when everything is known and nothing works. Practice is when everything works and nobody knows why. At Microsoft, theory and practice are united: nothing works and nobody knows why."  -- Anonymous  Recently, I happened to globe totter on the WWW on the history of computing in general. Thanks to my high school, my first introduction to a computer was in the form of a ZX Spectrum. It was one of those really pivotal machines in introducing ordinary people to home computing (in school). Spectrums featured a coloured display, an easy to learn yet versatile built-in BASIC and they also quite possibly served as low cost educational and productivity tools. In fact an entire generation of programmers wrote their first lines of code on those rubber keys -- and for a few years the machines also served as the #1 gaming consoles. Its all nostalgia when I take a trip down memory lane and recall the early years of working (read: gaming) on my first home PC. Thanks to my dad, it was an Intel 286 powered by an 8MB RAM chip and equipped with Quantum's 40MB disk running Microsoft's Disk Operating System (DOS), the coolest OS to hit the market then. Believe it or not, this mean little machine played host to hundreds of DOS-based games.  Microsoft. DOS. All too familiar names. Bill Gates was just on the way towards his glory days then, soon to be the most revered software techie the world had ever seen and the man behind the empire called Microsoft, which today, is clearly struggling to live upto its name. Hardcore MS detractors or Open Source software protagonists, whichever way one would like to put it, would say that MS never deserved to bask in glory, so there was never a question of living upto its name - it was only a hype in an industry on the verge of bursting open. Gates was quite clearly the single biggest role model for every kid who wrote source code during that time. The God of all tech nerds, I even remember myself going gaga all over when I was told that I shared my birthdate with Gates. An avid gamer and a software tweaker (if not exactly a coder) during those days, I could have hardly hoped for a better person to share my birthday with.  Microsoft reached its popularity pinnacle after it released its Windows OSes, specifically its 3.x and 9x versions. To a larger extent, MS became a monopoly on the lines of other companies like AT&T. After coming up with NT, 2000 and the latest XP versions, nobody would deny the fact that the world still loves MS, but at the same time there are people out there who would leave no stone unturned when displaying their hatred towards the software giant. In essence, and as I see it, the common man has very much a love-hate relationship with MS.  On the other hand, Microsoft is being subject to intense hostility and animosity the world over, not only in the form of  urlLink legal lawsuits  by competitive companies in the software market, but also in the form of day-to-day  urlLink humor and ridicule . Upon taking a closer look, on a much more wider - political, industrial and technological scale and perspective, the issues with Microsoft and its competitors, namely Netscape/AOL and Sun Microsystems, seem to be more clandestine than they actually appear. There are still egos to settle and plenty of naysayers out there on both sides of the court.  The problem with Micrsoft is three-fold, and on different levels, making it the bad boy of software today. The three issues pretty much border around each other but it makes sense to apply some form of distinction so as to discuss them individually. Three questions arise.  (I discuss one question here and the remaining two in Part II of this blog, in order to achieve some semblance of brevity in my writings).     Why is Windoze believed to be just another pane in the glass? Does Microsoft really produce software that meets the user's expectations?    >>  Whether Windoze is just another pane or a tougher glass shield, is more of a technical issue dealing with the core design of the OS, rather than something that any naive user can comment on. But I have to admit this. The degree to which Microsoft and Windows have lowered my as well as fellow users' expectations are baffling. Why then - after more than a decade churning out one OS after another - Microsoft fails to embed a simple virus scanner into its OS is absolutely beyond me. Outlook Express, the Windoze based email client and the most effective breeding ground to-date for all worms and trojans floating around in cyberspace, just does not seem to improve. Now you know, why someone talked about theory and practice at Microsoft. Moreover, forget virus scanners. If Microsoft cannot find the cure, how can it possibly prevent any subsequent anomalies? Why does every new Microsoft OS have the biggest security loop-hole, forcing users to download patches after patches, time after time, only to find that by the time they are trying to get to terms with the OS and possibly get some fair share of their value for money and time, in comes another new release touted to be the next revolutionary thing to have hit them? This is followed by numerous version compatibility problems with files and documents. Furthermore, failure and recovery remain some of the issues that are still dealt rather sloppily - a classic example being Microsoft Word. To top it all, products come with a not-so-cheap price tag. Are customers paying  exclusively  for the robust, reliable software product? I don't believe so. They are almost compelled to pre-pay, in advance, for future  customer service , in the form of countless patches that the company sends out, only to label them as  free downloads . The common man doesn't complain much. Microsoft and Windows have had such a huge impact on the home/desktop PC market, that nobody gives a damn. After all, why would someone bother about robustness and reliability if the only thing one does is play games, browse the web and listen to music? Fair enough. Let the worms wriggle inside, who cares? People have no problem downloading frequent patches and updates. And then luckily for Microsoft, not every user plays with Word documents everyday, in order to get a chance of standing testimony to the fact that data loss is a common phenomenon under the hood of this system.   The truth is, Microsoft gets away with buggy software on enough occasions to actually ride on that wave and be successful. Perhaps, on a more positive note to make MS fans happy, I can transpose the earlier statement and say that it manages to do just enough for them to make them happy!   (Part II continued  urlLink here ...) 
      
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Continued from  urlLink this  blog...    "There are people who don't like capitalism, and people who don't like PCs. But there's no one who likes the PC who doesn't like Microsoft."  -- Bill Gates    The second question deals with the 'free' software movement, known as the  urlLink Open Source Software  (OSS) development (such as the Linux OS), as opposed to Microsoft's  urlLink Closed Source Software  (CSS) products. Is this simply a question of "who owns what, how and why"?    >>  My one word answer to that is  No . Its not simply a case of dealing with copyright issues and ownership of source code. This is a commonly asked question but is outside the scope of this blog (that's me: a true software engineer at heart), but I might take this up sometime later. If you are insanely curious,  urlLink this  page gives a good, brief overview on OSS and CSS in a nutshell. Any more than that, and it will be pushing this subject into technical territory, which even I haven't explored a whole lot. Suffice to say that Gates reaction to Suns Java Technology was:  "Anybody who thinks a little 9,000-line program that's distributed free and can be cloned by anyone is going to affect anything we do at Microsoft has his head screwed on wrong."  Its a pity that Gates attempted dig at Suns Java programming language was not only foolish, but Microsoft even had the audacity to come up with their own supposedly competitive version of a similar language called  C#  (pronounced C-sharp). No guesses as to who won the battle!    Are Microsoft's trials really fueled by plain envy? What has Capitalism and Ayn Rand philosophy got to do with software?    >>  This is by far the most controversial issue to have hit the software industry, more so after Microsoft's Anti-Trust cases over the years. It has spawned off a plethora of legal issues relating to the  American  approach of doing business and competing with others in the modern age. The  urlLink Ayn Rand Institute  for  urlLink The Microsoft Defense  and  urlLink The Center for the Advancement of Capitalism  have been the two most fervent supporters of Microsoft, and have backed Microsoft's business strategies and processes full throttle, challenging the supreme court on the anti-trust issues. Terming Microsoft as  America's persecuted minority  and blaming their competitors' actions as nothing but sheer  entrepeneurial envy , these defense organizations have accused the US government of carrying  false philosophic and economic ideas and of trampling on the rights of Microsoft .   Honestly, my gut feeling is that the picture at the Redmond based Microsoft is far from rosy. People can be blinded by philosophy. Its a cult following. Ayn Rand lived in a substitute world of her own. Her philosophy is close to being impractical in the 21st century where being as idealistic as her is not exactly the name of the game. The supposedly  unknown ideal  and philosophy is perfectly fine by me, as long as facts are separable from fiction. Not everything applies to the 21st century  real world , or else, why even call it as the  ideal ? Moreover, the institute believes that Microsoft was punished for being successful and for making products that people  want  to purchase. Everything is fine here, except for that italicized word.   The truth is, Microsoft never gave people the chance to decide what  they wanted . That was one of the many reasons why Netscape/AOL filed an anti-trust complaint against the company in 2002. Few people are aware that Netscape was the first to jump on the Internet bandwagon and to release their web browser. In fact the first  browser  that captured the imagination of the public was NCSAs Mosaic, developed at the National Center for Supercomputing Applications at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. The developers of Mosaic went on to create Netscape. Mosaic was also the first to be available on Windows. Microsofts Internet Explorer browser to-date is based on Mosaic itself. There is a feeling in the open source community that Microsoft never innovates. It buys, imitates, or steals and makes things difficult for software developers, and thus eventually for users.  In the mid 90s Microsofts chief intent was to gain supremacy over the  browser  war between itself and Netscapes Navigator. According to the complaint, Microsoft was not content to compete by attempting to offer a better product and persuading users to use its browser. It illegally exploited its monopoly power over Intel-compatible PC operating systems in order to undercut Netscape's ability to distribute their Navigator. Microsoft carried a series of anticompetitive and exclusionary acts so as to undermine Netscape's ability to grow into an alternative competitive platform. It forced Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) to accept exclusionary license restrictions that caused them to stop dealing with Netscape and instead exclusively use Internet Explorer. The company threatened OEMs with loss of their licenses to the Windows operating system if they did not comply with these illegal provisions. Microsoft also coerced exclusionary dealing arrangements with Internet Access Providers and Internet Service Providers that limited Netscape's browser distribution.  Microsoft is even known to have forced Apple to replace Netscape as its default browser with Internet Explorer by threatening Apple with loss of the Macintosh Office application. It was clear that the purpose and effect of Microsofts anticompetitive and exclusionary campaign was to reduce Navigator's market share and viability so as to prevent Navigator from becoming a platform for software applications that could in turn, threaten Microsoft's Windows monopoly.  Simply put, vendors and customers did not have any other  choice  when selecting the OS and the Internet Applications. The package was thrust upon them. How then can the people decide what  they want ?  I have been more of a Windoze user all my life. Only in the last three years have I started appreciating Unix/Linux and Open Source Software. I still use Windows, and I wont say I am a staunch Anti-MS person. Linux too has its share of bugs and has  some  way to go before it captures the desktop market. Morever OSS development has its own pros and cons. In the end, what we need is a secure, robust and supremely efficient computing environment. If you consider all the factors, nothing beats Linux. Traditionally regarded as clumsy, crude and extremely cryptic to work with, Linux seemed to be meant more for geeks. Slowly but surely, this has changed. Companies like RedHat, Mandrake and SuSe now distribute Linux versions that sport stunning graphical user interfaces (GUIs) and integrated development environments (IDEs), much more sleeker and smoother than a monotonous looking Windows GUI. Even five year olds will find it easy enough to handle.  Anything  that can be done on Windoze can be done on Linux too; in fact there is much more to it than any other OS. The good news is that companies like Dell now sell laptops pre-installed with Linux.  Go Linux! And dont bother about philosophy for a while.
      
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      News is that Mark Knopfler, along with Guy Fletcher (keyboards and backing vocals) & Co., is recording his new solo album for release in the autumn of 2004. Guy is even posting weekly  urlLink diaries  of their studio recordings in California.  Mark's got a new Pensa guitar of late, and after taking a look at his fret playing in detail, he seems to experiment with a variety of electric guitars over the years, even though the strat is probably the dearest to straits monomaniacs like me. Stratocasters (the early Dire Straits "strat" sound), the les paul gibsons (the "calling elvis" sound a.k.a. Jimmy Page, Slash, Gilmour etc.), the national 'o' style (on the cover of  Brothers in Arms ), the pensa suhr (MK's personal favorite), telecasters, et al. The sultan of swing seems to have played virtually every electric guitar.  I wait with eager anticipation. It's exciting to hear about MK working on another album, and working, hopefully, on material that is atleast as good as  Sailing to Philadelphia , and pray, not on the lines of  The Ragpickers Dream . Ragpickers was just too country, too celtic and too oldies style, moreover, without any of his signature fingerpicking. Well, we didn't notice it anyways!  Will Straits regroup? "They might!", is what everybody I talk to, says. Not sure whether there's a touch of diplomacy or sheer optimism with that remark. Even if they do, I hope they reunite with their original classic lineup of MK, David, Illsley and Withers. With due respect to Alan Clark, Fletcher and the others who joined Straits in the 80s and 90s, (and I guess, who are still a part of his solo recordings), we desperately need the  best  lineup back on the circuit. Imagine MK playing his pinched harmonics on that fender red strat and David on his own, supplying the "white" rhythm in the background. Nice and laidback. But chances of Straits cutting an album with that lineup are less, given the fact that MK is a self-confessed country music fan, and the other threesome, not ready to don the roles of puppets once again. Personally, a reunion in the form of a live gig is asking and expecting enough, especially to satiate my desire to see MK strumming in front of me, with my jaw dropping.  For now, though, let's just wait and see if the new solo cut is a fresh lease of life for MK fans or just a baloney again!?
      
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, folks, time for yet another music review. And since I hear shouts of "oh no, not again!", I plead guilty straightaway. Music being my be-all-end-all sort of thing at present, I'm helpless. As if adding fuel to fire, is the state of reaching a blogger's block, where I just cannot think about anything else to ramble on. So fellow bloggers, feel free to throw your brickbats. And then, if you prefer movies over music, I recommend watching Jack Black's  urlLink The School Of Rock . Quite simply, it's hilarious.  In my previous blog, I wrote that I was gradually getting over Rahman. Very true to a certain degree, but classic rock isn't a good enough reason to stop me from checking out another ARR release. I sometimes feel as if my brain has been temporarily manifested with some sort of a bipolar disorder, the one - psychiatrists would say - characterized by profuse and rapidly changing ideas. So, in the quest for that much needed variety-is-the-spice-of-life thing, like it happened today, you might find me listening to Led Zeppelin in the morning, and Jagjit Singh/ARR in the afternoon. Got ye all stumped, eh! Hardcore rock listeners try to convince me that rock music is akin to a rabbit-hole and that it takes time to dig in and feel comfortable with it. If you listen to classic rock on the radio, almost 70% of the rock borders on the side of pop, and most of the bands apart from a select few, appear to sound the same - i.e. the same traditional "triads" structure of music. I can imagine how the 60s-70s rock era gradually paved the way for more of the pop and grundge sounds of the 80s and 90s, and its nobody's fault. Music is bound to change with passing generations; and whether it has really evolved further or not, is completely upto the listener to judge. Getting back to the point about radios, because radios aren't for active listeners, and since I  am  one of  them  of late, I don't have the right to lament on the radio scene. Radio, is well...radio! My problem with rock music is, I'm either crazy about it or I am completely dispassionate. Radio doesn't work good for me, because I rarely listen to individual songs. I usually like the works of a band or an artist, as a whole. I'm more passionate about the entire "sound" or musical quality of a band, as opposed to hit radio singles. Nevertheless, radio is probably a fair means of getting introduced to a new genre of music.  urlLink Yahoo Launchcast  is a fantastic concept, where you can tune your radio to your liking by rating music. Moreover, they have a pretty impressive compilation, as long as you take some efforts to seriously rate the music you hear. All Yahoo needs to do now, is to spare a thought for the Linux user.  Anyways, back to a quick review of ARR's latest - Yuva. The music has grown by leaps and bounds since my first listening session a few weeks ago, when I thought it was far too popsy for my taste. It still  is , but not to  that  intensity. Going beyond the conventional pre-conceived notions about music, if I have to summarize Yuva in as few words as possible, I would say it's the "height of experimentation". ARR has gradually reached those unchartered territories as a musician/composer, where, perhaps only an elite bunch of musicians in India have successfully managed to reach. His knowledge of symphonic orchestration, sound arrangements, music programming and the wide range of creative sounds, continues to baffle me. In a sense, ARR is to Bollywood music, as Pink Floyd was to Progressive Rock. ARR uses "sounds" and "loops" which seem to go beyond the definition of traditional music theory. A musician's musician. In many of his compositions, he cleverly manages to catch the listener off guard, with subtle scale changes, sudden introduction/deletion of instruments in the most unusual fashion one could ever think of, pauses, fading ins-fading outs, etc. Critics call it as mere "fusion" of the eastern and western sounds, which, over the years, I have begun to feel, is such a cheap word to describe somebody as talented as this guy. Well, well...I could go on and on about this.  I liked all the tracks, except for, not surprisingly,  Dol Dol  and  Fanaa . Hip-hop/trance-like numbers are a strict no-no for me, and although they might boast of a few typical ARR percussion twists here and there (use of mridangam/ghatam), they're too typical and just too artificial. This type of stuff is  ideal  for rickshaws in Pune, that seem to be adorned with state-of-the-art hi-fi sound systems, blaring jhankar beats all the time. The remaining four tracks, fortunately, are examples of proper music, in their entirety. Opening track  Dhakka Laga Bukka  (somebody lyrics please!?!) has some mind-blowing strings and bass and contains some magical tricks that can only be captured on earphones. At one point, the drums do not sound like they are in a regular musical time pattern.  Khuda Hafiz  is Lucky Ali and Sunitha Sarathy all the way, and along with the harmony, there's a short yet wonderful bit of piano piece that steals the show.  Kabhi Neem Neem  is more of typppical ARR - a classical-folk extravaganza.  Badal  is a tremendous, tremendous song; my picks of the song being the spanish guitar leads (or is it mandolin/ukulele?) and undoubtedly, Adnan Sami's highly underrated vocals.   Yuva Pros : Experimentation, Experimentation, and Experimentation!  Yuva Cons : Could go down as one of those "average pop" albums, essentially targetted towards the youth.  And now, the only thing that will stop the flow of writing, is the smell of caffeine...
      
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There's one primary reason why I've been writing absolutely nothing of substance these days. I am tripping on music. Music and guitaring are the only things I resort to in my spare time (which means "most" of the time). Even reading has taken a complete backseat.  The "trip" can be traced back to just more than a year ago, when I got hooked onto Dire Straits and Knopfler. Since then my taste has gradually acquired a wider perspective, as far as the genre is concerned. Straits led me to the more haunting and emotional pop-rock elements of Fleetwood Mac, the Macs paved way to more of the pure blues (and may I say a melange of psychedelic rock too), with bands like Cream, Derek and the Dominos, and Blind Faith (all "Eric Clapton", in short) occupying most of my listening time. In the meantime, I happened to discover that The Eagles were a jolly good bunch of musicians too. Until a few months ago, I didn't even know that they composed some truly classic rock songs apart from Hotel California. Hehe, what a pity. After (literally) growing up on this musical diet for a few months, it was time to welcome Pink Floyd, which was to be the latest addition to my ever-growing collection of rock. Arguably one of the greatest psychedelic and conceptual rock bands ever to rule the roost, Pink Floyd has brought me to a stage where I've perhaps come to realize what a "trip" means. Jethro Tull's highly progressive and acoustic+blues+folk+jazz escapades are mesmerizing too. Especially Ian Anderson's downright crazy flute riffs. The guy is almost always known to perform with Pt. Hariprasad Chaurasia when he tours India. "Strange" is the best one-word answer to describe Tull. Their music contains extremely weird chord progressions, unheard of before. More psychedelia in the form of bands like The Doors, too, is waiting in the wings, and yes, I've even started appreciating some Led Zeppelin works, even though I would prefer the smooth and husky voice of Waters and Gilmour to Plant's screams. But who knows. Another year down the line you might find me tripping on even more heavy music.  Getting introduced to more and more complex music, like the classical-jazz guitaring of John Mclaughlin, is helping me learn the guitar too; they call it ear-training. Guitaring will always remain on the list of my "hobbies/interests", but it will also be something that will remain on the very top of the list of "things-that-I-regret-not-having-pursued-early-in-life". But nevertheless, bands like Straits are educating me, almost as a favor to me. It's a slow process, and if one is not obsessed, one doesn't take the trouble to understand it. It's infinitely complex. You derive something out of it, only after you listen more and more to it. Eventually a day comes when you listen and know what each instrument is exactly doing.   It would be unfair if I did not express my gratitude to three pals who have been partly responsible for this addiction. So, thanks fellas -  urlLink NK ,  urlLink Sid , and  urlLink Saurabh . Thank you for drowning me in the world of music. As Saurabh, says:  "Isn't it interesting that the rebellious rock has always been the music of choice for nerds? This was the music intended for people out there wanting to overturn the establishment, and yet it has been adopted by people who actually enjoy being cooped up and ogling at source code" . Saurabh, I agree wholeheartedly. Strange world, it is, out there!  I have almost given up listening to folks like Kenny G, Yanni...even ARR to an extent (oh dear!). They are the masters of their own game, and will always remain dear to my heart, but its time for life to take a different course. I wonder how one eventually develops an ear to a totally different genre of music, and not only gets accustomed to it, but a time comes when that is the  only  thing you really like and really want to hear. Sometimes change in life can be a bitter pill to swallow. Betcha, this is surely not the time!
      
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The new Blogger rocks. The templates collection is neat and trendy. Everything is more easily navigable than before. My only concern is about the rounded templates being too narrow; they don't take up the whole horizontal space of the browser window. The narrow width makes my posts look way too much longer than they are in reality (*grin*). Also, for now, I would prefer to stick with my backBlog comments; not too impressed with Blogger's comments feature, it loads up a separate page to post and view.
      
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In this golden age of bat dominating the ball, the news of a bowler (repeatedly) crashing into the record books is very much a rarity. Muttiah Muralitharan - the diminutive, unorthodox off spinner, could lay claim to be one of those few players in world cricket, who always keeps the statisticians busy. Murali manages to give the red cherry such an enormous amount of tweak, that it's no surprise he has tumbled, crashed and banged into cricket's elite list within no time. Unless you are as gifted as a Tendulkar, Sidhu or a Ganguly, who tend to play spinners like they are literally having a ball out there (in quintessential Ravi Shastri lingo), I sometimes wonder how it is humanely possible to read and play a ball that turns square, within microseconds.  "Javelin thrower". Ironically, the only word that I have ever liked Mr. Bishen Singh Bedi say. Because otherwise, Mr. Bedi comes off as one of those really contemptible personalities in the media. His viewpoints are not only injudicious and completely thoughtless, he tends to show an absolute lack of respect for cricketers (ah yes, the famous anti-Ganguly xenophobia). Now, Bedi calling Murali a dacoit and a thief might seem on the harsher side, but javelin thrower, yes, I agree. Very much. Forget the doosras and teesras, even his "pehela" is  so  doubtful at times (*chuckle*). 44 five-for's and 13 ten-for's over a career spanning just 89 matches, beggars belief if you picture a "normal" bowler; but clearly, Murali is not!  A fact even more bamboozling than a Murali doosra is that of the ICC trying to  bend  the rules in order to save his career. Save Murali's career after he plays for a decade and bags 500 wickets!? Can anybody possibly shed some light on  that ? Letting bowlers bend their arms 5/10/15 degrees after studying all the bio-mechanics is utterly non-sensical. This is nothing short of a joke, and is making sheer mockery of a tremendous sport. So, I ask ICC. Will on-field umpires now carry devices like "bend-o-meters" or something to keep track of how much a bowler bends his arm/elbow? Chucking is mostly regarded as a very subjective and sensitive issue, but as Bobby Simpson says, its still very much blatant! And rightly so. Why have a career at all, if the player is not "physically" in the right shape to play the game? Why create exceptions for rules? Moreover, incessant chucking, as in Murali's case, after so-called experts have analysed and suggested improvements, definitely calls for a ban. Personally, the thing that gets most on my nerves is, even after the doosra has been banned, Murali doesn't hesitate to bowl that delivery, and match referres like Mike Procter continue to turn a blind eye towards the case. As I write this, I am reading the news that Procter has reported a Zimbabwe bowler from their second-string side for his action. This is nothing short of petrifying; not because a Zimbabwe bowler should not be called, but because Murali continues to get away with  his . C'mon, who needs Procter, bring on Darrell Hair!  Looking at the current trends in the ICC's approach to tackling the chucking problem and simultaneously "globalizing" the game, twenty years from now, I foresee professional cricket being played the "under-arm" style. Incidentally, the very way most of the sub-continent grows up playing. Perhaps, then, the only person that will have the last laugh is Trevor Chappell, heheheh.  Sorry Muttiah Muralitharan, your record rings a little too hollow.
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wednesday, June 23. Another perfect day in Colorado. Sunny, and temperatures in the 70s. Plan is to raft on the Cache La Poudre river.  "Man, just cannot get any better. Kya weather hai sir..." , I say to Vaibhav, affectionately called "Sir" in the 21C household, as I pack my backpack.  Sir  probably does not hear me, either because he's happily dozing off, or because he chooses to ignore my words -- he's entitled to feel tired of me saying this with every passing day of the summer. Moreover, after all, the nocturnal being that he is, he hardly gets to experience any proper daylight. No worries, Sir.  It's 5:30 pm and off we head into rocky mountain high...  Mike spends a few minutes briefing us on the topic of  'Rafting for dummies' . His cheerful persona along with occasional friendly banter makes him an ideal person to lead outdoor trips like rafting and hiking. Plus, he makes things look very easy. Rafting, in hindsight, doesn't seem too much complicated. Rather, to me, it doesn't seem like a sport which you could discuss and dissect at length. But Mike shares with us lots of inside stuff, every nuance of information he can think of. We are enlightened, ofcourse. I am impressed, because I admire people who can talk and make you listen without batting an eyelid, especially on topics that don't exactly appear to be engaging.    Session I:   Here we go. The raft is all set. Life jackets and helmets are on. Milind and Sameer get ready to hop onto the raft. They take the first strike along with Mike. Meanwhile, Snehal and I drive down to Picnic Rock, the point where the three would be meeting us after paddling downstream. It's the first time I drive a SUV. Not good, because the acceleration was sticky and heavy. Not bad for going a couple of miles. I begin to wonder how  anybody  can be comfortable driving that car for more than a few miles. I am not the only one feeling arthritic -- later on Milind would feel the same.   After exactly 45 minutes, Milind and Sameer and Mike arrive on the banks of Picnic Rock. The guys are shivering to their bones, but all smiles nevertheless. Round 1 went well as expected.    Session II:   Yours truly, Snehal and Mike hop in. Snehal in the front (confused yet paddling with gusto), me in the center (awe-struck by how a simple little raft couching three men, on gushing and rapidly flowing white water could actually float without flipping), and Mike in the rear (our navigator, also paddling). Two minutes into the river, and an approaching,  seemingly harmless wave of cold water slaps my body from the right side, blinding me for a second.  "Wow, that was awesome!" , I remark, even as I frantically try to check whether I am still on the raft.  "What happened?" , asks Snehal. Mike chuckles, as he realizes that Snehal wasn't too lucky to experience the wave-splashing. Shivering starts to set in...which later on, we would realize, wouldn't stop until we reached the warm confines of our home. The water is COLD. Snehal is doing a good job of paddling, for a novice, and gets some words of encouragment from Mike. Mike quips,  "Do you guys want to take the adventurous route, or the safer one?".  Adventure being the name of the game, Snehal and I aren't the least bit hesitant. As we cut through the waters, it doesn't take us long to hit a big rock in the middle of the river. We are stuck, and our efforts of leaning the raft on the side of the rock and trying to force it to move, prove fruitless. Not really a dreadful situation, but plenty of adrenalin-pumping action. Then, much to our disbelief, Mike hops out of the raft, onto the rock, and skillfully lifts one end of the raft to usher it back in the water. Naturally, and as expected, the raft begins to move rather quickly with the downstream flow, but Mike is alert enough to literally jump in the air from his position on the rock, across onto the raft, at the very instant the raft is about to take off downstream. Enthralling experience! Straight out of the movies. I wish somebody's there to film us. Thanks to Mike, because he keeps his nerves all right.  Snehal and I switch positions. I take over the cockpit and the paddle, and Snehal's in control of the other one. We do well. Mike adds,  "You guys should form a team or something, you appear to have jolly good instincts".  Although we continue to have our moments of understeer and oversteer, both of us quickly manage to get the hang of it, and correct our strokes. Never imagined rafting could be so exhausting -- its a terrific cardio exercise -- no wonder you see rowing machines in the gyms in this part of the world. The strange part is, the legs get more sore than the hands/shoulders, which happen to do most of the work. The butt too bears the brunt of the relentless rocky waters. Nothing agonizing though. Our journey continues through some magical points along the river, such as  'Mad Dog'  and  'Rock Garden' , and we especially enjoy subtly manoeuvring through the eddy currents. We are nearing the end of our stint, and are about 100 feet away from the Picnic Rock banks, when suddenly, out of nowhere, Mike who is sitting at the rear end, spills out of the raft, into the water. Nobody, including Mike himself, knows how he managed to do that. Time for some bursts of laughter. Fortunately, Mike grabs a rock and quickly stands tall on it. The water is not too rapid at this point, and although Snehal and I are stuck in the middle of the river on our own, we manage to steer the raft to safety. Another memorable moment to add to the eventful journey.  We are back inside Mike's Chevrolet reliving the moments.  "Country roads, take me home..." . Come home, we do. Tired limbs, and some much needed hot caffeine. There is perhaps nothing better to end a long day with some fine dining at IHOP. And so we did....  Anybody for a better  Wednesday ?!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't especially like to blog about day-to-day happenings in life. For most people though, that's what blogging is all about. They will carefully pen down everything that happened in the last 24 hours of their life. If that is not enough, they will even diligently reply to  each and every  comment people post. Nothing wrong in writing about all and sundry once in a while though...  Summers are awesome in Colorado. Long, sunny days, with intermittent showers (although 2002, I very much know, was an exception). It never really pours cats and dogs here; won't exactly soak you, but is enough to get some respite from the otherwise burning sun, and for the reservoirs. I haven't explored Colorado as much as I would have liked. The #1 thing on my outdoors wish-list is to scale a fourteener (a fourteen-thousand foot mountain, half that of Mt. Everest, if you would like). There are 54 of these in Colorado alone, out of the 100-odd in the USA. California comes a distant second with 14-15, I think. Needless to say, this place is a paradise on earth, if you truly wish to explore the back-country and stuff and are an outdoors fanatic.  Saturday was such a day -- wonderful, wonderful weather. Not too hot, not too cold, a bit on the breezy side with a little cloud cover, the sun choosing to play hide-and-seek. In fact 2004 has been amazing. Right from April, the weather has been more or less very much pleasant. Usually, in this part of the world, a few days of 80-90 Deg F, are followed by days where the temperature dips to 50-60 Deg F. The very unpredictable nature of the weather can sometimes be a welcoming prospect. Ideal conditions for activities like biking, if the wind is behind your back, ofcourse. So, went biking on the weekend to Horsetooth, Spring Creek and Poudre trails with Snehal, Vidya and Katrix. I have done these trails twice before, but every time I have went, there has somehow been a different feel to them. Especially the Horsetooth trail. It starts off with a steep incline, with a couple of really sharp spoon-curves, where, unless you have a good bike with a good set of gears, you have to walk it up whole. My gears slipped once in a while, so had to climb (walk) up a couple 100 metres. Plus, mountain bikes don't help; if you have a road bike, nothing like it. The incline gradually turns into a short flat stretch of road, where you get to see a beautiful view of the front range mountains and the famous horsetooth rock with the clear blue reservoir waters in the foreground. Then its a downhill slope all the way (which I must say, is a thrilling ride), and while you are cycling down, there's another panoramic view of the waters and the mountains. Snehal took these lovely pictures. Click on the thumbnails to check the larger versions. The first two were taken when we were on the Horsetooth trail and the last was on the Poudre, where Snehal did an excellent job of zooming in on the prairie-dog.   urlLink      urlLink      urlLink     I look a bit slumped in the second picture, don't know why, but don't be mistaken that I have put on weight, although I would be more than happy to put on more. We hadn't slept the previous night (Friday) at all, not even a wink, thanks to the usual chat session with Sid, Vaibhav and Snehal. To our own surprise, Snehal and I weren't exhausted even a bit, considering we biked 15-16 miles for sure.  Sunday was more relaxing, catching up on some much needed sleep, most of the time. But come evening, and we are itching to play cricket. Yes, that's our newly found passion this summer. Turning a couple of basketball courts into a cricket field, we are reviving the good ol' days of galli cricket, although admittedly, we play pretty hard, unlike those days where pure, unadulterated fun was the only norm -- not that its not pure, unadulterated fun anymore -- that is the very basis after all. It's just that we think of ourselves as "adults", now, or errr...should we not?! Ah, anything for a game like cricket.
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wake up in the morning today to find the news that there's been quite a furore over the Olympic torch relay in India. Rightly so. It pains me to see Bipasha Basu, Aishwarya Rai and the other Bollywood glam-sham joining the torch relay when honourable sportsmen/women like PT Usha be given a chance of the prestige and honour of carrying an Olympic torch. This is nothing but sheer disrespect of sporting culture and heritage, especially when it comes to Olympics. And then we complain of a population of one billion not being able to produce champions who can win medals for the country.   I won't complain about cricketers taking part in the rally, although instead of bringing in hordes of cricketers, they could have asked a select few to join in. After all they are themselves symbols of courage, bravery, and discipline in the nation's unofficial top sport, never mind if it's not a part of the Olympics. But what is the Bollywood gang doing here? Do they have even the slightest of ideas what a dishonourable act they are commiting by agreeing to take part in the relay? I sincerely hope they do! Aishwarya might be the darling of Indians, but as a citizen of India, she does not, and should not, deserve the right to don the Athens colours and carry the torch. Does she even know what it means to be a part of competitive Olympics? No! Nobody knows, except for the men/women who have actually competed. Aish and the entire filmdom has let us down, bigtime! And the next thing I cannot imagine is people thronging to see her (yes, only   her  ) making that 100 metre dash carrying the torch. Now, am I pissed off or what. I have seen the 2002 Winter Olympics flame pass through Colorado State University, and a very memorable event it was; not only for the University, but also for the few hundred people who had gathered around the picturesque Oval inspite of falling snow and cold wintry conditions, to cheer the torch-bearer.  What a sad day. We have fallen in the eyes of the entire sporting world. Shame on, India.   P.S.: Harsha Bhogle, brilliant as ever, hits the nail on the head in his  urlLink article  in the Indian Express 
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Continued from  urlLink Part III ... The Top Twenty Rock Songs: #16-20   16)  Led Zeppelin - Ten Years Gone   This is one of my Zepp favorites, right up there with most of their other predictable picks, like Stairway to heaven. Again, far better lyrics than perhaps any other Zepp song. Introspective rock, as they say. I always have a fascination for how a song starts off. It more often than not dictates the rest of the piece. One might think that every song starts off in its own good way. But the truth is, songs like ten years gone separate the good from the best. This is one of those songs that begins with lovely bass notes. Later on, there are some nice distorted electric guitar riffs. This one is also in dropped-D tuning (DADGBE).  17)  Led Zeppelin - That's The Way   Oh, that's the way is another classic. The entire Led Zeppelin III album has an absolutely brilliant acoustic side. The album is as good as or even better than IV, and just got overshadowed by IV. With songs like Friends, Tangerine, Bron-Y-Aur Stomp, and this one, Jimmy Page shows why he is a maestro on the guitar. Throughout his musical career Page was known to play songs in all sorts of wierd tunings, that perhaps only he knew. Which speaks of his risk-taking ability, like no other guitarist ever did. He managed to pull this off regularly on stage. This song is in an open G tuning (DBGDGD). Beautiful strumming patterns. Watch out for the mandolin too!  18)  Pink Floyd - Shine On You Crazy Diamond   I could dedicate an entire thesis dissecting Pink Floyd's music. None of the bands/artists/musicians mentioned in this list have had a bigger impact on me than Floyd. (Yes, Straits/Knopfler did, but that was only with respect to guitaring). Pink Floyd's music is on an entirely different level, and you need to be an  active listener  to appereciate their work. Floyd has been one of the pioneers of conceptualization in music. Their music essentially has an ambience and dreamscape like quality, lots of loops (in which a musical idea is introduced, allowed to disappear, and then re-introduced as the concluding piece), fade-ins/outs, philosophical/satirical lyricism, and plenty of experimentation to keep you guessing. A heady mix of psychedelic blues and progressive rock, they were always unafraid to take risks by composing lengthy songs. Shine On is their  BEST  musical piece. The entire Wish You Were Here album is an example of Floyd at the peak of their musical powers. If I had to buy one rock album, I would buy this one! What a concept! (The "feeling of loss" theme when Syd Barrett left the band). The piece is split into two parts, totally clocking over 25 minutes. It exhibits every musical quality that I have mentioned above. Dick Parry's sax is surprising but marvelous, and one of the most creative shifts I've ever heard in a song, from a melodic state to a soporific one. And don't forget to check out Gilmour's slide guitaring in the second part. Absolute mastery! I feel this was one piece where every band member has something to offer in the song.  19)  Pink Floyd - Dogs   Dogs (17 mins), from the album Animals is another example of the sheer profundity of Floyd. Animals is their most underrated work, and is more rock n' roll-ish than any of their albums. Roger Waters compares people to animals and writes songs to reflect the views of each type (Pigs, Dogs, Sheep). Dogs are seen as the users of others and cut-throat pragmatists. Lyrically and technically, this album is really creative. Roger Waters was not only a tremendous songwriter, but had a great smooth, husky voice to go along with (I think he sounds awesome in the album Meddle!). After their success with Dark Side of the Moon and Wish You Were Here, I guess this one was bound to be less successful, and I feel sorry for the band. Nick Mason kicks up a great rhythm in this song and even Richard Wright puts his patented synth effects to some interesting use (like the dog sounds). David Gilmour, is God, as usual.  20)  Pink Floyd - High Hopes   Goodness gracious, what a song to end this list. High Hopes is a post-Waters rock ballad, the finale from their final 1994 album - The Division Bell. A musical career couldn't have ended better. Most die-hard Floyd fans do not especially like the post-Waters era of Floyd, i.e. their last two albums, although not me! It's one of their best written songs, even considering the legacy of Waters (I know it almost doesn't make sense to most, since Gilmour and some Polly Samson wrote this). The theme of the album relates to the division within Pink Floyd that resulted in Roger Waters leaving the band, and the other members searching for an identity without him. Apparently, the album has a different Floyd sound and it takes a while to get used to it. I was practically reduced to tears when I heard this song. Apart from the orchestration, and Gilmour's exceptional ability to make the slide guitar not just sing and talk but also make it sound painful and heartbreaking, the songwriting is just phenomenal, just incredible - do check it out! What a song, and what a great ringing solo to end! Perfect!
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Continued from  urlLink Part II ... The Top Twenty Rock Songs: #11-15   11)  Jethro Tull - Velvet Green   Listening to Tull is a joy ride. Pure, unbridled ecstacy. If you think Tull is a hard rock/heavy metal band, then you'll be mistaken. Very few of their work borders on hard rock. Tull is first and foremost, a progressive rock band that incorporates a mix of british/scottish folk melodies, blues licks, along with wonderfully creative acoustic-jazz escapades, backed up by impossibly dense lyrics. By impossible, I really mean it! With plenty of puns and alliterations, thanks to lead man Ian Anderson, one might require a PhD to analyse all their songs (from 40-something albums!). And if composing such profound material wasn't enough, Ian is the lead vocalist, the lead flautist, as well as the frontman on the acoustic guitar, harmonica, mandolin, whistles etc. If you want to check ONE Tull album, get Songs from the Wood, from which this song is. It's not in a 4/4 time signature, I think. Just notice how the bass guitar, flute and drums are blended.  12)  Jethro Tull - My God   Wow, My God is a beauty. This one's for THE ONE --  "People - what have you done, Locked Him in His Golden cage. Made Him bend to your religion, Him resurrected from the grave..." . Brilliant flute playing on this. Anderson is known to do crazy things on stage - like standing on one leg and making wierd noises when he's actually playing the flute. (Well, ummm...let's say, if I am not wrong, he actually burps in some of his studio version of songs, or whatever that means). Totally crazy. Tull has an exhasutive list of great songs, and it is a pity that I could only include two in this list.  13)  The Doors - Riders On The Storm   Like Tull, The Doors, too, is not a mainstream rock band. Doors is really really psychedelic though. A bit like late 60's Syd Barrett (early Pink Floyd). Ofcourse, its much much better than the eccentricity of Barrett. Myself and  urlLink Sid , who is the original Doors freak between the two of us, have been imagining how Doors would feel like after getting doped. On the other hand, we've been told by experienced dopers that you  cannot  imagine! Doping theory apart, the Doors sound is quite unique. Ray Manzarek is a genius on the keyboards/organ/piano as is evident in this song (and also particularly in Light My Fire). Jim Morisson's improvisations with the lyrics is impressive too.  "Into this house we're born, Into this world we're thrown, Like a dog without a bone, An actor out alone..."  -- and what an attitude to go with, when he's singing. The song has a real haunting quality to it, and I recommend listening to it in a dark room (with no lights at all). Let me know how you feel.  14)  The Doors - Spanish Caravan   I have picked this song solely for its beautiful classical guitaring. Not that the song is bad otherwise. Robbie Krieger's fingerstyle, flamenco guitaring is awesome. I think all the Doors musicians were classically-trained players. And you can see it in their carefully constructed pieces.  15)  Led Zeppelin - Kashmir   Most of the people (including me) who first hear Zeppelin, are guilty of having a pre-conceived notion about the band's music, to be nothing but shrieks, screams, and shredding vocals and leads - "loud noise", to put it in simple terms. However, think about it logically, if not musically; because Zepp is not the numero uno rock band for nothing. I am gradually beginning to realize this myself. I still find Robert Plant's vocals too wild and frenzied for my liking. But that isn't to take away from their immense talent in creating some of the most influential rock music you will ever hear. Kashmir has a heavy Asian influence, the guitar riffs and violin creating a stunning base. This one has one of the better Zepp lyrics too. And I take my hat off to John Bonham. The thunderous rhythm he creates by literally pounding the drumset, is of the highest class. There is a point when everything else in the song pauses for just a few seconds (i.e. no vocals, no guitar, no base, nothing), except for a very shot drum interlude by Bonham. Only a genius can do that. Sheer brilliance!!    urlLink Part IV: Songs #16-20  
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Continued from  urlLink Part I ... The Top Twenty Rock Songs: #6-10   6)  Derek and the Dominos - Layla   This one needs no introduction. It's an Eric Clapton anthem. The song Layla (as well as the album) is considered to be one of the truly great blues rock albums. Duane Allman, a master of the slide guitar, shows why he's so highly regarded, by playing a great solo in this song. Layla as well as most other songs in the album were written at a time when Clapton was deeply in love with George Harrison's wife. Whatever the reason and inspiration behind making music, when genuises like Clapton and Allman are at work, we don't mind at all! Clapton's acoustic version of this song from the Unplugged album is a beautiful piece too.  7)  The Eagles - Life In The Fast Lane   I love The Eagles. Their music is not exactly as profound as some other bands on this list, but this is not the time to draw comparisons. Actually, some might disagree with this statement. After all, how can anybody forget Hotel California? But let us also give them their due for coming up with other equally good (or perhaps even better) quality songs. Take for instance this one: Life in the fast lane from the album Hotel California. The song kicks off tremendously with Joe Walsh's riff. A straight rocker which also officially established Joe in the band. Everybody knows what a great rock voice Don Henley has. Glenn Frey says:  "The song is about the lifestyles of the rich and miserable -- 'We've been up and down this highway, haven't seen a God-damn thing.' -- rich as hell, gettin' high, got everything they want, and yet they're living in a spiritual ghetto."   8)  The Eagles - Get Over It   Get Over It is a tremendous rock song from their album Hell Freezes Over, when Don Henley and Glenn Frey got together again and wrote it after a gap of 14 years. Don Henley has said that it's the fastest song, tempo-wise that they ever recorded, and my god, it sure is an out-and-out rocker. Pure energy song, this one, and definitely has an harder edge (as in the sound) to it than any other of their works.  9)  Dire Straits - Telegraph Road   I've felt this a zillion times. If I had to play music, I would play it like Dire Straits did. They might not be a tight bunch of musicians, but what the heck. T-Road was the very first song that introduced me to lengthy rock songs, or progressive rock. T-Road is hardly  progressive , but it's still epical by Straits proportions, clocking just under 15 mins. I appreciate it more for its overall musical and lyrical structure. MK as usual is brilliant on his stratocaster, but Alan Clark, Hal Lindes and Pick Withers too have lots to offer in the keyboards, rhythm and drums section respectively. T-Road has an  urlLink interesting history  behind it, if you are curious to explore more.  10)  Dire Straits - Six Blade Knife   Only one word to describe this song - subtlety. Grab a decent set of earphones and notice the licks, all harmonics. If you are an amateur guitarist, this is a great lesson in harmonics, although I can bet that after you give it a hear, you'll be so much over-awed by the level of guitaring that you'll end up being a frustrated guitarist. MK plays the guitar such that the fundamental frequency of the string is muffled, but the smaller vibrations of the string continue resonating. Lots of multiple bends. Amazing fillers in between the leads. He's just plucking away subconsciously. The fingerpicking, is all about the feel!    urlLink Part III: Songs #11-15  
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Continued from  urlLink Twenty20 - The Preface ... The Top Twenty Rock Songs: #1-5   1)  Cream - White Room   The very first thing that struck me after listening to this song was the intricate rhythm pattern. Ginger Baker is arguably one of the top notch drummers in blues rock, and his inventive percussion highlights the song's unique 5/4 time signature. White Room was compressed from an 8-page poem to a single page of lyrics and was supposedly inspired by Jimi Hendrix, who himself was a big fan of Cream. Jack Bruce's soaring vocals, Eric Clapton's wah-wah guitar and Felix Pappalardi's viola work provide the ideal accompaniment.  2)  Cream - As You Said   This is a very off-beat Cream song, a band known more for being rock's first supergroup. Cream blended typical delta blues to psychedelic rock but still managed to create a unique sound of their own. They released four groundbreaking albums in just two years and made an enormous impact on rock n' roll. Their wildly adventurous music is reflected in this song. Wonderful acoustic piece, this is. The surprise element is the cello, used as the base. Jack Bruce was asked to play the acoustic guitar by Clapton himself, much to the embarassment of Bruce.  3)  Fleetwood Mac - Gold Dust Woman   If you haven't heard the album Rumours by Fleetwood Mac, from which I've picked this (as well as the next) song, you haven't heard one of THE all-time Classic Rock essentials. The Macs, a hugely talented bunch of musicians, were never quite stable, never quite united as a band, always in sort of a disarray. Love affairs between Lindsey Buckingham and Stevie Nicks, the McVies (John and Christine), and the constant differences of opinion between individual band members actually brought out the best in terms of their song writing and compositions. I am not (and was never) a fan of love songs as such, but the Macs are very very different. They never indulged in a slap-stick style, always penned mature stuff. This particular song is written and sung by Stevie (for Lindsey) --  "Lousy lovers - pick their prey, but they never cry out loud...Rulers make bad lovers, you better put your kingdom up for sale.."  -- great lyrics, these, and a lovely bass guitar to go with. Brings out all her pain after she broke with Lindsey. Stevie Nicks was not only sexy, but I think she also had the best female rock voice once upon a time, during the 70s-80s. Always known to wear black costumes during live performances, she had a mystical aura about her. I am a big fan of Stevie!  4)  Fleetwood Mac - Never Going Back Again   Lindsey Buckingham is/was no doubt a hugely under-rated guitarist. There are very few well-known rock guitarists who play an electric guitar primarily with fingers (fingerstyle). Mark Knopfler, Jeff Beck, Eric Clapton, Robbie Krieger, Chet Atkins, Duane Allman...Lindsey is one of them. This particular song is strictly acoustic though. In fact, if you want to hear a two-minute fingerstyle acoustic guitar masterpiece, then don't look any yonder. This time, it is Lindsey's time to write a song on Stevie (very good writing, again) and showcase some amazing guitar fireworks. The song is in a dropped-D tuning. The only thing that lets me down is the song length - just two minutes!  5)  Fleetwood Mac - Bleed To Love Her   Another example of Lindsey's talent not only on the guitar but also on the vocals. I don't think this one is particularly easy to sing as well as play! What a fantastic chord progression. Nothing more to say. Give it a hear!    urlLink Part II: Songs #6-10...  
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now here is something that could be of some constructive value to the reader, or listener, if you would like. In a four-part blog, I decided to come up with a list of twenty rock songs (by nine different artists), that I feel you really ought to check out. As usual, I provide the disclaimer. Don't regard this list as a "best of" or "greatest hits" collection. Neither are these songs individually rated or listed in any particular order of preference. I've tried to pick songs that are not really run-of-the-mill hits. Meaning, a lot of these songs aren't predictable hits, so to speak, although they are practically still well-known and part of very successful albums by the artists. To further elaborate (if I may..), I have chosen songs by arriving at a certain degree of complexity about them. I find a complexity to rock music that is somehow emotionally very evocative, aside from the actual musical complexity of the song. The emotion is not necessarily sweet or soothing, at times neither happy nor sad. But, as a friend once said, there is no reason why an expression of emotion should always be sweet, soft and "less noisy", in order to be judged good or bad. So, if you are a fan of elevator music, a la Backstreet Boys and Britney Spears, and identify rock as "noise", here's your chance to grow up.  Okay, enough of grandpa talk. Time to  urlLink get rocking .
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After three weeks of one of the most hapless, and unhappening of times in my life, it's back to business. I am trying to apply finishing strokes to my research work; two words that I somehow never came to  terms  with (is this a good pun or is it just me?). Ofcourse, I am also into one of those voraciously-devouring-book-worm phases of my life-cycle. My topic of reading at present is rock music, something which does not deserve any special mention on my already rocking musical abode.  But just so you know, I finished reading this book called  Seventies Rock: A Decade of Creative Chaos . Nice book to keep yourself busy, if you are a jobless soul (thanks to  urlLink Katt , been searching for the right words to describe myself) on a pleasant and refreshing friday night. Chronicles all those glory years, stretching from the early trippy, slam-bang days of Jimi Hendrix right upto the emergence of punk rock in the form of The Sex Pistols and Clash by the end of the 70s. It's timepass, basically. The biggest disappointment for me was Frank Moriarty's (the author) failure to mention  anything  about Dire Straits. How can someone forget Sultans of Swing and Mark Knopfler's cleanest Fender Stratocaster of 1978, at a time when punk rock was stealing the show from the classic blues rockers? Not having Straits' name anywhere inside a 300 page book depicting 70s rock is sheer crime. Even though the book is supposedly personal (which book is not?), it potrays all the big and small bands of that era, except Straits. The fact that Frank is not biased in his writings nor in his taste for British or the American genre of rock, calls for even more surprise as to why Straits/MK didn't deserve even a side-note in the appendix, forget a noteworthy praise or two in the main chapters. Actually, I figured Frank delves too much on the punk scene, one reason why he probably forgot that Sultans not only brought back the fresh blues rock years, but also the art of air-guitaring to solos, on the fender. Plus, he seems to be a huge fan of The Who and David Bowie, both getting ample coverage in the book, almost in every chapter. I haven't heard their music, but if you have and don't happen to be a fan, watch out.  Man, I feel for Knopfler! By the way, I am keeping my ears open for his new  urlLink solo album  releasing in September.  My next reading session will feature a book called  Rock and Roll Music: A Social History,  which presumably contains more subtle, thoughtful and well-researched material. Pretty soon, I plan to move onto the biographies of Led Zepp and Jethro Tull. Great, great bands. Should make for interesting reading.  Not too bad a friday night, was it?
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing special to rant, rave, ramble or muse. This has been a really boring week. Started off with big plans of scaling Longs Peak, but unfortunately for the second consecutive summer, my "Colorado Summer" wishlist remains unchanged.  I will most likely play my first CSU Cricket match this weekend. Had a rather glorified nets session yesterday, but all-in-all, felt good to bowl with the red cherry after a long time, at full-tilt. Nothing like fast bowling, with the wind behind your back and the ball swinging sideways. Hopefully, I can unleash one of those swinging  "bewdies"  and knock some guys over later on in the big game. Yepp, high hopes, alrite! In the next net session, I plan to hone my batting skills and smell the leather myself (perfume balls?!).  Now, let me recommend a couple of good reads. The first is  "India Unbound"  by Gurucharan Das. Good book, if you want to be enlightened on India's  "Social and Economic Revolution from Independence to the Global Information Age" . Great read if you want to know the basic facts about the whole socio-economic situation of India of the past generations, as it touches on stuff like caste systems, democracy, capitalism, economic reforms and a whole slew of other things. It gets boring in the later stages at times, where I felt the author was getting a bit repetitive in putting forth some ideas. But, I believe it's a must read for Indians born in the present generation. Not only that, I  sincerely believe  they should introduce some of the text from the book -- if not the entire book -- in high school history books, and clear an otherwise distorted picture of some aspects of modern Indian history. The book is not only unbiased, but also seems to be based on extremely thoughtful and comprehensively-researched material, as expected from a Harvard educated person. The second book is  "One Two Three...Infinity: Facts and Speculations of Science"  by George Gamow. I remember reading this book sometime during my 8th grade, I think, when my father tried to instill some Math and Science passion in me, after knowing about my horrifying grades in Math and Physics. It is good to get back to those days now. This book is undoubtedly a science classic. Those fun and learn sort of books, written at a time when physics with a dash of math was not considered to be as esoteric as it is today, what with philosophy coupled with metaphysics being the buzzwords. So, if you want to recreate and recollect those wonderous science moments in high school, here's your chance.  Before I wrap things up, as usual, an update on my  "progressive"  music front.  After all, a post that does not have anything to do with music, almost implausible, eh?. These days I am listening to bands like Rush and Yes, who epitomize progressive rock. There is an amazing complexity to prog rock, (like say science or math), that is really difficult to comprehend at first. Makes us realize that musically we are  so  immature. Prog rock was a style that combined rock, jazz, classical, psychedelic and literary elements and emerged in the late 60s and 70s with art/space rock bands like Pink Floyd, King Crimson, and Genesis. In a sense, progressive rock is something like hindustani classical music. The music typically features lengthy material, continuously evolving musical themes/concepts and liberal use of shifting time signatures as well as some wonderfully creative rhythm sections. I recently came across a quote that said:  "Complexity is best judged by musicians..." , and I don't think anybody can doubt that. Even as a novice bathroom guitarist, I now know too well why I am quickly falling in love with forms of music that go way beyond the three chord structure of pop and even classic rock to an extent. On the flip side, the most beautiful things in life are simple, so I won't be surprised if classic rock remains the staple diet in the future.
      
</post>


</Blog>