<Blog>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i bought an aphex twin cd today: come to daddy EP. woo hoo. my eyes are closing. i dont wanna go to school. i really dont know what to talk about... hmm.. flim kicks ass. im gonna go do something that's not this boring. im still, idle. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi hi im playing nintendo now with a friend. yaaay. my site rules, everyone should see it!  urlLink    yaaay  ok im gonna go and d/l more music and play more zelda. buh bye
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im making lotsa things to my site!! woo hoo! its great cuz i now can upload all of my images. i made a forum too! this is  great. mobynuke.net has the worlds best modules like you cant believe! it kicks!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im gonna got away now. im going to post arg. i read funny email
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      roar roberto is next to me. im gonna hit him with the keyboard. "*weird noises*" lol then i started opening his disc drive and stuff heheh 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ive gotta write about what happened today in spanish class (drowning the...) so there.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and no one came to visit me today.. im gonna play with the usb cable
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I WROTE THIS ON THE adress bar: Search `-00000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000                                       BV  argh.  jj is next to me you suck JJ!!! ARGH im gonna hit u with my keyboard. lmao he said OW OW that hurts. its funny hello jj im gonna hit u agin OW whats ur problem? again! "ARRARAGH" again! arg he hit me.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My grandpas dying. remember? well i visited yesterday, and he sez he is extremel bored. he just sits all day  there, and he says that it sucks because the doctors dont let you do a thing "damn heart" he sez.  if he wants to go to the bathroom, they wont let him o unless hes got permission to. He ssays that the worse part is that you have to take your bath in a wheel chair while someone cleans you. lol. then we started playing with the monitor XD when takes a deep breath, the monitor goes all the way up. and then when he exhales, it goes all the way down. im planning to stay with my grabdpa on friday, its better than my life. hoho. o yea, i had to wait for my mom outside the hospital (cuz only two persons can be in, and my uncle was in, so we couldnt go in all of us at the same time (did u actually understand that?) so i was waiting outside the street and people looked at me like if i was some sort of threat (maybe its true). well, i sat down ar the other side of the street, and a guy with a disorbited eye and something sticking out of his chest came up to me and asked for money. i knew he waas not into drugs, so i gave him what i had. actually, it was nothing, i feel like crap now, i only gave the guy 150 colones, but thats all i had at the moment (argh) well, then he gave me a speech about how grateful he was, and may god help me and i was like: "i only gave u 150 man. if i had more id give you more sorry." and then he continued with the speech, and started to walk aimlessly across the park (the park is in front of the hostpital) and asked people for money. then another guy came and asked: "why are you sitting there, kid?" and i said: "im waiting for my mom" "did u already make the line?" "um... no ive got an entry card" (and  i showed a white cardboard paper, with lots of things written on it) "good... good... take care kid..." and then he walked on.... so i stayed there looking around (specially at the policemen who were working on a crash, they had been there for around two hours) and then a face popped out of nowhere so i was really scared and.. "hey, is your uncle in?" "yes mom." and then we walked in to the hospital, while we both saw the drunken cop on the entrancee of the hospital. what an amazing experience. and i talked to him more "hi im back" "hi! hows things outside?" "um... the same as it has always been. grandma woke up with a cold today" "really?" "yea" and then we both looked at the monitor and then stared outside the room, and didnt talk for a long while.  "and.. um.." "hmm?" "sigh" "......" "......." "....................................................................................................................................." and then my uncle went into the room: "ok lets go, good bye dad" "bye grandpa" "bye" and then i looked at him. I dont think he'll survive the operation thats why im going there on friday.  ARGH where are my hedphones?!? i lended them
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So the day has been pretty weird. i just realized that you can upgrade blogger to blogger pro, which has new things that i dont know what they are. apparently some new persons will vissit my site. yay? if u want it to. i had a stupid talk with *someone* from school today, im willing to post the written part (yes, its written) but im not sure if ill have permission. I just came back from math lab. VERY boring say. Why? because internet is not working.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im gonna go sleep, cuz my mom always wants me to go sleep early ARGH
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      remember the guy who is watching in the window? hes still watching   stalking freak neighbor
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       at 22 blog.com im not sure what to do with so many blogs:  this im using it for writing down thoughts. blog-city -- recess in school blog livejournal -- my whole day 22blog -- my shcool log papers (transcribe) (=boring)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      apparently, you can make a free one, but u need the code that someone'll give you (i hope jenni gives me one) and you only get the basic crap. If you do pay, 25 bux for 12 months, u get the full service, with lots of weird things.... like mood, music, and polls. (hmm polls!) i hope my parents pay me some months off (two months off, thats actually an option) and then ill get to work on that one and maybe ill finally leave this crap... or use this a s a thought blog, and thew live journal one as a general blog, where i write big entries about the day (which at this moment, has SUCKED big time, golly XD)  thats about it
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im 4a
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hes got the curtains open, and he's looking straight at me! ARGH
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Theres a dude from the house over to the other side of the street who has been staring at me for like 20 minutess.... oh man, it IS creepy. XD
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi. im in lunch. i am so very extremely bored. the cleaning lady is on my grade's hall, so i cant go through there.... it sucs.... im gonna publish now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ho  ho ho ho ho ho ho  im listening to deep down and dirty by kicked in the head... i modified my blog to show only posts from one day.... but there aint a button. oops. lol lol lol lol lol
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      that when i started qriting today, my writings had a 12 hour difference between the last post? that iz cool. i like blogger, cuz i can talk a lot, and i can use my site. yay.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just jumped around... it seems that if i jump and touch te ceiling for like 13 times, i get tired, so when i jump a can barely touch the ceiling. sometimes i cant. and sometimes i fall. ow.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      went and crapped XD and i dont have to go to school yet!! ( i think... ) ho ho ho ho ho i am happy, ands im playing pete standiong alone by boards of canada... it rules
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      that its not 7... its 6!!! argh
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ITS 7:15 here. i think ive never woken up so early... but my WLAN rules! i can chat all over the house... tthats why its so easy for me to type... ho ho ho man its cold... brrr im listening to chelsea baby while... I EAT! its so cool to have WLAN ho ho ho
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      what would u put as your funeral music? ten tracks  pretty cool : Felipe Messeguer's Funeral Soundtrack  and the box sez: parental advisory exlicit content  lol i wont invite a priest to my funeral: dont want to bore peeps.... NO ONE will get bored in my funeral, even if ive got to revive to make them happy
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im listening to aphex twin's let my fish loose mix. im going to fall down and drop dead.  *drops dead*   yaaay jenni signed in!! (at last, someone who can give a better chat and more words than:  -cool -yea -really? -whoa -awesome -yea? -oh -hmm -rawr -brb  and the list keeps on
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      a long blog.... but i cant it seems just so terribly impossible, i mean, i caan write like 9 pages of an old stupid blog, but i need to publish... hit that publish button... its so hard not to resist!!!  1 way to say no: sorry but theres a disturbance in the force another one: id love to, but the man inside the TV told me to stay tuned. i got those from some textfiles... i COULD write a long blog, i mean, just get all of my entries in one day and make them one, but i need people to know when *exactly* was i writing everything... i cant... resist.... must...not.... press.. button... i need too..... aaarg
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      what would happen if i made a post every minute?  hmm... would i be on the fresh list all day long? i wish i haad that much time
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      nobody is talking to me... please talk to me
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I bought a reese's cup today: look, (a math word problem only for you) i get 1000 colones a day reeses bar are 350 i can afford only two bars a day  AND I LAST 134 SECONDS EATING THE STUPID BAR  arg
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MeTsseguer! therefore, there are patterns everywhere in nature dice: tengo a toooodoth bloqueaaadooooth F£LØ dice: no digashhhhhhhhhhhhth MeTsseguer! therefore, there are patterns everywhere in nature dice: bisita mi pagina amigo pooodfa MeTsseguer! therefore, there are patterns everywhere in nature dice: www.bootlog-tools.com F£LØ dice: de q es? Bootlog dice: ahora mismo solo i¡un blog  as i told you, woo hoo
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      eating tomatoes makes EVERYONE happy
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      in a while ill go out and see if wlan works
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my dad dissappeared... he was eating next to me and when i started talking he was not here so i was talking alone
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      is a really good song... by aphex twin of course... i listen while i eat
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my dad sez my grandpa is dying, (aetherosclorosis) he can stay like that and die the next month, have a needle go thru the artery and get rid of the fat (my dad sez it wont work) and do an operation and have a 50/50 chance of dying. if the opration works, he'll live for 5 more years.... i go for th operation... this has been a weird day... ill write later cuz im eating... my dad set up a wlan for my house... it kix ass!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      whats happening?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      lots of cheap sites, like gallinabarata.com, stink! they should be deleted from this planet! i posted the brutus thing up, i hope someone knows how to use that crap, and fucks every thing up.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so shut up
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im working in lo fi. sucky
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      for being an orange bear. there is not a black bear. there cant be. if cant be changed, everything would stop being fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ....with a magnet hoho. come on you little funny man!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and this is the message body.   sexy aint it?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dont do it anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and now ill have to act weird. im an orange bear. like the one in the aphex twin video? anyone heard aphex? i think not -_-
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im so tired. ive gotta do intro for projekt. gonna work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello again                 ROAR again 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i came back from my epic journey to the mall. it was creepy. i went to the store and watched snow white on the store's tv. it was muted. the blue prince is the kind of person that goes to a morgue and fucks dead people.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i got to go
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      aand i still think this one is better. ill leave this one to my thoughts, and the other for my school journal.  i will spraymount the next and i see to the wall because i couldnt sleep yesterday. its been 5000 nights of me unable to sleep because of some stupid turkish disco. next time, ill be even more perfect.  (vat the hell) and now im russian.... er... roshan, my little fdiend. vatch out! the suvmadine iz on faia!  watch out, or i will hit you with my telephone propelled... chopstick.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wheres my pepsi? im going out with my parents. aw. yes.  well my parents got a creditcard, id have to use my debit card up.     man, i LOVE my parents.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dont hate me because i am perfect. you suck, im perfect, loser. dont hate me, lame ass.   ho. ho.   what? im no one? well no one's perfect, and im no one, you unperfect little biatch.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im making whole new sets of blogs! gotta upload *eyes spread wide, and then i die, and all the world dies, because i invented the world. yes, its my fault math is so hard.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      against key board.  bang bang bang  fdhkvbgshdbkggkklvslgdfbndgkyndbgbtnhngbnhtbnhtgbnhtghbnghghnhnhnhnbnbhnbyhtnhbnbtngnthhgtnhgtghthgnbhjnjmhnnmhj ufujinu  njn nhu jfjuinmfu njnh fn hjnh nhjnhyudhnyudhnyud nhyu dunuy ndhyn yun u hj ddnh u dnh udnh unhd dhny nhd ynd yuynyn und yhunuydnhu  nhd uud nuy hnhd nh ydu yd hyu hyunynh yud nnhnjn jd d dudnud im obsessed. with blogging... its cuz its thoousand times easier than with my old site, and my old layout. woohoo. lets post!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i had to hear the screams of a supid crying cat, i hate cats. i hope the goddamn cat died cuz he didnt let me sleep. everyone that doesnt let me sleep should die. roar. wait.... theres the cat across the window! its taing a gun out! its---  damn i got killed by a cat for the 6th ime in a row. ill guess il;l have to revive. roar. *snicker* wheeeeee. look, ive got spray mount glue! yay.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im listening t turkish disco by fugaxzi, and im stupidly shaking my head from side to side, and i just crunched an ant between my fingr and the keyboard cuz she stepped in my way: the T key. ho. ho. she will evntually die, and suffer more pain than the on she did befor by every time i press the T key. yes, T. TTTTTTTTTTTT MWAHAHAHAHAHH.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am the inventor of tic tac toe! its mine! i bought the patents!!! now, I cant looooseeee. arg. im paranoid. i hate having my back to things i dont know whats going on. maybe it was because I STARTED EATING POPCORN WITH CHOPSTICKS!!! so i wouldnt mess up the keyboard with grease. but im pukingly full of popcorn and i am about to burn it. *keeps on singing*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes, he IS a ninja. golly! (hahahah) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hunh. lol im scary XD. im listening the end credits for age of empires the conquerors. a guy called my phone and asked for a weird name. i dont know who he is. he might be a ninja. i bet he's a ninja. he MUST be a ninja.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why? cuz i saw so XD.im listening to kicked in the head, and theres no one to chat with. argh. my house looks like a hole. agh. i wanna go out!! plsss. what has everyone else done?  im gonna publish. bish. rubbish. ish...mael lmao. ok.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok. i took a shower and now i am really bored. i was calculating how many days hane i live.... a few hundreds more than 5000 dyas. im trying to figure out how to change the links on my blog... hmmmm.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      now ive done it... now on to erasing more files. see you later alliga--- GIAAHHH!! MY ARMMMM
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tuesday, June 25, 2003 - 5:26 pm  Whoa. I cant believe I actually did this. IT'S SO GREAT! What am I talking about? I'm talking about my great blog layout! Ok, look, can you imagine this is my second layout ever? No? IT IS!! Ok. Enough of that. I finalized a CD for Mario... It's filled with great MP3's. I'm listening to it right now... if you just take the Aphex Twin tracks and play them, they take you on a 2:23 hour joyride. Cool hunh? I'm supposed to be doing my math homework, but I don't have my book. I'm gonna play "Let My Fish Loose" by Aphex Twin... It's a remix from the original song by Nobukazu Takemura. Yay. I'm not scared of talking to Ms. Post anymore. She's stupid, and her test was extremely easy. I'm laughing my ass off at you, Ms. Post!! AHAHAH! YOU SUCK! I got a new uh... policy on my blog: I'm trying to keep web language (lol, lmao, brb... etc) at a minimum, because it's supposed to save time, but I don't need to, so I prefer to let myself be clear than to be a poser. By the way, for those who haven't noticed, I'm a straight edge!! Um... what else can I say? Um... oh yea, in Gaia, I made a guild: The Anarchy Guild. I , made it like a week ago, you know, to be in the official guild list, you've got to have at least 10 members; I've got 5 members already! And only a week has passed!! YAY!       Saturday June 28, 2003 - 9:19 PM  Today was so cool!!! I went (still didnt want to) the mall. It was the pain old mall it has always been, until I checked out a CD store... AND THERE IT WAS!!! After endless months of irrelevant search, I FINALLY FOUND ONE!!!! What was I looking for? APHEX TWIN!!! And there it was!! I bought Aphex Twin, Come To Daddy today!! It includes the following songs:   01. Come To Daddy, Pappy mix. 02. Flim. 03. Come To Daddy, Little Lord Faulteroy mix. 04. Bucephalus Bouncing Ball. 05. To Cure A Weakling Child, Contour Regard. 06. Funny Little Man 07. Come To Daddy, Mummy mix. 08. IZ-US  They all kick ass!!! It's not like any disc you've seen, it's got an extremely wide range of songs, and none of them having an similarity except for the theme! (the mixes dont sound alike) Some are tranquil... (IZ-US) Some are demonic (Come To Daddy, Pappy Mix) some are VERY alternative (To Cure A Weakling Child, Contour Regard) and some are really violent (Bucephalus Bouncing Ball). Though this may sound weird, at no moment will the sound disturb you, I could listen some of this music while studying! --- But now, apart from listening to my newly acquired CD, I'm extremely bored. Maybe my mom will send me off to bed soon... ARGH I hate sleeping. I'm not sure of what to write... um... I had this talk with weird red Mr. Powell, I was listening to Minor Threat (no one hears that) and then he came, borrowed an earphone and said: That's Minor Threat? Oooh man, thats cool, they made the straight edge thing! I was more like : shut up Powell, you freaking kid rapist who don't know a shit about what you're saying. Man I need to get myself a scanner. I do way too much drawings. Yawn. I know what I can do!! I'm gonna make some emoticons for my site! Woo hoo.  HI TYSON. duh. lol. (I put that 'lol' there because I was actually chatting heheh.)  ARGH RAWR *dies* NOOOO IF I GO DOWN IM TAKING YOU WITH ME!! *and then i uploaded the blog and went to bed, and yes, i took you with me.* Hmm.      Tuesday, July 1, 2003 8:21 PM  I think: people are weird. We're like fruits that you can buy at a supermarket. We come in different size, shape, color, and if it was as simple as that, i wouldnt even care to think about it, but have you noticed how strange it all is? its not in the body, its all up here in the head, either you understand or you dont care. Out of all the people i know, very few are included in the section of people who, study, analyse, and look back at every second of their life. How many people care so much about the past. drink. smoke. fuck. die. try. compete. lie. 3rd party. defeat. grow. I am amazed at how much crap i write.   Kicked in the head - breakdown Take a chance so you can be free Get out of this hole shoveled deep by insanity Why run and hide? Is it 'cause it threatens you? Trash anger for something new This fad has come and gone  Why can't you release the fear?  Open your eyes...Open your mouth... Open your ears...Don't hold yourself back Open up and release the fear  It's time so open wide Don't fight it let it ride Detonate history Destroy this legacy Why live a lie? You're just getting screwed Talk's cheap you're turning blue Pull the plug and push on  Open your eyes...Open your mouth...  Open your ears...Don't hold yourself back Open up and release the fear  Breakdown! Breakdown! Why don't you breakdown! The time is now! Can you taste it! You've got to kill it or it kills you! Open your eyes...Open your mouth... Open your...mind!      Wednesday July 2, 2003 8:33 PM  ROAAAARRRR!!! I AM INCREDIBLY PISSED OFF SO ILL WRITE THIS IN CAPS.... WHAT I NEED IS SOME FUCKING ATTENTION!!! SOMEONE LOOK AT MEEE!!! IM DEGENERATING, CANT YOU SEE IT, IM NOT WHAT I USED TO, IM NOT WHAT I SHOULD BE! IM STARTING TO GET SICK! AND ALL I WANT IF SOME FUCKING ATTENTIOOON!!! FUCKERS!!!! LOOK! IM FUCKING MAD. sigh. ROAR. arg i hate being mad... im over now. im quiet. lets jump around now, lets jump around like little tykes. woo hoo. and then we'll draw two x's on our hands, because we both know that we cant drink, and that we cant fuck, and that we cant smoke, and we will always be drug free, cuz were the only real persons who wont fall into the extremely categorizable category. lets open our eyes and imagine a whole new world, where there is no religion nor people, its only me, and i cant get bored because there is nothing to do. if there is nothing to do, iu wont be able to compare what i do with something else, and so i wont feel bored. i cant find my plave in this world. i cant and i shouldnt, and we'll all e happy, except me. im boring. still i dont know why people read this... do you wanna know how much i hate you? hahahah,.... now, i OWN this world. i made it. its mine. i can grab it and kick it, because its mine, its like giving a gun to a little kid, and yes, im the little kid. but someone has to take care of the little kid... so i think we can share the world, if u take care of me... right? might makes right. I am right now very pissed. mime. sure! old time hockeey! im happy.   i feel something pinty on my arm. ive got to save fast mom says i will go to sleep in more or less 13 minutes... i dont want to go, i dont like waking up. why are the keys getting so hard? this music really is ecessie i like no music dont. blurry. bluryy. bye itssss slippy tammi. v upi yp,pttpe nur     Saturday July 12, 2003 11:05 AM   I am so bored. Thanks to Gay J, this site is public, so I cant post anything here. Fuck you, Gay J. I'm going to Ignacio's house at 11. I don't want to work. I finally got Cap'n Crunch's ICQ number (My idol.). yay. I could actually repair the button down there. "Why should I waste my time? I don't want it, you can have it. I've got a new name for you, it's L.O.S.E.R.!" -- Loser, by Slapshot. and uh... I found that the same store that sells Aphex Twin CD's also sells Underworld. Woo hoo. My camera fucked up. The button for changing the pic mode doesn't work, so it got stuck on the video type. Now I can only take 80 second videos. No photos. Duh. Oh yea, Gay J also screwed a little too much around with my contacts (o.O). and uh... Gaia Online won't work. Aargh. Maybe I'll post up something more later. I don't want to go, but I have to. Damn. Arnoldo smells bad. Heh. It's eleven. Aargh. Vat da hel iz Cold Fee ooh she on? This sucks. I really dont want to go. Internet suddenly got SO slow. Man, I've got to go.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am sick. of making site layouts, i am now officially only writing blogs at blogger. phone. wait. ok. and uh.... say, im gonna go take a shower and then ill come back and write more. now my problem: how the hell am i going to put all of my old blogs up? like this: 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ƒøяgøттєи says: yeah it does but you believe in god dont you? Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: um.. Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: sometimes Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: when i actually need him, its more like hypocracy ƒøяgøттєи says: oh.... Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: do u? ƒøяgøттєи says: no   Damn we all suck. We should all be ashamed of ourselves, because we are all the same, even if u say its not true.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I also listen to a japanese band called "there is a light that never goes out" they are great! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: what are u doing, Mr After Midnight? Dennis [sXe] says: nothing really, listening to music and chatting with some friends Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: listening to what, Mr After Midnight? Dennis [sXe] says: REFUSED, T NC, UNION CARBIDE PROD. AND MORE(DAMN, capslock) Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: lol Dennis [sXe] says: gaaarrh  t(i )nc Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: all DC? Dennis [sXe] says: no, refused is hc(ve say hardcore here ), noise conspiracy is punk, and union carbide is punk/hc/garage rock Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: ooh Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: im writing down so me listen later Dennis [sXe] says: refused is one of the worlds most famous hardcore bands Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: hmm Dennis [sXe] says: new noise with refused! Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: neva heaard of it, until u told me yesta day Dennis [sXe] says: the somg to listen to! Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: ok.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      apparently he's frome a band. "oppose". they aint known, but he passed on a song.. they kick. It really reminds me of alexisonfire. ju ju. all i know iz that hes a vegetarian sXe.   senseless mentality:  same old story nothing new noone helps you to get through  you fight a distant war a war that never ends you paint on dirty walls the crowd have no friends   help me fight this war (once again) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: im singing dead head Messeguer!   Out of Step   says: whee  Korinamegami : nyao? says: uhm..great
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my conversations on te fone are weird. I get called to see if the cleaning lady/ janitor saw me. well.. she didnt. then i talked about the soc. studies test, and now im installing an IRDA port so i can jump images from the pc to the fone (after like 12 weeks of trying lol)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just came back from school, where a guy was making money out of retarded people who cant understand math [ahem] i think he's gonna earn a lot of money. I lasted--- wait... ive gotta change track... lets put fugazi. ok -- i lasted 15 minutes from school to here, and it was until i got here that i noticed that my dad had weird music on the radio. when i figured that out, it was too late o change it and I died instantly. How am i writing this? um... i can come back to life whenever i want. Damn, gay j's on the fone
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i had a recent interview, because i am very important  reporter : so how do u feel? me : im puking, i liked this cake, but i have eaten too much and now im pukingly full reporter : and is--- *gunshot*  ....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A YES i dont know why i write this. Can i know if someone isits my site? in dreamweaver?I dunno. Whaa?Uhhunh. ah... ok. You dont have a life. no. no i dont remember!oh.XD.What the fuck is a fucking ATB??? ANSWAAA.- im gonna hit nancy with the keyboard. Whats wrong with you? Again. STOP! again. Stop! no! noW! NOW FELIPE! again XD Felipe, STOp agin sig... stoop!! whats wrong with you???  im gonna hand the keyboard to GAY J now.  ROAR I now have control over the blog,a well, nothings is really happening, nancy is leaving and Felipe said AHHHH  Roar again, im bored Felipe wants the keyboard Ill hit him hit it. He said no nO NO and then he stop talking. Ill hand him the keyboard.  Im changing my sig to: I'm gonna hit you with the keyboard. WE CRUSH YOUR HEAD --- rachin.tk  ill look at jj. he got scared and the keyboard is falling off my lap as i type oh no.  again. he got scared. the bell rang so i am going to stroll away.  Its Gay J again, Im hitting Felipe. Hi hitted me back while trying to defend himself, it didnt hurt.  I hitted him again and he said OWWWW  O well not so many W's.   SHUT UP GAY J ITS MAH BLOG!! Y'aLL  XD
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      thish is fun 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      gayj, are u retarded? argh
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im here chatting, and ive got this colgate box next to me, so took it and realized: Man, toothpaste boxes smell good! yum yum. ok
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Congratulations!! You're a glass of water!! . .. um    urlLink   What Drink Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My mom just agreed with me to get  out of here! were going away to the mountian.  take you away, take you to play
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My mom just agreed with me to get  out of here! were going away to the mountian.  take you away, take you to play
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just made an account on live journal. i scratched my head and noticed that i didnt wash my hair right.   ive got loads of shampoo on my head.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You should do the following: 1) Read about security of servers. 2) Read about social engineering. 3) Learn what an exploit is. 4) Learn to program in C and C++. 5) Determine your method of attack. 6) Create, modify, or find an exploit for the servers you are attacking. 7) Hire a lawyer. 8) Beg the corts to let you have a minimal sentence. 9) Tell Buba that he should enjoy you while he has the chance because you will only be there for 15-25 years. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so i started chatting... and a girl told me to try the boob test. heheh XD i did it.   urlLink     im not sure if that'll work
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im planning on writing stories. an anarchyst's story. thatd be cool... illl just write them at school, during the boring classes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im so tired. Im listening to forty days by apollo 440, and its really good. :) :) :) :P :) :) :) :)                                                                                                                             ^ yawn. me ish bored.                                                                                             |   me                                                                                                                              | today was my grandpa's birth day. he's 67. i am 13. i will die in like 50 years. That would be in 2053. kind of cool year to die.its... diferent. every one dies in 1996 or 1987 or 1965 but im dying in 2053... does anyone know Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Turtles in Time? Its a game on the Super nintendo. the go to the futures, etc. im gonna die on one of the last scenes. cool. besides, its my favorite scene. it has really good music, and you travel through the future city's streets. I love teenage mutant ninja turtles.  Power rangers, pokemon, digimon, and all of that crap sucks. its nothing compared to the turtles. power rangers or any of those would never say: "suck it to me baby" "DAMN!" "fuck you!" or "SHIT" in one of their shows/movies. they use cheap ass guns that only blow you away, and they dont even trespass you, teenage mutant ninja turtles has organized crime, death, torture, drug abuse, punks, prostiitution, rape and [pizzas and] kick ass fighting. They fight so cool. and the family message. thats something. and the way shredder gets his ass kicked at the end of the first movie! (splinter the rat throws him off a building and he falls in a trash truck, and the dude, uh... the hockey guy whatever his name was, says: "whoops!" like, sarcastically and pulls down a lever, and the trash truck turns on and crushes shredder's head. It's so good.. and the way the blood comes out of his helmet... blood would never have an appearance on power rangers.    TURTLE POWER
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am nervous. I dont know wha to think. I could smash your head with my hands and not feel anything. I can go on 2 guys and not feel fatigue. I dont know what to think. I need to kill someone. o shit. my dad left some weird movie on the TV and my parents are gonna think im watching porn or somethin. I need to kill.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think that person doesnt have a thumb.    I am going to die. Now.  Im suffering a goddamn break down.  *trembling*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I like to look at peoples pictures. I liked someones picture. No that person got a different picture. It shows more than the face of that person.    I dont like that person that much anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just want to write about something, though there is not much to say. Gabriel tried to shuv me into his house, but i didnt want to, so i said i was having dinner with my parents. Its boring, we dont do a thing. We just play nintendo. By the Way, remeber that i never play zelda? well i played it today. I am retarded. I finished the game (big deal), whats retarded is that i finished it, and then i accidentally wrote a new game over the one i had just beat. ARG. about 6 hours of coninuos play, lost. well, at least i can play in pajamas since the beggining of the game. w00t.   I learned how to (i manage to) make a handstand. I also learned how to write without looking. I still look, cuz its easier. But i could write a lot witout making errors.  hallucinogenne. I printed some fotos today too. I went to the supermarket and bought about 80 dollars worth of junk food. neato burrito. I wonder how blogger will be in 10 years. and me too.  Im probably going over to alex on monday.i dont have a spudgun, its at my gramps, one hour form here, so i dont really know what are we going to do all day. Wheres my copy of medieval? hmm....    I want to say i really want you I want to say i really love you But now i know what youve been doing all this time Its sick to think that i once wanted you as mine you disgust me.  And im going to kill you tuesday at 1 am. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really dont know what to do.  Schools was off yesterday and i dont have anything to do--- that kind of anxiety when you eat chocolate cake with ice cream and chocolate chips with white icing and a glass of milk and vanilla. You know what I mean?   I like to keep my music to myself, i dont like other people who i know enjoying the same music as i do. Alex listens to refused. Lots of people, MAnuel, Robeerto and Ignacio listen to AFX. Some people listen to Against All Authority. Im keeping KITH and oppose to myself. I hate you, people.  I dont know What The Hell happened to ju ju. HAS NOT logged in. Now, if i could only find another suicidal friend or some oppose lyrics, i would be just fine.  Take You Away, Take You To Play.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My google pop-up killer just got to 201 pop-ups.   hooray.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Think I'm joking about your smoking Think it's fair to steal my air You you you you you take my breath away   Don't cry freedom cause you've stolen mine Smoke filled rooms make me blind You you you you you take my breath away.   Leave odor on my clothes Spread your venom up my nose You you you you you take my breath away.   Right to smoke in it's place Far away from anyone's face You you you you you get it away.   Did you ask if I minded For my eyes to be blinded Make my lungs black From your smoke attack   You're gonna burn you'll learn you'll learn You're gonna burn you'll learn you'll learn You're gonna burn you'll learn you'll learn You're gonna burn you'll learn you'll learn   Don't you dare and steal my air Don't you dare and steal my air Don't you dare and steal my air Don't you dare and steal my air   Don't you dare steal my air cause I care 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Compete, compete, do it for the boys Empty barrels make the most noise You're always on the move You've always got something to prove  What the fuck are you fighting for? Is it because you're five foot four? You better be happy with what you've got You'll never get any more  You laugh at a man when he tries You're trying to make up for your size To you life is a rivalry Keep a step ahead of me  SMALL MAN, BIG MOUTH 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just noticed my pc isnt as fast as i thought it could be  its 1.3 ghz.  im out on the balcony, and a plane just flew low
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i like my new blog layout, and found out that the previews contain hidden links XD
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      YOU cant believe how much I hate batteries. ARGH! im out of batteries for the mouse, so i got to get the remote controller and change the batteries. Now i wont be able to change the channel until i get more batteries.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I Am The Walrus  I am he as you are he as you are me and we are all together. See how they run like pigs from a gun, see how they fly. I'm crying.  Sitting on a cornflake, waiting for the van to come. Corporation tee-shirt, stupid bloody Tuesday. Man, you been a naughty boy, you let your face grow long. I am the eggman, they are the eggmen. I am the walrus, goo goo g'joob.  Mister City Policeman sitting Pretty little policemen in a row. See how they fly like Lucy in the Sky, see how they run. I'm crying, I'm crying. I'm crying, I'm crying.  Yellow matter custard, dripping from a dead dog's eye. Crabalocker fishwife, pornographic priestess, Boy, you been a naughty girl you let your knickers down. I am the eggman, they are the eggmen. I am the walrus, goo goo g'joob.  Sitting in an English garden waiting for the sun. If the sun don't come, you get a tan From standing in the English rain. I am the eggman, they are the eggmen. I am the walrus, goo goo g'joob g'goo goo g'joob.  Expert textpert choking smokers, Don't you thing the joker laughs at you? See how they smile like pigs in a sty, See how they snied. I'm crying.  Semolina pilchard, climbing up the Eiffel Tower. Elementary penguin singing Hari Krishna. Man, you should have seen them kicking Edgar Allan Poe. I am the eggman, they are the eggmen. I am the walrus, goo goo g'joob g'goo goo g'joob. Goo goo g'joob g'goo goo g'joob g'goo. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man, i just saw a foo fighters video and they kick ass, im not sure the name of the video, but those guys kick ass, ive never seen a video so good, or creative, or the type you might call *high*. hehe
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today im going to my cousin's um.... baptism yea. It started 20 mins ago hehe. its been a while since i last went to church.. like 2 weeks. minimum. (d'oh!)does anyone know i went to a volcano? yea. we walked like 16 km and my feet's skin started to fall off. I think we're going now, so bye... Oh yea, i got a new cellphone, its got windows smartphone, its really cool, its like 4 years more advanced than all of the other phones out there, its got mp3 internet (www, not wap) wma, camera, COOL. my aunt forgot her candle for the baptism, so they somehow got it. why a candle? whats the candle for? ill find out today. lalala. Theres so much to tell but there is no time.. i wish i was a blogger freak once again. GOOD medieval total war's download will finish in about three hours, that means that when i come back, iwill already have the game. GOD! one hour! :D:D:D:D  I dont know what else to say, my dad bought something to make my bike stationary, (ive got a road bike, and you dont, hee hee) and figured out that my bike is too small already. the only way to make it fit is either buying a new handle, because mine was a small one or buying a new bike. The new bike will be cheap, because the guy who sells the bikes is a friend of my dad (like all of the other bike shop owners) and will accept the used bike and give us a cheap price for the next one. my mom says lets go bye  okbyethanks.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      it is until now that i started coding. i am 14 years old! ITS TOO LATE, MY LIFE CAN GO TO HELL NOW   i should have started earlier, why didnt i? im the worst thing ever happened, im 14, im too old to learn, im too old to be anything at all
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why do i suddenly think someone is copying what i do? step by step?   the person is.. a code writer a phreak  and i think he's sXe, and i think he's copying me. that creepy, and i dont like it
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm tired. My mom just hired a maid to come and clean the house. Im not free anymore. -_-  I'm outside on the balcony, it rocks. Hehe. I had caesar salad today. I ate two bags of it. I dont know why, but some chilli was in my mouth, and I hadn't noticed. Weird, hunh?  I'm kinda tired. I dont want the day to go by... nor my laptop's battery; I finally got my docking station back. I HATE IT!!! The PC keeps undocking by itself, hahah.  I wanna get two more batteries. My PC can hold 3 at a time. The only bad thing is weigt. Meh. Hahah Wheeeeeeee!  So I just finished proof-reading this entry and I noticed that the first three paragraphs start with "I'm"
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I Didnt Like It. Wheee.  I got there, gave the gift, sat down with gramps, ate bubble gum, sat down, looked at kids, sat down lor like 1:30:00,  talked to people I dont know, ate pizza, ate MORE pizza, ate bread, ate ice cream, ate sugar packets, ate candy, used camera, got full of cake icing, cleaned my shirt, disposed of the camera, said bye, got bored, got on car, listened to music, got home, looked at the repaired docking station, got bored on gaia, received avy pic, now, will torture Pizza Hut cashier 'till death.   This day was boring
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i  lIKE tYPING lIKE tHIS
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im so bored, today i will go to my cousin's birthday. he's uh... 4? 3? im not sure, my other cousin's baptism was really boring. As if i could say much about it hehe: I went to Quique and bought... What did I buy? I bought new shoes: they're the kind I always use, some white Reef shoes that look a little too tight. I still like them. I also bought a long-sleeve red Quicksilver (?) shirt and a yellow short sleeve one. Um, some weird cargo pants of some fabric and because of going to the store we got late to the baptism. How late? The church had closed and the mass had ended. Bleh. We went straight to my uncle's house and spent the day (3 hours) there. I went to the park with the little kids (they're all younger, so I can't really make comments, because they're too young [or stupid] to understand. I think I get along pretty well with the kids. They bore me too much, though. ¬¬ Yeah. When I  grow up I wanna have all of Aphex Twin's discs. And listen to them all day haha. I just took a bath and my mom got home. Time to get dressed.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a weird dream esterday. I dreamt that ppl in the past before discovering "oleo" i think thats oil paints, used to keep watercolors inside them, and they had fishnets inside them to keep the paint out.  I dreampt this because: i learned that ppl before discovering oleo, used eggs. This girl, orestria, talked about her fishnets falling apart in the guild, and talking to my dad about having a fake heart and what would keep it in. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just read the whole blog... its so cool i remember everything lol  sorry for not writing throughout my vacations. ill write at least one post per day i swear!!!!!!  bla
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why wont any of my contacts talk to me?  o well
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gay J came home yesterday. He fucked around with my contacts for a while and then we looked at he pc for the rest of the day. Why do I think he doesn't really like oddtodd.com?! Hah. We also played N64 for a while, because I rented my gamecube (like if I even touched it). We decided to drink ginger ale until we died, but after a glass of it his parents came home. I finished watching Saturday Night Live by myself, and then my mom made me go to sleep. So that I could wake up early to write this. Meh.   The End
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAHA.  Today taking a shower was fun.  I don't know why, but when the neighbor and I use the water at the same time, only one of us gets hot water. The one who puts the water on second will get the hot water, and the other on will lose it and get the shower to pee out cold water. I noticed that when I lost the hot water to my neighbor, if I turned the water off for like 15 seconds, I would gain the water back. I think the neighbor noticed this too so we were like turning the water on and off; when I lost the hot water, I could hear my neighbor's water knob turning. It was really fun, we spent all of my time in the shower fighting for the hot water. I don't know, I think that's the highlight of my vacations and it made this day much more fun than I thought it wuld be heh. La!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.go-gaia.com/index.php?referral=bootlog@hotmail.com
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
                                                      
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      tere are just some people that shouldnt have come to my life...  AAARGH I AHTE YOU STUPID WANNABE HACKER LOOK AT WHAT YOU MADE ME, FUCKER  ok.  did i tell you my spanish teacher is gay?  i mean, he really is, and he's also perverted, today, he talked about boobs and how 12 year olds have boobs oO. yeah. oO. then he put us a perverted story for homework in which the sister and the brother have sex. OO. THEN,  he started talking about sexual abuse and stalking. he started to caress someone's ear and said: if anyone does this to you, this is molesting.  -_-U  Felipe Gurdian made a "Caca Krispis" XD drawing and got a yellow slip. IT WAS FUCKING FUNNY. ok  i cant think of anything right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      its never too late to be early or to try and maintain some scrap of integrity and certainty...I guess. But I wont apologize and 1977 was a long time ago. I dont care how things were I wont apologize. Fuck you. the Alamo has been penetrated and there is little hope for the white man so hop on your rainbow and ride it into oblivion. For all I care you can be early or late, what ever.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      sorry ppl im sorry for not having said EVERY DAY of my life. nut i just have to.  ok so ive only blogged once since i entered school. Oops.   So what did I do today? Let's see...  I found out that my graphics design teacher is sorta deaf, so he uses an earphone. Ooops. Maybe that was why when i talked to him he didnt hear me. Heh. He also kinda doesnt like me. Maybe because im the first one to finish my Flash assignments (half an hour before someone else in the class). So he tries to find something in my work that's wrong. He makes me do layers and rename layers. He also tells me to delete frames and do it again but the short way. Ok, well, at least thats better than getting a 50 on the first class of the year.  I went with Gay J over to the library and we practised our graffiti sigs. My graffiti nick is SoulLess. I also liked Stiffy. It sounds cool, but I like SoulLess best. Where did i get SoulLess from? From Muse - Newborn. There's one part in the lyrics that say: soulless is everywhere. They're not talking about me, but if they were, It would mean that I'm everywhere hehe.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      AGAINST ALL AUTHORITY LYRICS  "Nothing To Lose"  He's running wild through the streets at night But he's hiding in the shadows by the break of day He's got a clip-on Spyderco knife But it's just for keeping the wolves at bay It's 2am, fucked up again He's living in the bottle cause he's living with the pain Insane, poking his veins, he's standing in the rain With nothing to lose but everything to gain Unwanted and unforgiving He's tired of fighting and he's tired of living here Swigging beer with nothin' to fear He's got nothing to lose so he's always winning He's suffocating, the pain can be excruciating And liberating, it helps him forget the worlds he's hating And now he's waiting, there won't be any negotiating He's got nothing to lose He's been beaten and he's been bruised He ain't taking anymore of your abuse He's had enough of their institutions And all the rules he was told to obey They offered him no solutions So he hit the street before they put him away In a deprogramming youth care center To rid him of his insubordinate ways "You know that boy ain't right" is what you hear his parents say down on the world and down on his luck he's got nothing to lose so he don't give a fuck about shit taking risks in the street throwing bricks he's got nothing to lose but you've drove him to this trying hard to forget the past he's sleeping under the overpass of 1-95 just trying to survive just waiting for the moon to arise 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I FEEL SO FUCKING APATHETIC I WANNA KILL MYSELF AND EVERYONE ELSE DAMMIT I HATE YOU ALL AND IM SO FUCKING PISSED OFF IF I COULD ONLY DO SOMETHING WORTH THE WHILE IN MY FUCKING LIFE I WOULD BE FUCKING GRATEFUL  4 FUCKING COMMANDMENT     DONT FUCKING GET MAD AT YOUR FUCKING PARENTS HOW THE FUCK IS THAT GFONNA FUCKING HAPPEN? DAMMIT IF I AT LEAST HAD SOME DECENT PARENTS WITH A BIT OF FUCING COMMON SENSE I COULD PROBABLY GET TO IT, BUT MY FUCKING PARENTS ARE SO FUCKING INTRUSIVE I CANT EVEN GO ON MY GODDAMN LIFE!!!!!   AND YES I HATE IT WHEN THEY SAY IM WORTH NOTHING AND THAT IM A FUCKING BUM IF THEY ONLY KNEW WHAT THE FUCK DO THEY MISS OUT WHEN THEYRE NOT FUCKING HERE
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      THIS IS SO COOL  //I actually managed to spike my 4 inch long hair today! XD  it looks so cool heres what u gotta do:  -get some gel, hairspray, and your hair  i made big chunky spikes, so what i did was to wait for it to dry when its dry, i work spike by spike without water.   what you do to each spike:  you grab a chunk of hair and twirl it up. While holding it with one hand, you put gel on it with the other. i put lotsa gel on it while i was at it.  after youre done with your spikes, grab the hairspray and put it all over, lots of it, or itll fall after a while.  youre done! dont move until its kinda dried, cuz itll fall :P look at the pics:  urlLink SpikedHair002.jpg  and  urlLink SpikedHair003.jpg 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Conclusion.doc   et le abstracteu   urlLink abstract.doc 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      varas   urlLink Introduction.doc    urlLink Objectives.doc    urlLink Objectives[1].doc    urlLink Bibliography.doc 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OMG OMG!  XP  guess what!!? I JUST WENT TO WATCH um... 28 DAYS!! YEAH!!!  its so good its one of the best movies i have seen in about... a big while :P  I had to lie to the ticket dude to let e in, and i accidentally said i was 16 and i was born in 1984.  but if i WAS 16, i would have been born in 1986.Oo and im 14, december 28 1988  WEL LTHE MOVIE KICKS ASS  the movie is about (dont read if you do care for spoilers) a disease that enrages... things (hhumans, animals, bla) and everyone gets it, but only a few number of people dont catch it. Well i liked every single second of the movie i liked, because its really that tense. in one of those parts when there is supposed to be lke a big suspense, i grabbed my dad's arm violently and he jumped very high XD XD XD  that was the highlight of my day, 28 days.  but some of the parts in the movie were pretty obvious,  [spoiler]      like the part in which they have to decide between going underground or the safe fields Oo. or the fact that all europe gets infected but no one helps them Oo. or the fact that infected people dont fight each other Oo. the activists on the beggining of the story were pretty stupid too, like: oh theyre infected, and the disease is intravenous, but releasing them and getting a bite shouldnt be too dangerous. DUH!  oh and my dad also bought a wireless keyboard for the ipaq. its model is 3090 or something like that. Its good, and it has a mirror because the guy who designed the ipaq was stupid enough to put the IR thingy on top of the ipaq Oo.  im talking to sarah about 28 days and she says she was talking about it like 20 mins ago with her sister :D im tired and my headache is about to start.  today, by not having spikes at the movies, i noticed the difference between EVERYONE staring at you like if you had done some very sinful thing, and having like two persons just look at you and then look at something else.  im thinking about buying a shrits that i saw that said: "keep staring, i might do a trick" while having my spiked hair. itd be good for a laugh. :P ok so im uploading this and ill see wat ill do for the rest of the day (sleep, perhaps?)   cya!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im doing like, drawings in class, and i drew a little punky guy, and i liked it, and it came to be that it is easy to draw, so now ill draw it a lot and it will become my main drawing character. It kicks so much ass, hes got a spiked mohawk and long sleeved shirt, and and and... im making more characters, which i suppose would comopose like, his friends or something, and theyre all punks, and theres a loser who is like a bouncer/enforcer, becuase i really hate them, cuz they dress like sissies and act a little too over the top of tuff. Im thinking about adding more stuff to it.   so long amigos dee doo   Against all authority Freedom  Everyday i listened to you and nothing's ever good enough you're always complaining about something you act so goddamn tough but all you ever do is let someone do your thinking for you and you have no respect for my opinion well at least i think for myself i`m not brainwashed to think like people that rule i'm not a pool and i'll rise i wont compromise and i'll never give up, i won't walk walk walk away there won't be another day when i can say hey hey hey... freedom you talk to me i see your lips move but the words that come out aren't yours they're someone elses you dangle from their strings beneath the wings of the eagle you push but i'll never fall i'm not the only one whose willing to stand up.. we've had enough your laws just benifit you we watch you get richer as we get sicker and we'll rise with battle cries and we'll never give up WALK WALK WALK AWAY THERE WILL BE ANOTHER DAY WHEN I CANT SAY HEY HEY FREEDOM HEY HEY HEY
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my cares.........   listen up. its been a bad week.  On saturday i went to a party. It was kinda boring, but i still went. (with my spiked hair) so people didnt really like me/my hair and decided to undo it. two spikes fell off. It was raining outside, and most of the ppl were outside. I went with them. unluckily, i was so bored, that i just had to talk to someone, and decided to risk my spikes. Oh well, i ended up undoing them after they were totally wet. (falling down wet).   People keep saying im not straight edge. Some ask me why the hell would i want to be one (alex and may more). Others think its retarded, and others...   just dont care about being straight edge.    like, out of the about 8 people that i know who are straight edge, well.. break their edge every week. (oO)  AND THEY STILL KEEP SAYING THEY ARE STRAIGHT EDGE (which kinda makes me feel that i should beat them up, but im making my best to keep pacifism at hand)  sigh. The fact that they consider themselves straight edge and do not think of it as life makes me feel insulted.   im still straight edge, i will never drink smoke or fuck, i am sorry for whatever errors i might have done, (i actually feel like i started a fad, which makes me look like an idiot) i can still think, and i will have my edge for life.   i hope gay j reads this because im kinda getting mad at him. he's just way too stupid and weird. specially when he's mad because its kinda funny, he talks to you in the same voice he talks to his pets.   ...      HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH  ok.  gay j, you should also learn to adapt (but not submit) to your surroundings, AND LEARN ABOUT PHYSICAL HARM  did you know that poking someone with a pointing stick at probably more than 10 km/hour inside the ear might cause severe damage? did you know that pushing someone on the stairs can also be a problem, that throwing 3 kg rocks at people's feet with a bit of strength might do something?  well you did that to jose alvaro. you also tried to attack/kill ignacio with a piece of broken glass but you fell and ended up cutting your hand (RETARD XD). well i actually wanna talk about that today, and too bad if you dont, cuz its my site and im feeling authoritative.   its not a rant, im just showing you how stupid you look. Remember the piece of wood (the one that i tore off the desk)that had some nails sticking out of it in the library? DO YOU REMEMBER POKING ME WITH IT? XD well whatever i dont care. anfter you poking me, (which hurt a lot, thank you for hammering a nail at my ribcage) i punched you? well i dont know what happened but whats kinda funny is that you got mad because you ppoked yourself because of me punching you.    XD  ok im gonna change subject again.   Remember the story that i made (the one where i cross out parts of a sentence, thats called fred james or something like that)? i showed it ot ms post. ACK bad idea. i talked about the main character smoking pot. Unluckily, she didnt notice that the main character (or the narrator) was a protagonist, talking in 1st person, and she thought that it was me talking about my day.   well first of all i dont normally shoot tvs or dogs, neither do i wake up at houses that aint mine and steal lamborghini diablos.    AND SECOND IM STRAIGHT EDGE  well after letting her know that i am not into drugs, she got pretty pissed at the fact that i hate bush.   i think she's right wing, or she's up for war, or she hates everyone bla bla bal   then i showed her my capitalism notes. she liked them, then we debated on why shouldnt capitalism exist (i dont want capitalism)  it has been like the best conversation (and probably the most intelligent) i have heard in MONTHS.  it was so cool i had fun. i wish i could make myself heard once in a while. I AM NOT A FREAK.  my mom is so weird. she always thinks that im failing every single subject at school. she thinks the worst of me. maybe she loves me, but the fact that she cant trust me when i tell her that im doing good offends me.   im not your puppet.   i will not tolerate thiskind of behavior. ive grown, im opinionated and im strong, so shut your mouth, I WILL NOT OBEY. this might not e in my rights, but i knw what is good for me and i can think, i know when there is something wrong.   disobey  against all authority  hey disobey and im not gonna listen to what you say hey disobey im not gonna listen i wont listen to you when you say im not aligned i wont listen to you fucking right wing slime you try to hold me down but i pull myself back up lets just skank together  and PICK IT UP  GO!   *jumps around*  bye peeps  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink BLA BLA BAL.doc  urlLink Fossil Fuels.ppt 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      mae juan jose, estas son las cosas q le tocan a ud.  health (q le hace a uno) alternatives (otros fuels) y la conclusion  aca esta la bibliography  http://www.enviroliteracy.org/subcategory.php/21.html http://www.darvill.clara.net/altenerg/fossil.htm http://www.solcomhouse.com/fossilfuels.htm http://www.ucsusa.org/clean_energy/health_and_environment/page.cfm?pageID=88 http://www.oneworld.org/energy/fossil.html http://www.doc.mmu.ac.uk/aric/eae/Sustainability/Older/Fossil_Fuels.html http://www.umich.edu/~gs265/society/fossilfuels.htm http://www.wri.org/press/lancetnr.html#summary   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAPPY HALLOWEEN. I just wanted you to know that I waz thanking of you. STAY OUT OF TROUBLE AND DON"T DO ANYTHING THAT I WOULDNT DO call me at 928-343-4073 if you get this card plz  LOVE YA LOTZ  ME   - Amber     ======================================   ok and.. im obviously not gonna call that number because, apart from being shy, hating my voice and thinking that that number is fake, im notgonna make a damn call lol.  is there any phone number checker in the internet? Oo im gonna check
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well its halloween again. for this halloween, its 11:23 a and im waiting for my mom to come pick me up at school at about um...12... maybe later >.  then im gonna stay at my grandma's all day long until something happens. My dad will then pick me out, we will check out the colored gel (its realy cool) maybe buy one, if the colors aint too gay, and then we will go check out a boxing club to see if i enroll or something. Then at 8, theres a [15 birthday] halloween party. i will probably take rene to the party. if i can, he lives about... very close to my grandparents, like 4 kms away from my house. well then i will take my spiked hair to the party again, well check out later how did ppl like it.  oh yeah, um... to go to the party you needed " halloween colors" like purple, orange, black, yellow.. (yellow? wtf?) and i didnt have any of these colors so we went and bought clothes, but i bought some coffee color carpenter[-like] pants and some weird polo shirt [no, not the brand] and some converse black boot shoes. i like my new shoes. i got home and put some yellow shoelaces on them. yay.  rene's number is... 285 24 01  yeah. bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i remembered that when i was like 4, i was sitting with my parents in my old house, and my dad was sitting on a grey couch that we had, and he was reading the newspaper magazine, Viva, and my mom was sitting on the sofa too but on the part where you rest your arms, and i rememner that infront of that couch was the living room, which was very small like 3meters squared, and we had a small sony tv and more grey couches around the TV, and i ran up to my dad and sid: daddy that says Viva, because i had learned to read somewhere in time near that moment, and then my dad sat me on his legs and i stared at the newspaper and i dont remember anything else. I would give my life to be there... when everything was simple, i didnt really want anything, and my parents either couldnt afford what i wanted, or they just didnt want me to have it. and i was ok with that. and so i didnt really have a lot of toys, just loads of books, and my room was dark and small, and you could only walk a bit around my bed. my room had this large window that led to the room where my mom washed the clothes, so she made the landry at night and i remember that i couldnt sleep well because of the noise.   I also remember one time in my old house when i was like... 5 or 6 that i was sleeping, and an earthquake started, and i was scared so i got out of bed, and it was so dark that i confused the closet to my room door because they were next to each other and i went inside and bumped against all the clothes hanging and realized where i was and it stopped trembling. then i went to sleep with my parents. ^^  thats about all i remember. oh in 4th or 3rd grade, i remember that i had gotten sick (well manuel actuall told me this) (but i remember getting sick and him calling me) and so i didnt go to school that day and manuel called my house to see if i was like, ok and i told them that i was fine and bla bla bla and then the call ended and the day went on. like, 4 months ago, manuel told me about that day, and he says that in the morning an earthquake started and he says that he remembers the big book shelf i had next to my bed and that he thought the tremor had made it fall on top of me, and since i wasnt in school, he thought that i had died or something. so he called me and asked if i was ok. it makes sense now hunh? the moment when he called me started to make sense the day manuel told me about it.  -------------------------- Minor Threat - Salad Days --------------------------  wishing for the days when i would wanna shoot baby has grown older its no longer cute man, too many vvoices theyve made me mute baby has grown ugly its no longer cute  but i stay on i stay on where do i get off? on to greener pastures the core is getting soft look at us today weve got something back waiting for our moments theyre just not coming back man im serious,  about the stuff we lack dwell upon our memories but there are no facts on i stay on where do i get off on to greener pastures the core is getting soft ( do you remember the time, i dont know, it fact it was about 3 years ago  [bla bla bla] ) wishing for the days when i would wanna shoot baby has grown older its no longer cute man, too many vvoices theyve made me mute baby has grown ugly its no longer cute  but i stay on i stay on where do i get off? on to greener pastures the core is getting soft (do you remember when... yeah so do i.. we called those the salad days and do you remember when... yeah so do i we called those the good old days whatever,  i call it A LIE  ======================== 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      AGAINST ALL AUTHORITY LYRICS  "Court 22"  I was raised in a trailer Always told that I was a failure Never thought that I would get outta there My father kicked me out when I shaved my hair Never fit in with the other kids Singled out because of where I lived I learned to fight at an early age Court 22 my aluminum cage I got the music the music's got me The underground sound Always sets me free I got beat I got punched and kicked Cause I didn't fit in their social clique I never ever felt like I belonged I thought that everything I did was Fuckin' wrong Punk rock was my only escape A new found spirit no one could break I turn up the music and feel the beat It's the only thing I ever want to keep
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      how was my day?  It was sort of... uhm... dissapointing >.  Upon arrival, our graphic design tests were checked. We were supposed to do an animation using whatever method we preferred (frame-by-frame or motion tweening) and so I chose to use frame-by-frame because it was the most suitable one for that type of movie (a jumping robot, which moves every part of its "body" [composed by a tin head, a tube and some sort of plate in which it stands]) and what did I get for a grade? 25! (out of one-hundred) YAAAY!  I hate Mr. Escalante he's like the most retarded cripple ever created. And why did i get a 25? because I used the most appropiate way for a particular movie. That what happens when you look too smart for [a cripple] someone. WHAT A FUCKING CRIPPLE... I wish I could just steal his earphone or something [which would be really funny, BTW]  and then, in drawing, the teacher checked out sketch-books. Oh man. you wouldnt believe my grades, they were so bad, and my art teacher thinks im retarded or something... "This isnt switzerland... how should I know it's not switzerland? I could say this is in africa, the US, costa rica, anywhere!" "but there arent any.. alps in those countries?" "SHUT UP DONT DISCUSS WITH ME YOUVE GOT 27!!!" so basically a 27 is a very low low low low low (...) low low low low low grade. >.  Stupid pothead.  Anyways, then I went to french, which was ok, then to lunch, when Max[XD] made me follow him around because he has no friends, and his popularity [his what?] comes from playing paintball [and smelling real bad] Because i had no other choice as to follow him or not, i went and read about fascism. Now I really know what fascism is, and learned that its pretty bad. Oo;.  Then in spanish, um... nothing special, boring as always. I drew a bad face and then listened to more music.  And then I... came home and ive got to start and finish a proyect for tomorrow, math homework, and uh.... thats it. ^_^  I better get to work , bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      today im gonna try to spike my hair with some bar soap. ill check out how it works. if it does, i might get a few pics.  then im gonna test drive bar sopa on the weekend.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      expecting at three will get green hair dec 19 will buy dye soon looking at msn trying to waste some bandwith with small msgs looking at people who have blocked me going to shoot potatoes today going to laugh at chilenillo listening to djey music gonna change to alexisonfire in a second nice whit spikes running out the window window window window sill will peoplewho have blocked me tralk  to me why did they chocolate bears flying away eating chocolate bears you cant hide my eye is everywhere velvet plaster breaks in through your plaited garment blood sphinxes everwhere where is my extasy on the palm of my hand race through me like a band of bees never gonna forget what you did to me swwet vebngeance bleeding from my eyes fell down on you bruises in your soul tv set racing throught the bathroom floor couldnt help but shoot my eyes bleed sorry about the fall i didnt know errors could be so big big enough for the world smirk across my face wanna punch my stupid look bread jumping out of toaster  ok wtf was that i dont know sweet dreams fuckhead
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey cool haha its fake tho  urlLink trimmed green hair.JPG 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      youuuuuu...laugh at me  because you think you’re so tough listen up and keep in you mind I`ll get the last laugh!  STRAIGHT EDGE CREW and I can smile because I’ve got  x-clusive lifestyle  just one more you don’t know when you’ve had enough you can’t stand you’re falling down tell me now: who is tough?  STRAIGHT EDGE CREW smart enough to stop wide awake we`ll be on top   you lie on your bed spinning around, trying to hold down the things you ate you can’t recall, cause your mind is gone but you know the score you don’t like it, but you still go on the peer pressure; don’t be like everyone else!  STRAIGHT EDGE CREW we’ll always be standing together individually  -----------------------------------------------------------------  guess what? oh nevbermind, i dont eve want to tell, gay j is a lying bastard, he told ppl i had deleted everyone so that they wouldnt talk to me bla bla bla bla  STFU  and uh... mr escalante (graphic design) the freaking cripple sent me a red slip because i had wet hair and sprayed it on the table  go fuck yourself  "im not gonna bend to fit society im not gonna remove whats deep inside of me moneys your god its got no hold on me a puppet on a string is all youre ever gonna be"  well um what else? what can i say?  theres something deep inside of me that you cant see or touch and theyll never take away from me no matter how hard they try; theres fire fueled by hate and its burning deep inside of me, and i cant take it anymore: society.  uhm... anything else?  im pretty pissed off at everyone right now, so i wouldnt give a damn if you died this instant, wether you be pretty, nice, egocentric, rich or a true motherfucker, to me youre all the same right now, and ill smile the day you die oh and to mr escalante:  one day i started to pray my eyes looked into the sky i asked god why life is so hard he turned away and i started to cry you turned your back on me so il turn my back on you fuck your system and fuck you too you tell me to follow your rules but how the fuck do you expect me to follow them  when you cant even follow them yourself?  youre just trying to keep me down! TAKE ME DOWN! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      sorry i just dont care much about my blog, so uhm  damn so much time has gone by and i wanna say so much many things but theyre thousands of experiences :(  lets see... lets start by saying that ms klein is not our teacher anymore. she had to go to the hospital so we got mr miller. alejandro says that when we have mr miller as a teacher in science next semester, if i ask him for some potassium, he will probably give it to me yay then alejandro is gonna be our math teacher. ok now the spudgun gay j almost killed me, his spudgun was of little quality and fell apart without shooting it. he said it was ready. i would have been killed or something.  so now hes making a better one that actually has sanded joints. so classes with mr miller are pretty damn annoying: we read huckleberry finn all day. i dont understand why cant we get better books with a bit of sense. i dont care about the days of a misguided kid who rides a river with his slave and his friend. its just stupid. cant we learn about politics or something? were all dressed up weve got no wehre to go! and uhm i tried to cheat on a proyect, but a stupid classmate told on me. if i hadnt been for that stupid girl, all of the generation would have gotten 100 on the test stupid dickheaded girl   AHH I HATE YOU ALL IF ONE MORE OF YOU SAID SOMETHING ID PROBABLY BE IN JAIL RIGHT NOW  SO IM GONNA MAKE A RED BOX AND IM GONNA TAKE REVENGE ON ALL OF YOU WHO HAVE REJECT ME AND LET ME DOWN IM NOT TAKING THIS CRAP NO MORE, THIS IS PSYCHOLOGICCAL WARFARE! THIS IS NOT A JOKE ANYMORE AND IT DOESNT FEEL NICE AT ALL im sorry but i cant give you ONE MORE CHANCE YOULL HAVE TO RIP IT OFF MY FLESH IF YOU WANT IT THAT WAY i need to buy my hair dyes for vacations. iguana green is already in. whoo full music volume!    YEAH    oh by the way, i just made a really good pencil drawing with an angry face :P
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink science lab.doc 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im so tired. its a friday and i just woke up. i havent even taken a shower. ut its gonna be a dan long day. and i havent slept in years -.- . when i et back home its gonna  be glorious urlLink Introductio1.doc   urlLink arte.doc   the 1st file is my ab, the second is some art thing.  i can see clearly now the rain is gone i can see all obstacles in my way out of the dark clouds that had me blind its gonna be a bright bright sunshinin day i think i can make it now the rain is gone all of the bad feelings have disappeared there is the rainbow ive been praying for its gonna be a bright bright sunshinin day i can see clearly now the rain is gone i can see all obstacles in my way there is the rainbow ive been prayin prayin for its gonna be a bright bright sunshinin day
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink ippex online  urlLink Introductio1.doc 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      on friday, carlos told me:  if the universe IS in fact infinite, then every single thing you once imagined MUST exist somewere. everything exists, its not your imagination; that mosnter under the bed can actually be touched and seen.  so somewhere, the must be a person with a telescope pointing towards my window, and i cant see him, and he cant see me, and we will never see each other.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ever wondered about the stars? when you look at one, youre looking at what was happening milions of years ago. its not happpening right now. that exact image is MILLIONS of years old. what ou are basically doing is looking into the past, literally. imagine that if there was a planet millions of lightyears away, and you had a mega telescope that lets you read a book that is millions of lightyears away, and that this planet was just as civilized as ours; that is that in that planet, right now they are doing what we are doing now; then if you looked into that planet, you would probably look at reinassance people or even much older than that! it even happens that what you are looking at doesnt even exist any more!  now, what if we planned to go into another distant planet, and we got there, and there was nothing? cool hunh? or wouldnt it be cool to be able to cast a spaceship's shadow on the moon? ok im gettin over the top now. ill see ya tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so like, i got to know (not introduced by each oter, but just out of luck) this girls: well she her friend her sister her sister's friend (lets call her poop) poop's exboyfriend (lets call him piss) piss's brother  strange enough right? and now one of them (poop) is mad at me because her life sucks. Sorry, but i couldnt care less. just shoot yourself and then i wont have to talk to you.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so like, after a LOOOONG while of reading blogs i sat down on the pc. Its hard to write a blog: you have to take the time to sit in front of the pc and actually do something. And i just write about what happenesd. sometimes a stupid critic or two, and if i write poetry then im either high on oxygen or im a tad depressed or maybe i need to stick a pencil up my nose. yeah. well anyways i was reading this blog, by an old friend who i eventually came to call "asshole" lemme giveyou the link...   urlLink    and after reading it i found out how fucking full of shi* she is. i mean, shes always writing poems and stuff, using complex words that at some point actually impressed me. well im finally noticing that she always writes the same kind of poems. let me invent a poem that would not surprise me if it was hers. And no, I dont read the dictionary every day, or look up complex words, so this isnt really good.  "yeasterday i woke up coffee coffee coffee cup my aunt fucked up //then she needs a bad word in here... and my cunt went up."  thats stupid, i know, but its HER kind of poem. and it sucks a lot. hehe. arg i gotta get this head band off my head its going to kill  me, its too tight argh. done my mom and i agreed to wear a head band if i wanna keep my hair long. ugh. and she aint letting me dye my hair.  i woke up with a cold today. and it still hurts, my eyes hurt a lot. yeah. people should start to read blogs. they... they sorta tell you how to be, not who to follow, but how to act. youll notice the difference between a sloppy blog (ahem) and a well done blog  urlLink   yeah. i gotta start a proyect for tomorrow and so ive gotta finsh or ill probably fail hehe. Mr miller didnt like my animation. he didnt even laugh at rene! but ale did. mwhaha.ok i gotta work/sleep/eat cook-ays or something. I DONT WANNA WORK SAVE ME!  or maybe ill just read more blogs. i was also reading on vegan food recipes. and i cant use a headband. two more days and i dont have to see anyone from school for two months. which kicks ass.  i want a hockey mask.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink EL FAINAL PROYECY.html   thats my graphic design final proyect. just click on it to watch (dont be mad at me if it takes too long to download)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well its that time of the year again. veryone is spending all of their money to create public appreciation, kids are blowing theirselves up with gunpowder, people are getting drunk and hitting their wives and i got all of my presents. YAY  so um, yesterday it was pretty boring cuz uhm i didnt do a thing i just spent the day with my parents and took lots of pictures hehe. if you see the pictures, my dad isnt drunk hehe.   i wanted to go to mcdonalds on new years eve and take pictures and act stupid, but my parents didnt wanna go so we didnt go duh.  uhm  i got a CD! (i never buy any, im too lazy) its like an Underworld anthology cd, 1992-2002. yeah,and u=i like it and so do my parents. whee!  there are one or two people who i wish very bad stuff as a christmas present for me >:D so heres some lyrics by fallout boy, its "yule shoot your eye out"  These are your good years don't take my advice you never wanted the nice boys anyway and I'm of good cheer cause I've been checking my list the gifts you're receiving from me will be  one awkward silence and two hopes you cry yourself to sleep staying up, waiting by the phone and all I want this year is for you to dedicate your last breathe to me before you bury yourself alive  don't come home for Christmas you're the last thing I wanna see underneath the tree merry Christmas, I could care less  happy new years baby you owe me the best gift I will ever ask for don't call me up, when the snow comes down its the only thing I want this year  one awkward silence and two hopes you cry yourself to sleep staying up, waiting by the phone all I want this year is for you to dedicate your last breathe to me before you bury yourself alive  don't come home for Christmas you're the last thing I wanna see underneath the tree merry Christmas, I could care less  don't come home for Christmas you're the last thing I wanna see underneath the tree (don't come home for Christmas) merry Christmas, I could care less  don't come home for Christmas you're the last thing I wanna see underneath the tree (don't come home for Christmas) merry Christmas, I could care less   thats it. i dont know what else to write, today some of my family will come to eat and as always,ill babysit while everyone has fun. christmas sucks. maybe the true meaning of christmas is cool, but not this gift-giving bullshit. it just scks, bunch of greedy bastards. so ill just have the worse time of my lifee playing with my cousin bla bla bla. I hope you have a merry christmas and you get lots of girls and then you get drunk and kill yourself. ho ho ho merry christmas  maybe ill write later if i dont die
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Macromedia Dreamweaver - Creating a web photo album with Macromedia Dreamweaver MX and Macromedia Fireworks MX: Prepare your site for the web photo album    im making a web photo album YAY  and i see my final proyect is not working so ill reload it as a flash file, youve gotta open it with internet explorer yay  .swf!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      bla bla bla  so whats up[? my mom finally agreed to let me getr a mohawk. were prolly going ovber to it this week (i hope tomorrow haha) and so im gonna take lotsa pics bla bla.   my mom also made me get a beanie to cover it up in certain places (ahem, church) or ill just wear it undone hehe. every day i see more mohawks, i hope it doesnt become mainstream before i get mine done ;)  what else? oh yeah, i got my second aphex twin cd today. uhm... selected ambient works 85-92 hehe. its a pain in the ass getting those cds and so i just saw it at the store and went and bought it without any second thought. little monetary control? you bet your ass hehe. i HAVE to get mario kart for my gamecube or ill die of boredom -.-  im gettin tired.. a bit :p  I HAVE TO GET A MOHAWK I CANT QUIT THINKING ABOUT IT  and ive got to stop scratching my pimples or whatever theyre called. i need to buy a beanie and get a [hopefully]dyed mohawk whee and uh... i have to listen to my cd and burn an international noise conspiracy cd and uh...get mario kart yeah. ok ok night [i guess]
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so no, the gallery didnt quite worlk well. and i was supposed to have a new site layout by today, but i cant make the CSS thingy work. it all comes out unformatted. maybe its my browser? my mom is outside paying her stuff. the economy in this house isnt all that cool. and my mom is thinking about getting divorced. that sucks. so, my site doesnt work, my family doesnt habve money, i give a damn if one of my friends dies, and my parents are getting a divorce. i guess it all goes downhill from here. it sucks. im talking to this girl (who is a pain in the ass) so ill just block her forever. its weird to think that i will never talk to someone again... here it goes...  wow.  its cool. what do i care about now? i dont care about anything. its almost cool.(i dont blame you when you piss and moan) i dont know what can i say. i dunno, i wish i could just die cuz theres nothing in the world that i can really enjoy, nor is there anything at the end of it. i wont kill myself, living is good enough as it is, but if i dont wake up tomorrow, i dont think i could care less. (besides, am i going to lament it later? haha) oh yeah, i had this dream yesterday in which someone died, but i could talk to it, so i asked how was it like, and after a few questions, i learned that when you die, your life is indeed infinite, you just walk around the earth forever, and you can touch stuff, say, you can sit on a couch and stuff like that, and everything is like a wall, you cant push a desk, only small stuff, and stuff that moves, say a bullet, goes right through you and you dont feel it. yeah.   i am so bored. so yeah that was what was going inside my head the past minutes, (normally all day) and i want a cookie. uhm yah.iu dont know what else to talk about. my vacations are almost over and i didnt do a damn thing. my mom doesnt like me spiking my hair because she says i will end up in the streets. my mom also tells me that being straightedge is a bad influence and bla bla bla bla. she doewsnt like my friejnds either. she doesnt like me being inside the house. she tells me that when im old im gonna be a mess. oh man, fuck you, fuck all of you, im gonna go take a piss in your face.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading the log but i got bored. i just checked out hallucinogenne.com for availability. its available. im sortof bored. im prolly ggoing to a web design technician course. its a real degree like the ones u get at the universitiy. yay. uhm. yeah. i wanna go somewhere cool or do something different. this routine is getting uber-monotonous. yeah, suxors bleargh. now that i think about 'bleargh' i HAVE to upload my huckleberry finn comic strip. i lasted about uhm... 15 minutes doing it and got a 75. its stilll funny. well a bit but i liked it. uhm. tralalalalalalala ive got nothin to say so bye
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so like um   i got a moahwk   its really cool, my mom is in the hospital so my dad let me do it. im prolly gonna dye it tomorrow and post some pics.... i need the camera. >.  anyways bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am so bored.  my mom is getting an operation so i had to stay with my grandparents last night. i used my grandpa's bed, and he just changed it (i used the old one) because it was giving him back pains. but...  after a long day of being with a guy shooting bottles and watching keen eddie, i get to the bed and drop on my back... just to find out that the cushion was about half an inch,, followed by misplaced wood boards. so yeah, it pretty much hurt, and i just got into the bed and something fell down. i dont know what it was, but it fell down hehe. then i found out that i cant sleep sideways in that bed. nor can i sleep on my stomach. ok so i couldnt sleep at all, but to better it, there are strange sounds on the roof (damn foxes/peeing animals) and so i start hearing sounds coming from the living room (most likely they DID come in, through the hole on the roof, but i decided it was better to not check at all.) so yeah, i scare myself to sleep (sort of) and it was like the 15th time ive slept on my back in my life. after being woken up by tyhe neighbor's roosters and the constant wooing/crying of my grandma's dog, Lolo (haha, i know) i remind myself that i was supposed to invite a friend over at like 8. thinking it was late, i jump out of bed, knuckles and legs, back and neck cracking. that hurt as well. my grandma tells me to get up, and i stagge up to the sofa. my grandma says im going to go blind because of watching tv (O.o) and so she makes me go take a bath. so to explain the nest part of the story, here are some lyrics by Goldfinger.   "My Girlfriend's Shower Sucks"  The temperature changes It chills me to the bone It makes me wish that I was cleaning myself at home  It makes me grumpy and sometimes I lose hope The water's hard, so I can never rinse the soap  and it's got no pressure The water dribbles down on me and it's got no pressure It's like the shower's going pee   ================================  then i get out, sort of dry myself and put my clothes on inside the bath. then... (sigh) i get the news that my little cousin is coming over (today was my nintendo/tv only day sortof) and so i really get down. to couple that, a friend (oh yeah, call me a friend, you only care about me when you can use me, asshole) calls me so that "we" can  play need for speed and shoot stuff with his newly acquired (two days ago) rifle. so i have to get him over. argh. then i help my grandma put a curtain and then... uh... i watch tv/play nintendo, i dont remember which. oh no, wait, before playing nintendo/watching tv i spend like 10 mins sitting on the couch thinking about someone who i dont recall who it was. o.O THEN i play nintendo. its more like: THEN i connect my nintendo. after connecting it, my cousin gets here and my day is thrown into oblivion. then my friend gets here (after like 20 mins of playing a tonka game on the pc). "we" play nintendo while i watch my cousin. then we go out with my cousin to shoot some coke cans. well, fanta cans. i discovered them today, now that i come to think about it. my cousin is afraid of the dog, so my asshole "friend" tells my cousin to run away from the dog. the dog obiously chases him, jumps on my cousin, my cousin falls on some metal, and the dog bitewes him. even if hes like totally wasted, my friend STILL encourages my cousin to run. i felt like shooting his ass with the rifle, but what the heck. i scare away the dog and poick up my cousin. my friend is laughing. i really dont want to see him right now. after wasting like 20 pellets/thingies, we go up again and play nintendo. i felt bad for my cousin cuzz my friend wouldnt stop being an asshole to him (apart from getting angry at a 4 year old because he cant play nintendo, you fag) so he makes my cousin's day a piece of crap, and i feel really bad and i want to punch my friend. but i cant, so i just let it slip and try to play with my cousin. i ignore my friend. then he asks me (my friend) if i want to go over to his house for sleeping over. i tell him that i have to go to the dentist tomorrow, and that i dont like sleeping over. reasons? reasons:  1- its not my bed 2- its NOT a bed 3- its not my bathroom 4- re-read lyrics. 5- i cant sleep tight, or dream about nice things, or any other thing you do while sleeping. 6- once i was taking a bath, and the dude just walks in, opens the shower, and shoots a gun. yes, im naked. yes, im seen. and yes, he stares.  so there you have your reasons.  then, uhm... he tells me that i should be thankful that he is iviting me and that im a bad friend. you wouldnt imagine how much i care. so he just goes sad/angry/silent/retarded (i dont know which) with me for the rest of the day. once again, i ignore him. then my cousin tries to get attention by bothering us and begs for me to play nintendo with me (he doesnt like playing with my friend, because he kicks his ass and tries to make him lose. me on the other hand, i just sit with the controller on my lap, eyes closed, and wait till my cousin tells me i can move.) then my grandma asks us not to play with the rifle. my friend gets even more pissed off/faggot-ish when my cousin tells him he doesnt want to play with him because he beats him up. my "friend" spends the day of the day angry at my cousin and i just sit there staring at my gramp. then i go pee. then i come back and sleep. then someone wakes me up by throwing the controller at my balls. guess who. my "friend" so i just pray and hope he goes early and my prayers are heard: he gets so angry he almost starts crying and asks for a fone for his mom to come pick me up. i mean he. duh. oh yeah, well ill use the 'backspace' on another oportunity. he gets angry and has an angry face (its sorta really bad acted i guess either that or he's really deformed cuz it looks like upside down 'scream' movie dude) and doesnt talk to ppl. not even my gramps. so after being completley convinced that he is, indeed gay, my cousin's parents arrive to come pick him up. along with my father, who i ask to take me home (followed by some bad jokes of my friend like: youre such a bad friend [look who's talking] why arent you thankful that i invited you? ohh but baaaaby doesnt have his little blanket and he doesnt sleep in his cute little bed and he doesnt bath in his cute little bathroom [no its not my little blanket, its a piece of your damn rags, no its not my cute little bed, its a damn piece of cloth im sleeping on, its not even a sleeping bag you cold-hearted greedy bastard, and FINALLLY, ITS NOT MY FREAKIN CUTE LITTLE BATHROOM, ITS A JAIL SHOWER, BUT I CAN AT LEAST KNOW THAT NO ONE WILL COME TO SEE MY DICK WHILE I CLEAN MYSELF, YOU PIECE OF GAY ASS PRICK]) after a while he leaves, and i get glad he's gone (my friend) and so i show the bed to my father and he asks me how the hell can i sleep on that. then my grandpa comes in and tells me that that is probably why his back hurt. then my uncle comes and lets out a big laugh. then my grandma comes and asks me why didnt i tell her anything. then my aunt comes and says the 'oh-poor-kid-im-going-to-cry' sermon. then my cousin jumps on the bed, bouinces off and breaks his neck. no not really, but he comes in, jumps on the bed, and makes a face that says 'ow' on his forehead.then i pack up my stuff, say bye, look at my uncle's new car (which has those windshield wipers on the front lights, which is pretty cool, but i dont know why would he want that) and leave. then i get here and write this.  im going to wait to see if i get to do something for the rest of the day. bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      messeguer - i need to do something better than watch tv and eat ice cream all day. mm ice cream. dice: hey i was listening to this song you senty me uh empty faces? XDennisX   dice: yah? messeguer - i need to do something better than watch tv and eat ice cream all day. mm ice cream. dice: who's the band? messeguer - i need to do something better than watch tv and eat ice cream all day. mm ice cream. dice: lol XDennisX   dice: room two37 XDennisX   dice: local band from västerås messeguer - i need to do something better than watch tv and eat ice cream all day. mm ice cream. dice: cool messeguer - i need to do something better than watch tv and eat ice cream all day. mm ice cream. dice: its a good song XDennisX   dice: with most of the people from my old band oppose 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      XDennisX   says: åååååå ååå istället för musik förviring messeguer - BRICK BY BRICK, WALL BY WALL! dice: i gotta get some swedish classes lol XDennisX   dice: haha, do so! messeguer - BRICK BY BRICK, WALL BY WALL! dice: yeah!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WAKA WAKA WAKA  TYPE!!!!!!!! HA! i was gonna get a camera and takes pictures today, but the library didnt have one and i was too bored to wait for it   BOOYA!!! DOES THIS SCANNER WORK??!!?!??! WAHAHAHAHa  uh... no. what a piece of shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      soy fabrizio tengo un ipod :) :)    se me perdio :( abu.   ahora soy felipe y me transforme. :3  yo como chiquitos. que digo que digo que digo   :O  encontree mi ipod  :3
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WAAAAAAH  estoy en la library.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink interview.doc   ese es el article d inglés
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this is the image for my wishlist :3   urlLink wishlist.png 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this is the image for my wishlist :3   urlLink wishlist.png 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WHOA XD  urlLink bootlog.gif 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well its been a while since i last wrote here. i can write more, but i dont wanna erase the older stuff. im thinking about archiving it. yay. 
     

    
</post>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well its me again, doing random crap again. Uhm yeah. So this will be my basic blog. I'll type whatever i wanna, so yeah, this is where i dump my sadness, my political crap and my rants. maybe ill tell you what i did during the day. MAYBE. But I have to sleep now. Im going to a concert tomorrow. So I'll see ya.    Bye!    &nbsp;  No! Wait! theres something else. Its a small paragraph rant about  urlLink www.gaiaonline.com     &nbsp;  I really want to crush every skull on gaia. I mean, every single guy is a nerdy motherfucker who tries to act tough. GODDAMMIT I WANNA KILL THEM ALL!    &nbsp;  No, i didnt get flamed, but their stupidity makes me angry. thats it. probably ranting about it some other day. anyhow, goodbye.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       w00t w00t. so uhm Ill just make this blog in english cause i think most people will read it in english. or... uhm... yeah.     &nbsp;   Concert crap:     &nbsp;     Chivo - Chivo - Chivo - Chivo -  Fecha: Domingo 18 de Julio. Hora: 5:00 p.m.Lugar: Gospel Music, Outlet Mall, San Pedro.Valor: ¢1.000.Grupos: Osho, No Resolution?, Up Shock, Neginot, Días de Agonía.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   Ok, so this was my first time at going to Gospel. I shouldve known this before, but people there told me the concerts at Gospel generally start at about 6:30. i got there at 4:50. The concert started at 7 pm. *gonk* well, that was a lowdown on the café, since most people got there early. Not at 7.     &nbsp;   I only got to see Neginot, Up Shock, Dias de Agonia and No resolution?.     &nbsp;   The concert started out with neginot playing. I basically went to the gig to check out neginot, since i know the bassist dude and wanted to listen to them. So basically you could say the play death metal? You know, a hardcore type of scream, and some changing riffs... everyone in the band can play really good. The singer was constantly jumping up and down the bandstand, blah. Sorta got everyone in the mood, and the sound guy was using them to try out noise. everyone was just getting seated when they played.     &nbsp;   next was... no resolution. I cant really remember these guys, i liked them but not that much. their music could get better anytime. sorta crappy riffs and crap that made me hungry. yeah, hungry. anyways, ill give this band 6/10, just because i cant really remember them.     &nbsp;   Then came dias de agonía. i had never heard this band. First of all, every guy in the band was straight edge, from what i could see. These guys play hardcore. Just hardcore. Didnt really get the lyrics because of all the screaming. The singer dude looks gay. i mean, maybe he was trying to look tough, but he really looks gay. like hes coming at you to rape you. the drummer got his drum loose and they had to stop playing. everyone clapped except me, who... was maybe too tired. the singer really needs to know how to sing. i mean, yeah, screaming sounds cool but if all you hear is GIAR GIARR YEARHG! for like 20 minutes it gets boring. overall good band. but not worth buying their cd.     &nbsp;   then came upshock. ok these guys i had already heard, but i dont like them that much anymore. its general punk that you would get by listening to pennywise. the singer was constantly wooing out the lyrics and then screaming a bit. Really retarded. and he's like 40, i mean, what the fuck. ok this band sucks ass, dont even pay for one of their concerts. get a guitar and make quick noises and there you have upshock.     &nbsp;   so basically lets talk about the place. Its your general internet cafe, a 20 by 20 room with red dim lights. The sound guy sucks. He plays the music so loud i got bored and left. it starts hurting after a while. specially when they play hardcore. The room is so packet up with chairs theres no room for skanking/moshing. besides, all the people gather around the center like if they cant get to see the band from 10 meters away.     &nbsp;   There was this slipknot fan dude who kept making coreography to the music, looked kinda like a dj with no turntable. the only difference between the dj and this dude would be that uh.. yeah.  BEWARE  you might find this guy at a concert. he wears bike glasses so that he can aerodinamically soar to the bar, wears a slipknot hoodie and finger cut gloves. I dont know why everyone knows him, but to say the truth i really couldnt care less.    The pit consisted of 4 people. The slipknot dude and three other kids. well there was a big guy but whatever. The reason of why you cant make a pit in a 1x1 four people space is that you cant move around. these guys were waiting for the other guy to finish so that they could punch the air like a moron. Then there was the human windmill. who moves his arms so fast you can actually see them.     &nbsp;   basically the concert sucked. i did enjoy listening to neginot though. I told the bar dude to get some ear plugs or he'd go deaf.     &nbsp;   There was also this little 5 year old girl in there. apparently i was the only one who cared, because all those other motherfuckers just laughed at her. i mean, she was with her mom, who worked at the café, but what would happen if you see a hardcore show everyday since you were 5? i mean come on, how can a little girl be in a place like this? yeah anyways. i saw like 6 ppl from school. blah.     &nbsp;   like, everyone at the concert was wearing like 50,000 colones in clothes. what the hell, arent they supposed to be the working class? anyways ill rant about this tomorrow or some other day when i have the time. and i also have to talk about the art exhibition i went to today. it was.... lame. yeah. but now its 11 pm and i needa sleep some. bye bye   
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        i cant believe where everything is going. this new media, this new thought. yes, be free, be unique, but guess what? everyone is thinking the exact same bullshit that you are, and everybody is a fucking freak. not saying it is bad, but they rub it on your face and it feels like shit. and if you had been in my exact same position you wouldnt be laughing. you would be crying or drugged up somewhere in the country. i made a difference and this is what i got to see: how everyone has gone down to a level where it isnt even WORTH trying to change a thing. anyways. i think i should talk about something nicer, but there isnt anything nice to talk about. oooh how great, youre a fashion victim! and you, you spend your money like there is no tomorrow. and how many people actually care about suffering? no time for things we need while people starve and people bleed. thats what the song says, and none of you will ever move your picture because your explanation of the world is a label with some clothes on it.    and drugs. fuck i hate drugs. whats so cool about doing them? oooh look i drink this liquid that looks like dehydrated person pee and tastes like crap just because everyone accepts it.&nbsp; whats so cool about that? "oh i heard that smoking makes you forguet your problems" it doesnt. it only delays it a bit and then fucks up your health. and guess what? youre a fucking sissy piece of shit if you cant even control your own emotions. ooooh im so tense i need a cigar. you lame piece of degenerative crap.    second, everyone just acts like a total asshole. im getting bored of you all trying to act to some stupid rule of society, and deep inside i know that none of you are like that. stupid two faces, bunch of motherfuckers. heres a little secret of my own: I hate you all. im just waiting for the day when you will die so that i can live my life happpily ever after without having to worry about your stupid prejudices. sick of your dirty looks, of your inching away, ASSHOLES.    so yeah, the world is going downhill and im staying on top of it to watch it fall. maybe its just for the kicks, i dont know, but i surely dont wanna be part of this thing you call "being cool". jesus.   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Okay. i wanted to talk about the taxes? Ive noticed that the government is always acting like "oh jebus we dont have money whadda we do? i mean, i really wanna buy that car and the rest of costa rica! MONEY!" 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So lets talk about the art expo. In a word, you can say it was... lame. It was a glass-fusion, wood carving, sculpture, painting expo. O.o yeah. It was three artists, dont remember their names but who cares, i mean, they sucked! ok lets rate the painings:  Annoying. The guy just grabbed a brush, dipped it in his six color staedler kids paint, splotched a bit on the paper and "there you have it, its a volcano!" bleh. and then he folded the paper to make a "visual effect" on the art. on the volcano. i mean, come on,  the paintings sucked .  &nbsp;  ok now the wooden things. its basically a piece of wood that has een shined out. then you make three little holes: the boobs, and the stomach. then in the holes put a stone in them and it looks like a pregnant person. you know what the worst part is? that  every single wooden carving had the exact same shape !&nbsp; Then there was this piece of wood that had like writen "ove, love, lo ve, lo ve?" written on it. then there was a dick right below it. this was probably the worst thing in the WHOLE exhibition. i mean, i think the guy who wrote this crap really wins the prize.  &nbsp;  urlLink http://www.funfreepages.com/prize/yourock.jpg  &nbsp; So what the heck, i realy wrote that on the guest book.  &nbsp;  uhm now there comes the glass things. ok its pieces of pearlescent crushed between two glassplateswith different colors. it was generally a triforce with different colors inside a circle. if thats art, well good riddance.  &nbsp;  some of the sculptures were cool, but they  were all the typical "girl coming out of a rock" thing . there were about 5 of these. if i was gonna make a scuplture, id make batman climbing out of a stone with a hotdog in his hands and name it "scotch tape" and it will have a better name than evryone else's art. and i will become leader of the world and paralize you with my lazer beams.  &nbsp;  but thats just me.    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ok im "esteban says: IMBECIAL HANLFABETO" and im talkingto esteban.   im also "jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas."      jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:  ya bengo   esteban says:   *vengo  jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:  si callese   esteban says:   IMBECIAL HANLFABETO     esteban says:   XD     esteban says:   entendio   esteban says:   esta malo     esteban says:   pero vale    (...)     &nbsp;    jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:   ai amback mal    jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:    [quote] esteban says:  IMBECIAL HANLFABETO     [/quote]   esteban says:   q andaba haciendo     jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:&nbsp;  &nbsp;JAJAJAJAJJA     jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:   mae nada     jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:   no jamando     jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:   jajajaj   esteban says:   XD    jaj... a las cholas de canal once... ojala las atropellen. viejas polas. says:      [edit] there was a crappy "XD" smiley here, which i cant post right now. the eyes were white [/edit]     esteban says:   mae q mierdas es esa cara     esteban says:   parece q esta llorando     &nbsp;   [nick change!]       esteban says: IMBECIAL HANLFABETO says:   esque se le borró el negro     esteban says: IMBECIAL HANLFABETO says:   callese no pregunte   esteban says:   XD  esteban says: IMBECIAL HANLFABETO says:   xD        &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  this is by far the best convo ever.    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and i wonder, how many so called "punk rockers" do something?  because singing about it is certainly not gonna do anything. id like to see a singer climb down the bandstand and start a march. but they wont do that. all our heroes are dead or corrupt. - international noise 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        These last months&nbsp;I had being watching the news about the the situation between Mexico and the&nbsp;United States. Like most of you may know the U.S. don't wants&nbsp;to allow&nbsp;people to pass through the border between these to countries.&nbsp;I really comprehend this action made by de U.S. since, among the average foreign Mexican in the U.S., there are&nbsp;drug&nbsp;dealers and people you wouldn't like&nbsp;in you country if you are a straight president&nbsp;with a high and strong moral. The problem I have with them is that they generalize making everyone look like a drug dealer. They complain about us being the ones that sell the cocaine, marijuana, and so on, but I wander who are the stupid that buy it? Where ever you go in California or Texas or any of those states that are close to Mexico, they see you as just another Mexican that came here because, either we cross the border to see&nbsp;what the land of the free is all about&nbsp;or ether because they are so merciful that saw&nbsp;you and saw the misery&nbsp;you were living in&nbsp;your tree house with a roof made out of palm trees' leaves. Mexicans&nbsp;went&nbsp;there because the U.S. crashed Mexican economy with their NAFTA&nbsp;starve-to-death-agreement in the early 90's. Whether you are Brazilian, Venezuelan, Ecuadorian, or Nicaraguan they see you just as another pathetic-ignorant-country-music-lover-Mexican with no&nbsp;right to look at their pair of omnipotent eyes. These discrimination and indifference to latinos irritates us creating a situation just like the one you have with the black people. I wander why is it. Your politicians, they are making a fascist country out of yours and that's because&nbsp;you discriminate,&nbsp;you are afraid of everything that is different from you, black, Latino, Chinese, Indian, all those so called "minorities" are just what you are afraid of because they aren't minorities and you know that.   
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ¿Qué es la paz? La verdad es que no sé. En un mundo donde los políticos no son nada más que fascistas enmascarados con hambre de poder y guerra, uno no puede distinguir entre blanco y negro. ¿Qué clase de personas elegimos para que nos representen me pregunto? Tenemos lideres obsoletos que sirven para nada mas que destrucción la tan llamada “sociedad civilizada”, que no es más que un circo de payasos y malabaristas que de intelectuales y humanistas. El mundo en el que vivimos no es nada más que la decadencia del ser humano. Hoy no se puede sembrar y cosechar frutos para mañana. La&nbsp; sociedad de hoy es una banda de cuervos que en el momento más inoportuno arrancaran el ojo del débil y el necesitado. Muy pocos se preocupan de los demás. Esos tienen que ser nuestros futuros lideres. Seamos solidarios, compartamos ideas, seamos consistentes con las ideas y miremos hacia un futuro unido, porque en el momento más insospechado, va a venir la maquina a destruir todo para fortalecerse y en ese momento no habrá mucho que hacer. Todo el mundo estará entontecido con las ropas de marca, autos de lujo, y en sí será una sociedad consumista.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gueeeeno. hace unos dias estaba en el parque de daiversions aca en costa rica. lo linda que es mi costa rica y su bonito monopolio de parque de diversiones. :)  aunque por un lado es bueno. osea, quien querria hacer un parque de diversiones en costa rica? O.o pero bueno. estaba en uno de esos chunches de agua.. como se llama? el que no es el reventazon, el... ese. mis contactos aqui me dicen que es el pacuare. mushas gracias. bueno. llegando al final de las escaleras en el pacuare, ustedes pueden observar que detras suyo, volviendo a&nbsp; ver para las afueras de nuestro afamada construccion, se ve un caballito. si muy bonita la yegua esa, pero lo que uno no se da cuenta es QUE EL COCHINO CABALLO ESTA DEBAJO DE UNA ANTENA ELECTRICA INDUSTRIAL.   y no tengo nada contra la electricidad. no soy como el mae "rebeldon que no prende el microfono porque esta tan enojado con el sistema que no usa su corriente electrica". no no, mis segnores, no estoy aqui para discutir esas... "cosas". solo les queria decir: como se va industrializando/ poblando/ "desarrollando".  osea, di si, no me voy a poner en varas de que es malo para el ambiente, porque aca ya todos lo sabemos, y si, entre mas edificios y menos arboles tenga un pais, mas "desarrollado" lo es. pero que raro que la gente necesite esto. di, no les propongo la solucion porque soy muy estupido e ignorante como para averiguarlo (y la verdad me da mucha pereza, no joda, toy en vacaciones) pero les meto el problema aunque sea por la nariz para ver si algunos de ustedes (ya que son todos tan "inteligentes" y estudiosos) saben que hacer. yo no. pido una patada en el culo.   y como my compita aqui abel pachuco dice: muchas gracias.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meh. Been feeling a bit depressed and empty lately. My parents are starting to lecture me everyday. 'Tis a real bitch. They're always telling me I'm too hateful and angry, and they're so damn nosy. Searching my room, always looking at me suspiciously. I know it's only because they care about me, but I can't help but feel annoyed and slightly pissed off.  Anyway....I got a phone call from someone I didn't even know today. It was....weird. She knew who I was, but I had no idea who the fuck she was. =\&nbsp; The conversation went something like this... Me: *picks up* Hello? Her: Is&nbsp; Angela there? Me: This is her. Her: Oh hi! This is blah blah blah. (Note: she didn't really say "blah blah blah", but I was distracted and didn't hear what her name was) Me: Ummmmm....hi Her: Do you know me? Me: ....I don't think so.... Her: I'm one of Olympia's friends. Me: Oh, cool Her: Have you seen me? Me: ......I don't think so.... Her: Oh. Are you going to Timpview? Me: Yeah... Her: Cool. I might go. Do you know anyone that's going there? Me: Errrr...just some of the people from our school. Her: Oooh, do you know blah blah blah? (Can't remember who she said) Me: No.... Her: What about Cecelia? Do you know her?  Me: No.... Her: Do you know blah blah blah? (you get the point) Me: no.... Her: dang, you don't know any of the people Olympia hangs out with! Me: Heh. Her: Do you know Cruz? Me: Yeah.... Her: Cool. You know Javier right? Me: Yeah..... Her: *launches into long story about how Javier is moving to Springville* Me: Fun. I know people who live there. Her: Cool. Are you Mexican? Me: No.... Her: I always thought you were Me: Nope, sorry. Her: Are you Mormon? Me: No.... Her: Are you Catholic? Me: No.... Her: So you're nothing, eh? Me: I suppose you could say that... Her: Well, I have to go! Me: Bye. o.o  God. That was an awkward conversation. Considering that I had no idea who she was, and all. I hope she didn't think I was rude. ^^;;;;  Ugh, anyway, I'm off to post in my LJ, then study for my English exam (WHY ME?! *screams at the sky). Night all.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i was buying swimtrunks cuz were going away to the beach tomorrow. so i was in the dressing room,trying to put on the trunks (i also realized my pants weight a lot? O.o) and there was this really crappy/commercial reggae on the radio... and the music ended and then the dj started accepting phone calls.   most&nbsp; of them were rants about the government, so here's one i snatched into my memory:  why does the government spend all that money on tourism and not on rebuilding the goddamned roads that we have?  i mean comeon, the roads have like huge holes in them and what does the MOPT do about it? they start drawing hearts on the street?! HWY DO YOU HAVE THAT STUPID GUY IN CHARGE?!   and what would happen if they actually got to fix the streets? more tourism! because the gringoes get bored of crappy roads, dont you get it?! how many gringos have ever set foot on say, [insert name of remote place in costa rica here]? why? because theyre not gonna spend four hours in a grav-- i mean, swamp type of road, just to get to a goddamn beach/thing/whatever.  so i say, get better roads, get better tourism. invert on tourism, and you only get a bunch of gringos infesting the local mcdonald's up.  *licks the reader* 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am mad.&nbsp; i just had a discusion with someone and that ticked me off.&nbsp; that person called me a loser.&nbsp; i told him&nbsp;to go and eat shit.&nbsp; not everybody thinks like you.&nbsp; you live in your little world were you suck on your mothers tit.&nbsp; you act like searching for a girlfriend was a sport and act as if they were trophies. i dont play that little game and you call me a loser because of it.&nbsp; FUCK YOU.&nbsp; you think youre so rebellious but you a are a hypocrit towards what you truly are 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If youve read the last two blog entries from esteban and messeguer you may already know that i (gurdian)&nbsp;am being hunted down.&nbsp; People in 07 are too proud.&nbsp; They think they are so united but still they exclude and pick on people.&nbsp; I have started my own little revolution against it and&nbsp;the AGUANTE&nbsp;constantly tries to crush it.&nbsp; It all started when i got drunk at a party and insulted the kiddies there and pablo and manu tried to beat me up. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       First of all I will have to explain what does&nbsp;"aguante" means&nbsp;and what does the "aguante la&nbsp;'07" means as well. "Aguante"&nbsp;it's&nbsp;like to confront something with brave, so you can guess what does "aguante la&nbsp;'07" means (for the ones that couldn't guess it, it is like "you can do it generation '07"). Generation '07 claims to be a united and powerful generation in which everyone is an&nbsp;important part of the generation '07 society, kind of like communism, including the dictatorship part of it since if you are not part of it they want to kick your ass up to your face as you could see with the rant Felipe did about Friday's party in Pablito's house (if you didn't then do it). Now the truth is that this unity is as true as George W. Bush being a "peace president". On our generation (or class) many people is bullied everyday (in school days), like Gay J (he deserves it since he is annoying) Patricia, Mow Mow, Tatiana, Oscar... And the list goes on and on. I personally have being bullied for about&nbsp;two and a half years, which means I have being suspended and have had to fight some of the persons who bullied me. The curious thing about it is that some of the people who bullied me now are trying to be nice and sometimes it pisses me off, because I think I have more friends in other generations than in this generation '07, and when someone who bullied me&nbsp;found&nbsp;me talking to someone from other generation they start being hypocrite and start acting like they have always being my friends. Now you can like have an idea of how is our generation. These doesn't means there are good persons in the class, but unfortunately there is more bad than good in my opinion, like for every 5 persons 2 of them are cool. This ratio is not objective since it is my opinion. Now back to the main theme. If this generation is united then why the bulling? That's because it's not true. If someone deforms your face no one will care about it in fact they will just stare a you wail they do it. Our proud generation also comes with its own home page:  urlLink  www.tuleparty2nite.4t.com  . At the beginning it was owned by Tufo, Fabro, and Chris (friend of us). Then Fabro left and came in Carlos, there it start the reing of stupid polls. They first made a poll which said: Who is the most freak in our generation: in which featured Felipe, Gurdian, Tatiana, Daniela Montealegre, some other persons I don't remember and me. This poll was made by our hypocrite (according to what people have told us) friend. Then it came another poll in which it said: Did you went Patricia's party, options,I wasn't invited, No, Yes, I don't fucking care. In the comments they start to making fun out of her. Finally I post a page long comment complaining about this generation and our friend Chris delete the poll. Now the web page is mainly owned by Chris since Tufo doesn't care about it and Carlos left the web page. I think mainly that's the main stuff about the problem and with that, you reader, can see our opinion. Thanks.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So! Review of last night's "party"!   *ahem* ok first of all, whoever wrote down those instructions and directions on how to get the is like an idiot who shouldnt have been born (pablo?) i mean, a brick colored house with two palms on it? thats like so totally perfect, considering that every  goddamn house in the place was brick colored and had at least two goddamn palms on it.   Even if you DID follow the instructions, you would've ended like two blocks down the road, looking at the guardhouse. probably in the park with the rocks (park with rocks? wtf?). but i got there! after like 8 phone calls. xP&nbsp; but pablo is an idiot. its like "keep going! now turn to the left, turn to the left again, again, and turn to the left! youre there! (if you noticed, i just made a turn around the block) god!    So i was there in the terrace/livingroom/thing next to garden/bar and kinda bored. like, chris making out with manuel's sister (o.O) and blah. and everyone talking about how they wanted to beat gurdian and estebitan up. its like   pablo: "DID YOU HEAR?! i wanna kill gurdian! he's such a loser! i mean, he actually told me that i wasnt a true 07'er! can you believe it?!"  manuel: "DUDE! what an asshole! do you wanna beat him up?"  pablo: "yeah! thatll teach him!"  daniel: "When he comes, i join! and i wanna beat estebitan up!"   and hte convo goes on, but you get the idea.   but i mean, what the fuck, even chris got mad at me for saying "he's kida tright about it" and he like gave me a strange look and stuff. O.o;   so yeah, if any of you get into a fight, i get in, im not letting everyon beat you two up. (ill get my ass kicked too, but not so badly haha)    but the party was kinda boring. i mean, what the hell? i arrive there and people (drunk) start talking about my edge. what the fuck? and its all like: "what do your fist say?" "uh... drugfree" "WOW!" "uh.. yeah." and then they start talking to like each other, and these two "punk" kids (who seem like they just got out of the quiksilver store, with beanie and all) start talking to me about punk. O.o;   one word: i dont care! one more word: I cant count!   who the hell wants to talk about punk? its like:  kid: since when are you edge?  me: like 3 years ago.  kid: cool.  me: uh yeah.  kid: you like hardcore?  me: uhhunh. you?  kid: yeah..  me: like what bands?  kid: uh... crass and uh.. green day.  me: ok.  kid: you?  me: [dump bandlist here]  kid: oh. ive heard minor threat!  me: good. i uh.. gotta go.  [gurdian and estebitan&nbsp;arrives] ::relief::    and so when gurdian and estebitan arrived, i told them that ppl wanted to beat them up. and estebitan starts talking about it out loud. JESUS MAN, SHUT UP! i mean, you couldnt be inciting the fight even more XD   so we got bored of just standing around in there, and decided to go for a walk around the place. because.. uh... we dont really familiarize with most of the people there. at least not me.   so we sorta walked around.... late night... uhm, there was another party going on in one of the blocks in which people started whistling around at us. i hate people. lol. anyways, we kept on walking and heard some music on my radio then stopped at the park with the rocks and started talking about pr0n. yeah. kinda bored,eh? i also took a piss like a meter away from their faces. xD   i cant piss when people are watching me. its hard to.   at eleven i had to call my parents to tell them to pick me up at one because "the party was great and theres a lot of people" while gurdian made a body image of "youre talking crap" which sorta consited acting out crapping and hten taking the shit into your mouth and spilling it all over. yeah.   we came back into the party like at 11:20. bo-ring. a lot of people had come. well no. but anyways, we ate some cold hot dogs we found resting on the bar. we&nbsp;gulped them down with some water. yeah. then we like randomized and helped cleaning the place up. poor maid, everyone's an asshole.   but maybe ill rant about the maid some other day. and about the 07 generation. but someone else might wanna do it. what about you estebitan? im gonna get ready to leave now. be back in three days!    urlLink www.hotelpuntaislita.com  (thats where im going :O)   &nbsp;  [edit] oh, to end last night's convo, if i found daniela on my bed with her legs spread open, i would pull her eyes out and fuck her eye socket. im a sick fuck, but daniela is a hpocrite [/edit]    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was bored today.&nbsp;&nbsp;         LOVE ME!      
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Esta misma noche del&nbsp;25 de julio del 2004&nbsp;a las 0:18 am. Felipe Gurdián y yo (Esteban Alvarez) comenzamos el plan para un nuevo movimiento llamado “Unidos sin Hipocresía”. Este movimiento tiene 7 pasos fáciles de seguir si nos da el apoyo que necesitamos para que funcione (Messeguer esto también es para usted).&nbsp;     &nbsp;    1) Todos tenemos que ponernos el mismo nick en MSN:  -¡¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!!!!  Seamos honestos tenemos una generación dividida y no podemos sacarnos este nick por nada  2) Explicaremos este plan a dos de nuestros amigos (Robin y Jose) y pediremos su ayuda  3) Pondremos propaganda que incite a la unión de esta generación alrededor del Colegio Lincoln  4) Pediremos a la gente que defienda a los molestados y los ayude  5) Hacer reuniones o “fiestas” y vamos a poner a la gente a q se siente y hable de este nuevo cambio y de la forma hipócrita q muchos hemos actuado entre nosotros  6) Vamos a mantener esto con constancia y con fuerza y con esto también buscamos q la gente no se pelee y q la gente se apoye si no es mucho pedir  7) Cada paso que se cumple se tiene que hacer con ganas y con fuerza para que la gente vea q este plan no es cualquier estupidez que no va funcionar como el anterior. También vamos a tratar de mejorar este plan con propósito de mantener unida esta generación   Estos pasos necesitan de constancia y de empeño así que por favor el que lea esto sea fiel a nuestra idea. Y para Messeguer, Jose y Robin: tenemos que mantenernos en  contacto todos los días , absolutamente todos los días y comentar sobre esto para ver como van nuestros planes. Gracias. Ojalá esto no sea para ustedes más que letras al azar y que de verdad esto signifique algo para ustedes, porque al final esto nos va a ayudar a todos.&nbsp;        A final word, wait it's not a call to action. We ain't no sect we ain't no fucking faction. Unity unity you’ve heard it all before. This time it's not exclusive we want to stop a war. Unity as one stand together. Unity evolutions gonna come. – Operation Ivy           
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okei ya estoy harto de toda estra mierda de que si los mae playos se pueden casar o no.  primero que todo, me gustaria acalarar que TODA ESTA MIERDA sobre estar casado o no es un monton de picha. que significa estar casado? todacia no se para qué el registro civil quiere saber si uno esta casado o no. me parece una imbecilada. es como que en su cedula saliera si ud tiene tele o no. a quien le importa? toy seguro de q a mis apreciadas figuras de autoridad no les importa.  ahora, para que tanta mierda de que los playos no se pueden casar? okei, diganme PORQUE PUTAS NO!?  porque va contra la iglesia? y que?! entonces para que dejan que hayan nightclubs por toda la ciudad? porque matan gente? porque es que los pedazos de mierda que se estan quejando TAMBIEN HACEN PECADOS?!  porque desde mi punto de vista es lo mismo serplayo que cometer un pecado: sigue siendo un acto contra dios.  ahora, no es que tenemos que mantener la distancia entre el estado y la iglesia? ahora, QUE PUTAS ESTA PASANDO AQUI?! porque lo que veo no es gente discutiendo el tema con un apunte objetivo, son un monton de playos de la iglesia quejandose de que dios no quiere esto y dios no quiere aquello y si no lo hacemos nos quema la casa. saquen a los padres de la tele y de los periodicos! porque con uno de esos cogechiquitos aqui no va a cambiar nada.  y que pasa con la gente que nisiquiera es catolica? esa gente q se casa con omo 20 zorras porque les da la gana? esa gente que?! no es que se merecen un voto en esto? AH PERO NO! los unicos con derecho a discutir son el padre minor y mister bush. no me jodan, al chile, si van a empezar con esta mierda al menos hagan algo con otros temas como "porque es que todos los padres son unos violadores?" no se pongan a discutir con los playos. hasta donde yo se, ellos no pasan violando a los menores como ustedes.  bueno, y mi punto final:  en conclusion, yo quitaria la vara de poder casarse "civilmente" porque estaria enfocando solo un lado de las religiones. no todo el mundo es igual. que se quite la posibilidad de casarse! y ya no hay mas problemas!  p.s.: a los playones que se quieren casar bajo el nombre de la iglesia: no pueden. metanselo en la upa, monton de estupidos. eso es como querer unirse a una secta satanica porque le gusta dios. es como hacerse sXe porque le cuadra emborracharse. es una imbecilada. callense y den una buena discusion, no una mierdita sobre jesus. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hoy fui al corazon de lo que es "pipi".  hoy fui a multiplaza. vi a dos carajos que andaban muy orondos con su nuevo look "punk".  Una faja de studs camisa quik gorra camionera quik y un rristban (wristband).  MAE ESAS GORRAS HACE DOS AÑOS USTED LA HUBIERA CONSIDERADO "CHOLA". que asco USTED ES TOTALMENTE LO OPUESTO A LO QUE SU "MODA"DICE. mae usted si es cool quiero ser como usted otro hijueputa en esta sociedad decadente. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to post the tab for part of one of my favorite guitar riffs. It's from the Goldfinger cover of 99 Red Balloons. I've never seen it tabbed this way, on any sites with guitar tabs, but I prefer playing it this way.  Goldfinger plays it with heavy distortion, which is why it sounds spiffy.  E------------------------------------------------------------------ B------------------------------------------------------------------ G----------------------------------------------------------------- D--------------------4h6p4------------------------------------------ A----7-7-4h7p4-------------7-7-4h7p4-------------4h7-------------- E-----------------------------------------------7-7--------------------  Click  urlLink here  for the tab of the whole song. There are mistakes in the solo, and possibly in other places, so watch out for those. Other than that, it's a pretty good tab.  Note: blogger won't let me post the vertical line-things, which is why the tab looks messy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       so what the heck are people thinking.  actual news in costa rica:      (transcribed from my memory)      "some random guy from the states wants to come into costa rica to search for gold in somewhere blablabla. this will give costa rica more money and more jobs. bla bla bla"      ok i mean, WHAT THE FUCK.      id like to point out that this guy's 'gold search' is going to be sponsored by the govenrment. BY THE GOVERNMENT. JEBUS.      and theyre not even fucking sure if there is gold in the place. what if there's no gold in the goddam area? well the government, not the guy, will have spent millions of dollars to find out that theres no gold, they just fucked up the environment, and they have an external debt because of some weird treaty the country made. (like always)      what jobs is it gonna give? because they always say "oh, its gonna give jobs" but its bullshit. they usually do this: ok lets bring 40 locals and make them work 10 hours a day at minimum wage for a year. after that, they fire them all. jesus man, that was hell of a job oportunity, specially when the next people you hire are stupid gringo tourists who propel sexual tourism. go figure.      out of the gold that is extracted, how many of it is the country gonna keep? this are the things that my beoved president would probably do:      1- donate the gold to the US for no apparent reason   2- share the money among themselves   3- spend the money on building roads, which translates to having Ignacio Santos buying cars with the money, or making random amounts of cement poke out of the roads, ike you can see near plaza del sol.   4- give it to the guy who promoted the gold thing.   5- give it so that we can "boost tourism" which means sped it on nightclubs and more advertisements of night clubs along the road   6- give it to the church, so that priests can become richer   7- give it to me. ill make good use of it, trust me. xD   8- give it to the MEP, so that THEY CAN ACUTALLY PAY THE TEACHERS   9- im out of ideas.      well you get the idea.      second, why would i want to help them make this proyect? so that the president can become richer and NOONE noticing? fuck off, im not paying my taxes for that.      can you imagine the enviromental damage? ok lets see:      -the biggest erosion that costa rica has ever seen, apart from the teca wood.   -lots of dead fish because there's no water   -less frests, more dirt roads   -houses having entire mountains falling on them      well you know. read mamita yunai. whats going on right now is the same as to what happened 70-100 years ago, in the book. (i donno when it was. sue me.)      i say, fuck the proyect. thats not the goddamned way to go. and if youve got a problem about it, im fucking waiting.          NO REFORMATION WITHOUT  REVOLT  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         me siento agradecido de por lo menos tener 5 buenos y confiables amigos en una generacion de 90 hipocritas.   y creer q en algun momento pense unificar a esta genercion.     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        la verdad es que no me importa si me odian. eso es lo q menos me interesa. tengo otras cosas mas importantes que discutir. -messeguer      esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: mae metz es una mierda todo IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: *sigh* IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: sip IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: pero yo no quiero unirme IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: porque mini nunca va a pensar igual esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: mae yo ya me desanime IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: jaj. esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: todos creen q yo les huelo el culo a ud y a gurdian IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: vale. hay mejores varas por qué pelear. esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: y q soy un wannabe punk IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: vale picha IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: a quien le importa lo q otros digan esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: di si esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: la bara es q yo creia q podia confiar en ellos IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: mae, hay q pelear por otras varas, un carajillo muriendose de hambre y nosotros hablando de que hay q unir la generacion. esteban - ¡¡¡¡VAMOS A UNIFICAR ESTA GENERACION Y DEJAR DE SER HIPOCRITAS!!! says: mae si al chile en este momento yo me paso por el culo a la generacion "07" IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: jaja IT STILL LOOKS PRETTY UGLY TO ME! :@ says: a la mierda con esa "union" lo unico q hacen es pelearse  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okei, todos sabemos q eso es caca. es algo en lo que yo no decidi unirme. asi que aqui esta la lista de esos elitistas qe se creen unidos:  manuel arce manuel alvarez mini daniela montealegre karina ruiz paola ruiz pablo ramirez hernan cordero daniel vivero roberto ortiz  a los maes q escriben aca (tebitan y gurdi) mae sigan updateando la lista. Ni se metan con esa gente, dejenlos vivir su mentira, la verdad esque no necesito amigos como esos basos. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       long have you awaited it... maybe the original is gone, but it was written by stupid racist people so here you have... THE HITLIST! (to add something, just edit this post) if youre gonna post something, make sure it hasnt been posted. use ctrl + f to find a word.      - abel pacheco   - fascists   - george bush.   - george bush jr.   - goths   - punks   - sk8ter bois   - posers   - hot topic   - marylin manson   - bad music   - U.S.A.   - Avril Lavigne   - McDonald's   - American chocolate   - people who don't take a stand   - nazis   - people who can't debate   - fast food   - sellouts   - capitalism   - people who piss me off   - rumors   - ravers   - DJ's   - one man bands   - leaders   - GG Allin   - Taco Bell   - fashion   - people who act like theyre different but are just like everyone else   - modern artists   - mindless people   - bad news reporters   - morals   - corruption   - meat-eaters   - cheap cd-r's   - stores   - stupid teachers who made my life hard    - labels   - hentai   - good cars   - people who look down at you   - bad hair gel   - keyboards in spanish   - fat people   - anorexic people   - pop punk   - quiksliver and all of that crap     
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CONFLICT LYRICS  The Guilt And The Glory (How Many More Lies)   Do you know that at least 70% of the human population of this planet starve and many more do not get enough to eat? You must now be familiar with reports of the famine In Ethiopia, where the weather has been so dry that crops fall, where the people are so hungry they have to walk many miles to the nearest relief station where there might be food If proplr have been generous. In any one station at least 40 people a day die. totally shriveled. They haven't the energy to brush away the flies that are waiting for THEIR meal. These poeple are the victims of our western governments. In Britain alone there are massive great food stores where surplus grain sits, In the EEC there are food mountains, In Amrerica farmers are paid to destroy part of their harvest, while big corporations plunder the 3rd world countries at the expense of the natives. Why Is this - economics, the science of greed. That which says people must pay western prices for their food. Natural starving countries can't afford this especially when their government takes the best fIrst. The western government have plenty of money. They tax us on our income, then they tax us on what we buy. They take the money we have worked for and use It to buy arms. They would rather be able to destroy the world 12 instead of 10 times over than transport surplus food to those who die. Indeed, they become 111 through obesity. Must we tolerate these obscenities? When soon even we may be starving because of their taxes. Some people don't see the connections between big bussiness and destruction. The biggest murderers are MacDonald's. Not only do they breed and slaughter millions of cattle, great rain forests are pulled down to make way for grazing ground. This destroys hundreds of unique species each time not to mention the fact that we need trees to produce oxygen for the planet. Many birds In North America migrate to these forests, on arriving and finding no forest they die. The drop In population of birds means more insects and the Americans only answer to this is pesticide. We all know about factories who manufacture pesticide, you know about Union Carbide. They're an American Company who set up dangerous plants. It doesn't matter, nearly 3,000 Indians are now dead due to their callousness, thousands have strokes and injuries that will never heal. Innocent people who had done nothing, whose life is not easy anyway, and why? So America can steal food from the starving millions. Nearly all big bussiness, is based on explanation of the worst kinds. Cosmetic companies use dead animals to make their products, then poison many more by feeding it to them with the end result of encouraging sexism by convincing men and women to look the same as each other. Advertising promotes this and advertising of any kind usually portrays women as a sex object only, there to be raped. Drug companies (like Roche &amp; ICI) claim to Invent new drugs to cure Imagined diseases. Thousands die at the hands of their useless research. They try to make drugs to cure heart disease which was originally caused by the sufferer eating meat and dairy products to excess. Booker McConnell own everything from butchers to health shops, as long as the cash rolls in who cares? Other companies who make machinery and domestic appliances (like Thorn EMI.) also makes defense gadgetry. British Aerospace specialize In fighters in favour of passenger jets. Governments pay more for weaponry that domestic consumers pay for domestic items. That's why many many comapnies world wide clamour for defense orders, some would go bankrupt without them. The final Industry, uranium mining, sponsored in Britain by RTZ plunders the landscape, kills the wildlife,exploits the natives and gives them cancer. The product makes bombs to kill all and 15 used for nuclear fuel. The kind of power that produces waste which can be pumped Into the sea In Cumbria. Deformed babies and children dying and leukemia are coincidences we are told. how many more lies must we listen to? 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the fuck is everyone thinking? i mean, they get mad when they find out this psycho guy kills cats, but theyre all too happy eating their fucking hamburguer. for god's sake.  i showed this link:  urlLink http://www.textfiles.com/anarchy/MISCHIEF/1001cat.txt   and people got pissed off. why? because they couldnt believe i would kill a cat.  "you woud kill a cat? what did the cat do to you in your life?"  at least in my eyes, its the same to kill a cow, than to kill a cat, than to kill a squirrel, than to kill a fish, than to kill a human. youre still a killer, you took someone's life away.  so why do these people complain so much? i mean, maybe i'm not vegan, but if i went vegan it would be for the good of it, not so that only one animal loses its right to live.  anyways, my dad just talked to me so i lost interest in going on writing. i guess you get the idea.  bai. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what the fuck is everyone's problem? everyone i see in a random forum on intrenet is all like "WOW MAN I GOT FUCKED WHEN I WAS 12 I RULE! EVERYONE I KNOW IS A BIG SLUT! I ROCK! I FUCKED A SLUT AINT I COOL!?"  it pisses me off. specially the way these people look at girls. "sex object only" come on, you couldnt get worse like that. a girl is not a fucking prize. i could go to any fucking place and get a blowjob whenever i cant, but its just not cool. wow your best friend is a slut so you brag about it, but deep inside you know she has fucked basically every other guy you know. thats not fucking cool. it makes you sound like an idiot actually.  anyways, if what you wanna do in your life is be a "fuck machine" go ahead, but youre no better than anyone else around here, and i dont fucking need you scrubbing it in my face, asshole.  thank you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay im sick of people trying to sound smart when they couldnt possibly be. this is an actual e-mail: (after responding to another one)      Just trying to figure out how massive amounts of chaos equals setting things straight, but that's alright.  
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In response to one of Felipe's previous posts:  Sex is supposedly "in" right now. Take MTV for example -- nearly everything revolves around sexuality. If mtv says it's cool, half the teens in the world will think it's cool. The minds of teenagers and children and easy to manipulate, and brainwash. There's really not much we can do about it. I think it's safe to say that more people will believe mtv/abercrombie/etc rather than a few kids who can actually see the truth, or at least something near the truth.  If everyone wants to fuck around, it's their choice. In fact, I have a friend who lost her virginity earlier this summer. She's only 13, and she did it with some older guy. The guy, I've heard, only likes girls who are pretty and easy. I lost a ton of respect for her.   We can hope that they'll understand someday (although hope is usually just a waste). It just sucks how so many people lack common sense these days. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What are vegans in a short definition: people who try to change the world without thinking too much. The simple fact of not eating any meat is stupid. You say you don't want to become an animal killer, but I bet you eat and wear child-made products and you don't give a fuck. I'm sure you don't think about it when you buy your tasty Milky Way with processed chocolate in a poor African country, or when you buy your Quicksilver shirts or your Nike shoes, I can understand that because you also have to be worried about what people say about you in school. Let me tell you something Tilio told me: ""School" is just a fraction of your life" and that is true, unless you are going to die at the age of 20 and you know it, then you are really fucked up.  I hate those "persons" who call them self humans and claim to be charitative, while they spend 50 cents for every $5 invested in their mascots, to charity. That is hypocrisy not compassion. Showing off their $100 shoes and their father's brand new Porche Carrera GT. I think that's the worst combination in a human being: hypocrisy and superficiality. If you want to be hated for the rest of your life, this is the key for your success, either this or killing the pope and twenty babies, but that is sick and difficult. Today the average human has became blind, shallow, and ignorant. Just like Felipe or Susi (Felipe's alter-ego) put it: Who the fuck cares about you having sex with a bitch! Good for you, but you may end up with herpes or aids or even a child, so now, does that worth it? Now, everyone cares about what's good for him. If you are combulsing in the middle of the street they see you as an animal with nothing to lose and probably most people think you are crazy. Only few are the ones that stop and help you, few are the ones that really care about you and the million persons around them. Those few are the ones that difference us from ants, they don't walk in one direction and fuck everyone who is on their way. They stop and talk to you and gives a meaning to what does being a Human is. If you enter a store nobody cares of saying "Good Morning" or "Thanks", everyone's is thinking "Dude, that's cool, I want it and nobody is going to take it away from me, even if don't buy it ever. Yes! I am a soul-less consumist, BUY! BUY! BUY! MC DONALD'S, QUICKSILVER, CELL PHONES, MORE!!!." Today it is like if you are   the only human left in the world and everyone else is just inferior.  Consumism is another thing is making everyone look like an ant. I say an ant because ants keep walking without caring about the other ants, they only fulfill their mission and nothing else. They don't talk they only work. The only difference between ants and humans is that ants are more consent with what they do and how they do it. We harass with the environment killing the animals and lately killing our selves. The good thing is that at least we are trying to improve and to correct our mistakes, but still not all the countries do that, for example U.S., Kyoto, does it tickles something? If it does then fuck you for doing nothing!!! Continuing with the subject... consumism is what is making us all the same. Disney is the ultimate consumist empire. There you can pay for a hotel and you can buy food, toys, shirts, toys, play in the theme park, and buy toys! You pretty much can to everything there, and since everything is Disney's monopoly in there you just consume. You may be asking your self... What about it? And that is exactly my point. Nobody cares. They just accept it, like if its normal, and certainly it is normal. Everyday we read advertisements, watch advertisements, and some people are even human advertisements. That is not bad at all, what is bad is to buy things that we don't need. Things that are just unusable is what is stupid. You could invest with that money in other things, either for needed people or just throw it at the bank. Other thing that comes along with this problem is than people feel insecure about them selves because they don't fit with the stereotype companies show to the consumers in the advertisements. Many fat people end up having problems for using products and pills that promise you you will lose all the fat in your body, and the ironic thing is that after those advertisements finish Mc Donald's, Taco Bell, Subway, KFC, commercials come in. What the fuck! Corporations are using us and the only thing that can help us decide what we want or what we need is us.  End    PD.: I don't know how I started talking about vegans and finished talking about self determination.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      School starts in a week. Hopefully, I will be able to finish my summer English assignment before then. I really need to get it together, I've only finished about a quarter of the novel. DDD: Schedule: 1. French 1 2. Biology 3. Geography Honors 4. World Civilizations 5. Honors Art 6. English 9 Honors 7. Algebra 2  Blah, I can't believe I'm taking every honors/"advanced" class available for my grade (9). >. I really hope this school year will be better than the last. I got into a ton of trouble this past school year, and I hope my record doesn't carry over to the new school. I'm kind of annoyed because I have Geo Honors and World Civs with a really annoying Star Wars fan who loves to argue with teachers over stupid topics. It would've been nice if 9th graders could take US History, since my expertise includes The Civil War, but World Civs and Geo Honors will be fun too, I suppose. Yeah, yeah, enough of my ranting over school subjects. I'll just end this now, since I seem to have nothing else to write. Ta.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this is a current event i have it due this friday for US HISTORY so its is full of shit.  Article:   urlLink  http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/business/3549408.stm                This article is about the rise of oil prices in the world setting a new record in history. This is caused by the menace Iraqi militant cleric Moqtada Sadr set after rejecting calls to end the fighting. This implies that Mr. Sadr may sabotage refineries and pipelines in Iraq since Sadr followers had taken over the cities of Basra, where 90% of Iraq’s oil exports go through. Iraqis officials shut down the plants to avoid a possible attempt of a terrorist attack. This reaction caused the rise in prices. In the article also talks about the impact Yukos may have with this. Analysts say it will take about six weeks for the effects to come.             It is pretty obvious that this is a great problem the world is undergoing. The simple fact that oil has made a new record in prices alarms everyone. If oil prices are high, then, considering that much of world’s oil comes from the Middle East, countries around the world will suffer its effects. Another problem within the subject is the effect it may cause to Yukos, which is one of the world’s biggest oil companies, since if it haves a big impact on Yukos economy, then prices will go even higher aggravating the problems.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FAWK! ok so im getting bored of vacations, and im all like, man! i wanna go back to school and talk to friends blablabla. I really miss school. going back to school is gonna be a blast!  BUT NO! it had to be another way! i had to get there and stand under the sun for like 2 hours! and listening to the principal talk crap!  and guess what?! I GOT US HISTORY TAUGHT BY MY PRINCIPAL! WOOHOO im gonna fucking kill you, asshole.  jesus. and all my teachers are stupid except for the math teacher and the computer teacher. think im going to die now. tada.   ps: wE ONLY HAVE AN HOUR OF RECESS! NOO 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>