<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A very lengthy and not-easy-to-digest article on  urlLink Open Source as a Paradigm Shift . I'll need a couple more reads to understand his points. It seems to be call to the open source community to look around and be more aware of what they were doing, but my sense in my initial reading is that the future is not so much about open source, but open content, created by the users, for the users. Of course, open source in the backend will be an important factor in bringing about this future.  Most of the software I use (except for Windows and Office) is already open source, or at least free. I'm also using a lot of free Internet services (web hosting, mail, etc). However, we must not forget that behind most of these things there are companies, and companies need money to sustain themselves.  Anyway, as I've said, I need to read the article again. Maybe I'll have a clearer understanding then.
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michael Schrage from MIT's Media Lab wrote this  urlLink interesting article in CIO Magazine . Do IT certifications mean much nowadays? Are they a good indication of how good an IT professional really is? In contrast with this article, check out this  urlLink article calling for more certification  in the IT industry, by one of our local technology leaders.  We don't really need more certification. We need  better  certification. I have both Bachelor and Master in Computer Science. I'm currently not certified in anything (my current job doesn't require them), but when (if) I ever get certified in something, it sure will not be just a piece of paper.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a post to kickstart this site. Time has an article on the  urlLink blogging phenomenon . Why do people write blogs and why do people read blogs? Perhaps they want to keep in touch with their friends. Perhaps it is to vent their frustrations to the world, and who cares if anybody reads them at all? Or to preach their world view. Or perhaps it's simply a good medium for like-minded people to share ideas and discuss current affairs, interesting articles and maybe even other people's blogs. Or maybe it's for people with a hidden agenda, political, commercial, etc. Or maybe it's just plain c00l. Whatever the reason, there's something about blogs that make them so fascinating. You could probably write a whole book on blogs, why they are so popular, what they mean from a sociological and psychological perspective, etc.  What do you think? How do you think this will evolve? Where are we heading? How will people interact with each other in future, either directly or indirectly?
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just read this essay,  urlLink The Other Road Ahead" , written by Paul Graham back in September 2001. Very excellent and relevant, even today, looking back 3 years later. His site has a lot of other interesting  urlLink essays  as well. Comes with Japanese translations (woohoo, I can practice my Japanese ^_^) and RSS feed. I think I'll put him on my reading list.
    
</post>


<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Bought meself a wireless LAN access point. Was kinda worried about filling up the house with microwaves, but what the heck, I get them at work anyway. It was quite simple to install actually, including setting the encryption keys, and I'm quite happy with the coverage. Now I can be connected in the comfort of my sofa in the living room and not have to be tied to my desk all the time.  Finished reading "The Truth" by Terry Pratchett today. Wonderful book, as with all previous Terry Pratchett novels. This one's about the invention of the newspaper. I've always loved the Discworld stories, amusing, wacky and yet so true to real life.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, just signed up with blogger and got a site on blogspot. Now what do I write? Hmmm......
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Just downloaded  urlLink w.bloggar . Maybe it will encourage me to blog more often, heh. :-)
     

        
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, what do you know? For the first time, I engaged in the national pastime....queueing. :-P With Chinese New Year just round the corner, I went down to Chinatown yesterday for the first time in my life to buy the locally famous Lim Chee Guan 'bak kwa' (barbequed sliced pork). No mean feat, for enormously long queues always form the week before the Chinese New Year. Yes, you can buy the sliced pork all year round, but it is a most desired foodstuff during Chinese New Year, and you have to get it within a week from the Chinese New Year, because it doesn't keep its taste well after one week...or so the elders say. It's not the only 'bak kwa' around, but our elders swear that there is no 'bak kwa' better than the decades-old Lim Chee Guan brand.  So you had me, along with hordes of people - the elders, ever loyal to the brand, who had been coming here year after year, and the young who came as a demonstration of their filial piety, queueing up in the wee hours of the morning, before the shop opened, just to buy a couple of kgs of that so oh-hard-to-get sliced pork. Partly because I needed to buy some for my sweetheart's family, and partly because my brother spend 9 hours (yes, 9 hours!) queueing up the night before to get some for his gf's family, and I thought I could do better by coming early in the morning, and perhaps I'd be done by lunch. Well, turns out I was very much mistaken about the effectiveness of my strategy...  Just how long is the queue? The shop opens at 9am. I was there at 8am, and there must be over a hundred people in front of me by then. By the time the shop opens, I dare say it has enough customers already lining up to give them business for the entire day! "-_- How many shops can lay claim to that? I brought a book with me and settled down for the long wait...  There was an old man in the queue with me who chatted with me throughout the day...in Hokkien. I'm not particularly conversant in the dialect, and it was hard to make out what he was saying, because of a lack of a few front teeth. He told me he has been coming to this same shop for over 30 years, and that he and his wife had tried other brands of 'bak kwa', and nothing compares to Lim Chee Guan's.  Personally, I don't really like the taste of this brand, and neither does my mum. And some people have been commenting that the quality has dropped over the years. It's pricier too at $46 per kg. But still, enough people like it to result in the annual Lim Chee Guan bak kwa queue, as famous as the bak kwa itself.  I finally saw the signboard after 11am, but it was a case of "so near yet so far". I estimated that the queue moves ahead by about 4-5 people every 15 minutes (later I found out it was because that's more or less the number of people who can be in the small shop at a time). It was a pretty uneventful wait. I skipped lunch, and so did the old man. He looked so pitiful though - his hands were shaking all the time, and I was worried he'll collapse from exhaustion and lack of food. Luckily there wasn't a lot of sun yesterday.  I envied those who came in teams. One would go for lunch, do some shopping, etc, while the other waited. Entire families would come down to take turns at the queueing up, babies included (yep, start them young :-P).  Oh yes, did I mention the tourists who stopped by and gawked at us,shook their heads in disbelief, and started taking pictures with their video cameras? And there were also the locals who walked past and proclaimed loudly that we are all crazy. And youngsters who laughed at us too, not knowing that one day in future they might be compelled to join the queue.  I finally got to sit on the chairs provided by the shop in front of the shop at about 4pm (yeah, "so near yet so far"), and it wasn't until 4:40pm or so that I finally got to buy my 2 kg of precious bak kwa. The limit is 10 kg per person, and some people looked like they maxed out on their quota (to the swears and curses of those behind who just wanted 1 or 2 kgs). Many people tried to "jump the queue" by asking those near the shop to piggyback their orders. Sorry, no way Jose. You want the bak kwa, you put in the effort, otherwise how about next year you come down and queue up for me?  Result? I took more than 8.5 hours, not much better than the 9 hours my brother took. Duh.  One observation: there is actually another outlet across the road, a bigger one. But all the 'bak kwa' were made at the smaller main outlet. I see the employees carting over heaps of 'bak kwa', wrapped, across the road. Someone commented that you don't have to wait as long at the other outlet, but heard that the 'bak kwa' doesn't taste as good. The logic baffles me. They came from the same shop, were roasted by the same people, and they taste different? Maybe it has to do with the time they spent cooling down in the air before they were brought across, maybe it was the fact that they were carted right across a busy and polluted road, I don't know. But I don't think my tastebuds will know the difference.  After getting my 'bak kwa' (by the way, payment is by cash only), I went straight to the nearby MacDonalds to fill my growling stomach, and there I saw the old man again. He asked me how much is that value meal I got, and left after hearing how much it costs. It struck me how some people would queue up to buy 10 kgs of sliced pork ($460 in all), coming in teams so that nobody has to wait, but there are also people like this old man, queueing up alone, enduring the sun and the hunger, all for just one kg of premium sliced pork, which he spent $46 for, but couldn't bear to part with $5.60 for a Filet-O-Fish Value Meal at MacDonald's...  Here ends my account of our national passion of queueing up for all things desirable. So am I going to do it again next year? Will I come at 6am, or even 5am, next time, just as what those people in front of me had done? We'll see...
     

        
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
         The  urlLink Robosapien  is selling at Carrefour for S$149. Since it's just beside my office, I went to take a closer look at it during lunch. Cool! *drool* But I don't think anybody has done much hacking yet coz it's so new. Can't wait to see what people can do with it! ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow, just saw this on Slashdot - a  urlLink flying model of the USS Enterprise  *drool* Scroll down to the bottom of the page for the  urlLink video . It's propeller-driven, but I couldn't see clearly where the flaps are located to steer the aircraft. I suppose they are on the main disk.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Discovered  urlLink blo.gs  today, and added my regular reading list to the website. Actually I could've just done it manually myself, but with  urlLink blo.gs  I don't have to go into the code to add/delete links, plus it also tells people when the blogs were last updated. The only downside is that it will keep reloading the list from the blog.gs server for everytime a user refreshes this page, but whatever...who reads this web page anyway?  Anyway, I personally use and recommend  urlLink FeedReader  for reading RSS feeds. However, it currently does not support Blogger's Atom feeds (why oh why Google did you develop your own version?).
     

        
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, I *thought* I knew CSS, until I tried to insert a logo in the website header. It took me a while to get the positioning right, but it's finally up. Okay, okay, it's a cheesy logo. I have no professional training (in design, that is) and I have no regrets. :-P Anyway, I intend to enhance this blog site and re-do my other home page so that everything looks good.  Not much of a weekend. I just borrowed the anime  urlLink "Gundam Seed"  from a colleague and am trying to finish them all before he comes back from his vacation. It's a really good series. I'm at episode 20 out of 52 already (oh, my eyes, my eyes!)  I was also going through my guitar scores today and I realised that I have so many I can't really keep track of what I have or don't have anymore. Time to do some serious re-org. I should concentrate more on practising than on collecting scores, most of which are beyond my current capabilities anyway. I'm working on Barrios' "Villancico de Navidad" or "Christmas Carol" right now. Not too hard, compared to other Barrios' works. I can't believe that I could actually play his "Sueno en la Floresta" once. I've lost so much repertoire since I started working...  Still missing her...I wonder what's she doing right now? I hope she's having a great time.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today I couldn't stop thinking about her. I know we've agreed to revert to being just good friends just this Monday, but... Well, she's now taking a vacation in Australia with her family. It's only the second day, and I miss her already. *sigh* How I pray for a second chance with her. I want her to be happy, and I want to be the one to give her happiness... My darling dragonfly, even though we are just friends now, know that I'll always stand by you, and I'll always love you. I've taken you for granted in the past, I will not do so in future. I'll try to be the companion that you need, to be your strength and support, to be the one to make you smile, to be someone worthy of your love. I hope you'll give me another chance. Love, me.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I spotted  urlLink William Hung's CD  the other day in a record store. Nope I didn't ask to sample the CD, I don't think I want to listen to it, much less buy it. I get mixed feelings looking at that stack of CDs. After all, I was from  urlLink Berkeley  too. I'm not sure what to feel about William standing in front of the  urlLink Campanile  (it's on the back cover of the CD). I want people to know Berkeley for its academic excellence and proud history, not for some poor American Idol reject. Well, I guess I'm supposed to feel happy for his "success", but I feel rather sorry for him. I wonder if people are making fun of him at his expense? I hope not...
     

        
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ...and new templates to use! So here's presenting my one-click new look (ah, the wonders of technology). I haven't wrote anything for a looong time now. Been rather busy with work and stuff. But I'll be more active from now on (yeah, right).  I just discovered Hello too, for posting of photos, and set up a little blog page for my Ragnarok Online character  urlLink Ivar Riodhr . I plan to upload screenshots as my character progresses through the game.  The new design now clashes with my other  urlLink personal home page  over at  urlLink Stanford . I've yet to decide if I want to separate the blog from the home page, or somehow unify the design so that they look like one mega website (I called it "Gecko's Matrix").
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Announcing the launch of Gecko Bytes v2.0! I've just finished the initial porting of my old website to the new design, and integrated everything together. Notice the new menu bar above? It's pure CSS. ^_^ Everything's functional right now although some content is not quite there yet.  I'm currently watching Excel Saga right now. Really stupid anime, but quite fun. Definitely not for newbies though.  Gonna take a nap, then switch my attention to work-related stuff. It's Monday again tomorrow. Why is the weekend so short?
     

        
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I spent much of the day working on the new website, and enhancing my Rojak Management System. I think it's almost ready for production. It's time to start porting the old content over and cleaning up the HTML. It'll be quite a bit of effort. It's amazing how much junk is inserted into MS Word-generated HTML files to control all the fancy layout you can get with a word-processing program.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just revamped this blog site. I simply modified the code of the older version. I'm still not 100% satisfied with the CSS yet, but I'll fix that later. When I finish revamping my other websites, I'll link them all together.  This marks the end of yet another weekend. Must prepare for work tomorrow. *yawn* *sigh*
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink This  is really hilarious! Hahahahahaha!
     

        
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've designed the  urlLink banner  for the new GeckoBytes website. Well, actually two banners, the  urlLink other one  is for my  urlLink GhostHack  website, meant for my technology-related musings. Now trying to get the CSS stuff working properly before I start re-doing the contents. I'm ridding myself of tables once and for all. The move to CSS will be worth it.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was thinking of a way to avoid using iframes on my  urlLink website . There's a technique to load external HTML pages using a hidden iframe and pumping into divs once loaded, but it's a descent into cross-platform hell. Still, divs are much flexible than iframes - they can be repositioned, re-styled, hidden, etc. I really don't know why the W3C decided not introduce a "src" parameter for divs (which Netscape once introduced). It's a rather popular gripe too. iframes are clunky and not very usable. If divs can pull in external content, I'm sure it'll make a lot of webmasters happy.  Anyways, I was thinking of something much more flexible than the solutions I see out there, more along the lines of a client-side "content management system", and something which can degrade gracefully enough in case it doesn't work. I call it my "Rojak Management System" (anyone else who takes this name shall be severely whipped, mwahaha!), since it takes little bits of HTML and puts them all together. ^_^ I finally got a proof of concept up and running, and it seems to work, although there's a delay. I'm not sure if it works on other browsers, but at the very least I tested it with IE6, Mozilla 1.7 and Firefox 0.9. Hopefully it'll work with future browsers too.  No, no demos yet. Need a bit more thinking. I'll put up more info when it's ready.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been trying out various music typesetting (i.e. score notation or engraving) software for some time now, both free and demos. I knew of  urlLink Lilypond  since a long time back, but it was designed to run under a Linux environment and takes advantage of many other tools that Linux provides. It is supposed to be able to produce some really elegant scores rivalling the professional typesetters. It is not Windows-friendly however. I had to download almost the entire GNU package in order to use it, about 150Mb I think. And uninstalling is also a mess. I had to manually remove some file type bindings. Not a good option unless you are a Windows user who uses GNU tools regularly.  Then I discovered the  urlLink ABC notation . I was unsure of its ability to support classical music, due to its popularity among folk musicians, until I discovered the  urlLink ABC Plus Project  which addresses specifically this topic, and which is a great resource.  The Lilypond authors said they came up with their own language because other formats out there are not strict and formal enough. ABC certainly does not have a very formal syntax, but it serves my needs in just about 2.5 Mb of binaries. The scores it produces also looks quite professional. I may have to do further research to get it to support some features of classical guitar scores (like barres, strums, which strings to use), but it seems to be extensible.  btw, both notation systems uses  text , not graphics, for entry. If you want a "user-friendly" environment, go look for the commercial software such as  urlLink Finale  or  urlLink Encore . I used Encore in the past (Windows 3.1 era). Now I just want something open, free, fast and easily portable.  ps - I'm on leave from work today. There's a breeze blowing, but man, it's still rather hot...
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Signed up for  urlLink SpyMac  last night, which is supposed to be targeted at the Mac user community, but what the heck. The free account is supposed to give you 1Gb email (they had this long before Google started offering their GMail), a blog, 250Mb photo space and 100Mb web space. Well, after fiddling around with it for some time, I can only say, SpyMac sucks! The whole site is too graphically intensive, has some really unintuitive interfaces (I thought Mac users would be the most particular about this??), and is sooo slooow. I still don't have a test site running yet. I hope it's just a temporary glitch. Anyway, need more testing before I decide if I wanna use it.   Afternote:  Well, SpyMac finally got their act together and I was able to log into the FTP server. ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Woohoo! Got my 1 Gb gmail account today (colleague got spare recommendations to hand out). And today's also the day that Yahoo decided to give 100Mb email storage to all their free Yahoo Mail users. *happy* Now what I want is free web space, lotsa them. ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Booting up in the morning is getting harder these days. Maybe I'm getting old....Contemplating a long weekend this week. Must...take....leave....
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mwahahaha! Finally solved the Mini Rubik's Cube and the Pyraminx I bought a while back. The Pyraminx is relatively easy to solve. The Mini Rubik's Cube is not so easy though. Anyway, I just followed the instructions and eventually nailed them both. ^_^  Saw a lot of interesting-looking puzzles online while searching for solutions. They even got them in shapes like Darth Maul and Homer Simpson! The geometrical shapes are more cool though. *drool*
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mom's making  ba zhang  (rice dumplings) today, for the Dumpling Festival, or "Duan Wu Jie". It's supposed to commemorate the righteous Chinese poet and patriot Qu Yuan (240-378 BC) who threw himself into the river after seeing the corruptness of the Chu Kingdom during the Warring States period. But it probably doesn't matter much to young people nowadays. And the dumplings are considered oily, fatty and gives you indigestion (I like them though). Give it a couple of generations, and this cultural heritage will probably be lost.  Some food for thought: The older the cultural heritage the richer it is, but because it extends so far back in time, it risks losing its relevance to modern society. But changing also means losing part of that heritage. How do we preserve the best from the past? Do we need to? What makes a Chinese a Chinese?
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Watched Harry Potter on Friday. It not as good as the previous ones - the story appears to move along by having Harry fainting and waking up. It seems a bit flat throughout. The Dementors didn't match how I imagined them from the book - what's with the big heads? Nevertheless, it's still rather entertaining, and the visuals are good.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Been playing with a "cheap" condenser mic (it's about as cheap as condenser mic designed for music recording can go) I bought this afternoon. I was trying to record my guitar playing. Here's what I learnt...   Lesson #1:  A condenser mic does not quite work when plugged into a computer sound card. Oh it records alright, but there is that funny "digital" noise. A cheapo dynamic mic has no such problem, but man is it noisy! A colleague told me he had pretty good experience with a cheap noise-cancelling mic, but judging from the recordings he sent me, the results are too soft.   Lesson #2:  A condenser mic works much better in normal audio equipment, in my case an old Aiwa portable tape recorder (I can't afford a minidisc recorder as yet, why are they still so damn ex?). I need to test it in a quiet room though, but the fidelity is great. I wonder how well it would work if I use the tape recorder as a pass-through to the computer's line-in? Hmmm...   Lesson #3:  Trim your fingernails and don't play just after a shower. Well, I got great fidelity, but my playing's atrocious! My skin feels weird after a shower...too smooth. I couldn't "feel" my guitar. Oh yeah, and I should've trimmed those fingernails last weekend, but I was too lazy...   Lesson #4:  If it sounds bad while you are playing, it will sound  even worse  when you playback the recording. The mic really amplifies every little mistake that you make. *shudder* It's a humbling experience to hear yourself as it sounds to the audience. I have a newfound respect for people who dare to record their music and post them online for the world to listen.  I need to experiment further with the mic. Perhaps one day I'll record something successfully and put it up on my website. Watch for my album some day! ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been looking at some Asian guitarists lately. I've been aware of them for several years now, but I haven't quite look at their websites or bought any of their CDs.  There's  urlLink Yang Xuefei  (楊雪霏) from China (now based in UK I think), whom I first heard on the classical guitar newsgroup about her being given  urlLink John William's   urlLink Smallman  guitar after he listened to her play. Anyway, I would like to have her CD for the piece  urlLink "Dance of the Yi People"  (彝族舞曲), originally written for the  urlLink pipa . I've actually accompanied the orchestral version of the piece before, playing the  urlLink erhu , so I have a rather special interest in learning this piece (yeah I have the guitar score for the piece). She's scheduled to come to Singapore to perform next year February. I do hope she plays this piece, and that the tickets aren't too ex. ^o^  And there's also  urlLink Kaori Muraji  (村治佳織). I saw her CD in Japan but the price was rather steep so I didn't bite.  Both the gals are rather sweet looking, don't you think? ^_^ I suppose if I'm looking for an idol to go ga-ga over it'll be one of them, but I'm not that type of person.  And from somewhere closer to home there's  urlLink Philip Hii  from Malaysia, who has a number of interesting articles on his website.  One thing I noticed was that all of them started rather young. And it seems that the girls are more succcessful. Hmm, maybe I should get my kids to start young too, that is, when I do have kids. Who knows? Maybe I'll produce the next John Williams, heehee. ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My usual barber shop is closed today. I hope they haven't finally succumbed to the competition next door. Yep, got meself a haircut today. Now my head feels so light and free, heh heh. ^o^
     

        
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Got my new  urlLink toy  at the PC Show. I was almost sidetracked from my goal by the  urlLink Canon Powershot A75 , until I found out that it eats 4 AA batteries (woah!). So in the end I did buy the Nikon Coolpix 3200, which is smaller, slightly cheaper and comes with the most freebies at the show. Now what shall I do with that traveller's bag? But the Canon gets my award for the weirdest freebie of the show (for digital cams, that is). I wonder which marketing guy figured that bundling air purifiers as a freebie would boost sales. Duh.  And oh yes, I found out that I suck at Soul Calibur 2 on the XBox. I really got thrashed by that kid. ^_^ But then again, he was hogging the machine at the XBox booth like nobody's business, and winning the comp almost every round, now will somebody tell me how that's supposed to be fun? My colleague tells me that there are more people in his department playing XBox than PS2. O_o Welcome to the dark side...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Went to the World Book Fair near my office after work last night (yeah, that's how my social life is on Friday nights) and bought a couple of books. The book fair is usually dominated by Chinese publishers, but there are also English and Malay books as well. I was initially there for some budget computer-related books. I got a Photoshop techniques book for just $9. Then I found a Chinese-translated version of a Kadokawa book (Japanese publisher) on drawing full-colour CG manga-style female characters (or "bishojous" for those of you into anime) with Photoshop. Only $11.80, and it comes with a CD.  Cool! ^_^ It would have been very expensive if translated and published in the US.  And for even more brain food, I got a 2x2x2 Rubik's cube and a Pyraminx puzzle on clearance for only $6 total. I like puzzles. I once solved my colleague's Masterball which had been scrambled for ages. Now no one else has tried to scramble it again. The guy at the booth told me that the 2x2x2 Rubik's cube (how does it hold the pieces together?) is actually harder than the Pyraminx.  What really satisfied me at the end of the day was that I found a classical guitar book from China, with an interesting mix of scores, including some Chinese folk tunes. I went to several booths, but all I found were folk song/rock/pop sing-along books targeted at the Chinese teenagers. But I finally hit jackpot. Actually I hit jackpot twice. I found a instruction book on flamenco guitar, but I don't think I want to start branching off into that style as yet, and I'm not sure I really like flamenco music. And price? $6.80. Things from China are cheap huh?  Later today I'm going to the PC Show at the Singapore Expo to hunt for an entry-level digital camera. I currently have my sights set on the  urlLink Nikon Coolpix 3200 , but I'll see what kind of deals are being offered there for the other makes. This is the season for fairs and exhibitions, being the school holidays. And the season for rain too. It rained earlier this morning, so it should remain pretty cool for quite a while.  Stomach growling, need to go look for food now...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Didn't do much today. Today's a holiday. I was rather tired from last night's karaoke session with my colleagues (I found that my bosses sing quite well). Anyway, I couldn't find enough enthusiasm to do much in my free time nowadays, what with a failed relationship and everything. I didn't really know what to say when my boss asked me why I wasn't with my girlfriend and was free to join them at karaoke. I just smiled. Last night was a good unwinding session though, I quite enjoyed myself.  So I spent a couple of hours after lunch today dozing off on a foldable reclining chair I bought from Carrefour (cheap cheap, only $9.95), and played Gameboy Advance for a while.  I do have a list of things I want to do in my leisure, like scoring down some of my classical guitar arrangements, expand my guitar repertoire, converting my VHS tapes of John Williams (the guitarist not the Star Wars composer) and Yo-yo Ma to digital before they succumb to equatorial heat and humidity, scanning in my old photos, working on a new CSS-powered version of my website, continue developing some apps I wrote, practise my sketching...the list goes on and on. I just have to get started. Maybe I should take a block leave to do some of these things. I was planning to do so anyway, well, at least that was what I was hoping to do earlier this year. Now that I'm supposed to start on a new project at work I'm not sure I should be taking leave anymore. Maybe towards the end of the year...  Oh well, another day idled away... I have a presentation to do tomorrow morning. I better start looking at how to best spend the rest of the night...
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      How many ways can you screw up a relationship? I don't know, but I just did one of them, no doubt about it. I had to go pick a fight with the girl I've broken up with but still care deeply about. Never mind that I spent my entire weekend and today hoping to see her online but never got to. Never mind that I've been feeling depressed and torn up deep inside but had been keeping up a happy face and acting as if nothing had happened for so long now. Never mind that I feel such a big emptiness inside without somebody to care for and to confide in, and to share my joys and sorrows. Never mind that I didn't really want to hurt her by saying rude and unkind words (and over SMS some more). It all started with a short SMS reply to my call. Something tripped inside me today, and at the worst time possible, when she was having a bad day too. I really blew it this time. And all I was hoping for was to have a chance to speak to her...  Perhaps I should have been more patient with her, perhaps I should not have been so sensitive. I couldn't stop myself from imagining things when I didn't know where she is. I feel very bad about it. Maybe I'm really a possessive type of guy, although I like to think of myself as a fairly understanding and liberated guy who would not think of tying down his girlfriend in one spot and preventing her from striving towards her personal goals. Or maybe I've given her too much freedom, so much so that she drifted away. That was what happened to my girlfriend before her...  But at the same time I'm also angry. Why am I always the one who has to give way? Don't my feelings matter too? Why must the guy always be the one who placates the girl? Why must she always be the one who's right? I'm tired of being Mr. Nice Guy. I'm tired of all the "logical" arguments why she's right and that I'm just being a unreasonable guy. I've been hurt so many times in the past, and yet I've always let it go... I could've argued back, but I didn't want to worsen the quarrel. She never realised it...  Yet I loved her, and I love her still. But I'm starting to feel that Fate is no longer smiling upon us, or such unfortunate things would never have happened in the first place... I don't know what I should do now. Will she forgive me? Or will this incident create an unmendable rift between us? What must I do to obtain her forgiveness?  I'm very tired. I still have a lot of pent-up emotions inside, and I feel like hitting something. I think I should go and sleep. Perhaps tomorrow will be better day...
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just this morning I was thinking about different approaches to visualising and navigating file systems, and then I happen to see these links on Slashdot. Check out the  urlLink Apple Design Awards 2004  and  urlLink Industrial Design Excellence Awards 2004 . I was trained to be a human-computer interaction specialist, but never got to do much of this in my real work. It's easy to get jaded and give up on our dreams. Sometimes you need to look at what other people have done and get all inspired again. 
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The Stanford servers have&nbsp;recently been migrated to another file system, and it appears that things are still a little screwy. It seems that all students and alumni home pages have been crippled. Hope they&nbsp;will be&nbsp;able to fix the problem soon...   Afternote:  Oh, it's up now.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's amazing how some people can look alike. I saw this girl the other day, she looked so much like my ex-girlfriend I couldn't help looking at her a couple of times more. I wonder if she has a similar character too? Anyways, the logical part of me told me that I should just leave it at that. Going after a girl just because she looks like an ex is definitely setting off on the wrong foot, and I'm ready for any more relationships as yet.  When I was studying in the States, a Taiwanese&nbsp;girl in my Japanese language class told me I look so much like one of her friends that she couldn't believe it at first. She even felt that our characters were similar.&nbsp;She and I&nbsp;often partnered together for dialogue practice. I sorta liked that girl, but nothing much came out of it. I wonder where is she now? 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been trying to clear out my office Lotus Notes mailbox and archiving them in a local file. I keep getting warned by the system that my mailbox has exceeded quota. I have 200 Mb and it's just not enough. *sigh* No, it's not due to spam. No, it's not because I'm a very busy and important person who get lots of emails (I wished!). It's because people never,  ever , remove attachments when replying, even when it's a 4Mb presentation file. So I get duplicates of the same document all over the place. It's a chore to go deleting them all over the place, plus you never know when someone might say "but I didn't get the attachment!" (at which point you whip out the email and say, "walla! Here's an email from  you  to  moi  with the bloody attachment attached!").   I get small consolation in the fact that the bosses probably have a greater problem with this (although, being higher-living lifeforms they get a somewhat larger quota). After all, they get to be copied on almost every email, heh heh.   Anyway, I wish email systems are smart enough to be able to just refer to a single copy of a document instead of keeping multiple duplicates. And you'll get instant document version control too! How often do you have to pull out the latest version of a document instantly? Oh well, I do see lots of implementation and behavioural issues, and maybe even confidentiality issues, that need to be addressed first. I think it's technically possible though. I think a hash on the file combined with the filename should be sufficient for identifying the file.   Even better still, I don't even want the duplicated text in the email.   Somebody should really look into this area. It's interesting that email has been around for donkey years and we are still stuck with this paradigm. Yeah, I know it's because email is simple and therefore extremely portable, but there's so many things you can do on the enterprise systems. Given my background in HCI, I think this will make an interesting study into the way people use email in their work. And it also raises some interesting problems, such as when do you consider an email (with lots of history threads) deleted? Hmm...   Maybe such advanced email systems do already exist today. But until we actually put in something like that in my office, it'll be perpetual struggle with email bloat. 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I have colleagues who tell me that time spent idling is time well spent. I supposed going by this definition I had a pretty well-spent super-long weekend. I realise that weekends never really turn out the way you expect them to.  I found that I could never really do work from home (was actually planning to do so). I'm a person who needs to be physically in the office to work. So much for flexi-hours and telecommuting. Anyway, I really needed a break. Did a lot of napping these few days. ^_^  I finally finished learning Julia Florida. Got sidestracked by a few other pieces along the way, which I found on a Korean website. Nope, I can only pronounce some Korean characters, can't read them. I just click until I found something interesting. ^_^ Looks like the Koreans are really into classical guitar, judging by how many of them like to share their arrangements and home recordings. And some of them play pretty well too.  Started playing  urlLink Ragnarok Online  again. My  urlLink character  gained one more level, and I'll need a couple more before promoting my Archer to a Hunter. I found out today that the Ragnarok World Championship just ended today in Korea, and that two Malaysian teams were placed in the finals. The top spot went to a team from Taiwan.  Let's see, I also managed to finish reading a book, and scanned a number of old photos. Rule #1 of scanning photos: keep your scanner surface squeaky clean or you'll see UFOs all over your pics, heh...  Some day I should go on an overseas trip instead of staying at home.  Anyway, gotta psych myself out of the holiday mood. Going back to work tomorrow. I hope things are still okay in the office...
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today's the beginning of the next 3 years of my bond to the government. I've finally reached the mid-way point. Thought perhaps I should write something on this day. The last few days have found me somewhat cynical and jaded about things in general. I call it my "mid-bond crisis". ^_^  I'm writing this from home. Took leave today so that I can rest and er, meditate on my life...  This scholars thing is quite unique to us. I don't really find the same thing in other countries. "We'll pay for your studies and living expenses overseas, and in return for using taxpayers' money, you'll have to serve us for the next 6 years". Not a bad deal I must say, free tuition, job security, etc. From the government perspective it is a means to identify and groom "future leaders". I don't have much regret taking up the scholarship in the first place, as otherwise I would not have been able to open my eyes to the outside world, but still, something burns within me, a yearning, a desire to know how things might have been, could be different. What choices would I have made if I had not bound myself to the government? Where would I be now? What would I be doing? When I was younger, I've thought of a career as a teacher, a professor, a game developer. If I had not chosen Computer Science for my professional training, I would probably have chosen Mathematics.  It is not easy being in the public service, especially when you are somebody who doesn't like to conform, who doesn't like bureaucracy, who feels that things should have been done differently. I learned that my friend, also a government scholar, has been writing down all the things that has pissed him off over the last 3 years in the service, and intends to collate them into a nice little book. I have certain strong opinions about the service too, but I realised that you can't change the world overnight. Different people thrive in different environments. Whether you think the environment is good or bad is a matter of perspective. If you don't like it, by all means go outside and find yourself a niche out there, after you've served out the bond. Many have served, and many have left. But I also have colleagues, good people and non-scholars, who have found enough meaning in this work, and enough rewards, to have stayed on for years. To each his own.  The scholar is an interesting animal. Some just want job security, some took it up because it offers them an overseas education which they could not afford, some have aspirations to be up there, to "make it" by age 32, some want to contribute to the country and the people (although I feel this is a rare and dying breed nowadays). In any case, we are all people who have been able to excel academically and have been identified to have the potential to take the reins in future. But being a scholar is no guarantee of success in your career.  I ask this of new scholars all the time. Why did you take up this scholarship? Are you interested in your field of study? What drives you? It's important to know what you want in life, what you are willing to give up for it. Otherwise, you will become disillusioned all the time and that's not healthy.  Sometimes being a scholar is a liability. A colleague who have worked in the private sector for most part of his career tells me that I should have been out there, and that I'm losing value every day I stay here. Well, I can't afford to break my bond, so I'll have to prepared to start from the bottom if need be when I eventually join the private sector, and I one day will.  What drives me? Perhaps this will shed some light on why I joined the service, and why I might feel disillusioned sometimes. ^_^        "I expect to pass through this world but once; any good thing therefore that I can do, or any kindness that I can show to any fellow creature, let me do it now; let me not defer or neglect it, for I shall not pass this way again." Ettiene De Grellet   urlLink What Motivates You?  brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Hah, civil service! Interestingly, my desire to do something for the people is one reason I went for a public sector scholarship in the first place...  Hmm, education is the list too. I guess the PhD is still a potential option. ^_^  Three down, three to go. Time flies. The next three years will probably be over before I know it. What will life bring me in the next 3 years? I do not know. But whether I decide to stay or leave at the end, I should not waste the next three years. I'll learn whatever I can, do whatever I can do, and then move on.   
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just finished reading Dan Brown's  urlLink "The Da Vinci Code" . I've heard much about this book, and from Amazon's reviews it seems there are people who love it, and others who denounce it as amateurish trash. "Controversial" content aside, I find that I quite enjoy the fast-paced action and numerous plot twists. It seems the author has taken quite a number of liberties with the facts in order to piece the story together, but overall I think it's a rather creative piece of writing. The book seems to be tailor-made for the big screen, switching scenes just when the plot reaches a cliffhanger. It's an entertaining diversion from my usual diet of science fiction and fantasy.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Found this  urlLink medieval-style "Personal Personality Profile" quiz  while cyber-surfing today. It says that I'm a "Dreamer - Minstrel", heh.   "Your distinct personality,  The Dreamer-Minstrel  might be found in most of the thriving kingdoms of the time. You can always see the "Silver Lining" to every dark and dreary cloud. Look at the bright side is your motto and understanding why everything happens for the best is your goal. You are the positive optimist of the world who provides the hope for all humankind. There is nothing so terrible that you can not find some good within it. On the positive side, you are spontaneous, charismatic, idealistic and empathic. On the negative side, you may be a sentimental dreamer who is emotionally impractical. Interestingly, your preference is just as applicable in today's corporate kingdoms."   Well, I'm not so sure about the optimistic part. I seem to be spouting doom and seeing pitfalls and potential roadblocks all the time. ^_^ But I do find myself being able to move forward however I feel about the task at hand. The dreamer/romantic/idealistic assessment is fairly consistent across the various personality tests I've tried. However, as an engineer/computer scientist I'm also rather practical and logical (that's the doom-spouting part of me I suppose. Engineers are trained to see the many ways something can screw up and blow into a million teeny-weeny bits... -_-")  Okay, now I shall go chant repeatedly to myself, "Tomorrow will be a better day". ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Didn't do anything today except watch  urlLink "Avalon" , which I bought sometime ago. It's a little slow and quite straightforward really, IMHO, contrary to some reviews I've read. Oshii asked his usual question of "What is reality?", which he also asked in his  urlLink "Ghost in the Shell"  movie. It's a rather popular theme. You find it in mainstream movies such as "The Matrix" as well as in anime/videogames such as  urlLink ".hack//SIGN" .  One thing I liked about the movie is how the scenes get brighter and more colourful as you go deeper into the virtual world. The hidden level, "Class Real", is in fact the real world in full vivid colour as we know it. Another thing I liked is the blending of the Arthurian legend into the story. I've always been impressed by the ingenuity and ability of the Japanese to take other people's culture and use them in a story. Some examples that come to my mind immediately are  urlLink "Jin-Roh"  and  urlLink "Evangelion" .  Overall, "Avalon" is not a bad movie, as long as you set your expectations right. Personally, I prefer Oshii's "Ghost in the Shell".
     

        
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today's the first-date anniversary for me and my ex-girlfriend. Our relationship didn't even to make it to the first year. I've always believe that a relationship needs at least one full year before you can consider it firm. Well, my previous (and first) girlfriend before this was with me for much longer than that and we still broke up in the end. Guess nothing in life's firm. *sigh* I hope that things will improve for me when it comes to relationships.  Next Friday I would have completed half of my 6-year bond to the government, a bond that I have to serve in return for their sponsoring my 4 years of studies in the States. Hmm, I suppose it's cause for some celebration. You either see it as half-empty or half-full, might as well regard it in a positive light. Except that I keep having this nagging feeling in me that I should have been out there doing something else...  People I know are leaving the organisation. Quite a number of them. Good people too. Some of them simply decided not to work here anymore, no next job to move on to. A brave thing to do, considering the current economic climate. It's sad to see them go, but I wish them all the best. I wonder how many more people I know will leave in my next 3 years or so here? I suppose this is part and parcel of working life, this constant movement of people.  As for me, I can't quit yet of course. I'm currently in a transition phase when I'm trying to close my current project and at the same time embark on the next one. I'm not really looking forward to it. Maybe I should take a short break. I'm starting to feel burned out and cynical.  One day I might go back to the States and get my doctorate, and after that I'll do interesting research at some university and nurture future generations of computer scientists, do things that I believe in. At least that's my current dream. My ideals might yet change in the next 3 years, who knows?  Picking out the notes of "Moon River" on my guitar, I wonder. Where will the river lead me?  This is a time for reflection. A reflection on what I'm doing now, what I've done in the past, and on future paths yet to be trodden. Maybe someone will help point the way, but I'll continue to walk and make my choices as they come.  As a popular fellow Berkeleyan once said, "I have done my best. I have no regrets". Now that's a good philosophy.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Received an email from someone saying how much he liked my arrangement of "White Christmas" for solo guitar (see my Music pages). I got another such email earlier this year too. So that's makes it 2 compliments in like, er...8 years? I was browsing some guitar websites, and I was quite surprised that people are linking to my score, although they are pointing to my old defunct website (of which I forgot the password to so couldn't update).  Other than comments on my guitar arrangement, I've also received a couple of emails regarding my college papers. I once had a student wanting to quote my paper on "Understanding Realism in Computer Games through Phenomenology" (ooh, quite a mouthful, isn't it?), and from two other people about my Final Fantasy 7 papers I wrote for a video game history class (yep, you read it correctly, video game  history . Amazing thing, the Web. You put something up online, and people will find it somehow.  I think I should start scoring down my arrangement for "Moon River" soon. So stay tuned! ^_^
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just read this essay,  urlLink The Other Road Ahead" , written by Paul Graham back in September 2001. Very excellent and relevant, even today, looking back 3 years later. His site has a lot of other interesting  urlLink essays  as well. Comes with Japanese translations (woohoo, I can practice my Japanese ^_^) and RSS feed. I think I'll put him on my reading list.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Picked up a copy of Mamoru Oshii's  urlLink Avalon , a Japanese film in Polish with a Polish cast (huh?), from HMV today. It was on sale. I haven't watched it yet, just sampled the first 10 minutes or so. I've read that this movie is a bit weird, and it's  not  an action film, contrary to what the first scenes of the virtual world seem to suggest. Anyway, I'll reserve my judgement until I've seen the film. It's Mamoru Oshii, and his films are supposed to be somewhat deep. Oh, ya, Mamoru Oshii made Ghost in the Shell, in case you don't know. I wonder if it's a coincidence that Avalon's Ash resembles Major Kusanagi in GITS. And it's kinda like Matrix except that everything is in sepia tones instead of greenish. Got the random characters effects in the opening credits too. ^_^ Think I'll wait to watch it with my brother.  On the anime end, I'm still making my way through Excel Saga. I have absolutely no idea what's the whole point of the story (duh, wait, there's actually a story?), but it's funny. Love the dog Menchi. It's an "emergency food source" O_o The ending song is unique too, sung by Menchi itself (with accompanying monologue explaining what the whining is all about).  And on the guitar I'm working on "Julia Florida" by Augustin Barrios. Beautiful piece of music. Give me Barrios anytime. Many of his pieces are hard to play though. I'm halfway through the score already.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just can't work at home during the weekends. I need a quiet air-conditioned office to work. And it's hard to find motivation to work when you know that the powers that be may just decide to reverse direction, depending on which power it is you've just presented to. Well, at least I only need to write a paper outline, not a full paper, with various Annexes that people don't really read, or have the time to, but you must include in case you get challenged. Most of the time, decisions have to be made based on incomplete information anyway. Oh yeah, and with "perfect" English too, the definition of which depends on who is vetting your paper.  Why can't people just sit down and trash everything out once and for all?  And I'm doing this on our national day. Talk about serving the country...hahaha...  Several of my colleagues went on short trips to neighboring countries over the long weekend. *sigh* I wanted to go see some fireworks (and test out my digital camera's supposed ability to capture them) at the Fireworks Festival at the bay, but it doesn't seem like she's interested... (why do I even care anymore anyway?)  Anyway, I better get back to finishing that outline. The weekend is running out fast.
     

        
</post>


<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The colourful and maze-like Toy Factory in Lutie. Nice vantage point huh? Too bad I can't snipe at all in this place... :-( What's the diff between cliffs and walls? RO physics is weird...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Let it snow! Let it snow! Let it snow! The town of Lutie, where everyday it's X'mas!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Meet mah best fren Mr Snowman!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Heh heh, just got a maskerade from Dustiness, so decided to go for a little vanity photo shoot. Don't I look cool and mysterious...? It's rather useless for me though, so I gave it to my brother's character Sigurdhr to wear. He's a swordsman so he can afford to wear "useless" headgear. We poor archers must be practical. *sigh* Time to go back to wearing those goggles...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cliff-sniping Wild Roses (a fast moving cat-like creature) in Comodo. You need some luck to catch one wandering your way though, and you must be quick otherwise they'll run away. A priest blessed me from below the cliff while I was recovering my SP. Very nice of her. ^_^ I saw a couple of Hunters here taking on the Wild Roses head-on. O_o *drool* Must...train...harder....
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Taking a well-deserved breather in the famous water city of Al De Baran after a long and perilous journey. Well, actually, I got killed by a mob of Argoses trying to get here, so I got fed up and decided to spend some zeny to get the Kapra to teleport me here instead. ^_^
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Nice view from a treehouse near the top of the mountain of gigantic flowers.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    These flowers are humongous!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Nice view in the Geffen mountains. Too bad the telescope doesn't work.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    On a suspension bridge on my way to catch some butterflies...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Forest warfare - Hunting Elder Willows in the "Willow" map.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I deal death from afar! But don't worry, I do not KS!  Heh heh, just created a blog for my  urlLink Ragnarok Online  character, Ivar Riodhr. I recently started playing RO. Been playing for a month now. I'm not exactly a fan of online games, partly because I don't wanna fork out 20 bucks every month to play (my brothers have played a couple though). I like RO because of its cute Final Fantasy-like characters. Did I mention that I like to play Japanese-style RPGs? Yeah, you know, like Final Fantasy, Seiken Densetsu, Tales of Destiny, Knight of Lodis, etc etc. Anyway, RO is from Korea. I must say they are getting pretty good at making these online games - they need to work on the English though...  You can find me on the Malaysian RO Penril server. I don't log on that often, being a casual gamer. At the time of writing, I'm a Lvl 51/38 archer, and I'm proud to say I *do not* KS (i.e. "kill steal" other people's mobs) I tend to play solo, and I'm gonna become a falcon hunter! I thought of making a "battle bard" but after some research I think I'm better off with birds than a guitar (btw, I do play the classical guitar in real life).  I have a feeling I'm one of the oldest players on the Malaysian servers. -_-"  What am I going to put on this blog? I dunno, just thought it would be fun to put up a blog to chart my character's progress through the world of RO. I'll put up screenshots every now and then (already got some old ones). Oh, btw, I came up with the name "Ivar Riodhr" after looking at some websites on Norse names. I believe it means "Bowman from the Forest Clearing". I hope it's grammatically correct. :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be taking a break from RO for a while, until my brother Sigurdhr comes back from his Canada trip. I haven't been playing much lately anyway, so the 20 quid monthly access is not very cost-effective right now. I should log on again sometime in July.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's a picture of me in front of the toy factory in Lutie, to commemorate my (finally, coz I haven't been playing RO much lately) reaching job level 40 and being eligible for the Hunter class. But I'm not done yet. I want to max out my Attention Concentrate skill first, so I won't be changing until level 42. I don't think I'll pump my Arrow Shower, unless I find some wonderful training spot.  My brother changed class from Sowrdsman to Crusader at job level 50. O_o He had a very hard time reaching maxing out the job. One of the nice things about being Archer is that you'll have almost everything you want by level 40. ^_^
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    They are stationed all over RO, ensuring that the needs of the players are served, getting them to different parts of RO at the snap of a finger (for a fee), taking care of their items with their wonderful multi-dimensional cross-space-time (but not across servers) storage system (for a fee), and running the emergency ambulance service that resurrects fallen players (the wonders of RO medical science) and brings them back to their last save point (now this one is free).  Who are they? Why, the Kapra (or Kafra, the translation from original Korean is not very consistent) gals, of course! There's Solin and Deprotai and Tayelin and Debril and Clarus and Penny. Six wonderful females working behind the scenes. Let's give them some applause to show our appreciation! *clapclapclapclapclap* ^_^ The above screenshots are taken from the Kapra HQ in Aldebaran City.  Who's your favourite Kapra girl?  Oh, there are male Kapras too, but I'm not interested in them. ^_^ 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Shopping in the City of Prontera. I realised I have yet to take a picture of the famous busy streets of Prontera, where merchants lurk in every corner selling their wares. There's more people playing RO now than when I first started. Interestingly, RO is one of  urlLink GameFAQs  top 10 FAQs. It must be really popular all over the world.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Taking a breather on the steps at the Payon Castle. Hunters look cooler sitting down than Archers with their funny kneeling position.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woohoo! Finally made it to Hunter! I changed at Archer job level 42, after I maxed out Attention Concentrate. And here's the various stages I had to go through (mouseover the pics for a short description)   urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink      urlLink     I wasted no time gaining my hunter job levels nearby and getting my falcon. Thanks to the current increased experience points, I made short work of maxing out my falcon abilities, and getting ankle snare. The falcon is not that strong though. After getting my +5 Hunter Bow I realised that Double Strafe is still the best.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My brother encountered this cute scene the other day. A bunch of people were posing for a group photo, and all them were wearing sunflowers on their heads. ^_^ We spotted a merchant after the group broke up and guess what? He's selling the sunflowers at 100k zeny each! Now that's what I call a brilliant business plan...  Yep, came back to RO again after more than a month break. The Malaysian team has just won 3rd and 4th places at the RO World Championship, and to celebrate they are giving out increased experience and drop rates for a limited period, so I just gained another level. ^_^ 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Sakura patch was applied today, and I went out to try out the nerfed Double Strafe. I suppose I can live with the 0.3 second delay. It wasn't really that apparent to me actually. I seldom get the chance to whack multiple Double Strafes that quickly anyway.  This patch is also supposed to be the one where the Falcon attack is now of Wind element. So it can now damage Ghosts but not too great against Sohees. I can live with this too, since I don't really rely on my falcon.  I've been wondering how much it costs to go to the new maps. From what I can deduce, you take a ship from Alberta (that means $$$). The Amatsu map seems to be diagonal to the Gonryun map, so you have to walk through a field. Need to find out more about the monsters there before I go though. Anyway, I can always use my Teleport Clip to get out of danger. ^_^ 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I read that the Sakura patch will nerf archers and hunters yet again, by adding a 0.3 second delay to Double Strafe. Woe is me! for I rely heavily on the ability to do rapid-fire double strafes. T_T Well, I suppose it means I have to be a bit more nimble on my feet, and start running around... Or maybe I should start paying attention to traps... $_$ *sigh*  With the Sakura patch comes the Super Novice class, who supposedly can learn any of the skills of other 2nd level classes. Wonder if they can use bows? I don't suppose they can learn the quest skills such as the swordsman's walking HP recovery? How about teleporting? You can come up with some interesting builds... *deep in thought*  I'm still looking for good hunting grounds. Right now, I'm mostly dashing into Toy Factory 2, use up my SP and then dash out again before I get killed (I hate those Cruisers!). Sometimes when I'm bored I make a trip down to Morroc to hunt Hodes and Sandmans. Still, in terms of the value of drops and the damage to experience ratio I think the Toy Factory is still one of the better places. My brother tells me that if I wanna get rich I should go to Glast Heim and pick up after the bots there (and KS them too since they are mostly bots), but I can't quite survive there yet, plus I don't really like the idea of KS'ing people deliberately. ^_^
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Observng a would-be dancer going through her rites of passage in Comodo. Looks a lot like Dance Dance Revoluton to me. ^_^ It doesn't look easy though. The other hunter watching the dance with me appears to be her guild member, no doubt giving her encouragement. I hope I wasn't distracting them with my cute looks, heh. :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Kapra girl at Comodo is so cute! ^_^ She didn't say what her name was though. Now with the Sakura patch coming soon, and the new lands Amatsu and Gonryun, I wonder if there'll be more Kapra girls in RO.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>