<Blog>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So today, guys...if you missed the game WHICH I HOPE YOU ALL DIDNT...because even though we should have won they need all the support they need.. it was harsh. some might say brutal.  what the hell...im not sure if you guys noticed but we seem to lose to the 4TH PLACE team in our division..a game we could have easily won with Mientkiewicz as the Player of the Game from yesterday..but no. we lost. With the 2nd inning grand-slam played out by Cleveland. Harsh man, harsh.  But as in the words of the Pope, Hope is the answer. My boys will come through. so for all you guys out there  that are wondering where the best section is to sit in? two words. FAMILY SECTION  lmao. im out. aSh
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey...nows the time we all need a moment of silence. This, my friends...is the tribute to *Bobby* (or my nickname for him: firecrotch) My friends, let me share with you the journey we have all had with good ol' Bobby. Those sparkling eyes and winning smile on the field let us all have a little hope for our boys. The attitude of a winner and an arm like a slugger....we're gonna miss you, Bobby... *single tear* 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
                   AMERICAS PAST TIME BABY        Thats right.  hey by the way this is Ash. an obvious baseball fan. and this is my blog. enjoy!  So.....the purpose of this blog is well, lemme break it down for ya real quick. First, and foremost, i did not create this blog to spill my guts about obvious facts of the world, nor did i do it so i could write my every thought. i didnt do it so i could have a place to vent about my feelings on love, friendship, or anyother bullshit high school drama that everyone else seems to have a blast with writing about. who the fuck cares? get a life and stop talking to  the damn computer about your problems. its no substitute for  people . but what i did come here to do is spread the love of...what, you ask? *baseball*  I finished up watching the KC vs Twins today. please tell me that you all watched it.. ahh sweet victory. now i see were only about 5.5 games away from Kansas City. i really think that the windy city should blow away too. the Twins got it in 'em jus not mentally. so props to you, boys for a win we all needed. and i suppose that you guys are wondering about the high lights?  KC came up in the first with a homer to deep center field. 408 baby and im thinkin....wow... with KC leading by 1-0, Jones steps up the plate and meets the ball at the sweet spot bringing up the twins to 1-1 Hunter also gets a homer, then to be matched by KC to make it 2-2. an amazing 8th inning rolls around with Hocking and his rolling single up the middle. Stewart is up to the plate with a sacraficing bunt that turns out to drive him to 2nd and Hocking to 3rd. With Rivas at the plate, Gardy puts in pinch hitter *AJ PIERZYNSKI* with a hit into center field. He drives them in and stewart scores on a wild pitch to Mientkiewicz. Jones added a double to bring the overall score to 6-2. Hawkins throws a scoreless 8th inning for KC and no runs in the 9th. We did it boys...   :)  Go Twins...and remember kids, the outfielders are in the OUTfield.  over and out,                       have any Baseball questions? skittles0387@msn.com ash  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow! looks like TEXAS aint big enough for the both of us, Rangers! {DRAW}  shot gun bang, the Rangers go down. yippie : )  tonights game was awesome. Ri Ri had some great lil hits, hunter wasnt quite up to par. but its all gravy in the navy when you are only .5 games back. great job today fellas.  nice little story, for you all. since im sure since ur reading this blog you've got some time on ur hands. so hear me out. let me flow. cuz i work best when my true colors show. ahem.....cough cough... so i was working today. panera, guys. come in and try the bacon turkey bravo. NO! i take that back! lemme fix you up with a nice italina combo. 1,040 calories in that one baby! maybe for dessert you can down a stick of butter...but anyway back to the story. which really isnt even a story.. theres this fella, a nice guy, kinda creepy, likes to stare..that tends to 'overhear' some conversations between me and my bobble buddy stephanie. he decides to fill us IN on how  MR. DENNY HOCKING AND FAMILY  came into the SLP PANERA LAST THURSDAY and yet no one seemed to give a rats ass on how cool this was. i mean, its frickn PANERA for shits sake.... so anyway, i guess he has really small ankles and huge calves.  so thats my story. i think if i would have seen him it would have been an automatic restraining order.  todays player of the game: Dougie (since i missed calling him the POTG when he stole home)  lets just say that being a baseball fan is an awesome thing...lots of benefits.  i mean, im talkin high roller here. like how about makin friends with all of the 'lenny's' out there?....learnin about polar bears? having the hook up with where all the cameras are? being yelled at alot? learning about other peoples lives thru text messages and reflections? having your dad make friends with the 16 year old hot guys in the row infront of you? eating the taco salad? being on the jumbo-tron? (or lack thereof) drinkin beer? ( root  beer, that is) 1$ dome dogs? half price wednesday? super fan? fan of the game? makin friends with tommy teenager? granny gray hair? tailgating? driving to games in traffic? takin short cuts? making THE best posters? clever sayings? the kiss cam? the AJ alien face? getting foam fingers? having social anxiety disorder? talkin to the cracker jack gal? seeing the infamous 'glotter'? losing ur appetite to hot dog fingers? seeing body particals fall into ur soda? always seeing ANDREW? going to the twins fest? getting goody bags? reading the twins magazine? planning road trips? going to florida? santana and his song? catching home run balls? (or being afraid and moving away...) wondering wtf ppl are thinking when they ask if there is a 1/2 time in baseball? moving up rows to avoid embarassment? free DQ hat night? all the great promotions? matching t shirts? seeing all those blondes with the ripped jeans..then seeing them as the 'fan of the game'?   creating a blog that revolves around your love of the Minnesota Twins?  PRICELESS.   lets just say im a fan, and leave it at that.  with love and baseball,  ashley
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am never the person im not.    just wanted to clear things up, u know how we do.  so the TWINKIES have been doing fairly well..although i do think that the CWS are now a much larger threat to the ALC race than KC is *ahem...Kansas City..not KC* only 1 1/2 games back boys. keep it up. and DOUGIE u had some great stretches this game...i think you got cheated outta some too. *single tear* AJ u were looking cuter than ever. : ) but.....i must.. i must share with you..the very pain i felt while innocently viewing the Twins game on FSN... *let me set the scene for you* theres me, sitting on my couch. living room. second floor. Flag ave. Ri Ri is up to bat. im sitting there, wishing that my little RIRI could pull somethin' great. somethin' unexpected. somethin' good. and he did. wow. did he ever. got a nice Homer in the Domer--left center field...so i was thinking, OMG nothing bad can come out of this.. until...DUN DUN DUN....they do a close up of that lucky little 7 year old that had the privelege of catching RI RI'S homer. EXCEPT IT WASNT A 7 YEAR OLD AT ALL... >:0 it was HARD HAT that little S.O.B. u know...the one OLD guy that gets all the GOOD seats and YELLS at me and STEPHANIE to hold UP our SIGNS for the CAMERAS?! yea thats the one.  but its ok...*snodaze smile* at least RI RI got a homer in the domer. : ) *tee hee*  but thats about it for now. ive got the stories up the wa-zoo for next time.  butter believe it, baby. [387]  with love and AHH! REAL MONSTERS-- ash 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      man! its been along time since ive blogged. *single tear* wow have i got alot to fill you in on... lemme start with the game i went to..u all know it...the 14 innings one? damn. was an awesome game until romero flipped it up...threw to 1st base when theres a runner heading home....once again, romero...LEMME BREAK IT DOWN FOR YA REAL QUICK.... *your sole purpose is to COVER HOME... >:0* arg. shit almost hit the fan when i saw that one. so i removed myself of the situation and walked away. with my father. whom joined me at the game. the one time when there are like 7 guys my age right infront of us. and stephie isnt there. GREAT. but dont fret, i mean my dad got to be real buds with them. stuck up for them too infact. but thats a different story for a different time.  ahh yes. then comes to winning streak from the TWINS which, as always, comes with a losing game. its ok tho it was against KC Royals.   side note: dont refer to Kansas City as 'KC' >  that was the game today.  5-4. player of the game: AJ and Doug. jus cause theyre hot.  tee hee : )  remember kids, the wave died in the 80's...and Denny has a GREAT SMILE.    side note: not my father..Mr. Hocking >   love and the way the Bossssssskie runs,  ash
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well heeeelllloooo newman. {jerry newman} the twins won today. weve gained yet another 1/2 game. first place here we come!  *tee hee* but monday is just around the corner and it looks to be the last game of the summer for me and stephbi---- i mmeeaan stephanie.... to go to before we pitch a tent on September 6, 2003.  today i went to work. and was staring at Johns name tag. why? u ask? because hes a baseballa and likes the twins. so i find that my eyes tend to glaze over while in his presence. and i was thinking that my boys have come along way.  yes, a long way. long as in 11 years long. and they've come so far. and i am so proud. props to john for having the TC on his tag. ahh gotta love it. Tyler came in today. tee hee. i couldnt hear a damn thing because of the crazed middle-aged women going thro menopausal shreaks every 5 minutes. its was ok tho cuz i just peeked at him thru the bread baskets... :-/ it was all in good fun. nice, innocent, fun. last night rocked. i wont go into details.  so great game boys sorry i missed it. todays Player of the Game: AJ pierzynski cuz well, lets face it, hes a hottie with a body.  with love and i guess im a younger kevin, ash  ps.-oh YEAH~i didnt do it with joe. OKF   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      halo halo! twins game today was awesome with some great plays and runs. yay Ri Ri (lOUIE rivas) for his great catch in the 2nd. im proud, very proud. Sha-non (shannon stewart) had a great homer to tie up the game. that was sweet. today was eventful...woke up then went out for a lil drive with an expected and quite frankly, unexpected phone call. its all gravy. got home and mowed the lawn. now, normally i wouldnt talk about mowing the lawn cuz who cares you know? but i KNOW that all you baseball fans would care cuz i mowed it to look like a baseball field. yay. :) it didnt really work out so dont u all get excited. then went out to maple grove to look at some cars. no luck. but i did listen to the game on 830. ahh yes. excitement flows through my loins. tee hee. ; )  Todays Player of the Game: Louis Rivas    ohh my Ri Ri ! ah the smell of sweet, sweet victory.  with love and sparkling eyes and a glowing face fan fo life--   Caula
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AH yes. and yet another blog has been added.. good stuff. so about this Twins losing stuff, im not likin it. i, agree with danyuel that i thought they had it in 'em. its ok though cuz were gonna come through. i think that im going to have my own little 'Player of the Game' for all you guys out there. starting now. and todays POTG was Doug Mientkiewicz #16 with his awesome sliding catch and back handed flip to Rincon to get the 2nd out in the 8th inning. Great job boys.  with love and my announcer mouth,  ---ash  ps..lets just put it on the record saying that Anthony John is hot. ..and also another POTG considering he troted into homeplate today to make the final score 3-2   yay
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well well well. looks like were only a few games back from chicago? da white socks suck. YEAH THATS RIGHT. i said it. : / so anywho....just sitting here back from a late night run to Bee's of the Apple. rriigghhtt. i joke. it was T-bell. what a win, boys. im proud. The first inning HOMER? by who other than the hotttttest guy ever? ....better back off i can see stephanie right about now cursing me and my Y2K chapstick.... dougie. whatta guy. so right now im just planning our trip down to watch spring training over break. its gonna be awesome. there seems to be a little kink in the plans, considering it would take me all year to save up for a 3 day AMTRAK trip.  G.R.E.A.T. so yes. i think im gonna hafta call it a....a....a...ROADTRIP ..daddy? you know, with my new Conquest car. im excited. so good job today, fellas. : )  with love and AFLAK STUPID DRIVER     ---ash
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      halo howatchu? im doin might ffiinnnee considering the awesome job we've done these past few days. WOWZAH that game with the Indians??? GREAT STUFF but on a sad note..*ahem* the Tigers game with MN. wtf was that fellas. WE.LOST.TO.THE.TIGERS. its all good tho cuz we came back and won. yay. : ) so today is sunday aug 3, 2003 and ive had a long day. no, not my usual tough schedule with the long hours watching the Real World re-runs but i hadda get up at 6 in the a.m.  why, u ask? KOSKIE BOBBLEHEADS yepp. sat out side today with my good pal and fellow super fan stephanie, u know, playin speed and eating gummy crocks. an seeing, well, a Jolly Green Giant. i wont name names. so it was cool. gates opened at 11 and we made the cut. just one of 10,000 lucky lil twinkie fans. but thats about it. we won 7-2 vs Tigers. it was a great game. but thats about it for now ive covered just about all i can tolerate at this point. hope u all watch when we win the WS '03 cuz then ima rub it in ur face. booyah.  remember kids.... KOSKIE is the BOSSKIE.   with love and church boys,                  skittles0387@msn.com ash
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OH MY FRICKN GOD  CAN WE SAY....UM...MAYBE THE BEST 3 HOURS OF BASEBALL IN MY LIFE? YES. ROGER THAT. {but not roger clemens, mind you}  CENTRAL DIVISION CHAMPS  better get out for the homer hanks! tee hee tee hee tee hee  ohmygod. the yankees are goin di-zzown player of the game: christan guzman hottie of the game: as always, AJ. pitcher of the game:JOHAN SANTANA  team of the century: Mn twins                   and to think...im missing the SLP homecoming dance to chill at the homer dome for playoffs on saturday and sunday...what could be better? : )  with love for the twins, but never a super-duper-blonde haired- fan, ash
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Twins beat bumbling Yanks after 13 straight losses   -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- By Buster Olney ESPN The Magazine     RECAP | BOX SCORE | GAME LOG | PHOTOS  NEW YORK -- As the Yankees ran out of outs in Game 1 of the Division Series, the grumbling from the Yankee Stadium crowd increased in intensity and the chins of the hitters seemed to drop further with each strikeout. The Yankees' tradition and great expectations had once been a weapon for them. Now it looks like a burden.   Game 1 breakdown     Hero LaTroy Hawkins. He was nearly unhittable in his two innings -- seventh and eighth -- of work, striking out four while walking none. In all, he threw 27 pitches, 21 for strikes.  Goat Bernie Williams. Letting the ball Torii Hunter hit to the right-center gap in the top of the sixth inning get past him and go to the wall was pivotal as it allowed the Twins to have a big inning. Not only did Matthew LeCroy score all the way from first base on the play, but Hunter also scored when Alfonso Soriano took the relay from Williams and threw it wild past third base.   Turning Point With runners on first and third and out in the bottom of the seventh, Hawkins came up big by striking out Soriano and Nick Johnson to end the inning. In striking out Soriano, Hawkins threw a perfect pitch -- a fastball -- on the outside part of the plate that Soriano swung through.   It Figures Leaving runners on base usually proves disastrous for teams and that was definitely the case for the Yankees. The Yanks stranded 10 runners, including five in scoring position.   On Deck The Twins will send Brad Radke to the mound against the Yankees in Game 2. Radke was 9-1 with a 3.24 ERA in 14 starts in the second half. The Yankees will counter with Andy Pettitte, who led the team with 21 wins during the regular season.     The Minnesota Twins, on the other hand, almost bounced off the field, after winning, 3-1, to take the first game in the best-of-five series. There is a respite in the series Wednesday, giving the Twins 48 hours to rest a bullpen that contributed five strong innings in Game 1, 48 hours to relax and enjoy New York.  But for 48 hours, the Yankees must try not to think about what might happen. They looked very flat in Game 1, playing sloppily, making mistakes, looking very little like a World Series favorite and more like they did when they were swiftly eliminated by Anaheim in the 2002 Division Series.  "We've got to show up on Thursday," said catcher Jorge Posada. "I know we can do it, I know we'll show up on Thursday."  Said Minnesota left fielder Shannon Stewart: "This is a huge win."  The Yankees had beaten the Twins in the last 13 regular-season meetings between the two teams, and New York starter Mike Mussina was 20-2 in his career against the Minnesota. But that history did not matter; if anything, the Yankees looked more like they did when they were swiftly eliminated by Anaheim in the 2002 Division Series, playing sloppily, making mistakes.  And they caught a break on an unexpected injury, after getting dominated early by Johan Santana, the Twins starter.  Santana appears to throw from a relatively low arm angle, making it difficult for the hitters to pick up the ball; they constantly react just a little late, as if Santana is throwing from 55 feet instead of 60 feet, 6 inches. Right-handed hitters kept peeling fouls into the stands along the right field foul line, while left-handed batters fouled balls into the stands behind third base.  Santana struggled to throw any of his secondary pitches for strikes in his four innings, his slider spinning high, his changeup often flopping in the dirt. But his fastball was so good -- masked by the deception built into his delivery -- that the Yankees rarely mustered healthy swings against Santana, even when they knew he had to throw a fastball.   Right-handed hitters kept peeling fouls into the stands along the left field side. "He was tough," said Soriano.  The Twins scored a run in the third, after Alfonso Soriano failed to bare-hand an infield single by Cristian Guzman, and in the bottom of the fourth, the Yankees' Nick Johnson walked with two outs. Derek Jeter got ahead in the count 2 balls and 0 strikes, and with Jason Giambi on deck. It was a great situation for Jeter, knowing that Santana had to throw a fastball.  And Santana did throw a fastball, 92 mph. But Jeter swung late, fouling off the pitch. The count went to 3-1, another hitter's count, another situation in which Jeter knew he could hack at a fastball. And Santana did throw a fastball, 91 mph. But Jeter swung late again, fouling the ball off.  Jeter eventually walked, but Santana struck out Giambi on three pitches, Santanta's third strikeout in four innings.  Santana went back to the dugout, but as he sat on the bench, he felt his right hamstring camp -- an occasional problem with his left leg during the regular season. Gardenhire scanned the lineup card and began matching up his relievers, the Twins' right-handers against the Yankees' right-handers, lefties vs. lefties, and the call went to the bullpen. "The phone rang and we were like, 'Oh, my God,'" said Hawkins.  Rick Reed got a couple of outs, before J.C. Romero took over to get the last out in the fifth. The Twins still had four innings to go, and their margin for error still very slim, with the Yankees trailing by only a run.  That would change in the top of the sixth. Twins DH Matt LeCroy pulled a single inside the third base leading off against Mussina. Jacque Jones struck out, but with Mussina's pitch count climbing toward 100, Torii Hunter smashed a line drive into short right-center field, the ball skipping low. Bernie Williams moved over to cut the ball off, appearing as if he had an easy play and would be able to hold LeCroy at second.  But the ball skidded low on the outfield grass -- veering to Williams' left, he said after the game -- and the speed of the bounder appeared to surprise Williams, rolling past him. LeCroy rumbled to third and was waved home as Williams retrieved the ball, and when Hunter sprinted around second and decided to try for an extra base, cut-off man Alfonso Soriano fired toward third.  Soriano's throw sailed high, however, bouncing off the facing of the seats on the third base side and a rolling away from third baseman Aaron Boone. By the time Boone recovered the ball and threw home, Hunter had swiped his hand across home plate with Minnesota's third run. "It was unfortunate," said Yankees manager Joe Torre, "but you have to make the plays, obviously, when you play in postseason, because they are magnified."  Hideki Matsui and Boone reached base to start the Yankees' seventh inning, but with one out, reliever LaTroy Hawkins blew away Soriano with a 96 mph fastball, then Nick Johnson with a chest-high 97 mph fastball.  Hawkins picked up two more strikeouts in the eighth inning, before Twins closer Eddie Guardado took over for the ninth. Williams singled, and Hideki Matsui drove a ball deep to the left field wall. Stewart retreated, jumped and made the catch in front of the outstretched hands of fans, banging against the wall and falling. "At first I was like, 'Whew,'" said Twins catcher A.J. Pierzynski, "and then I was thinking, 'Thank God, not Jeffrey Maier' " -- the kid who reached out to pull in Derek Jeter's home run in the 1996 playoffs.  A run scored on Soriano's infield single, but Guardado retired Johnson with a week grounder, and amid the muttering of departing fans, the voices of a couple of dozen happy Minnesota players could be heard.  It could have all turned badly for the Twins in the innings that followed Santana's injury. But the four relievers combined to get the last 15 outs, Santana figures to be ready to pitch Game 4 with even more rest than expected, and the Twins' bullpen can rest Wednesday.  The day off might only increase the anxiety for the Yankees. Andy Pettitte, the Yankees' starter in Game 2, has recent postseason failure hanging on his psyche: he failed to get out of the third inning in Game 6 of the 2001 World Series and couldn't reach the fourth inning in Game 2 of last year's Division Series, and the Yankees were beaten each time.  Pettitte and the other Yankees have an extra 24 hours to think about what went wrong in Game 1, what went wrong last year, and what could go wrong. The pressure on the Yankees builds.  Buster Olney is a senior writer for ESPN The Magazine.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so ima just say that im happy. the twins are awesome.  tit-tat-pussy-wack-give a perve his child,   ash ; )
     
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My favorite place, is by far, is the Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome.  Not only is it a great place for all baseball fans alike and america's pastime, but it also provides great educational value as a vital geographical landmark of the Minneapolis and surrounding area.     Physical parts of the Metrodome are critical when describing the geographical theme 'place.'  To have an enjoyable evening or afternoon at the ballpark, one has to understand the 'little men' behind the scenes that make it that way.  For one, they maintain the inside temperature of the Homer Dome at a comfortable 70 degrees fahrenheit throughout the year.  Although the dome has been the butt of many jokes in the sports world since it opened on April 7, 1982, it's archetectual achievements have had fans in in awe after a greatly played game of baseball by the Minnesota Twins.  As for the terrain of the Metrodome, a nicely manicured Astro Turf lines the field, undoubtibly similar to the realistic 'grass' from the popular 1970's television show The Brady Bunch.  Quality dome dirt covers the four bases, as well as the pitchers mound which holds 23,000 pounds atop of an electricly powered plate and is 18 feet in diameter.  Vegetation inside the HHH Metrodome consists of your average debris, usually leaves and/or dirt brought in by your average patron.  It's no jungle in the dome, such to keep the temperature down. If you think about it, it is a good thing there is no active vegetation, as the Metrodome would no longer be a sports center, but a green house.     Being a public place, people have brought in a fair share, if not all of what you see in the Metrodome.  With the avaliable capacity of 48,678, you are bound to run into many different races, languages, religions and ways of life.  The dome now becomes less of a green house, and more of a tossed salad of culture.  It is also important to point out that all of these different ways of life, races, and religions can come together for the sake of Minnesota baseball.  If you are lucky and craving some ethnic cuisine, meander up to 2nd floor, section 208 for the Cantina Mexican Grill for genuine authentic mexican tacos and nachos.  Better yet, get tickets for Heritage Night at the Metrodome sponsored by Hormel.  Baseball plus cultural education?  Nothing beats that.     As for the region, the HHH Metrodome is located in the greater part of Minneapols, Minnesota.  Located at 900 South Fifth Street, it serves great purpose and easy access to sports and recreation.     All this talk has made me a little verclempt, as now I will leave you with the warm fuzzy feeling from talking baseball.  I have become reminiscent to the Kenny Roger's song 'The Greatest.'  Strike three, and im out.   you cant play a playa.  x0x0  ash
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      WOWZAH. man today was EXCITING! for all of your that need some background info: today was the Hormel AJ Pierzynski Bobble Head giveaway day at the metrodome. naturally, being the Twins fan that i am, make plans to camp out for those lil buggas. so me and my bobble buddy Stephanie get all packed up and ready with our lil napsacks and fridge and head out at 4 in the A.M. to camp. so get there, find a cozzy lil spot on the grassy knoll under a tree and get ready for the day ahead. i was thinkin this was gonna b pretty good. (i mean, we had a GREAT spot in line and everything)  then it started to go downhill.. more and more people were lurkin from the streets and coming in line. no problem, u say..well you say WRONG cuz it was a very big problem. so theres this old guy, (lets call him Herve...herve the perve)  im going to say about 45-50 years in age, ripped shirt, pot belly , bald head, and some glasses on. to the average eye this guy poses no harm. until now. so me and steph are sittin there, and notice that this guy....has a little black camera in his fanny pack. u know, nothing out of the ordinary for a twins game, right? WRONG. we musta been watching him for a good hour before me and my BB realized that this guy wasnt taking your average pictures of scenery, but of your average little boy. yup. no joke. there were some little fellas playin catch and he would just walk right up to take their pic. it was sick. and i was thinkin i was about to blow chunks. so i try to just, u kno, put it in the back of my mind, while i reach into BB's goody bag for a bagle. and then he comes. 'do u mind if i take a picture of u?' -herv the perv  'uhhh no, u cant take a picture!' (looks away with hands over my face) -me and herv walks away.  im sittin there, thinking OMFG lets leave this guy is sick...but then there was the fact that weve been sitting in line for about 3 hours and didnt wanna leave our spot...so we tucked it out. but then i watched him take more pictures of little boys. and teenage girls. and couples sitting together. and couples making out on the grassy knoll. and women with their little boys. and then he was starring at me again. and i was gonna b sick. so BB has her back to him to make sure he wont b able to see me. but he keeps dodging his head about stephanies to get a look at me. I AM NOT FLATTERING MYSELF so dont say that em the flem....he was perv. the his friiend turns his chair around to face me and steph and Herv comes back around, stands in front of me and steph, puts up his camera and takes a picture with our hands over our face. talk about SICK. so then we got our stuff and left.  but we still managed to get our bobble heads, so it was ok.  then we watched the game and had the brilliant idear to sit out side and wait for the players to come out of the dome and go to their cars. and we saw most of them (gg cc gg cc)and i got a picture with AJ and his autograph and RON GARDENHIRE SAID THAT HE LIKED MY HAIR! HOW AWESOME IT THAT??!! very.  then me and steph went to Best Buy in maple grove for Johan Santana's autograph and we got a picture with him too. omg it was the best day im telling ya.  but thats about. and im getting a cramp in my fingers from typing all of this so ima fill u in later...  love and the way my body was shaking when AJ Pierzynksi put his arm around me,   --Bobble Buddy #1  p.s. were in 1st place suckas!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      omgomgomgomgogogmogmgomogmgommog.  tonight was prolly the most fun ive had in a long time.  man, do i love T Mobile. And the Bend and Snap. and Katie. {:-/} and Panera...[knollwood] and Jacks Pizza...[on sale 6 for 10] and bacon turkey bravos and Ru-eee-see-a. and tube streaks. and hoods. [J-T is that you? as in jonathan taylor thomas? as in home improvement? as in tool time? as in i'll be home for christmas? as in santi claus? as in sitting on old mens laps? as in DOMINATING?] just checkin...  so friday is the big PAR...TAY. according to 'omg ur brothers gotten a whole buncha ppl pregnant and he gets drunk offa sunny D???' yeah. as in her. so im thinking.....we load up out egging guns and hit the streets that are filled of little children aimlessly wandering the streets and eating poisoned candy...and we get em. i hear they like that. at least i did when i was little. [well only if you replace the words 'egging guns' with 'my daddys tube steak' and 'wandering streets' with 'playing invisible']  yesss. {cluck *whistle* arm pumps -yesss-}  so i had alotta fun. yes. we. had. fun.  mm hhmmm  with love and hoods and little arms and mustaches that i thought were going to be funny.....  asssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssh
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well let us see on what has tickled ashleys clit to write about today...  first, if the thought of working at Panera has EVER...ever and i mean EVER entered your pitty little piss brains, dont work there. you dont want me to elaborate.  second, if i look like shit, dont tell me i look like shit.  third, if we happen to have a firedrill, dont go running down the hall as if someone shot a rocket up your ass. its only a drill. say it with me : d-r-i-l-l-.  fourth, dress up for halloween. its all in good fun.  fifth, if you happen to talk   real   fast and get   real   excited when you tell a story please remember to swallow the spit that has built up along the edges of your mouth. its only polite.  sixth, listen to music for the feeling you get when you read it. not the instant hard on you get when you watch a brittany spears/madonna video. and we all know that you put it on mute anyway.  seventh, please dont be a poser. it will save us all and extra 'ugh why does she do that' comment  eigth, is that how you spell eigth?   ninth, if you honestly, truely, dont remember what you wrote in your blog, dont have me explain it to you because it gets me mad.  and finally one last thing to talk about?..  tenth, shits gonna hit the fan when i lace all that cand--- i mean   thats all. happy freak day   ash
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      everything with substance is gone
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i used to know the sound of a smile in your voice.  isnt that true? i mean you can totally tell when someone is smiling when you talk to them on the phone. And then it makes you smile.  ive been influenced to write my views. and you know what? i think thats what im gonna do.  Sometimes, dont you just sit there, half awake but lying down, and think about the world? i often find myself wondering what i would be doing if i wasnt, me. Which, then obviously, gets me thinking about what people think of me. what i look like to other people. But...i must add, Do Not Get Me Wrong. i think that when people say that they dont care what people think, they are lying like asian rugs.   i think that we all walk around, constantly wondering what we look like to everyone else. (speaking of...why do people always check themselves out in every reflection they walk by..have you changed in the last 5 minutes??) i think that as shallow as it is, it will never change. but the thing that separates me and my friends from most, is that even though we are curious as to what people think...it will never have an affect on us. i wont ever look at myself and say 'maybe i shouldnt wear this to school...dont wanna be shunned by the abercrombie clique' dont get me wrong, though. i dont have anything against anyone, unless they are unable to accept other people as they are. i dont understand how some people walk the halls, completely oblivious to the fact that as they walk, and as they give those looks, they are taking away someones thunder. i just think that we are only in highschool for so long..why not get to know someone that you never pictured yourself as being friends with? i find myself talking about this stuff all the time with my friends. and once again, we cant understand the human race... or maybe just the slp highschool race. cuz we   know and accept the fact that no matter what we do, its never going to be okay in some peoples eyes. but i say that being your own person is definatly okay.   its weird... usually the people that understand everyone else, is the most alone.   just somethin to think about until baseball starts up again.. o0o0o0o ash
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so today is monday. and already im putting a pistol to the brain. nah...i jest.  so im just thinking about how useless this blog is. i mean, for me, it will always make me giggle. but....ima thinkin that its not having the same effect to the rest of the 2 whole people that read this damn thing. but u know whatever works.  hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm. today was fun. i feel bad.  i think someone likes to play butt darts. but he doesnt even know it yet. poor guy. rhymes with 'bandrew'  but yeah. thats all i have to say right now. pretty pathetic yes i know need u RUB IT IN?! c'mon man whats with the third degree...   with love and Dr. D's cameltoe, (ahh i miss that old thing) -ash  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So its friday night an i feel alright. not really, actually. long day if i do say so myself. i dont really get some people. i think they were sent here to destory. self esteem, i mean.  but anywho its been a long week without my baseball. i guess i dont really know what im gonna do til april. {sidenote no one remembers home openers? WELL I DO AND WE LOST} sry. outbreak. its all gravy in the navy.  but now since baseball is over and nothing new is happening--this blog is left with nothing. now, dont get me wrong, its not gonna become a pitty page cuz god knows how much i hate them, but i think for now im just gonna hafta write whatevers on my mind and if u dont like it dont read it. : )  but u know, i always come through. hopefully this is gonna b entertaining and all. cuz well, lets face it, u didnt read my blog for your health (speaking to the 2 people that read this of course)  but for now im off. its a busy day in the life of WonderWoman.  with love and saving the world from selfless pity, ash
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ohh man. today was hectic.    now dont get me wrong. i dont wanna sound all dyke-ish but i have a feeling that thats what its going to sound like. i recent situation has provoked a thought that i should probably write down sooner or later.   im serious. you are my best friend and i seriously dont know what i would do if u werent here.  i never really thought of myself to have very close friends, well i do but i just never considered them to have that much of an impact. i didnt realize how much just one person can have so much of an effect on you that if something happened you would feel totally lost.   i dont frickn know who i would go to with my stories or to listen to one of their own. im not sure who i would talk to online when no ones on, not sure who i would laugh with considering no one has my sence of humor except you. i dont know who i could just drive arond with but somehow have the best time and i dont know who would do my hair for me when the color goes out. i dont know who i could go to southdale with and head up to UT with, dont know who i could go into pac sun with, dont know who i could envision my boyfriend with. dont know who i could get a pizza with and sit on excelsior, dont know who i could go to mound with. dont know who i could go to jubilee with and i certainly dont know anyone else who could understand me. this is all a little sick but u know what, as dyke-ish as it sounds, im happy were friends and weve stayed friends cuz i dont know what i would do without you.  with love and ASS, gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i got this survey from Donnies blog..which im sure he doesnt know who i am..nor does he know that i read his blog..but its all in good fun. so these are my answers for ya. copy and paste into ur blog so i have something to read..  1)The singular most boring question: Do you have a picture? Yes (2) Are you happy with it? depends on which one it is. (3) Are you named after anyone? yes...but we wont talk about that. (5) Your screen name: i have alot. lets just say im a lil obsessed? sgrrbitztwin (6) Would you name a child of yours after you? nope. (7) Then what would you name your children? Elizabeth Profanity : D  (8) If you were born a member of the opposite sex, what would your name be? alex. (9) If you could switch names with a friend, who would it be? no one i like my name.(10) Are there any mispronunciations/typos that people do with your name constantly? YES. *cough cough* Ms. Karyusef........ :-/ (11) Would you drop your last name if you became famous? it already is.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~  BASICS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (12) Your gender: female (13) Straight/gay/bi? Straight. (14) Single? i suppose.. (15) Want to be? i get confused. (16) Your birth date: feb 3  (17) Your age: 16 (18) Age you act: i have a 3rd grade boy's sence of humor. put it that way. (19) Age you wish you were: 17 (20) Your height: 5â€™5â€�  (21) The color of your eyes: green and brown (22) Happy with it? yup (23) The color of your hair: dark brown with red green and blue.. (24) Happy with it? very. (25) Left/right/ambidextrous? Right (26) Your living arrangement? mom dad brother 2 dogs.. (27) Your family: :-/ ? (29) What's your job: sandwich line/ dish bitch. (panera) (30) Piercings? ears (31) Tattoos? not at the moment (32) Obsessions? music. (33) Addictions? music (35) Do you speak another language? spanish IV....not that i have anything to show for it (36) Have a favorite quote? your friends should like you for the person you are, not the many you can be -peg leg (37) Do you have a webpage? this is it.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DEEP THOUGHTS about life and you in it  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (38) Do you live in the moment? of course (39) Do you consider yourself tolerant of others? as individuals, yes. (40) Do you have any secrets? many.  (41) Do you hate yourself? sometimes (42) Do you like your handwriting? by 7th hour, yes. (43) Do you have any bad habits? yeah. (44) What is the compliment you get most from people? they like my hair. or i make them laugh. (45) If a movie was made about your life, what would it be called? Confessions of a gum chewer. (46) What's your biggest fear? guilt. (47) Can you sing? hell. no. (48) Do you ever pretend to be someone else just to look cool? hell. no. (49) Are you a loner? at times. (50) What are your no. 1 priorities in life? live happy, be myself. (51) If you were another person, would you be friends with you? im hella cool. (52) Are you a daredevil? just call me evil kanevil. (53) Is there anything you fear or hate about yourself? yes. (54) Are you passive or aggressive? depends on who i am around. (55) Have you got a ? feet....? (56) What is your greatest strength and weakness? i think i can relate to people and what they are going through...but i tend to brush people off.. (57) If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be? i would want to be upfront with people..not let things slip away. (58) There are three wells, love, beauty and creativity.. i dont know. creativity? (59) How do you vent? my blog. yes, and thats sad.  (60) Do you think you are emotionally strong? yes very. (61) Is there anything you regret doing/not doing in life? yes, i regret not making things happen. ive wasted so much time on that. (62) Do you think life has been good so far?at times. (63) What is the most important lesson you've learned from life? be who you are...and no matter how well you think you know someone that can always change. (64) What do you like the most about your body? :-/ (65) And least? it would be hard to narrow down the list. (66) Do you think you are good looking? i have my decent days.  (67) Are you confident? now i am. (68) What is the fictional character you're most like?gus gus. (69) Do people know how you feel? not all the time. (70) Are you perceived wrongly? definatly.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DO YOU...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (71) Smoke? no  (72) Do drugs? no  (73) Read the newspaper? the sports (74) Pray? no (75) Go to church? no  (76) Talk to strangers who IM you? not really (77) Sleep with stuffed animals? one (78) Take walks in the rain? being wet makes me miserable. but i like puddles. (79) Talk to people even though you hate them? yes (80) Drive? yes (81) Like to drive fast? when there arent any ice slicks that could further provoke accidents...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WOULD OR HAVE YOU EVER...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (82) Liked your voice? oh ho hell no. (83) Hurt yourself? not physically. (84) Been out of the country? yes  (85) Eaten something that made other people sick? yes (86) Had sex? no  (87) Been unfaithful? no 88) Been in love? yes (89) Done drugs? .. (90) Gone skinny dipping? yes (91) Had a medical emergency? yes  (92) Had a surgery? no (93) Ran away from home? yes. although the actual duration wouldnt even be considered running away... (94) Played strip poker? no (95) Gotten beaten up? well i do have an older brother (97) Been picked on? yes  (98) Been on stage? yes (99) Been so drunk that you know you're supposed to go out on a date with someone, but you can't remember with who or when and then you faint when you look at yourself in the mirror in the morning, not to mention your breath? ...sadly no. (100) Slept outdoors? yes (101) Thought about suicide? yes (102) Pulled an all-nighter? of course (103) if yes, what is your record? i dont remember (104) Gone one day without food? 0.0 what?! dont act so suprised...yes, i have. (105) Talked on the phone all night? yup. (106) Slept together with the opposite sex without actually having sex? yes (107) Slept all day? yes (108) Killed someone? no  (109) Made out with a stranger? no (110) Had sex with a stranger? no (111) Thought you're going crazy? yes  (112) Kissed the same sex? no (113) Done anything sexual with the same sex? no  (114) Been betrayed? yes (115) Had a dream that came true? yes  (116) Broken the law? yes (117) Met a famous person? yes (118) Have you ever killed an animal by accident? yes (119) On purpose? yes  145) Told a secret you swore you wouldn't tell? maybe... 146) Stolen anything? mm..dont think so (147) Been on radio/TV.? yes. (148) Been in a mosh-pit? yes (149) Had a nervous breakdown? yes (150) Considered religious vocation? no.. (151) Been criticized about your sexual performance? no ..theres nothing to criticize.. (152) Bungee jumped? no  (153) Had a dream that kept coming back? yes   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  CLOTHES and other fashion  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (154) Shoe brand? etnies (155) Brand of clothing? no pref..just not a 60.00 piece of ripped cotton they call a 'shirt' (156) Cologne/perfume? yeah. sunflowers. (157) What are you normally wearing to school/work? Jeans and a music tee (158) How about parties? same (159) Wear hats? only baseball. (160) Judge other people by their clothing? im sure.  (161) Wear make-up? yes. (162) Favorite place to shop?  anyplace with music tees..hot topic etc... (163) Favorite article of clothing? AFI shirt (164) Are you trendy? to me i am. (165) Would you rather wear a uniform to school? no   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  BELIEFS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (166) Believe in life on other planets? yes  (167) Miracles? yes (168) Astrology? yes as in stars... (169) Magic? no (170) God? yes (171) Satan? i hope not.. (172) Santa? the spirit i guess.. (173) Ghosts? yes  (174) Luck? yes  (175) Love at first sight? yes  (176) Yin and Yang? ? (177) Witches? no (178) Easter bunny? i always got the shaft on easter...damn bunny... (179) Believe it's possible to remain faithful forever? yes (180) Believe there's a pot of gold at the end of the rainbow? i dont like rainbows. (181) Do you wish on stars? yes  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  DEEP THEOLOGICAL QUESTIONS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (182) Do you believe in the traditional view of Heaven and Hell? i dont think so (183) Do you think God has a gender? No (184) Do you think that science counteracts religion? ...idk (185) Do you believe in organized religion? NO (186) Where do you think we go when we die? i have no idea. *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  AMIGOS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (187) Do you have any gay/lesbian friends? no (188) Who is/are your best friends? emily katie stephanie meghan..some others (189) Who's the one person that knows most about you? emily (190) What's the best advice that anyone has ever given to you? be yourself (191) Your favorite inside joke? LOVE 'EM. and there are way to many. this world would be very dull without them. (192) Thing you're picked on most about? im not sure.  Friends (194) Newest? mm....idk actually. the baker square guy? yea. him. (195) Shyest? all at times.. (196) Funniest? all. (197) Sweetest? .....idk (198) Closest? emily (199) Weirdest? man..every last one of us. |tee hee| (200) Smartest? stephanie (201) Ditziest? katie. haha. (202) Friends you miss being close to the most? im close with all my friends. (203) Last person you talked to online? meghan (204) Who do you talk to most online? emily and steph..which isnt all that much. (205) Who are you on the phone with most? katie...or tyler (206) Who do you trust most? you cant trust anyone. (207) Who listens to your problems? emily steph katie meghan manda everyone (208) Who do you fight most with? emily. its a love/hate sorta thing. : D (209) Who's the nicest? katie (210) Who's the most outgoing? eh....i dont know (211) Who's the best singer? manda (212) Who's on your shit-list? i dont have a shit list. (213) Have you ever thought of having sex with a friend? no (214) Who's your second family? katie or manda or em or steph i guess everyone..? (215) Do you always feel understood? fully understood? never. (216) Who's the loudest friend? it depends on the occasion. (217) Do you trust others easily? at times. (see 206) (218) First person you fell in love with? shane (219) Name one person whose arms you feel safe in: i.. dont know (220) Do your friends know you? like the back of my hand (221) Friend that lives farthest away: shane  **********************************************************************************   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  LOVE, and all that  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (222) Did you get frightened or uncomfortable seeing that as a section title? ..... no  (223) Do you remember your first love? yes (224) Still love him/her? Yes (225) Do you consider love a mistake? no (226) What do you find romantic? guitars (227) Turn-on? passion for a hobbie (228) Turn-off? ignorance  (229) First kiss? friday? lol (231) If someone you had no interest in dating expressed interest in dating you, how would you feel? like that would happen... (232) Do you prefer knowing someone before dating them or going "blind"? no pref. (233) Have you ever wished it was more "socially acceptable" for a girl to ask a guy out? what?! i dont see what the big deal is about girls asking guys...who cares (235) Have you ever been romantically attracted to someone physically unattractive? yes (236) Do you think the opposite sex finds you good looking? some (237) What is best about the opposite sex?: shy smiles (238) What is the worst thing about the opposite sex? confusing (258) What's the last present someone gave you? piece of gum. and yes i consider that a present. (257) Are you in love? i think so. (258) Do you consider your significant other hot? i dont like the Q..but yes (264) What would you do if you were walking down the street and saw some hot guy/girl standing on the sidewalk? smile..? *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  THE BATTLE OF THE SEXES  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (267) Have you ever wished you could experience being the other gender? at times. (268) If you did experience that for one day, what would you do? observe (269) What do you love most about the other gender? I donâ€™t know (270) What do you dislike most? I donâ€™t know (271) What do you understand least? Everything (272) Honestly, what do you notice first in the opposite sex? their presence *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  POSSESSIONS  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (273) What is your fave possession? ring (274) What physical, tangible possession do you want most? a person (275) How badly do you want it? very (276) Have you ever seen The Exorcist? Yes (277) How long did it take for you to understand why the last question is in this section? 1 second. *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (279) That haunted you? none (280) You wanted to kill? none (281) That you laughed at? katie (282) That laughed at you? katie (283) That turned you on? baker square guy (284) You went shopping with? katie (285) That broke your heart? shane  (286) To disappoint you? family (287) To ask you out? tyler (288) To make you cry? family (289) To brighten up your day? tyler (290) That you thought about? tyler (291) You saw a movie with? katie...spy kids all the way (292) You talked to on the phone? emily  (293) You talked to through IM? meghan (294) You saw? katie (295) You lost? shane (296) You went head over heels for? shane 97) You thought was completely insane? society (298) You wanted to be? myself. (299) You told off? ? idk (300) You trusted? a contradictory responce...but my friends (301) You turned down? ? i dont know  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (302) Smiled? now (303) Laughed? now (304) Cried? thanksgiving (305) Bought something? Today. (306) Danced? in the car (307) Were sarcastic? Today (308) Kissed someone? ....friday? (309) Talked to an ex? hah. (310) Watched your fave movie? last week (311) Had a nightmare? dont remember 312) Talked on the phone? today  (313) Listened to the radio? today (314) Watched TV? today (315) Went out? tonight  (316) Helped someone? no idea. (317) Were mean? i think others could answer this best (318) Sang? now, to bright eyes. (319) Saw a movie? tonight. spy kids.  (320) Said "I love you"? today (319) Missed someone? today (322) Fought with a family member? all. the. time. (323) Fought with a friend? day before thanksgiving. (324) Had a serious conversation? today (325) Smoked weed? ... (326) Got drunk?... (327) Had sex? never  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  A LAST TIME for everything...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (328) Last book you read: the great gatsby (329)Last movie you saw: Already answered. (330) Last song you heard: more than a feeling. (331) Last thing you had to drink: water (332) Last time you showered: this morning (333) Last thing you ate: seasoned french fries (334) Last CD you bought: i dont buy. i steal. (335) Last thing you bought: movie ticket.  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  RIGHT THIS MOMENT...  *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*  (336) Had Sex? no  (337) Are you going to? eventually  (338) Will it be with your significant other? ...idk yet (339) Or some random person? no (340) What are you wearing right now? grey pants and a hoodie (341) Body-part you're touching right now: nothing..im typing (342) What are you worried about right now? life  (344) What's on your mouse pad? scribbles.  45) Use 5 words to describe how you're feeling: closest case of regret. period. (346) Are you bored? yes  (347) Are you tired? very  (348) How long did this survey take u? almost an hour   not that you all care. but i like these. im out for now. got work in the morning- ash
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i think that this thanksgiving had to be about the worst. i love the holidays, i love the snow i love everything about them. i love not having school and i love being able to sleep in. but...  yesterday sucked. its like of...like....feeling like an outcast in your own family. i didnt think it could actually happen but opp yup it did. and everyone seems to think im still 14. but....im 16. so i guess that doesnt really work now does it..  andi have this towering guilt thats over me and i cant do anything about it. i suppose i can....but i dont wanna. and i dont know why that is. muscles is sceeerrd. *oh, dwayne*  but alot of things made my day yesterday..i got to explain what 'painting' was. and no it doesnt involve a brush.. it brought me back to those old times. i miss 'em. but among everything else....the day sucked. 8 of my past 24 hours were spent in a car..with...the family.  i just realized how much i cant wait to get outta here. with love and LIMO ZEEN   |tee hee hee| -ash
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      lo siento. it should read gusgus3470 (below)this is the correct BATTLE CRY:        What Is Your Battle Cry?        S talking on the fields, wielding a burning branch, cometh  Gusgus3470 ! And she gives a vengeful roar:    "This one's for you, mom! Man, that's some good coffee!!"         Find out!  Enter username:   Are you  a girl, or  a guy ?         created by  urlLink  beatings    :  powered by  urlLink  monkeys       
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
            What Is Your Battle Cry?        S talking across the cliffs, carrying a meaty axe, cometh  Gusgus3471 ! And she gives a vengeful bellow:    "I'm going to reduce you to ash, and sell you as spice!!!"         Find out!  Enter username:   Are you  a girl, or  a guy ?         created by  urlLink  beatings    :  powered by  urlLink  monkeys       
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess i havent blogged in a while.. meaning....i have a life? oh ho ho hellll no. r u kidding me?  so this past week went by rreealllyy fast. props to that. and props to mother nature with all this snow.. but that means more accidents...with my driving skills, u know. but the fast week also means that this weekend would go by even faster considering it was a much needed break. and suprisingly it wasnt all that bad. seems like things are startinto look up..i hope?  friday was undoubtebly the most fun.. can i say..80'S LADIES? OH YES. the I Love the 80's MARATHON BABY. i do love them..classic.  then on saturday i got to work...not a whole lot to talk about there..except for the fact that i will now be keeping my mouth shut from now on unless otherwise spoken to about the joyous time in which i am working. but until then....my lips are sealed. [mary kate and ashley what?]  and About Last Night... {cough cough} good stuff. i liked it. and i liked the PPP from pizza hut too. it was a fun night except for the fact that i found out why my dad didnt want me to sleepover... we will chat later about that.  thats about it now. only 2 days of school this week. then 5 days in which i DO NOT HAVE TO WORK. yippie. its sad how things like that make my day.  oh dad, put that away. im too cool for school.  ashmmm 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      today, had its ups and downs i guess. MOA was super trooper fun. i mean...the whole zumeiz thing and such. 'thanks...id love a blue lemonade...' =A Thrilling Time Will Take Place Tonight= yup. speaks for itself.  but anyway, baker square was fun. gotta love late night bathroom runs. but today , work went by terribly slow. i mean....like whoah. but its all good cuz Joey agreed with me that the whipped cream is by far the best. aka zumiez fella. god i love the mall...   im out for now thanks for being a shoulder, ash
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      :'( omg sad. my AJ PIERZYNSKI is gone. all gone. and its like he died or something u know...like hes just..disappeared. on his way to play for the SF Giants, which im sure he will be the star player of there. oh well i guess he wants to play for a team that quote unqoute 'is ready to compete' poor twins. they better make it to the series this year. hmmph. -althought i have to say that really wasnt a good way to end the week. monday went by pretty fast..and seemed to get prgressivly slower as the days grew on. i woke up this morning tho and thought it was only tuesday. so i suppose thats good that it was friday. right... classes were good tho. did good on some tests so theres a plus right there. ive gotten so used to getting d's on everything it was actually quite a suprise. but its like, for every one thing that makes my day, another 3 get me down. i think i do too much thinking. yea maybe thats it. but what i need is reassurance. then again reassurance is just fancy talk for a giant lie not to hurt ur feelings. and i have to say that they whole concept doesnt make me very happy. at all.  yay only 3 months and 11 days until my  12 th birthday. cant wait....17 will still just make me feel even younger.  im outie, [actually innie but u catch my drift] -ash-holy-o
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was wednesday which means work...which usually just means a pain in the arse but suprisingly with a few visitors and a lil spanish talk, it can do just fine. wasnt so bad today cept for the little comments. and by little i mean huge and by comments i mean shot downs on my self esteem..but its all gravy in the navy. i guess u just have to tune out things like that sometimes.  so besides thats it was pretty good day. besides the math test that i failed, my car almost staling on the way home from bruegers and the early mornin meeting for afda..it was pretty good. once again.  im signing off now, with a song stuck in my head and syptoms of heartbreak, ashley   im really sorry if i come off that way. i dont mean to be..... : (
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont know. maybe i should just stop this whole blogging thing...as its becoming somewhat of a journal... sometimes its just good to write what you feel i guess...let it all vent u know?  so today was tuesday missed my real world but had a great time otherwise, talking about binge eating and all that jazz. BUT not bulimia u know cuz god knows u cant tear me away from my precious food that is. im getting my grad pic done with a bag of doritos {g cc gg cc g c g c bobblebuddy} seems like food is my savior these days. [these days? cmon ash who ya kiddin]  so in recent events....the emotions are commin off a little strong. lets take a look: work sucks, and i hate my job. i smell like bread, from my job.  i have to take out the trash at my job. [10 30 at night? cmon, not like anyone would rape me anyway]i hate my life right now, i hate how nothing seems to be in place, i hate how im seeminly just a blip on the radar, i hate how everyones coupled up [although, more power to ya cuz its cute at the same time] i hate how individuality is a death sentence, i hate how i feel like im 5, i hate how everythings just slipping from my grip and i cant get ahold of it. i hate that feeling. wheres the love? {oh JT} but on a more serious note... i guess im just not gonna ever understand what makes the world go around. so in that case im gonna have to make a retraction from my previous blog post stating 'friends make the world go around' cuz lets face it, they dont. and very few are actually there when u need them most. mentally, i mean. its sad..it really is.  with love and missunderstanding, ash   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      friends make the world go around.  well..with the exception of a few unlucky souls who manage to ruin the already horrible days in which is my only exsitance. other than that you guys are awesome.  {just a side note from reading peglegs blog} [so i thought id add in my own 2 cents]  signing off with area code '952' -ashley 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow ive blogged alot lately. more that usual {i must say}  so today is my day free from the hell we all label as school. and im blogging at 10:56 AM on my friday. [its not like i have anything better to do..] but just as well.  so i was thinking about how much music helps me. i have a very broad music taste and like just about everything. except for country. and bluegrass. but other than that i cant listen to everything. its just awesome to put on a song that u know u can relate to--every word thats there was written for you. and i guess thats why i like music so much. because when u listen to it, no ones judging you, no ones telling u to shut the hell up, and no ones saying that what you are doing isnt cool enough for everyone else.  signing a note with six letters,  ashley
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      this week felt like one of the long dry spells of the summer. and i hate it.  like, when no matter what you try to do, nothing gets better and everything just keeps getting worse.  but then theres something that just happens to turn everything around, and its all soooooooo much better. only now its me sitting there with nothing to think about except how flippin much this sucks and how nothing ever   happens  . even though, yes, u could argue that there is someone who does take affection to me, and i will openly admit that. but just please, if you know that people think you are cool/hot/nice/popular/awesome/tyte what   ever   you wanna call it, take it as a compliment and move on. i just...idk. im sure all you (yes and by 'all' i mean all 2 of you that read this) dont really feel like reading this and although im sure it will come off as a pitty page thats not what its supposed to be.   i just hate it when i still feel like im in fucking 2nd grade.   -lonesome town has got its good, and sure has got its bad-
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i think that u guys should do something that you dont wanna do.  now, dont get me wrong. im not talkin about dropping ur pants or anything, or pulling over onto the side of a road to an unmarked car, nor am i talking about whipping out your guitar and strumming kumbaya. and im not talking about swaying in the breeze, or frollicing through the tall grasses of the 1960's, because hell lets face, thats on my list of things to do next week.  but what i am talking about, fellas, is that you needa step up. [step step step up...avril lavignes lyrics are dancing in my head]{which isnt a good thing as only true fans would prolly recognize that song}*which isnt me so maybe i should just go and delete that while its still fresh*-nah-  but back to me ruling you.. =youre not the boss of me dad=+oh hell yes i am+ if u know that someone likes you, and the feelings are mutual, then go for it. make that move. jump off the high dive. frollic in the grassy knoll [only not, cuz thats what im gonna do]. pet that tiger that just ate the little kid. {its a little uncomforting that ive related love and relationships to a vicious tigre and innocent children..funny how it works...} nike says it best. just do it. drop trow and squat. [maybe that wasnt the point of this blog...] oh hell thats a different story for a different time.  but for now, kiddies, keep on keep on truckin. and dont puff the magic dragon. it screwssssssssssss you up man. "Mr smith! even preTENDING to be a pothead is a mortal sin!"  muh bad. stay sweet, shuga. x0x ashhhhhh
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so ive got some friends at punch pizza? so thats awesome. last night was probably the most fun that i have ever had..i didnt think that anything could beat the nights at perkins but last night did. it was like one great thing after another. talkin to nate   finally   wasnt something that i expected to do last night..but thanks to the phone call at katies it was a very unexpected suprise and it was nice to hear from him i must say. too bad hes in california.  and yes, thanks to katie for making me pick up the phone and talk to him so i wouldnt have any regrets : )  so this next week will be our final test. and i have no worries on it and im super excited.  nice talkin, blogger- gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      twas been an okay christmas this year. despite the whole anti-social-feel like a loser-in my own family sorta stuff.  i got all i wanted which is good but clearly not the whole point of christmas. but lets face it thats what i look forward too. ive come to hate the snow, actually. see, im usually really big on skiing and snowboarding...which, dont get me wrong, i love doing. but im miserable this year. unless it involves a snowball fight--which im all up for doing. : ) but...tomorrows another day. which im excited for. i think im going to hit up best buy again. ive got some cd's in mind now that ive got the dough...maybe APC? : 0 ? ! you will never know. and ive also got to get something else done tomorrow, too... which we wont speak of at this time. maybe over lunch? im excited for the rest of break. but ive got a shia load of h-dubb to do. fo shizzle. im out for now happy holidays to all...  Bah Humbug-- ash   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well well well. might i say that tonight has been a night within itself. you know, with the constant running around looking for a place to see santa :( alls well that ends well though i have to say. i think were gonna hit up mr claus with our own camera. sounds like a plan. so from there it was off to make plans for the movie that never happened. whoopsie poo. im really sorry about that one. it wasnt my fault ;-) after the radio fiasco we ran over to ridgedale...again...for some gloria jeans. you know those cards i found are startin to come back and bite me in the ass. it was a good find, though. ran into jimi at spencer gifts. and that about made my night..i didnt think that the night could possibly end on a great note considering the circumstances but it did. ahhh i find myself acting like a giddy little school girl when i think about it. yessm. so that was my night. gotta rest up for the big day tomorrow. im finally doing my room. it will be done by xmas day yippie. im not exactly excited for xmas itself tho..its different this year. it seems so...vague..i dont know if thats how i should put it but oh well.  night-- ash
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      img src="http://images.quizilla.com/V/vinacross/1041991326_fPerfectGF.gif" border="0" alt="You're Perfect ^^"> -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     AIM: plupermoo
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well today is saturday. its been good i must say.. oh, a recap, u ask? well for sure.. got up early this morning....a whole lot early. im talkin about 7:45.. and thats about what time i get up for school so im not likin it too much considering its the weekend before the fun starts. winter break here we come.. so i got up for work. it was pitifully long and boring. and there were hardly any hungry consumers that would eventually add to my paycheck, but it was alright. and mike got fired. idk.  he wasnt really anything special you kno? but jon is. man do i love to talk baseball with him. [even tho he insists that hunter is great at offence....cough cough] but i can handle that. and it looks like everyones gonna be quitin now..thank god ive taken off my share of days so i wont be coverin anyones shift. so theni got home...took a little showa you know, weekly is always good. i keed i keed. get ready and do some xmas shopping. i dont i know. holidays arent what they seem this year. and i know its the thought that counts but i dont like busting my ass to make sure i atleast get   something   for everyone, but..i dont know. im not gonna say anything. so i had my little ventures at ridgedale, met up with billy. i still see him as a little kid..but he was hella fun. those good times. and good deals at sam goody made my day.  went into Lids too. looked at some hats. tried some on.. billy was really into going into victoias secret. lets not get into that though.  ran over to best buy and talked to Tim. went to park last year. he was helpful : ) ive set a date with katie to come back and see him [cough cough] good man. likes good music too, so thats a plus.  ran home..checked in....tried to get some take out...BUT hellll no. the one night that i really really want some real good chinese food and it turns out that there was a fire tonight...and just our luck, will not be serving. great. decided to stop at arbys for some ficken chingers...i think they thought something was up.. ended up making some friends with the managers and got some coupons : ) and i rang the bell for good service. and they all applauded. i felt accepted.  BUT NOW im listening to the awesome punk goes acoustic cd. theres something so appealing about an acoutic guitar that puts me in my happy place. and i love it.  with love and ficken chingers little big baba tree
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow almost a week from my last blog...i think that was some kind of record.. anycow- today was most eventful, you see. had a little study time at panera and made the mistake of...eating in general...seeing as though panera food usually makes me sick...but i do it anyway. serves me right, as i galloped to the bathroom practically keeling over with disgust as the vomit is seeping through my lips.. and i 'spit up' my wild rice soup like a wimpering little baybay..sick  tthheeenn it was off at this hell hole i like to call a 'house' with the family. ran up to my room and wrapped the pitiful pieces of crap i call presents for my friends. i apologize in advance. got some pretty good stuff tho....manda's gonna like hers..  : ) and sweet sweet victory tomorrow is friday. i used to really like fridays when i was younger [last year] strictly for ABC channel TGIF marathons...god i used to love those. i recall Sabrina used to be on..[what?]   : }  see that? you know, the ' : } '? yea. thats what i call some good math skills on the 'ol laptop. aka graphing calculator. long story. lo siento. im looking forward for tomorrow...shouldnt be too bad. have a great friday. im crossing my fingers for it, baby.  this is me, signing off... Little Big BaBa Tree   *sniff sniff sprinkle sprinkle flip oh bo oh bo oh bo thrust whip in snap pull back guns OH OH OH slap forehead slap in*  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate who i am right now. its not alright to be like this but sometimes i dont know what else to do. tonight was...yeeaahh i hate the way things get to me that i have no control over. i hate the way i get mad when something happy, happens. i dont like how somehow...in   some   way, something brings me down. im so jealous of the people that have things going for them in their personal life. im so jealous because i dont understand. and i hate that tonight felt like everday of last summer... like no matter what i did or where i went..there was nothing.  and i hate how no matter how much i try, like no matter how much i want something its never attained. and i hate how its really sad that i have to write this in a blog. and i hate that i cant ever SAY anything about this to anyone because all they say is some remark about tyler or shane or something.. and i hate how i find myself SCREAMING inside and no one can ever hear me. i dont like no matter how much i try or think about something it never happens... i dont like how i get my hopes up about stuff and then shit hits the fan and manages to only hit me...  i didnt like tonight. except for the music. i do love how i can become so free when i listen to stuff and forget about everything...its about the only thing thats keepin me goin right now.  i'll leave you with some lyrics (props to you-you know who you are)  The only thing surrounding you now, Are the circular memories that infect your conscience, They are the make up of  your worries, regret, and doubts.   Collective portrayal of your person, Radiates confidence, shine with silence, And shadow the ones below.   This drought is leaving me, With cracked soil and brown leaves, Floating on a dry lake bed, With a dry mouth and a foggy head, Waiting for the snow…   But, when the water comes, I will overflow, I will overflow . When the water comes, I will overflow.   There’s one more thing I forgot to tell you: Worries and doubts will only help you, In the long run, you’ll shadow the ones below.    This drought is leaving me, With cracked soil and brown leaves, Floating on a dry lake bed, With a dry mouth and a foggy head, Waiting for the snow…   But, when the water comes, I will overflow, I will overflow . When the water comes, I will overflow…   Whoa Is Me -gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont know why i did that LOTR thing. maybe its cuz ive got a daddy date tuesday night? urrg yessm.  lo siento- gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Congratulations! You're Elrond!    urlLink   Which Lord of the Rings character and personality problem are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      its already saturday afternoon. and i havent even gotten my board for history day... and i have to work tomorrow... :-/  last night was eventfull, at that. started off with a little trip down to ridgedale and what not. always a good time. didnt see too much. although it was jam packed with hotties. dropped pluper off then went home....to a house full of candles (oh nick) *cough cough gag* that was cute to walk into, i must say.  so after...that...chilled with the boys. i guess it was just a re-run of new years? yessm. u know what im talking about pluper...haha  and today..in about an hour and 13 minutes im off to charlie and the chocolate factory. should be a blast. then off to PUNCH! pizza for the grand opening :) what can i say tis good to have a 19 year old brother in the pizza industry. especially when ur a moo moo like me. : )  i keed i keed.  and i dont know..i guess it is   really   starting to bother me when i read through my usual blogs everyday (and yes..i do do that) and come across how *happy* people are that our class is, you know, coming together....not haveing so many clique's....accepting other people...expanding the barriers of friendship...talking to people they 'normally wouldnt talk to'..and its starting to make me sick... >0 notice how the only people who actually think that everything is different are the popular snots that comsume themselves with abercrombie and the scent of j.lo? you know, the ones who actually believe everything has taken a turn for the better when all they really think about it how good they will feel if they talk to the less fortunate, cuz lord knows we all strive to be JUST like them. you know, the ones who actually believe its snowing, when all it is is cotton blowing in the air.... yea about that...  maybe you should pop that over-sized egotistical head of yours and come back to reality.  with love and, like, ugh gag me with a spoon, like, where are my prada shoes?! -ash
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i am missing out on yellowcard     hmmrgph..  are you apple juice? *no why* cuz you are   very fine    i thought of that one all by myself : ) i'll write more lata- ash
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      and so ends another day. another day, another dollar.  holler.  so what did 50 cent say when santa gave him a sweater for xmas? gee, you knit?  please dont have me explain that one to you....because it decreases the funny factor of it..thanks.  im excited for friday. no real reason, i guess. just glad to get this god awful week done with. which brings me to the point that i love music. i guess this came from my way home from school...flippin thru some old cd's. ive got some good ones tucked away let me tell you.  but for the time being ive got yellowcard amped (sp?) up. lets just say that there will be no more 'getting jiggy with it' :-/ right. thats all ive got for now..the yellowcard/acceptance/MCS concert is tomorrow. an i cant go. woe is me.  ive gotta get back to typin-theres something so refreshing about  the sound of a clicking keyboard.. maybe its just me.  with love and all those creative band names these days....brand nizzle? quality. -ash 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so its already tuesday huh?  yay. monday was actually quite good. its nice to have a good monday after a wonderful weekend, you know? 'twas all good until the ride home. i dont think im going to be doing that anymore. but whatever works.  tonight, although i despise the rich girls...it was become my guilty pleasure. watching it, i mean. i dont know...maybe its the fact that they think us midwesterner's wear cargo pants because we work in the fields all day and need those extra pockets...right... anyway-- it was a normal tuesday.   actually it was fine until 7th hour.  what ever thats supposed to mean. and that old man doesnt stop writing me emails about baseball..im not too fond of it i must say. but thursday i have something to look forward too...a nice little road trip : ) and then there is friday. im excited already. even tho i am lacking plans doesnt the word just fire you up? me too.  im out for now  ash   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so this weekend is flyin by...i cant believe its almost sunday. great.  so lets start with friday, shall we? just to recap... i guess i wasnt expecting u know 30 kids there to babysit and all... but let me tell you it was a blast.  a whole buffet of sweets and treats sure did get those kids on that sugar high we were all hoping for.. but the food fight was top notch. kudos to us on that one. ive come to the conclusion that when and if i actually do have kids it had better be a boy. cuz last night i realized how much i didnt like girls. ugh. its pissing me off to think about it. its okay though..we took the rowdy ones and slapped 'em aroud a bit. you know, show 'em whos boss. so we get almost 200.00 in tips..plus the money we get from the company..which = awesome in my book.  so then we meet david, u know, average 15 year old from edina..and yes you could tell too.  he was cool. fun times. so at about mid night me and katie found ourselves with 4 hotel rooms...and nothing to do. so we called up some people. hung out. u know, the usual. ; ) i dont think that im gonna ever be able to forget that night, either. yippie. So we chatted it up with erik and jimmy....cough cough and thats all im gonna say.... : )  and lets see..that brings us up to saturday morning in which i woke up in a daze from the night before and survivng off of 5 hours of sleep....and went shopping for xmas gifts.. in which i didnt really get a whole lot of shopping done for other people... but the VAN guy...woah. lemme tell ya.. very. very. awesome. chatted it up with him the whole time and that was that. which brings me to about...9:00 this evening... in which i ran over to baker square with pluper to see travis. which was fun. good times.  and that brings me to my blog........ ahh what an exciting life i live.  im out for now- 1004  ash
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey you-  so anyway its been a pretty eventful week i must saw. lets not talk about most of it. how about....i made a little trip to the hospital and lets leave it at that.  so today was Thursday-and once agian i didnt have to work yesterday, which is a plus but i heard it was pretty exciting. i miss jeff. he always said i did a good job.. now besides the excruciating cramps today that were probably caused from alli's  chemical mints/period/3 ibuprofen it was a good day. i had some great laughs by the way too...miss applebottom... lunch...was...weird. im not sure how much more of this weird-not normal-eating habits i can take. ugh it makes me sick to think about it. and math? yup gotsa test tomorrow..which i dont think i should do too bad on..which also isnt normal. and now ive got some good history day stuff..so that should be fun... and tomorrows friday. which means im gonna be at a hotel with 17 kids.. and *david*' ahh i can not wait any longer..  and tomorrow is also the moment of truth..but only katie really knows what thats about so lets keep it on the hush hush shall we...  and i went to the mall today...got my haircut by some guy that didnt know what 2 inches meant and somehow ended up cutting off 4.. but alls well that ends well.  and i just read emilys blog. sheesh she must be in a really good mood. which is cool. and she looked cute today -- in a strickly non lesbian way-- everybody likes compliments, right? right.  so im out for now-- ash 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mmmhmmm im thinking that recent events have provoked some quality blogging.  or just plain compaining whatever toots that horn of yours. couple exciting things at work today-charlie and justin need i say more. that was weird. things like that dont just   happen   you see...its all a part of this weird conspiracy thats starting to ruin my life. you know, the really boring one that nothing ever happens in..yea thats the one. and then there was ted. good name. good man. we talked baseball while i was wrapping his frontega-no chips. it was weird and extremely friendly and it pretty much made my day. its not all the time when a complete stranger will just strike conversation, at least not something youre remotely interested in to begin with.  he thought AJ was a punk...that is, until i shared my stories with him that soon changed his mind :D left and came home...got ready for the 'big night.' yes, big night.  of, what..you inquire? stalking. now, as ive said before this is a skill that takes time, dedication, and practice. not saying that im a stalker, but it all makes sense that one would have to be very good to pull it off...so anyway this is a   class assignment   to let you know... we were supposed to pick out someone and watch them....observe them...become one with them. we were supposed to use our 5 senses and everything.  it worked out perty well considering our very hot victims...:D tee hee big bowl was swell. we alllllll know that that guy was waiting there for us. no doubt. that kinda made my night as well....  but, dont think that this blog has come to an ending yet...ive still got a whole lot more to talk about. everyone knows, that when ive got some extra time on my hands i like to think. think alot. which, is NOT a good idea. because ive come to the conclusion that life sucks. and yes, it will never be fair. or understood. and there really isnt anything that i hate more than not knowing how things work. i dont understand, why ive got like...what...4 people that i mainly hangout with. dont get me wrong ive got school friends..but not the ones that i ever see on a regular basis.i dont understand what it is about some people that make them think they are so UNBELIEVIBLY untouchable to the world, the ones that think that they are just so ready to take everything away from everyone else...and that i hate. i hate not knowing why things happen the way they do, i hate the way everything always ALWAYS stays the same, i hate talking to people expecting them to understand and realize that they either a)dont give a fuck or b)have no way to even remotely relate to me because their life has been so sheltered and perfect and they have no idea what to say. i dont want to sound mean but thats what i know i sound like right now. i just dont understand why i seem to get the shaft in the whole life department.  i dont expect anyone to understand it expect for those people who know exactly how i feel. and i feel helpless, like i cant do anything about where i am right now because everytime i try its always the same. i know i can make my own reality. i know that if i really what something to happen, i have to make it happen. no matter how bad i want something, it will never happen. and i know that. and i dont even know what im even typing anymore but sometimes when you type, dont your fingers just keep going so fast you cant seem to make them stop? yeh thats what it is right now. i guess the plus with all this AIM and blogging i can type an essay in no time flat. :D  see? ive still got a little bit of optimism left :D right.  skittles0387@msn.com  tell me your thoughts? thought so.  night  gus gus
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there are so many things that are eating me away right now. its all bad karma. and ive been catching the clock at 11:11 all the time now too. i always have, but its taken on a new meaning which the events that have thus entered my so called life, or lack thereof. damnit. once again. caught in the middle of a whirlpool. with drama and useless shit that   really  doesnt need to be there. not saying that i dont have my days, because i most certainly do..but when im dealing with certain people i know where my boundaries lay. and wish i knew they knew them too. anyway..im very excited for tomorrow. its one of my hobbies and now i get to put it to use :D im thinking....maybe get the whole experience with the whole taste thing, eh fellas? ah who am i kidding. [only myself] so thats tomorrow....after a day of work. maybe hittin up okfag for a sec but only that long. im thinking i will fill you eager little jack rabbits in when i get home tomorrow night. until then, fuck off.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa oh oh  Ooh hooh No No No   See i dont, know why, i liked you so much I gave you all, of my trust I told you, i loved you, now thats all down the drain Ya put me through pain, i wanna let u know that i feel   Fuck what i said it dont mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw em out Fuck all those kisses, it didnt mean jack Fuck you, you hoe, i dont want you back  Fuck what i said it dont mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw em out Fuck all those kisses it didnt mean jack Fuck you, you hoe, i dont want you back   You thought, you could Keep this shit from me, yeah Ya burnt bitch, i heard the story Ya played me, ya even gave him head Now ya askin for me back Ya just another hag, look elsewhere Cuz ya done with me  Fuck what i said it dont mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw em out Fuck all those kisses it didnt mean jack Fuck you, you hoe, i dont want you back  Fuck what i said it dont mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw em out Fuck all those kisses it didnt mean jack Fuck you, you hoe, i dont want you back  Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah  Ya questioned, did i care You could ask anyone, i even said  Ya were my great one Now its, over, but i do admit im sad It hurt real bad, i cant sweat that, cuz i loved a hoe  Fuck what i said it dont mean shit now Fuck the presents might as well throw em out Fuck all those kisses it didnt mean jack Fuck you, you hoe, i dont want you back  Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah Oh oh Oh oh Uh hun yeah 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well hello...nice of you to stop by.  hmmpghrf..where should i start? this semester is goin okay so far...have had some run-ins with the unexpected but hey whats not to love about that. nothing like waking up to seeing ms[mr] morgans face...pillow face....its starting to look like she just crawls out of bed and comes here to 'teach' math if thats what you wanna call it.  7:50 is a titch bit too early for that i'd say.. and my careers class.  i actually really enjoy it. some nice, quality times in there. with my computer buddy..but i wont name names. not that anyone reads this anyway but things have their way of getting around you dig? and then theres US history. last semester owned. nothing better than that class. but i suppose ive got gandrew [what?].  im just glad that i can be busy on my own with my hippie and haight ashbury thing goin on. im real excited about that one.  through my research..ive come to the conclusion that i am nothing but a neo-hippie.  i dont want to elaborate so i wont. ok? ok. i had fun writing my erotic story about fruit yesterday, thanks to ms. norris :D which leads to chem...which isnt so bad.  and if youre not put to sleep yet.... i really hate some people. the day that i understand guys i'll call myself a monkeys uncle. my sense of humor is totally shot tonight. it was pretty gouda today, though. had some nice rolls during lunch.  truckin... gusgus ',: |   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now usually thats about the only place i can count on....but lately? its been a little bit underpar.  and thats all i have to say 'bout that.. oh forest. : )  ash
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh gawd. [yes, g-a-w-d] what a night it was. and not it a very good way, mind you. lets see where do i begin... work was fine. did the whole line check deal-io twice and got on my way...but not before KEVIN scheduled everyone to git outta there at 1 and leave me all alone at the sandwich line to do everything myself....ahem. but, punched out about 15 minutes early and got some soup and a bagel yummay. drove home in my car that is practically white with all of the salt thats been splashed upon it but heard some new linkin park on 93 X so i guess that made it a little bit more enjoyable...as much as it could, i guess. got home...came online..dabbled in this, dabbled in that, got in the shower got ready for the most exciting portion of my night thus far: the st paul ice palace. good lord. never again. im not sure what made me dislike it so much...maybe its because of the excessive amount of very good looking guys with their girlfriends plastered to their arm as they huddle about in the streets...or maybe it was the whole below-freezing temperature and the numbness of my legs that eventually got to me...you know, lack of blood circulation cant always be good...or, i dont know..it could have quite possibly have been my strong disliking of Disney mooovies with the whole, ice-castle-y perspective that kinda hindered my moods. im perty sure it was the evening with the family though.  i stood in line for god knows how long for a   light show.   ok? a   light show  .  now, i guess ive never really seen a really GOOD light show to compare it to to begin with...but i think im being fair when i say it was mediocre.  not brilliant, or spectacular...hell, im thinking i could have made something look a whole lot more b-e-a-utiful on my light brite. and were talking when i was 7.   this is bringing back painful memories of this evening. i'll leave you with that to think about.  woulda been a ton more 'brilliant' if it consisted of me and a significant other. but lord knows thats not gonna happen. :D way to be optimistic, ash.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gotta love that song.  i think my slum is getting better. slum, you say? as in slums of beverly hills? [yessum] whoa whoa whoa dont let me get into that movie. it holds some perty indicent memories. tonight was filled with music and talking. and 'talking'. im not sure how to describe the most comfortable feeling that i know...the one where you may not even know the person..but something, somewhere made you talk to them.  where something just kind of, clicks. tis been a great night. did nothing, but it was just great. and i had to work today. and i put in my 2 week notice. and im going to be making ice cream sometime soon. and lord knows that a girl like me cant get enough of her ice cream :X te he.  yeaaah nothing else to say but thank you. thanks for keeping me up and night and letting me talk to you even if youre watching your Tv thats 2 inches away from the monitor. thanks for just being someone, you know? this is getting weird. i must go. the sheets are calling me.  la de de da la de da da dont worry baby im right here right here right baby at home  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love the piano. i love drums and i love guitars. i love music and they way you feel and what you experience when you listen to it.  i love how it can be something really simple but have such a profound affect. i love music.  ive been hittin up rollingstone.com and watching alot of their music videos.  came across a live AC/DC shook me all night long that was screaming my name. and lord knows how much i love AC/DC. god works in mysterious ways, i tell ya. most of which i will never...ever....ever..understand.   im starting to get that feeling again---where i feel trapped.  i want to experience things soo much. i want to get out of slp and see the world. i want to pack my bag and drive away. i want to meet new people. i want to make things happen--but i want to let that happen on their own.  it feels like im on the one-way slow track to nowhere.  ive got nothing to look forward too, nothing thats going to happen that will excite me. nothing ever happens. i crave change. i need change.  i need to let things run their course and i need to stop over analyzing everything.  i do it all the time. nothing can ever be said, and just left at that. i feed into it. i dig into everything. stories are running through my head every god damn second. stories of 'what would have' and 'what if' situations. i can never fully let myself escape--i cant ever just let it be.  i get myself wrapped up in everything and every little comment. i think too hard and get mad. and in the end im back where ive started. god this feels like summer again. those long days filled with sleeping,waking up, driving, and coming home. those were some of the best days i tell ya.  but on the other hand, it was just [nothing].  silence. blank. white. blur. sad. emotional. depressing. i hate how nothing ever   changes  . its just one thing after another, the same routine. and its getting stale.  phew. maybe if you could put that into a clearer picture everyone would understand.  but then it wouldnt be reality. cause no one ever does. life isnt fair, yeah i got that. but why does my life seem so different than anyother 17 year olds....?    Come on And finally the silence, looking out, looking back across the sky,  Trying to find a meaning , knowing that I just left it all behind Still I smell a lingering softness  Where did he go, how did he go, I wanna know  I wanna know that he'll be coming here to me Come on, without you I'll never feel the love inside of me Come On, you know that we belong come on, come on Thinking back before him, I never knew the meaning of alone Still the flag is feeling foreign, I live the day to escape into a phone Speaking of a world not real then  where did he go how did he go, I wanna know  I wanna know that he'll be coming here to me Come on...  he's coming, he's coming here to me ,  I'm needing ,  desiring to kiss him now ,  I'm living for him ,  breathing for him, singing for him fairytale.    pfft...as if ive never felt alone before him? c'mon. this is ash here...     -gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think that maybe tonight i should get a little bit more than 5 hours of sleep..damn text messages...because of finals and all. but it wont happen. looks like im going to be failing with flying colors :D : / yeeh.  so tonight was cold stone. woot woot. what an experience. at least josh liked my hair. along with some other things.  he plays tennis also. from eden prairie. so i think thats pretty cool. maybe we wil work together? nah...not after that whole episode of standing up infront of the whole damn group. but whatever works. i want to though. i think i would have a little bit more fun. speaking of work, looks like im gonna be closing tomorrow. i havent closed a wednesday in forever. i like it that way.  thats about all...i cant seem to stand myself up anymore. i have become dependent on you. i always do that. i need to stop.. because who would want their feelings hurt? not me. for the 2nd time. in the last year. k thanks.  not that anyone would know what im talking about..its nothing but my brain splattered out on this plain white screen. i cant wait for baseball.  rosie/gusgus/ashwipe/spice you name it, its me.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if there is one thing i hate, hate more than anything in the world, its got to be.. d.r.a.m.a... or those people that try sooo hard to try and make you feel sooo small.  its those things that i hate. skittles0387@msn.com see you there  young bloodz
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know, the very delight of conversation just makes me beam. i have to say that this past friday and saturday have been nothing but A+ and R rated. and i love it. i love mankato and i love the people. i love places and i love the school. did i mention i love the people? well now i have for a second time. booyah grandma :D its weird tho...i havent ever pictured it like that. with those people. but, it happened and it really wasnt that big of a deal. just, kind of..trippy i guess. and im glad that we made the treck down there for it. because i dont think that much could really beat it....unless i were to suddenly succumb myself to the DREADFUL #4 !!!!!!!   :0 yessm. (sniff sniff) PEE-YOU.  i love it that people think were funny. i really do. and with those words i leave you with just one simple joke. that just so happens to be one that my very own daddy-o taugh me...  so, whats the difference between beer nuts and deer nuts? -what?     beer nuts are 1.79 and deer nuts are always under a buck! :D tee hee -Gus Gus   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and were here. in mankato. at olaf and todds apt. can we say par tay? yessm.  i dont really have anything to say. so...im out. have a nice night, i guess>?  razzmatazzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz bitz and kibblez
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i didnt think they would find out...but yessm, they have. and their on to us. hot on our trail..i cant practically feel it now :-/  but on a lighter note, with no worries..had a little Bread Bash last night--twas not as bad as ive heard it would be.. ahem..and no, i dont cook up little stories about panera in my spare time. thx. jesse wasnt there. i was happy. the whip is the shit. with those cool containers. and the STP isnt that bad either, i have to say. twas actually quite good without the excessive amount of tomato ale mustard. being a child labor-enforced panini maker i remember these things. not by choice, really. :[  then along came a little suprise on the way home...which was totally unexpected.[obviously otherwise it wouldnt be a suprise] but that made my night. :D  aaannndd that leads us to today. which was good, despite the spanish, and the math test tomorrow....aced a comm quiz-a-dilla so thats cool. got in the car and sped over to the Unckies to do a little h-dUbb. always a blast. my head hurts now...i think ima get some ibpropen. right katie? propen? [click click click click click click] :D  with a tit for a tat that about does it. pleasent evenings, all around. my guilty pleasure is awaiting me...{RW san diego, mind you}  -serious? nah. more like delirious- gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well tonight seemed like a re-run of winter break. ]tee hee[ that was fun. especially since were so goooood at it. yes, thats good with 5 o's. for sure. and tomorrows saturday and ive got soo much to do. get up early and bring home the bacon -mmmm bbaacccoonn--- then catch up with the K-dawg and do some returning of the god-forsaken-diapers that some people call 'panties.' i keed i keed. they arent that bad. no worries. but i did get a good cd today, with my best buy store credit, of course. and i think that the guy in the sub's dept knows its us everytime we go in there. woot. but anyway back to my great cd. its one of those that you stick in and realize just how happy you were that you got it. : ) ive got so much planned for tomorrow its not even funny. and once thats over, i work on sunday, so a little h-dubb then start the week.   and then   its friday! and Mankato here we come!  i can. not. wait. -ms. leather gloves
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i didnt expect it. but it feels good because i guess i did spend a chunk my of my internet time working on it... but today i felt good. about myself, that is.  that pit feeling in my stomach is gone for now atleast..but im sure since i ate panera today its going to be coming back quite soon i must admit. what if shit had teeth? yea it would naw its way out. thanks for the image, emily. [omg you actually   pictured  that? ..freak..] thanks hunter for that one too. oh and by the way? fuck you. :D  i dont have much else to say bout that. and i think im gonna hit the showers then add some more color to the strands tonight. i dont know. time will tell. [william tell]  for sheez ash
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      phew looks like ive been bloggin alot lately...which im not sure is a good thing.  why must we all be consumed with the materialistic sides of the american society? beats me. today was a good day.  except the whole coming home part. its so depressing to walk into this house..until i can crawl into my little hole in the wall of a room and bathe in my misery. [not that i dont shower on a regular basis but that just seemed like a nice discription for my sorrow, you know?] i hate those situations when you really   really   want to leave but you know if you do youre going to get some eye rolls thrown your way, and theres nothing you can do abou tit. whoop muh bizzad...* it   ive got some homework yet to finish up...you know, for that partner presentation that i have to do in history but it some how ended up that neither me nor emily have partners for it...funny how that works. ohh mr. m....makes me giggle. aannndd history day is tomorrow. i can . not. wait. pfft. at least im getting it done with, i suppose. :0 its almost 9...which means i gotsta get ready to watch my little guilty pleasure.. which so happens to be the Real World... :-/  :D tee hee   ash  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your element is Water. You are a deep person and a good communicator. Incredibably loving and loyal when your trust is gained and you are fairly mature.Myterious to the utmost water is in everything. One can be an Ocean or a river but nobody truly knows you.    urlLink   What's your element     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You will marry Johnny depp. He has a mind of his own and chooses movies mecause he likes the idea, not to make money or become a hearthrob. He will always respect you and stand up for you. Congrats!!!    urlLink   Which male celebrity are you going to marry? (10 results that have pics!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate drama.  i hate high school.  get me out of here.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every breath that I exhale is a sigh -  every breath that I exhale is a sigh of exhaustion.  How sad - this is what your life has  been reduced to - a single room apartment containing no more than a mattress.  The strings have been removed from the blinds and all the outlets have been  painted over. The television screen is streaked with blood smeared from your  knuckles as you were trying to punch it out but you underestimated its  strength, or maybe you just weren't trying hard enough. Startled by a knock  at the door you rise for the first time in two days to answer, but you can  only greet the visitor with one short statement. Hello my first name is  distance and I really don't care if I never wake up again. Hello my name is  distance and I really don't care if I never wake up again. Hello I really  don't care if I never wake up again. I really don't care if I never wake up  again.   tru d@  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i once recieved some very good advice.  [if you want things to happen, you have to make them] and thats exactly what i did and it worked. and for once, im on that      high   again. that feeling like im on top of the world and i can do anything, and not give a shit. its a feeling...that i just love and never want it to stop. yet, i know that soon enough somethings going to happen and its going to disappear. so ive got to make this one last for my own sake.  this break went by soo fast.    too fast  . it was great fun though. i mean, besides the days spent at the nursing home : [ new years was really fun. [im sorry bob] : / and uhh man. ickemay isay othay . im in a state of euphoria and i love it. and punch was awesome tonight too. ahh. good times.  hope everyone else had a decent break...mine was top notch.    save me one more time   -shleyay
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i feel like i wanna cry. ive got a bunch of built up emotion that i dont know what to do with. trying to live everyday with a smile pasted across your face isnt all that easy, you know? but its not like i know where all this came from. its just...there...i guess.  no mas. ive got nothing else to say today. i smell like waffles. :-/ are you there?  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was just another one of those weekends i guess...the ones where it seems like so much happened but really, nothing. :-/ i was quite busy though, running around and such. my day started at a mere 830 in the AM..off to werk for a little get together aka meeting about how we wont get tips if we dont memorize the creations..yea about that.. ran home...curled up on the couch flipped on the fire place and relaxed to my newest blockbuster rental Willard. i really, really liked it. it was a little bit over the top with some of the stuff but i really like those creepy movies. and it was creepy. so i liked it. alot. :D ran upstairs to my room and washed my walls. gotta get painting tomorrow after work. i cant wait until i get my room done because, frankly my dear, i really am sick of looking at a log cabin boarder atop the yellow sponged walls. kthx. jumped into the shower, literally, as i was running late and needed to get it and get out quickly, hence the [jumped in the shower] so i really did jump. ran out with my mom and got some PUNCH. god i will never ever ever get sick of it. and the people that work there. they know me as a regular now..which im not sure is a good thing or not..but it works. hit up target and stocked up on the necessary things needed at the moment, convinced my mom of a few things. got back home...hadda teach my mom how to use the damned DVD player. yes, thats right..she cant even work her cell phone. oh mom. ran back to the mall for the usual hot topic trip and i have to say that i really like the guy. always greeting with a smile and i like that. and that one [dyke] |not that its a bad thing| was working agian at zumiez. you know..the one that was there when we dropped in on sno daze...lurking behind the racks. it made me a titch unomfortable..but yea.. went to byerlys and followed TIMMY around. hahhahahahah [leather gloves] he was cute. but something was little off...in his walk, i mean..i dont know. you would have to see it. good times though...best buy was next with the Lost Prophets cd. ive been craving it for a while and was pleased when i saw that yet another one of our friends named TIM was working..so that was cool. and i do have to mention that i rule at car racing games. :D booyah grandmother. the one guy in the car stereo dept was a but weird though. no harm done, no worries. thats about it. gotta work tomorrow. urrrk. i mean, yay. ive actually been looking forward to gettin at that cream with those handy little spades..its been a while. but im off for now..not that this was at all interesting for you to read anyway. and yes, it is sick that this has become a little diary. no more, i promise.  my mom is watching sex and the city. gross.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay im so going to h-e-double hockey sticks.. but what can i say. at least he didnt have those small stubby sausage fingers. ew. ^-^ tonight was a night within itself. southdale was a bit of a let down but we ran into Max so im pretty sure that was the highlite of the night over there..it was fun though. nothing like UT on a friday night. oh how we seem to attract the young ones..halloh halloh ;) hit up france ave, ventured back into panera [ick] the smell seriously makes me gag. ick. so we ran over to mickey d's.  damn happy meal toys. i seem to remember them always being worth my time :( not like those play place balls though. damn things crawling with bugs [but dad i dont see any bugs on them] [thats because they are really small] :-x ash got the shaft at the play place. and i hear emily did too. [te he] so then i guess we hadda hit up cold stone. see how Mrs. K [meghan] was doin. she has a tough time scooping that cream, lemme tell ya. had a little chuckle here and there. it was all in good fun, though. it really is hard to scoop..unless you have Mr. k's guns. :D decided to hit up the BK bathrooms. i really..really do not like public bathrooms. for obvious reasons.  and the whole, body to seat contact really isnt my sack of potatoes you could say..i managed to only sit on a small section of emilys pee..yeah, she denies it. but how else did it get there, eh? she sat down before me.. it was off to Bad Santa from there. funny, funny movie. billy bob isnt all that bad looking...if youre into that whole drunken santa thing. i dont knock it, but i would tap it.  i mean...what? :D thats it..i guess? more stuff went down. but lets keep this blog G rated. cant let the pussy outta the bag, so to speak. errr...cat i mean.  twas a fun night, small fry. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everytime i think that im finally over it...ready to move on..something happens with you, and i cant go anywhere. you put such a hold on my life with everything..random or not. i really do believe in soul mates. i believe that you only really have a true connection with very few people in this world and im doing my best to try and sort all of it out.  half the time i dont really notice whats really going on in front of me but then again im so sure of it, theres nothing to doubt. i really have a hard time with moving on too.  what is the point of moving on when you have felt only the best feelings experienced so far in your life when you are with him? whats the point of rushing to get over everything when you really dont want to? and i have such a problem with living in the past. constantly doubting things that i never saw at the time, wondering why things ended up the way they did and never understanding them, past or present.  ive got so many people telling me that it isnt real and nothing good will come of it.  ive got 20 people in one ear saying that it isnt worth the heartbreak and ive got you proving them wrong but they cant see it. and i want them too...but now im considering everything. i hate taking sides when its either something you want so bad, or reality.  and i dont even like using that as an example because i think that you are the reality.  ive put so much faith into you as a person over the past year with just talking..an it finally feels right. and i dont even know what else to say about it except that i cant help my feelings for you even if im not supposed to be having them. i just dont think that you would still be talking to me after more than a year if you only were in it for one thing. god i miss you. and everything about you. :-/ You might be just what I need  No I would not change a thing  Been dreaming of this so long  But we only exist in this song  The thing is, I'm not worth the sorrow  And if you come and meet me tomorrow  I will hold you down, fold you in  Deep, deep, deep in the fiction we live  I break in two over you  I break in two  And if a piece of you dies  Autumn, I will bring you back to life  Of course I see you  I do.   :( gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        footsie - you like to goof around and laugh with the people you care about.    urlLink   What Sign of Affection Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     i dislike feet. oh very much. but, ^it is true. eh.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dunno. i was thinking about what i need. and you know, im always the first one to say that i do not need a guy..and i dont, but that doesnt stop me from wanting one, no? i just need someone that meets these standards... 1)likes to play mini golf and actually wants to do it.. 2)can play a mean game of cards 3)knows what movies im talkin about when i start to rally off the quotes..[do you know what movie the title of this post is from?] 4)cant make me stop smiling...or giggling...which shouldnt be too hard. this is ash, here. 5)doesnt get mad when theres nothing else to do but sit and talk and stare. because lord knows that the eyes are the door to the soul.  and that perty much does it. not that...this is a personal add or anything. just thought id put it out there, since i never really thought about it that much before [cept that one time..in the car..with emily and going into pac sun..shh shh shh :X] never realy consumes my mind these days. so thur ya go.  thats it. nothing exciting today..seeing as it was hump day i thought somethin would be goin down. op! nothing. at all. chem was fun. [i cant help but start to fall for you]  great. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont get people. really, i dont. normally i can be quite understanding about certain situations of not being able to get something at the moment because you have other things on yer mind. BUT YOU STEAL MONEY so dont pull that crap about how you dont have any. jeez. >:O  on a lighter note..im quite pleased with the way this whole comment thing worked out. didnt think that i could pull it off with out any major problems but lookie like i did :D [just nevermind that comment link on the very top..doesnt work :-X] today was ok..math was math. i never really know whats going on in there to begin with so no complaints...cept conferences are coming up in the next week and im gittin scurrd. :[ yes dad, scurrd.  i figure that there really isnt a whole lot on grades right now with the new semester and everything. but try telling that to my parents.. :-/ ehh im starting to get nervous. chem we got new seats...i thought that maybe...just maybe i would be able to escape the wrath of zach but op! no no no no. sits right behind me now. not that im complaining..but hes into some real shady business ya hear? stuff that i aint lookin ferwerd to bein brought into. maybe i can just keep my headphones plugged into the screaming beats of three days grace that help me relax so nicely. :D and that i think i will. its hump day tomorrow. [wednesday, ahem] which means its the much closer to friday. big plans this weekend, big plans. im excited for them too. i havent seen 'em in forever so should be a good time. and then i werk all day sunday....woot for rakin in the tip money...yeh maybe more than 5 bucks this time, fellas. plzkthx. :D i love that face. what one? this one. :D thanks for listening, buttercup. leave me a comment>? :D :D :D :D te he  gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      god yet once again i find myself a frickn slave to the blogger. and i beckon once again: get me out of here.  why...WHY DONT YOU SEE that youre pissing me off. why do you insist on attacking me with your phone calls every dammmmmmmmned day and why why why do you continue to leave frickn voice mails on my home phone and yell at me, when i have a cell phone for you to call. why do you need to be so damn intrusive with everything thats going on with me, why do you have to keep asking what the problem is when you are the problem. why does everything happen all the fricken time and i cant get out of it. why do you have to do this all the time, and you dont even know it? why do i care so much about something that isnt even real? why do i have to get tied up in every little thing and why, when it doesnt go my way, do i kill myself over it again and again. and now im a rut and im helpless [yea took that from em] and why do i feel like this all the time. why cant you see that i dont want to be mad at you but i am? why does it feel like im the only one who will ever understand...and why cant you atleast try to? whats so different with me than with everyone else. and why is it so hard to respond to emails these days? why does it take so much just to listen once and while..and why does it seem to take so much effort to be able to wake up to the same old shit everyday. how come nothing changes and nothing gets better and every time something does happen you say something to take it all back. why do i kid myself of everything that i want when i know that i will never get it. why do i love complaining to this blog so much? i have no idea. but it feels ok to be able to write what ever the hell i want and complain about those 5 people and not have to confront them.  pppffffftttttttt.   Let me run with you tonight  I'll take you on a moonlight ride  There's someone I used to see  But she don't give a damn for me   But let me get to the point, let's roll another joint  And turn the radio loud, I'm too alone to be proud  You don't know how it feels  You don't know how it feels to be me   People come, people go  Some grow young, some grow cold  I woke up in between  A memory and a dream   So let's get to the point, let's roll another joint  Let's head on down the road  There's somewhere I gotta go  And you don't know how it feels  You don't know how it feels to be me   My old man was born to rock  He's still tryin' to beat the clock  Think of me what you will  I got a little space to fill   So let's get to the point, let's roll another joint  Let's head on down the road  There's somewhere I gotta go  And you don't know how it feels  No, you don't know how it feels to be me  help! ash 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dislike ms. norris.  very much, kind sir. her little vampire faces scurr me. but i do like her stories about sniffing bus exhaust. and here i was thinking im the only one who liked it.. :X  today went by fast...and by fast i mean that i dont really remember much of it.  the halls are just giant blurs of stupidity...you know i was really looking forward to junior year..getting out of this damn shell that has constrained me for so long and now its like i cant wait for it to be over.  it isnt really that bad but i think enough is enough...you dig? and everyone is talking about their BIG plans for college..and im just sitting here lost in the chaos of it all. i dont understand the big deal with traveling all around this god for saken planet in search of 'the school that will put you on the map-and give you a head start in your career!' who cares? i...really dont. im just thinking that as long as i can get as far away from here as my little engine will take me, then all is well with the world. i need to see new people and places and be a little independent.  everyone is sweating the ACTs and im just....eh? once again, could care less. i certainly dont think that those tests factor in anyway what kind of person you are and what kind of potential you hold. i dont know, i just want it to be over soon. too much school talk for one blog, i have to say.  tonight is my big fat obnoxious fiance :D yes yes yes ive been saving my monday night just for this and this only. i love that guy..anyone who will go on national television and do what he is doing is any friend of mine. what am i saying? gus gus dont have friends..:X well, unless you count joe. :-/  thats it. bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ive got nothing to do. and no one i wanna talk to is online. so i will sit here, eating my monkey bites [cold stone plug] and fill this out for you..yes, just for you. lucky dog.  01. Time you start: 12:28 AM 02. Full Name: ashes bolashes myeyelashes 03. Nicknames: asham ashm asherz shit for brains shit head loser fugly gus gus newman 04. Screen names: plupermoo   05. Pet(s): chewlsie 07. GPA: 3.2? 08. Sex: female 09. Birth-date: 2-3 10. Zodiac sign: aquarious  11. Location: MN  12. Hair color: Brown and red and blonde and blue 13. Eye color: green and brown 14. Siblings: nick 15. Best friend(s): ehh most of my friends are best friends. just leave it like that.  The CRUSH Side:  16. Crush: Johnny Depp 17. Girlfriend/Boyfriend: :[ single and ready to mingle, baybay 18. If you could go out with anyone, who would it be: Johnny Depp orrrr ed norton  The PAST Side:  19. Memory [thing] you miss most: never having a dull moment in life 20. If you could go back in time, where would you go:the roaring 20's 21. Memory you would like to forget: 2nd-6th grade. GOD i hated elementary school 22. What'd you do yesterday: went to target and best buy. never leave without makin some new friends, lemme tell ya. 23. Last person you talked to on the phone: mom 24. Last thing you said: thanks 25. Last song you listened to: umm everybody in the club gettin tipsy [everybody in the club gettin tipsy] uuhh mainstream radio. blimey.  The FAVORITE Side:  28. TV show: King of Queens and the real world..and the simple life :x 29. Song: the joker 30. Color: black or red 31. Day of the week: friday 32. Month: june 34. Number(s): 3 37. Ice cream: mint choc chip 38. Candy: goobers :D 39. Channel: Discovery, history and mtv 40. Shampoo/Conditioner: i guess herbal essences? idk. 41. Saturday Night Live quote: I love you, dirtbag. 42. Favorite sport and Sports Team: baseball- twins baybay 43. Actor/Actress: Johnny Depp, ed norton, tom cruise 44. Non-alcoholic Drink: 7 up 45. Band/Singer: led zeppelin, ac/dc radiohead yea anything goes with me. 47. Movie: "say hallo to ma lil friend" yes, scarface doofus. i really like Hook though. 48. *N Sync OR BSB: Barf on both. 49. Peanut butter OR Jelly: Peanut Butter 50. Boxers OR Briefs: Boxers 52. MTV OR VH1: mtv i suppose 53. Apples OR Oranges: Oranges 54. Vanilla OR Chocolate: niller 55. Flowers OR Candy: Candy yummay 56. Dawson's Creek OR Felicity: i....never watched either 57. Romantic, Comedy, Horror, OR other: i like documentaries 58. TV OR Radio: tv 59. Max and Liz OR Michael and Maria: Who ARE these people?? 60. Joey and Pacey OR Joey and Dawson: Don't give a rat's ass. 61. Do you believe in angels: Yes 62. Aliens: I believe there is life out there. 63. Heaven & Hell: sort of, but not entirely. 64. God: Yes, in a sense. 65. Yourself: always. 66. Love at first Sight: yessum 67. True Love: Yes 68. Soul Mates: ive started to doubt  The HAVE YOU EVER Side:  69. Been on a plane: Yes 70. Cried in public: Yes 71. Climbed a tree: Yes 72. Fell asleep in a Movie Theater: no. i pay, i watch.  73. Met a celebrity:the red head from the partidge family :-/ 74. Been scared to get a shot: oh no. 75. Shopped at Abercrombie & Fitch: in...5th grade...yea never again. theres a certain acceptable look you obviously need to obtain before you come to any sort of proximity to the enterance...so, thats the end of that. 76. Skipped skool: mmm no? i dont remember. yeai think once 77. Gone out of the country: yep for like....a couple hours.  The WHAT DO YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU HEAR :  78. Bill Clinton: just a horny guy 79. Dreams: Intuition. 80. Sex: oh geez 81. Whipped Cream: yum 82. South Park: MMKAY 83. Boy Bands: gag 84. Guys: backs 85. Girls: Friends 86. Death: human  The WHICH WOULD YOU RATHER BE :  87. Dog/Cat: Dog.  88. Chocolate/Vanilla: chocolate 89. Pen/Pencil: pen. i LOVE pens. but if i were a really nice mechanical pencil that would be even better.. 90. Boy/Girl: Girl. 92. Are you getting tired of this survey: no 93. Do you sleep with a stuffed animal: no 94. How many buddies do you have on your list: alot 95. Do you like this survey: yes i do 97. Last CD you bought: travis 98. Last movie you saw: along came polly 99. How long are you in the shower? maybe 15 minutes 100. How do you eat a Reese's Peanut Butter Cup: i eat around the edges first. and throw away the middle. too peanut buttery for my liking. 01. What does your screen name mean? inside joke, cow. 102. Right, Left, or Ambidextrous: Right 103. What is on your mouse pad: scribbles 104. What is under your bed: magazines. noo not girlie mags. sicko. >O 105. How many licks does it take to get to the center of a Tootsie roll pop: 1, 2, 3....crunch! Three! 106. ?? There's no question here.  The HAVE YOU EVER Side:  107. Been Kissed: Yes 108. Been In Love: Yes 109. Had Alcohol: yes 110. Done any kind of drug: yes 111. Failed a grade: No. 112. Skipped a grade: No 113. Sang and Danced while alone in your room: Yes to both 114. Missed someone: All the time  The WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU :  115. Cried: sometime in the early last week 116. Told someone not related to you that you love them: yea 117. You were on the phone: this morn 118. You laughed until you cried: last night 119. You stayed home all weekend voluntarily: couple weeks ago. 120. What time is it now: 12:49   Do you wear a seat belt when you are in a vehicle? Always, and so do my passengers.   2. Do you think that the right to bear arms is a universal human right?  are you cah racey? no i dont think it is. maybe just a machetti could do the job  3. Do you have a nickname for your penis/vagina?  were not friends  4. Have you ever been seen by a therapist?  once i guess  5. In your opinion, what is the best invention ever ?  microwave  6. What turns you on creatively ?, spiritually ?, emotionally ? Probably stories of others experienceing miraculous things, determination and passion.   7. Do you like your orange juice with or without pulp ?  Ugh - without.  8. Have you ever been questioned by a police detective? yeap  9. Do you support or oppose genetically modifying animals for use as pets? Haven't read about it much. Hate to give an uninformed opinion.   10.When you were a child, what did you want to be when you grew up, and are you doing it now? Wanted to be a mom and a teacher. so far im neither.  11. What was the last material thing you stole? Accidently? a button. On purpose? loose lips sink ships...shh shh shh. But I think "pilfered" is a nicer way of putting it. ;-)  12. What was the last material thing that was stolen from you ?  i....dont know.  13. When was the last time you told someone "I love you" in a romantic capacity? In a non romantic capacity? Romantic -- months ago Non-Romantic -- yesterday  14. Who is your favorite Looney Tunes Character? Droopy. :D  15. What is the opposite-sex version of your first name? ?...i would love to be Easton. but that has nothing to do with my name..  16. Would you use an airline that costs less but had less security? sure would  17. How many "one night stands" have you had? (a true "one night stand" meaning you have never spoken to or seen the person again) im thinking that inorder to do so, i should have previous experiences with the bases...meaning more than 2nd. in which case, i am not obliged to anwer this question.  18. Do you know what your parent(s) would've named you if you'd been born the opposite gender? alex  19. Have you ever eaten chorizo and do you really know what's in it? cant say that i have.  20. Does it bother you that the numeric keypads are opposite on calculators and telephones? not so much  21. If you could be a fly on the wall at any murder scene in history, which would you pick? kurt cobain. :O what am i saying??? he wasnt murdered...cough cough  22. What game show do you think is the best? super market sweep.  23. On a scale of 1-10, 10 being the best, how do you rate your job? 8  24. Who do you live with?  family=god get my out of here  25. Other than your name, what do most people call you? refer to name list above, plzkthx.  26. What pet-name do you call your boy/girlfriend or husband/wife ?  uhh. n/a.  27. Do you believe in magic? yeah  28. What's the longest period of time you were "grounded" as a child, and what caused it? must you bring up recent events? the weekend. for god knows what.  29. If you could be a pro sports star, what sport would you choose to play, and what position would you play (if applicable)? baseball-satchel paige  30. What would you say is/are the wisest thing(s) anyone ever taught you? live everyday like its your last.  31. What is your favorite swear word/phrase? fuck.  32. Which profession would you most love to have? biology teacher..that was paid decently  33. Which profession would you least want to have?  kindergarden teacher. damn glue sniffing 5 year olds.  34. Would knowing how long you have left to live be a gift or a curse ? curse. life is about expecting the UNexpected. not expecting the expected. duh.  35. If you were sentenced to death what would your last meal be ? Mac & cheese, cheesecake, skor bar, mashed potatos, a pancake, a banana for my lack of potassium and chicken strips. Yes, I would eat myself to death. haha....  36. Do you have a drinking problem ?  nope  37. What was your biggest disappointment ? experiences when i was being someone i hated  38. What accomplishment are you most proud of ?  making decisions that dont seem like they fit at the time but in the end its alright...being able to justify between dreaming and reality.  39. What one unique defining thing do you bring to the table? i never stop laughing. and..idk. you tell me.  40. Flashback to high school boys and girls. In your group of friends, fill in the following "class favorites" list.  Best Dressed : i dont really care about clothes Most Likely to Succeed : sarah Class Clown : i think that the people that are actually voted class clowns arent even funny to begin with... Most Warped : ... Most Flirtatious : iiiiii could care less Friendliest : sarah Daredevil : meee Biggest Spaz :um everyone at some point.. Most Talkative : i dont know Best Storyteller : i don tknow Life of the Party : i dont know Most Dependable : i dont care  whew. that took alot outta me. must have been fun fer you to read, eh... this is getting sick. goodnighty.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and so ends another night. oh what fun. this week has gone by so fast..its kinda hard to tell where the time goes these days. everythings really confusing right now, between friends i mean.  people change alot, whic is okay because i for one need that...but sometimes it just feels like they arent the same person anymore. like i have no way to relate to them unless i keep bringing up the same stuff over and over just like other time i see them, and its weird. i just figure that most of the people i talk to now i will never ever see again after high school..and its kinda sad. enough with the sappy stuff, honestly. careers was fun yesterday...which i didnt really have the chance to talk about. so we had a speaker come in from ITT tryin to talk to us about going there after highschool and he brought along a multimedia demonstration to show us what we could be doing..and i swear, oh mother of pearl it was the funniest thing i had ever seen. and see, theres me in the corner with no one i know in that class having the giggles to myself...anyway it was a mouse singing to a piece of cheeze you know that one song that goes "i believe in miracles..you sexay thing you sexay thing" ohhhh dairy it was high larious. i guess you hadda see it... :-/ but thats it. i guess. nothing else new.    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      buzz off.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tis been a long night. ive upgraded to 30 minutes online now..quite a jump i must say myself. its gross...how excited i get when i can actually go online and update this bugger. internet whore. [ohh maddox]  again..in careers. doing nothing. so you might as well stop reading this now. because nothing new has happened. and i really dont have anything to say...i just chose to fill my time to look like im doing something busy. which im not. so you can stop now.  but for you loyal readers out there.. in case you havent noticed, being locked up in your room can get you thinking. about alot of stuff...like life.  its just like everything around me is at a constant non stop speed and im still sitting here...at a stand still, a pause, if you will. like everything i try to reach out and grab ahold of something that i want it becomes untangible. is that a word? i dont know. something like that anyway. nothing ever happens, im a song played on loop. and even when something does actually happen, which isnt very often, i try to hold on to it for so long...and in the end i end up kidding myself. because i wasnt actually holding on to anything...just [air] and its like this all the time.  i have so many hopes for things that i dont realize will never happen. stupid valentines day too. [thought i might add that one in] nothing changes. and i hate it. because i need change. and its like the more i seem to want something, the more it takes for it to happen if it even does at all. and school? yeah, no. get me out of here as well. because its full of fake dreamers who want everything and in the end get everything. when they didnt do shit to begin with. i miss you. why did you have to leave?  thats all. interesting, no? gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally. its been a while since ive actually gotten my chance to blog...and lord knows that i cant go for long. lets just say that ive been keep in my cracker box room for the past two nights....watching tv. and i dont mean, you know, casually flipping through the channels..im talking hardcore.  hardcore like 12 hours straight of tv. damn discovery channel has me hooked...:-X and dont ask me why, either. because i dont even know.  all thats keeping me going is knowing that ive only got about a year left here then im hittin the dusty trail. just me on my own. and i cant wait for that...because i have no idea how much more of this i can take. you know, the whole jail cell in my room type of thing..   which brings me to updating this son of a gun in my careers class..because its kind of hard to update everything with a ten minute limit when im at home.. god get me out of here. sno daze was fun...besides the shitty music. at least they played pour some shook up ramen and some ac/dc. thats always cool. and i dont like catching eyes with people when they are dancing...ahem bryna...and...everyone :X i keed i keed. but i really dont like it.. thats it. bells gonna ring. i shall continue my correspondence when i have more than a 10 minute time limit at home. :[ tear.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was nothing but boredom.  i didnt think that it was possible to go through this meaningless existance phase we call life and have a day where [n o t h i n g] happens. im talking, absolutely nothing.  same old same old. did i mention that it was getting old? but theres always tomorrow...which is friday..and about the only thing im semi looking forward too. but theres just so much i that i dont understand about...everything. half the time i dont even know why the hell i write in this thing.  i dont know, i guess its a little bit relieveing being able to write about stuff and not get the 'i dont fucking give a shit' response out of it. like my little security blanket of sorts. :} giggle. but first hour has been fun...im starting to like my heater seat on the far side. [i love that cartoon]  and...careers. oh god. need i say more. i find myself taking deep breaths as to NOT pounce on him. :-X anyway. i dont really have anything to say. this whole day has been nothing but a clear waste of precious calendar space. bahhh   Love is just some lame excuse people give you so you put up with their bullshit. Love is a lie...  We all begin with good intent, love was raw and young. We believe that we can change ourselves, the past can be undone, but we carry on our backs the burden time always reveals in the lonely light of morning in the wound that would not heal, it's the bitter taste of losing everything I held so dear -Sarah Mclachlan   cheeseball bubbleshumperdink
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ^just though id add that in for all of you sappy little heartbreakers out there, cuddled up with your loved ones. and everyone knows how im never happy for anyone, so thurr ya go :D but really, lucky ducks.  sooo today was yet another eventful day. lots a laughs so thats aplus. tonight was really boring. so i dont have anything to say...ohh keep your pants [god knows its hard for me] and cool yer jets, cheif. i will be back to post tomoz. |tee hee flemily|  heres to all you couples out der: ,,!,_   ^ i made that up all by myself. betcha dun know what it is :D        ssssiiiikkkkk i stole it. so, i must give the proper props to       charles       for that one. (yea i had 6 fingers when i did it the first time) but its ok im sure yer not readin this anyways  te he secrets secrets..  later days- ash 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      theres just something so special about the day...the reds and the pinks and the [mmmmmmmm] chocolate. leave it to ash to bring up the food. |are you calling me fat?| [yeeeeno no no no :-X] good times. but does it really need its own day for the massive amounts of love confessing treats and goodies to be displayed? does the affection need to have its own day, im asking. love should just be expressed throughout the year...not on one little Hallmark holiday. damn you hallmark, damn you.  i had a good day....ohh those good times walking into school. funny guy, funny guy.   it was cool though, im not gonna knock it. [but i might have to hit it :0 :D] oh cheeze. besides those hardships i like to call math tests, it was perty good. had lunch [there i go with the food again :X] and college writing? ohhh man. i will never get sick of that class i know it.....: D ehh thats enough of that.  ...shud up..... ;-*  chem was...chem. my face gets so red.....so fast. i hate it.  and i dont know why it does..its not like im blushing/really flattered/in love but..its gross. anycow thats about it for the recap. im actually excited for snodaze... you mean a school associated social event? yeah, weird isnt it.  im a joker, im a smoker, im a midnight toker. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      guys baffle me. how long has it been since the mall of america...2 weeks? yeah. 2weeks and counting.  i will never understand guys and the way they go about things. isnt it a lot easier to just speak your mind in the start rather than mess with fragile feelings... i thought so, but i guess a lot of them dont see that aspect of it.  today was my very last day EVER of reaking like bread and sandwich line sauces. i even filled out a W.O.W. sheet for shandi :D i felt it was only necessary too, since after all i KNOW that everyone was really getting hit hard when i said i was leaving..:-/ right, right. but they all gave me big hugs so i guess thats counts, eh?  i dont get the grammys either...im not one to celebrate Mr. Cry Me A River, and frankly, my dear, i dont give a fuck. i really dont like him and his girly-man voice and the way his face contorts when he hits those womanly high notes...looks like *someone* needs to pop a squat and lay a deuce. am i the only one that noticed that? : X thats it for this edition..as if all two of you care... :D ta ta fer now-  ashm
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      twas a most excellent night. all doubts of extreme boredom were lost as we found more and more things to do with our black leather gloves. :D work was ok...not really busy but still a bust. woot its my last day der tomorrow. could i   be   anymore excited? could i   sound   anymore like chandler right now? :-/  so tonight...shead the dredful smell of panera out of my skin and got ready.  Drankin Pat Na came over to pick me up....went to southdale. might as well call it a reunion of the class of 2005...nevermind the fact that i havent graduated yet, thats not my point.  i think i saw about the whole school there. i got a happy belated birthday wish out of it :D woot. and saw some couples...but i'll keep that on the DL. yehp. then.......went over to noodles. no, kind sir: no bread/no water/no pop/no meat/no sides etc etc etc. he was funny though. then.......ran over to a certain coffee shop again. and, you know i have to say that i can not get enough of that place....thanks to micheal.  i will do anything to be able to hear someone play the guitar. i love it and i love just...being there. in the environment;in the atmosphere.  i got some songs dedicated to me by him, too. :D ahhh what a b-e-a-utiful night it was. te he he now i got the giggles so i best be goin....  im right here right here right here at home: ash
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know, its just one of those times when the   only   thing that you want to do is run through the isles of the grocery stores and run with your arm extended...dragging everything down and crashing it to the floor. but not even the worlds supply of glass goods can relieve me of this mass frustration i have that is continuously building up inside of me. and to top it off, ive got to work tomorrow. fuck it. fuck it all, and fuck those who call you their friend and yet they have so much deciete...and hate...and jealousy..that they wont let you live with out them.  they need to be there, around every corner, waiting and following.  i need to get through on my own, make things happen on my own. and i dont want you there all the time. i want to get things on my own, i dont want you to get them and then let me share. i want to be able to say that I got something...i dont want a hand me down. i want to be seperate from you, and i want to learn things through my experiences. you always take them away from me. youre always there to have the last word in everything, and everything always has to be yours. EVERYTHING. god. i hate it.  what a friday night. at least we met some best buy guys. whatev.  She can't stop pacing  She never felt so alive  Her thoughts are racing  Set on overdrive   It takes a village  This she knows is true  They're expecting her  And she's got work to do   He helplessly stands by  It's meaningless to try  As he rubs his red-rimmed eyes  He says I've never seen her get this bad   Even though she seems so high  He knows that she can't fly  And when she falls out of the sky  He'll be standing by   She was raised in a small midwestern town  By a charming and eccentric loving father  She was praised as the perfect teenage girl  And everyone thought highly of her   And she tried everyday  With endless drive  To make the grade  Then one day  She woke up to find  The perfect girl  Had lost her mind   Once barely taking a break  Now she sleeps the days away   She helplessly stands by  It's meaningless to try  All she wants to do is cry  No one ever knew she was so sad   Cause even though she gets so high  And thinks that she can fly  She will fall out of the sky  But in the face of misery  She found hopefulness  Feeling better  She had weathered  This depression   Much to her advantage  She resumed her frantic pace  Boundless power  Midnight hour  She enjoyed the race   blahhhhhhhh gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its been a most excellent 17th birfday i have to say. thanks for everything. but...bryna? i dont know what happened to my poster..: (  i went after 6th hour to get it, and it was gone. :-x *tear*i still have the one from you from 7th grade {tee hee} thanks tho i appreciate it :D thanks stalk ie for that most special birfday wish, too. ol buddy ol pal.  oh and [EM]ily..yes, yes he is planning on coming over...okfag not by my choice. askin when he should 'stop by'. uhh no plzkthx.  haha. that was fun to read in your blog. hope yer feelin better   im out for some bday cake yay:D ash
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meet me in outerspace  We could spend the night, watch the earth come up  I've grown tired of that place,  wont you come with me   We could start again   How do you do it, make me feel like I do   How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  Meet me in outerspace  I will  hold you close , If your  afraid of heights    I need you to see this place , It might be the only way  That I can show you how, it feels to be inside of you  How do you it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  How do you do it, make me feel like I do  Do oh oh oh oh oh  You are stellar    You are stellar    How do you it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  How do you do it, make me feel like I do   How do you do it, make me feel like I do, Yeah.   its by 17th bday tomorrow. yay?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its going to be bittersweet...getting back into the swing of things with baseball and leaving for florida in the weeeee hours of the morning...yet having to tear myself away from the computer, and talking to you. :'( tear. leave me some messages [plural] to come back to :D thank ya  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaha. i had a really good day today. yay for that...yeh.. as usual it started with the all uncomfortable skirt dress code for the meet today...and yes i suppose i didnt have to wear a skirt for it but i like to complain so booyah grandmother :D it was ok though. hmmprgh. and then me and my drankin patna did some hit and runs...[te hehhhe hehhe te hehe] *scandelous* it was fun. i like doin it. maybe tomorrow we will do that again. yay. annnnnd we won the meet, too. muy bien ashley on my 7.0 on ballet leg..that was cool. and scored 5 bucks from my mom on that one too. and i got a 100.00 check in the mail today. so double booyah, cept not to my grandmother this time, to you. ive got so much moolah now its not even funny. hey, i used to watch that show on ABC family *coughcoughwhatcough* moolah beach, yeh it was cool. dont deny it. err maybe i was the only one that watched it :( twas gouda, though. yup.  thats it. i have the mad giggles tonight. te he. damnit, seriously. make them stop. err no, cuz i like 'em. *AIM angel face*  gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate cramps. and weve got a meet tomorrow :-/ :D my legs hurt from this weekend. real bad. ouch. times infinity. mother nature, you bitch.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh, muh gawd. this weekend, was the  mostmotherfuckingfun  i have had in a realllllly lllooonnnggg time. thanks porkers :D i wasnt me, at all. everything that i did was totally out of my little bubble of comfort and i am  motherfuckinghappy  that i did everything this weekend. it was awesome. the environment, the people, the lights, oh god everything. it was perfect. i really didnt think i could have that much fun but i did. and im  so  happy for it. and then it was off to see tony. what a  motherfuckinghottie . seriously. yay. and i love the feeling of not being able to settle down because the blood is rushing through you with so much intensity and excitment that when you try to calm down you cant. im literally bouncing off the walls. :D *sigh* and today i did nothing. what a way to end a great weekend. thats all for now. FLORIDA in 4 days  woot woot   gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having four legs makes most things stable; chairs, tables, cars (four wheels, if not four legs), and most animals.  This number indicates stabily and firmness.  You enjoy hard work; and are practical, reliable, and down to earth. You prefer logic and reason to flights of fancy.  People look to you for organization and getting things done.  Like the cycle of the four seasons, you are predictable.  You can be stubborn, suspicious, overly practical, and prone to angry outbursts.  Please rate my quiz.     urlLink What does your name and arithmacy say about you? (some simple knowledge of adding is required on your part)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [what the hell, why not. when someone emails me one of these, i feel compelled to follow through..]  |Birth Name|-- Ashley Marie  |Age|-- 17  |Location|-- Minnesota  |Birthplace|-- Minnesota  |Hidden Talents|-- i can make my tongue touch my nose.. :- HAVE YOU EVER: |pictured ur crush naked?|-- yessum  |actually seen ur crush naked|-- no  |been in love|-- yep  |cried when someone died|-- well kinda. i havent really had someone reaaallyy close to me die, so i guess i just..whimper..  |drank alcohol|-- yeah  |fallen for ur best friend|-- no  |been rejected|-- um, obviously. this is ashley remember.  |rejected someone|--yeah  |been cheated on|-- hope not  |done something u regret|-- yes.  |been In Jail|-- no  |ran away from home|-- yes  |hit a boy|-- im a mean little wrestler, what can i say.  |broken a bone|-- no  |cheated on a test|-- yeah  |let a friend cry on your shoulder|-- yeah  |fell asleep in the shower/bath|-- yeah  |walked in on someone changing or showering|-- yeah :-\ sawee dad.. [hey it was when i was like 5]  |gone to church|-- twice  |never slept during a night|-- for sure for sure  |seen someone die|--- almost  |thought you were in love|-- yes.  |screamed at someone for no reason|-- when im pissed  |stayed up till 4 am on the phone|-- :( yes, i have.  WITH THE OPPOSITE SEX: |what do u notice first?|--style. eyes, i suppose.  |last person u slow danced|-- i dont slow dance.  |worst thing to say|-- goodbye  |do you have a crush|-- yeah  WHAT COMES TO MIND WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT:  |love at first sight|-- glasses  |life|-- short  |food|-- pizza  |favorite movie|-- clockwork orange..godfather...jaws :x  |favorite type of music|-- rock  |favorite fast food|-- subway [cookies]  |favorite ice cream|-- mint chocolate chip  |favorite television show(s)- the family guy, king of queens   |your ideal BF/GF|-- i guess someone that fits my personality but has enough differences to make life interesting. its only fun that way. someone who i can just sit and bitch with when i need to, and who isnt going to judge me on anything.  WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU: |took a shower|--couple hours ago  |cried|--wednesday  |watched a disney movie|-- i hate disney. [unless its fantasia..]  |received a hug|?- today  THE FUTURE: |where you want to live|-- by water  |how many kids you want|-- i hate babies. but if they could just jump to like, 5..then anywhere from 3-6  |what kind of job you want|-- criminologist  YES OR NO: Would you go for your bestfriend? no  Would you date your Bestfriend's ex GF/BF? no issue there  Ever been Kissed? yes  Ever dumped someone? yeah  Treasure the Past? very much so  Savor Today? yeah  Value Friendships? yes  Do you TRUST so much? yes  Do you live for yourself? when i need to  Value Education and taking it? if its something im interested in  Ever called anyone a Bitch/Whore? um yeah...  *Basics*  Name::: ashley marie Nickname:::gusgus  Age::: 17 Sex::: female Location::: MN Status::: single..i guess..  *Love and such*  Are you bi/lesbian/gay/straight?::: straight Are you in love?::: no Do you kiss on a first date?::: if its there then yeh Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend/both?::: nope Last sexual thing that happend to you?::: undisclosed  *Family and friends*  Favorite family member?::: nick Best friend?::: i have many Second family?::: i have many Who can you trust with your life?::: not many  *Do you...*  Do drugs?::: occasionally Drink?::: occasionally Smoke?::: no Cut yourself?::: no Attempt suicide?:::no Flirt?::: yessum Wear makeup?::: yes  Fool around with the same/opposite sex?::: opposite, and yeh i guess when i wanna..  *Have you ever*  Jumped out of a plane?:: no Drove a car?::: yes Ran/drove away from the cops?::: no Had sex?::: nope Got close to having sex?::: not really..  *This or that*  Cheese or pepperoni?::: cheese Pepsi or Coke?::: coke Pac Sun or Hot Topic?:::hot topic  Aeropostal or Weathervane?::: neither Male or female?::: male Blue or pink?::: black Movie or video game?::: depends TV or movie?::: movie  *Random*  Shoe size?::: 7 Carry a purse?::: i like backpacks at all times Boxers or breifs?::: boxers Do you have AIM/AOL?:::yes  What kind of music do you like?::: rock Do I sound hot/pretty?::: no Do you like tootsie rolls?::: yes What school do you go to?::: shhshh shh What day is it?::: friday What time is it?::: 1108 pm  *Silly shit* What color underwear are you wearing?::: pink and green Do you think cows are funny?::: i am one  Ever rode a horse?::: yes How about an elephant?::: no What about a guy ;-)?::: nope Do you like Outkast?::: yes Have any siblings?:::1 Any people really close to siblings?::: yes Think Im annoying?::: no  *Favorites*  Food?::: pizza Drink?::: water Band?::: many Color?::: black Website?::: idk. Screen name(your or someone elses)?::: plupermoo Person?::: me TV show?::: family guy/king of queens Movie?::: milo & otis Quote?::: say hello to my little friend  *Word assosiation*  Fuck::: you Lick:::me Stripe::: paper Pants::: but-ton Richard::: shut up Sammy::: ew Tim::: timmy! Helga:::german  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      no, no thank you. i do not like you. and yes, it is an 'inconvience' for you to be calling me and apologizing for how you....somehow...hurt? me. which you didnt, you just pissed me off. once again, need i explain to you that i did not like you like that. never did. never will. get over it   ppllleeaassee   >O nayways.. this song creeps the  shit  out of me. sounds like..an orca or something when it starts...so yeh im sitting here looking around all shifty-eyed for the sound and being startled. and then i realize that it is the song, yeh. theres about 6 days until im gone. onto the sandy white beaches an baseball. i can not wait :D and i cant believe it. i have set plans for tomorrow night...it will actually happen finally. and i know for you 3 people that read this are like whatwhatwhat i wanna know what youre doing :'0 to which i respond with 'nanner nanner boo boo' [giggles and runs away]  ......back again. im real excited for tomorrow. ive got practice real early..and then i can spend some quality time getting ready. then its off for a porker night yay. thats about. figure meet was today. it was ok. and that about does it bye.   gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      longest day since forever. i really like my schedule. and the people that i get to see in the halls walking to class...stopping for a quick hello. it makes my day, it really does.  and, yessum, i cam muy excited for college writing now. i actually get to write about something thats a little bit worth my time..i figure, hell...why not just do a research paper on serial killers? and then i said hey ash thats a great idea and thats where i am now. researching cannibalism and the serial killer complex. :D cute. practice wasnt all that tough today..since weve got a meet tomorrow. woot woot. and i cant believe  just how much it is going to suck. like whoah. im serious. :-/ then it was off to the libarry to look at some books and such...then to the cancer box. :X i know i know, but hey. ive got 7 days to get somewhat of a base tan so i dont come back looking like a lobster. :D yeh its like that, i guess. thats it, no more. Dead I am the life, dig into the skin  Knuckle crack the bone, 21 to win  Dead I am the dog, hound of hell you cry  Devil on your back, I can never die    *pats self on back*that song is catchy.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ohhkay. complete and utter anxiety taking over my body as i know it. i have the feeling right now. like i dont have control over anything...once again...and im freaking out because i hate it when you cant take a really deep breath of yawn all the way, you know like when you have a really nice yawn and your lungs kinda feel like they are going up and over..yyeeaahh maybe thats just what i get..like all the time.. i suppose now i will call it an anxiety attack. i have them all the time and i dont know what to do. i close my eyes and im spinning, i cant keep them open because i freak out and i cant breathe. and i feel like i am about to break down. uuggghh help :[ it was one of those kind of days again..those ones that feel like a mix between summer and a sunday at about 3:30. yea those ones that i hate. the kind where you wake up at like 1 in the afternoon and realize that its only like 5 hours until 6..ok maybe thats just me once again but either way it has been a very uncontrollable couple of days i feel like no one is here but me. which reminds me omgomg of my worst anxiety ever. which was over winter break...ohh god. so my dad drove me half way there...and my cousin picked me up for the last half of the trek up to her place and such. i was enjoying myself, hanging out with her and her friends at wal mart [coughcough] until about 3 days in. [i was stayin for a total of 7 days] when i called my work to see if i was scheduled for the day after i returned to my crackerjack box of a house. and they said yes, 7 in the AM. i figured it would all work out...until my cousin sais that she couldnt drive me 1/2 way back to meet my dad and none of my aunts or uncles wanted to and not even my gramma. there was no way to fricken get home. and if you know me, you know that i freak out and need to have things set and everything. and im not sure that this story does it justice, just how i felt. because it was aweful. never before in my life had i experienced any emotion like that. i felt like i couldnt talk...i had no voice. i wanted to cry every motherfucking minute, and i have no idea way. i hate the feeling, the one where it feels like i cant get out. not like claustrophobia of anysort..i had this constant nervous feeling in my stomach and a lump in my throat. and i couldnt talk to anyone about it because no one knew how i felt. and im like that right now. i feel like anything i have to say doesnt count because no one takes me seriously. well, thanks because youre giving me a tummy ache. >:0 that was heavy. im sorry if you had to read all of that but im happy youre still here :]  yeh its like that i guess.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess that would be cool if i lived in texas and that made sense. what am i going to say now, dont mess with the land of 10,000 ferocious lagoons? pfft. i didnt think so.  today was bleahghehrhdfnksjdfhjsdr. and practice was so mother fucking hard i cant stand it. and the next two meets are hard as motherfuckers so props to that... i dont have any motivation. no motivation to try a little bit so my grades dont suck. no motivation to do anything. i hate everything right now. nothings worth my time. and im ugly. so there. looks like ive got a lot of really good things going for me :D :-/ aanndd i can not forget about being here, at home. gosh, i love it. >:0 theres just something so comforting about getting cold pricklies for everything around here i cant bare it...  music for trio..baseball and/or 20s flapper shit. its pretty cool shit, though. so yea, thats it. yay.  i have bleach in my hair. attempting to fill in my frickn roots. and my finger tips are ghostly white. damn bleach is buring my neck now too. ow. :'(  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wowzah. this weekend flew.. and i guess i didnt really do nuthin. friday night i dun remember what i did. but i woke up early on umm saturday morning for synchro practice..got routines and all. should be okay. i guess :-/ i guess i like it though, alot, because our music for team is Once Upon a Time In Mexico. im muy excited it sounds like somethin fun to swim too.. and i guess for trio its gun be like...the go go's or the uptown girl shia. which im not really a fan of...so im gonna run by the libarry and see if they gots the Willard soundtrack :D now that, is what i call cream filling.  and then went out to Famous Daves. yummmmmmmmmmay thats also what i call cream filling. im sorry, but i love famous daves. cept that one biatch... but dont gemme started. >O haha. i love those little faces ^-^ kthatsenoughthx  we went and saw some oversized sacs :O :O :O yeah! whoa they were big im tellin ya. i think im going to get one :D fer me room, of course. Mark set us up with one..i loved it. nice and soft. and comfy. yay. 0: ) yeh ok thats it.  gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i need an angel face. because this blog title needs one in it :D  today was busy as a muh fuh. math sucked..Pi Day calls fer some real celebration, not this half assed 'heres some crayola markers. color the Pi symbol' shit she had us do. and to prove how pissed i was that we didnt get to participate in any pi day activities and since it wasnt EVEN pi day i didnt do anything.  mmmhm  ():)  DISCLAIMER: [i do not like Hitler, nor agree with anything that he has done]  im really into Hitlers mind. no no no, not like what he did to everyone..but weve been watching alot of videos on him and the Hitler Youth in US histoy the past week. i think that it is so motherfuckingbizzare what he did that its becoming 10x more interesting. seeing thousands of high school girls on a giant enclosed cement block doing exactly the same movements wearing the exact same thing with all types of individuality smashed out and all for the purpose of breeding healthy identical offspring for Hitler and his lebensraum that would have soon been occupied..i dunno. it fascinates me how his mind worked. what a great orator he was..how he led a whole nation by the palm of his hand as people raised theirs. how the people in the videos are so emotionally attatched to this man that was so far from any kind of emotion to begin with. girls crying and wanting to have his babies...its sick. and weird. and interesting. footage of a nursury with blond haired blue eyed boys in cribs that are now Hitlers Youth..its like, he was creating a machine of the 'perfect race' and it is so disgusting. and my all means i think he is one of the sickest motherfuckers but you cant help but to wonder what made him tick. especially because no one can really figure it out. phew..which beings me to my future career: sociologist and/or criminologist. i just figure its the perfect career. im always over analyzing and trying to figure out whats going on up there *taps on head* it looks very interesting so i can not wait. im not gonna write about tonight because i think that my entry on Hitler has provoked some feelings within me now, i.e. why why why questions, and by typing anything else out, my overall feelings of the night may be influenced by my new train of thought. i love it when those little light bulbs go off...  gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nor have a played a role in the hit movie Liar Liar [so how come no one ever seems to believe me] i do not know. but i do know that i am getting perdy sick of it. today was long and we get routines tomorrow. urrg. can i just quit, please? oh ho ho hell no. ive got military parents, remember. the ones that dont let you quit anything. [not actually in the military..] although my dad can be a real ...............Major Pain! hahahahhahahahaha nice one ash. *pats self on back* that was a pretty good one for today  :D  im satisfied. and im sorry to you, too....my condolences go out to you, buddy. but ive been there  a many times before..different circumstance but same concept..  im goin to tuck myself in, now. gusgus  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a girl asked a guy if he thought she was pretty, he said...no. She asked him if he would want to be with her forever...and he said no. She then asked him if she were to leave would he cry? and once again he replied with a no. She had heard enough. As she walked away, tears streaming down her face the boy grabbed her arm and said... Your not pretty, your beautiful, i don't want to be with you forever, i NEED to be with you forever, and i wouldn't cry if you walked away...i'd die...  isnt that sweet? let me go kill myself now :D
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      female undergarments..i am a fan, but not shopping for them. with moms and everything...ick and THEO was working, so yea...kind of diverted thy eyes on that one..  anyway today was a bust. really long. and i dunno..i sleep like 8 hours and yet every time a goddamned teached turns the fucking lights off im out. i camethisclose to mr miller calling of theme out infront  entire class abou tit [te he] he really likes smacking me with his little pointer, too...ehh now im picturing him and his whithered arm. mm sexay ; ) i think im applying to like, i dunno 4 or 5 colleges. wish me luck on that one. because we-heeell im going to be needing all the luck i can get. i dont like the way im writing tonight. its weird. my thoughts arent processing like they normally do. thinking is hard tonight. and ive got this errk zombie song stuck in my head but like, i can hear it, but i cant understand the words and i dont remember them and that really pisses me off. i dunno....yeah  15 days til im off on a jet plane...mmmm baseball i love you  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeh i guess you can count me out of college eh.. bullfuckingshit i dont like tests. and i dont like anything that has to do with tests and test taking abilities and those confusing scantron bubbles that some how always end up looking like i was trying to spell out something weird and number 2 pencils because i only like mechanical ones and how you can never fully erase anything and if you make the mistake of skipping one well then youre screwed and i  hate soggy fries. but i guess thats a different story for a different time.. school in general is so overrated. how many days until im out on the open road? too many. eek :X and i dont even really want to go through the college process because i already know where im going to end up. and it isnt even my top choice. i want to go someplace with opportunity and someplace where i can go to escape everyone and everything. i dont want to have to settle for something just because of one test. but at the same time its not like im going to actually do anything to prevent that. fuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuckfuck.  ohh look! the number of fucks is directly proportional to my score on the ACT practice test :D jeez funny how those things work out, eh?  thats all. im sick of you. yeah, you.  gusgus     i hope that you all counted out the fucks to try and see what i got using some sort of really cool smart person way of figuring things out so i can laugh at you and say that it has nothing to do with what i got. so now, i congratulate the stoopid people for reading this and not counting, because they cant even do that in the first place. hey, at least im with ya... yay :)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeh okay got that from flembot and this 'really cool best friend' or hers that i hear so much about. pfft other friends? c'mon. :D  today was long and boo ring..and a waste of time at that. got new seats in math..still close to my little creep stalked friend..so thats good i guess. talked it up with the D-man today about spring training. lookie like the whole fricken baseball team will be in fort meyers the same time as me and stephanie...im thinkin, a little get together, fellas? ;-) im. so. excited. its like, two weeks away. yippie. same old same old in every other class..nothing else really, i guess...ms swanie cracked. me. up today hahahhaha. oh cheeze. her and her 3rd grade tumble...god. thats the funniest thing ive seen in a looooong time. i got some pictures back today too! i like gittin them back. alot of retarded things make me exicted but what can i say..im simple to please. thats it though. nommuch else ta say ta day. yay for synchro pot lucks mmmmmm yummay  gusgus [linus] ():) 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i awoke this morning with a relaxed aura around me. i dunno why..but it was nice and calm. until my mom raged into my room and i wasnt allowed out of the house until i was finished painting/cleaning/washing/sanding my walls. it was like straight out of child labor.. but i got it done in a mere 2 hours or so. its kinda blue greenish i guess i dunno. its just the base coat ive got loads more to do.. is it really accpetable for a store  designed  to cater to swimmers and their equipment, not to have any swim suits? alls i need is a black one for practice and one for meets..but op! nooo.. the one time i need one.. ran back over to hot topic for the second time this weekend and picked up a cd. well, not mee persay but atiekay did for me. with her gc and all. yay so now im set for something to listen to this week. passing time is my favorite. just me and my head phones :X but today was weird. ugh it pissed me off. you know, when its about 2:30 and the sun is in a really awkward position and there are clouds, then sun, off and on...eeeek it felt like a sunday. but worse it was a sunday in the summer when you cant think of anything to do and youre just sitting there..kinda like when youre on vacation and its your last day and you this overwhelming feeling to get out of there..wanting to get home. or i guess its like when you get home from someplace really fun and exciting and you have to come home to your same boring life you left less than a week ago. yeh i guess its like that. and thats how i felt, so i got pissed off. but then i got home. and my room was clean. and now im happy. this was a very long weekend. i did so much :D hookups are great.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what. the. fuh uck. what makes it so different with me.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was quality. it really helped out yesterday. yay :D alls well. this whole blogging everyday is getting weird. is it sad that i cannot resist?  its like, blog love. and im addicted to it. :X  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for once i want to know how it feels to be okay with everything. when something really good happens in my life something else is taken away. the thing is...no, there wasnt anything there, ever. i was happy with that. because i knew that i never wanted something to happen with him because i would be pissed off all the time. i didnt want anything with him because i didnt want to handle all of that with him. excuse me, do not flatter yourself into thinking that i somehow feel in love the second i saw you. dont flatter yourself into thinking that i was smitten by your lack of manners and off beat way of handleing every situation that youve been in, because truthfully i really didnt give a shit. you were suffocating and obviously didnt understand the meaning of "if youre going to be late, let me know" because youre weird. and i think i wanted something good to happen with my life after last year that i actually believed it for a second. and i tell myself, ashley, dont go through that again. dont let anything happen because you always get hurt. and i was cautious, because i didnt like him like that after i had talked to him for 3 months and found out what he was really like. but there is a big difference between the 2 situations that ive been in. because one cares about feelings, and one doesnt. so fuck you. fuck you for even thinking that i was somehow madly in love with you and your fucked up life.and fuck you for telling me the things you did, because if you were looking to bring up the past and hurt my feelings, you sure as hell did. so, fuck. you. ive made my point. but im left with so many unanswered questions to everything and i want someone, anyone, to help me out here. whats so wrong with me, that nothing ever happens? im sad. and mad. and i hate not understanding anything.   Oh I know thats how you see the world, I know that you see anything you like. But now I'm doubting me, I know I shouldn't be but I've been down, I've been down.   phew. gusgus.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my head kinda hurts. and so do my arms. and my feet. and my back needs to be cracked. and im not tired so i cnt go to sleep. its been a long day. i sat at school from 750 inthe AM until 1 o clock then ran home then went back from 3-5 swimming then ran to subway to eat a little something then came back for the act prac thing for THREE HOURS SO IM A LITTLE EXHAUSTED. [i just figured i would copy and paste that from a conversation. no use in typin that beast again]  i heard some nice tunes on the way home tonight. i like driving in the dark? will you go with me sometime? it'll be fun. promise.  im pooped. nighty gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay okay i know...its bad blogging twice in one night. i just consider the previous one a side note to this one. get it? got it? good. i absolutely feel in love with today. it was just a good day. most of it i wasnt expecting but let me tell you, it was nice. you know, being noticed and all. but i hate the way these things get to me. like how i forget that these things really arent there...just figments of my imagination. sucks, yes, but ive become accustomed to them by now. ive got like 4 tests tomorrow..all of which im planning to fail with flying colors. like i know what the hell is going on in math, anyway. its hard to concentrate when your eyes are glazing over. :X and US history im begining [sp? looks wrong..] to dislike mr miller..not that hes not a top notch kinda guy..but i dont know.  hes getting to me. and i really, have to say that im liking that hes learned to call me by my first name. oh praise the heavens above on that one... 0:] ugh. and how can i ferget the dreaded hell that is synchronized swimming. especially when were missing a porker :( linda is such a motherfucking lazy ass. please, by all means linda, get in the water and do some of the shit you have us do. its a little bit difficult.. im not as pissed about going everyday this year though. i mean, i was perrty werked up about it but what can ya do. just make the best of it i guess. and irrrk that also means getting up at 8 in the AM for saturday practices. oh sweet mary and joseph. [ohh..joseph..he stole my silver spoons, joseph!] ah ahah. good times, good times. im gonna cut this one of fer tonight, keep it clean. [oh northwest] ick.  gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're Gangsta Bitch Barbie.  You're tough and you like it rough, and of course you like to pop a cap in any wiggers ass.    urlLink   If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    :D dont mess with me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was brilliant.for no particular reason, you see...but it was a nice day fer laughs. im not sure why but either way you slice it i had mad giggles. couldnt help it either. some people are just too stoopid to pass up and not have a little chuckle at. i actually had most of my homework done for today which is a first..and got most of it for tomorrow done before 6th period. yay more time to watch Americas Top Model. i mean...what? yeh okay. i do watch that. so sue me :D its a sick habit. especially when its followed by some classic Real World. but nothing is better than that. whats with everyone getting arrested these days... chem today was fan.fucking.tastic. i dont understand how  its possible to be in 11th grade and still not be at an 11th grade reading level. come on now, even i can pronounce 'martian' you know, those little green guys that cruise around on the silver saucer plates..gAWD. and im not sure what is so fucking high larious when someone [me] happens to nudge their [mine] cd player and it falls of their [mine, again] desk. how long did the laughter go on for? maybe somewhere close to 3minutes. non stop. chattering. about 'omgomgomgomgomgogmomgomg someone hahahah dropped hahha their hahahahhaha   ......  hahahaha cd player" [that sounded awfully similar to...dave... you know...the USA tennis guy] yea ok. either way enough said it was retahded. thats it. as always, i shall leave you with something to read..take it heart, will you? these things shouldnt be taken lightly. Well I don't know what I've been told You never slow down, you never grow old  I'm tired of screwing up, I'm tired of goin' down I'm tire of myself, I'm tired of this town  Oh my my, oh hell yes Honey put on that party dress Buy me a drink, sing me a song, Take me as I come 'cause I can't stay long  as always, farewell. gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are WILD AND CRAZY KIDS.  You couldn't get through life without a little fun... or a neon colored t-shirt.  You are a team player and really into Omar Gooding.  GO YOU!    urlLink   Which old school Nickelodeon show are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    dont forget to read that blog down there...yea, the one below this one. k thx :D 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my secrets out..im not sure what to think about it..or whats going to happen with it. i just hope they dont find out it was me. because that would be vewy vewy bad :-X  ive been listening to alot of tom petty lately. now, being in my house as a little kid thats all i heard. tom petty, jackson browne,  rolling stones, bob dylan, CCR, styx, zeppelin and so on. but it was a chance encounter that i made with my brothers untitled cd collection that got me started up again. its kind of sad. i used to come home from school everyday to a home busting with music and i knew i was at the right place.  everything around here was a lot more different than it is now. i dont hear the music everyday anymore. cept for xmas time when my mom gets really into the swing of things with the christ non stop KOOL 108 mixes for the holiday season. blastly radios damn them all to hell. thats the one thing that my mom said she ever had in common with her dad. her guitar and her music. knowing my moms dad, hes a nice guy and everything. but very isolated. keeps to himself and works on his old truck. and not having another gpa around its kind of depressing. for a period of about 4 years i knew my dads dad..and got quite familiar with his lap. used to sit there for hours on end. [not in a sick way you perv] i always feel bad for the one uncle. the one without a wife or kids but just a dog and his house. life seems lonely. i hope i find someone to spend the rest of my life with. i guess if you wanted me to sum this up, tom petty is great. he soothes and stirs emotions at the same time..which is a very powerful thing to be able to do and usually makes a great musician. this ones for you, pal: [not tom petty..i mean  you ] Some days are diamonds  Some days are rocks  Some doors are open  Some roads are blocked   Sundowns are golden  Then fade away  But if I never do nothing  I'll get you back some day   Cause you got a heart so big  It could crush this town  And I can't hold out forever  Even walls fall down   And all around your island  There's a barricade  It keeps out the danger  It holds in the pain   Sometimes you're happy  Sometimes you cry  Half of me is ocean  Half of me is sky   But you got a heart so big  It could crush this town  And I can't hold out forever  Even walls fall down   And some things are over  Some things go on  And part of me you carry  Part of me is gone   But you got a heart so big  It could crush this town  And I can't hold out forever  Even walls fall down   Baby you got a heart so big  It could crush this town  And I can't hold out forever  Even walls fall down  They fall down  see? if the berlin wall fell, the one around your heart can too.  that was a good blog. *pats self on back* gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i like lanky guys...lanky guys with dark hair thats messy and guys who dont stand up really straight... :X ive come to that conclusion, among others.  i was disappointed this evening at the lack of free hat supply they were supposed to have produced for the massive amounts of Twins fans..6, 279 fans went home without one. so much for every fan counts, eh? it was a great game. i like nathan. alot. i likeitalot. i like how were doing really well...lets just hope that we dont pull a Kansas City. woowee. that would suck. theres always so much to talk about at a baseball game..and i can never remember exactly what we talked about for 3 hours..i just remember a lotta giggles :D oh yeh...and that whole, replacement discussion. oh and how can you forget those awkward moments when walking in the halls or sitting in the desks..coughcough..stephanie and drew know what im talking about ; ) my favorite movie has been replaced. [again, with the circle of replacements] Soul Man. god. wtf, funniest movie ive seen in a shit load long of a time. and i didnt even get to finish it. dougs mug was just too painful to glance at. thank god he took a plow to that corn field.. :D back to his normal hot self. oh yeah, and i liked how after i ranted and raved about how much i hated prom during 5th hour.. go through 6th pretty painlessly..until the last, oh i dunno, 15 minutes. which were consumed with thoughts of prom. >:O what did i say about prom? yeh. no likey. my lips are chapped. wheres my lanky messy haired boy? i like mohawks. and i saw a reaaalllyyy nice one tonight. its like, looking at a precious foreign car. me likey alot.  where are you right now?! i believe your last message was at (12:17:40 AM) .... >:O gah. A-unit
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      with the great circulations of prom invites going on..i really feel like a loser. whatever. maybe i'll just go kill myself and make it all that much better. at least i wont have to hear about prom anymore. i want it to be free chipotle day again. i need to go to my car right now. make a run for it, i say. but ive got this to do. yup. update this stupid piece of crap. why i do it, i will never know. it doesnt even solve anything. just lets me sit here and think about all the shitty things i wanna say about how my life sucks so bad right now. doesnt get anything accomplished. neglecting homework is what this does damnit. its not like i actually have a life anyway, but thats besides the point. nevertheless, its not like i will stop.  i wanna do another survey, but i cant find anymore. :( for shits sake ive got nothing to even write about anymore. no more happy blogs. no more no more. not for a long time. because now, that one phase has ended and now youre in the other phase. where everything is..perfect..and you have the 17 year old life. prom, boyfriends, friends..invitations, pretty days everyday... god make it all stop. but its not like i didnt know it was coming. because it was always bound too. but its different now because ive got nothing.    fuckshitcocksuckermotherfuckerfuckshitcocksuckermotherfuckerfuckshitcocksuckermotherfucker. thats all i have to say about that. i just wanna scream one giant loud motherfucker.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as in..eating away at my heart. that kind of acidic. im not sure what kind of pleasure people get in making others feel stupid. and frankly my dear, eat shit. because sometimes thats how you make other people feel. i suppose for all of you that are going out of your way to read this and pass judgments, i sound like a pretty bitter young lady. normally im not. but when life throws shit at you you cant help but complain. i suppose its my whole..not understanding of anything that ever happens that is getting in my way of actually enjoying life right now. the only thing that ever cheers me up now are emails and baseball games. it used to be so much more. maybe it will take a turn for the better once im out of this jail of stupidity they like to call high school. time will tell. on a lighter note.. theres always the baseball game tomorrow. with our new signs! stephanie has got some good ones tucked away so im muy excited. and then on saturday..wooo hooo yay. hush hush on that one though. sunday i have to work. no muy excited. today was free chipotle day. and with the help of cats cell and emilys car..we got there with plenty of time to spare. saw theodore..:X gah. stood in line..you know...secretly wanting dave ryan to come up just  glance  at us...whoop! looks like he did that and he picked me out and gave me a nice little tshirt and cd. its too bad i dont like Usher..or i would have been more excited about it. and then there was that one guy..who i thought worked for KDWB too..but hes not on the website. hum. he was cute. came up and chatted it up, too, before i had to yell at the mexians for no beans...no,  no  beans. good lord son! no frijoles! it was funny. guess you had to have been there.  bah. what a useless post. yelhsa
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what is it about semisonic that induces tears.  i just read all of my past posts. talk about retarded. seriously.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my dad made ribs tonight fo dinner. mmmm finger lickin good. thats the way to ashley's heart :)  which just so happens to be 3 times too small... : ( come to think of it..i wouldnt touch me with a 10 foot pole. anyway. today was a little less painful that yesterday thank goudaness. gah! prom, i need you to shut up so everyone can stop talking about you. the sad thing is that i really would like to go. with someone who would also like to go with me. all i wanna do is dance..dance like ive never danced before..im a maniac, maniac... ah ahha. i like how i can easily crack myself up. what can i say, must be a gift. its sad when people were never noticed before but after one little who the heck cares incident they are all of a sudden everyones best friend. and forgetting about the real ones.. just a thought, i guess. i like the song sweet home alabama. alot. i like music and geetars and funny stupid things. i dont like garbage or people that are selfish. at least there is friday. and free hat night. im excited. weve got some rad posters to hold up. if we actually do hold them...this time...then it will all work out. i dont understand high school. and  i seem to really hate it lately. my life is pathetic and you make me feel so stupid sometimes. bah!  this is getting old. the complaining and such.. i think i need a break.  sugsug
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      love lyrics. love em to death.  They say you're off  (A bit confused)  But when the day is done  I'll be with you  I like your eyes  They say you're true  The others whisper and lie   And you framed the sun  Shot out the stars  You paled the sky  And hung the moon   They say, "your loss"  That your mind's diseased  But when you've finally won,  Tell me who always believed   And you framed the sun  Shot out the stars  You paled the sky  And hung the moon   Down way low  They never remember  Down way low  Down way low  You always remember  Don't let the words you hear Leave your head.   The say you're gone  That you left today  But if you change your mind  Know I still feel that same way   And you framed the sun  Shot out the stars  You paled the sky  And hung the moon  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we sucked today. but thats A-ok because i just dont give a shit. and my one eye is blurry. which causes for some real irriation on my nerves >O gah. today was too long. way. too. long. not only didi come home to a ton of homework but i still havent done most of it. which means, that i probably shouldnt be doing this right now. lucky chance of that ever happening.. :X i just..i dunno. everything is different now. people are really different too. the people who i could recognize as some of my best friends and now just whipped up into their own world. and to me it just seems so..selfish.  i guess i wouldnt and couldnt even dream of replacing the friends ive got. obviously times are a changin. most people dont know how much i like tom petty. im glad my comments work now. stupid templates, i tell ya. lemme at 'em. hold me back. that reminds me when i was 13. oh gah!  the horrors. this blog is pointless. and yet a second one for today. oh you lucky readers. pfft.  im pooped. too pooped, in fact, that i seem to now write about anything even remotely interesting anymore. *tear* maybe i shall fill up my space and/or time with more of those survey thingies.. :O i kid, i kid.  err...:X yeh. thats it. suck it. bye. gugu
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever... {x} Fallen for your best friend? uhm..yes kind of {x} Made out with JUST a friend? yehp {x} Been rejected? god of course {x} Been in love? yep {x} Been in lust? very much so {x} Used someone? i dont use people. {x} Been used? Yes {x} Cheated on someone? never have, never will. {x} Been cheated on? considering guys are cheating assholes, then im sure at some point. {x} Done something you regret? basically everything  up to this point  Who was the last person... {x} You touched? no one today... {x} You talked to? emily {x} You hugged? my momma {x} You instant messaged? meh. charlie. as always. {x} You kissed? hush hush {x} You yelled at? my father {x} You laughed with? emily  Have you/are you/do you.... {x} Considered a life of crime? yes of course! i have my very own partner in crime, as a matter of fact. {x} Considered being a hooker? considered? pfft..already am  {x} Considered being a pimp? gimp, maybe {x} Are you psycho? not in the skeevy way {x} Split personalities? mm nope, but my emotions do run a muck {x} Schizophrenic? yes. no. shutup you! {x} Obsessive? [freshmanobsessions] yes at times. {x} Obsessive compulsive? err with somethings {x} Panic? Yes {x} Anxiety? GOD yes. {x} Depressed? when i start to think {x} Suicidal? No {x} Obsessed with hate? no. {x} Dream of mutilated bodies, blood, death, and gore? eh..no {x} Dream of doing those things instead of just seeing them? no {x} Understanding: i like to think that i am, yes. {x} Open-minded: very {x} Arrogant: no. urk. {x} Insecure: might as well name it after me {x} Interesting: yessm {x} Hungry: gah obviously. {x} Friendly: i hope so {x} Smart: medicocre  {x} Moody: yes, yes. {x} Childish: thats the only way to get through life {x} Independent: at some things. hopefully all around, soon. {x} Hard working: meh. yeah i guess.  {x} Organized:i like to be. {x} Healthy: um sure  {x} Emotionally Stable: helllllno. {x} Shy: all the time. {x} Difficult: sometimes. {x} Attractive: :-/ {x} Bored Easily: yes. youve got to keep me interested. {x} Thirsty: all the time. {x} Responsible: most of the time {x} Sad: usually. {x} Happy: meh {x} Trusting: yep {x} Talkative: depends who i'm talking to {x} Original: i think so. {x} Different: oh yes. {x} Unique: just like everyone else. aha. {x} Lonely: uht um yeh {x} Color your hair? yeh {x} Have tattoos? not yet {x} Piercings? ears {x} Have a boyfriend? nope :[ {x} Floss daily? no :X {x} Own a webcam? a really old one, dont use it though. {x} Ever get off the damn computer? only to sleep :x hahah {x} Sprechen sie deutsche? uhm. right.  {x} Habla espanol? claro que si, pero no me gusta la clase de espanol porque yo suckie mucho. [i could translate pretty well, though :D]  Currents {x} Current Clothes: synchro skirt and shirt {x} Current Mood: gah. {x} Current Taste: cheeze its yumm {x} Current Hair: down and straight {x} Current Annoyance: ms norris creeping around seeing if were doing what were supposed to be doing :X o0o0o rebel {x} Current Smell: *takes big whif* nada. {x} Current thing you ought to be doing: pfft paper {x} Current Desktop Picture: nothing {x} Current Favorite Group: goodnight moon {x} Current Book: book of illusions {x} Current DVD In Player: nada {x} Current Refreshment: water {x} Current Worry: what the hell is so wrong with me.. {x} Current Crush: hush hush {x} Current Favorite Celebrity: johnny dep. der. Favorite... {x} Food: fluffernutters {x} Drink: wata {x} Color: green {x} Shoes: my birkies {x} Candy: sixlets {x} TV Show: im a sucker for the real world. :D {x} Movie: benny and joon, eddie scissorhands  {x} Dance: dunno {x} Vegetable: cucumbers {x} Fruit: an apple a day keeps the doctor away On Dating.... {x} Long or short hair? dont matter. too long gets a little...eh.. {x} Dark or blond hair? Doesn't matter {x} Tall or short? Doesn't matter. I'm short anyway {x} Mr. Sensitive or Mr. Funny? i would prefer both. {x} Good guy or bad guy? Both. Good guys will always win in my book.. but bad guys are intriguing {x} Dark or light eyes? Doesn't matter {x} Hat or no hat? o0o0o hat please. doesnt matter though. {x} Pierced or no? Doesn't Matter {x} Freckles or none? No preference {x} Stubble or neatly shaved? neatly shaved {x} Rugged outdoorsy type or sporty type? how about just someone i like to be around?  On preferences.... {x} Chocolate milk or hot chocolate? CHOCOLATE MILK {x} McDonalds or Burger King? Burger King {x} Marry the perfect lover or the perfect friend? perfect friend. {x} Sweet or sour? salty. {x} Root Beer or Dr. Pepper? be a pepper, dr pepper {x} Sappy/action/comedy/horror? im good with documentaries {x} Cats or dogs? dogs {x} Ocean or Pool? ocean. {x} Cool Ranch or Nacho Cheese? ranch. or nacho. doesnt matter. {x} Mud or Jell-O wrestling? Jello der {x} With or without ice-cubes? with {x} Shine or rain? rain and shine. sunshowers i likey. {x} Winter/Summer/Fall/Spring? Spring/fall {x} Vanilla or Chocolate? niller {x} Gloves or mittens? mittens {x} Eyes open or closed? closed {x} Fly or breathe under water? fly {x} Bunk-bed or waterbed? bunk {x} Chewing gum or hard candy? chewing gum. hard mints. {x} Motor boat or sailboat? sail {x} Lights on or off? off {x} Chicken or fish? eww fish. chicken most def.  What's your favorite:. {x} Number? 3 {x} Holiday? 4th of july {x} Radio station? 93x when i am listening to the radio. {x} Place? with you {x} Flower? anything thats picked and given to me. {x} Scent? rain and ocean {x} If you could be anywhere, where would you be? europe. {x} What would you be doing? packin the back {x} What are you listening to? dashboard confessional. {x} Can you do anything freakish with your body? hmm... ():D {x} Do you have a favourite animal, no matter how lame it may be? manatees ........ :)  whew. there goes anoder! gugu 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cracks. me. up. theres nothing better than those animated ecards. i have quite the chuckle when i come across one in my email. ah hahha. wow. this is the 2nd post today..so much for having a life, no? but its not like i ever claimed to have one in the first place i suppose. meghan has a retard humping her leg now :X it brought a tear to my eye. my mom cleaned my room today...and yesterday..and the day before.  i guess its more like everyfuckingtime im not sitting in my room as usual. she cant stand not gettin into my stuff. i mean, im not totally complaining here, either. because i came home from practice and see that she bought all these really cool little things for my room. :D life isnt fair, nor will it ever be. thats it for now..possibly more later. 3 times a charm, no? my mom is blasting john mayer. oh, sweet jesus. at least it isnt sex and the city again..  gugu
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and i find myself searching for reasons to keep away the demons.  op no such luck. ive got a shiat load of h-dubb to do tonight. and im super tired, too..seeing as though i didnt get to beddy bye until after 12. im thinking it was close to one, actually. managed to not do anything last night as usual. and now ive got to bust out some note cards and a discovery draft tonight so i can come here tomorrow and not have to do jackshit tomorrow.haha. when emily says shes got a hair a little below the chin it doesnt mean in length :D :X  and i think something good is on tonight. when is The Swan on>? maybe i should try out for that. i think i would stand a good chance.. ive got alot of trips planned. some small, some large, and some just right. ive got one this weekend. two, actually. one to the Dome. yay for Queen of Dairy free hat night :) and then one on saturday...shh shh shh. and then sometime in the end of july. road trip down to kansas city, woot. and then, of course, my europe backpacking trip. i know i know..ive got all the sites planned out. i know how much money i need and everything. ive planned for one. but time will tell, i guess. it all depends on where i am in a year or so. i guess it would be enjoyable to explore europe with a friend. err...you know... emily is lucky. her and her friday date. god, damnit. once again, whats so wrong with me. whatever. at least ive got my europe waiting for me. its going to be a blast and i know it.  you do know, that i would die for you....right?   .cogsworth.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a wonderful weekend. friday was less painful that i was thinking it to be. which was a nice suprise. i was thinking about bringing a pistol, which even if i did i wouldnt have had to use it. i did my salsa dance for everyone. that was abig hit i must say. i swear, i have never seen anna crack up more than when i do that. ROFLMAO [haha marma].. yehp..did a little decortating of certain said destinations at 2 o clock in the morning as well. [im sorry about that too, marma :D] and in the end i found out that when i draw a mustache on with little curls at the ends i look like Cogsworth. the clock. from beauty and the beast. what is it with disney characters these days, and me looking like them. goddamnit. saturday practice was also less painful, then took a turn for massively painful as we watched our routines on tape :X oh god. drove down to st peter. fun time that was, very many hotties. te he. went to the concert and i shed a tear during a certain song that made me think and it was all in all a great night. went back to P-UNIT's place partied here, partied there, you know how we do. it was fun. me and paul drew a penis on katies face when she passed out. :D muah ah ah aha ha !  drove home and now i am here. after hearing about certain stories from certain friends, i have come to the conclusion that guys are cheating losers but i wish i had a nice one for myself. and it makes me sad. and depressed. and i feel worthless because when i get asked if i have a boyfriend, and i say no, people act shocked. as if its really easy, which apparently it is, to find a guy that will take some time to get to know me. and that makes me real sad. so right now, im feeling a little bit down in the dumps. because i want someone, too. :[  some days are better, they're better than others  can't run forever, you're pushing me under what a way to live my life  i'm hiding from the battles i don't want to fight what i've become  and now it's going grey  all the lines are blurring and decayed i can't recall exactly who's to blame..... anymore  is it me or is it you , something isn't right  of all the things that we could do we just wanna fight someday i will find the courage to embrace you someday i will find the strength to erase you  some days i think i'm nothing without you sometimes i wish that i could just kill you what a way we live our lives it's hard to breathe it feels like i'm infected by my dad's disease  and now it's going grey  and you're the one i chose to feed me pain and i'm the one you bring home so ashamed.....through their eyes and i see myself in heaven if i can free myself from this hell  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im gone for a few days. doin a little bit of this, a litte bit of that. maybe if youre lucky i will being you back some hotel paper. did you catch that? anyways. fill out on of those survey things down there. or not. whatever. leave something either way. :l  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I AM NOT: a barbie, someone else, a super fan, or a cat lover. I WAS: ugly, then really ugly, then a little less ugly..and now i dont think im so ugly. I WAS NEVER: a barbie, someone else, a super fan, or a cat lover. I WILL BE: this way forever. I LIKE: meeting new people, music, blow pops and nature valley trial mix bars I LOVE: music, water, chocolate cupcakes and music. I DISLIKE: liars, cheaters, people who dont like music and people who dont like me. I HATE: broken hearts, commercials, flat pop, and alot of peanut butter. I WANT: to feel needed, wanted, loved and a cupcake right now. I NEED: to not be dependent, attatched, some water and a cupcake right now. I DONT WANT: anything to do with cliques.  I DON'T NEED: the school calling my house. I SHOULDN'T: worry so much. I'D LIKE TO HAVE: someone who likes me for me. I LISTEN: to music...a lot I EAT: food. I DRINK: water mostly I SMOKE: never. I DRESS: based on my moods I LAUGH: at stupid things I DRIVE: my car when i have it... >O I CRY: over little things, like in 3rd grade when i didnt have my homework done..pffft.. I YELL: when im pissed. I DREAM: for everything i dont have. I FEEL: inadequate I MAKE: good cupcakes I SAY: shit hits the fan all the time. I WISH I COULD: be there with you. I WISH I WAS: there with you. I WISH I WASN'T: bored with life I WISH I KNEW: what people really thought I AM HAPPY: when im doing independent things. and when i get presents. I AM LONELY: when i want what i dont have. I AM SAD: when i want what i dont have. I AM MAD: not mad... I THINK: things happen for a reason  A survey.... Current mood: relaxed after my ibuprofen intake this morning. Current music:dredg Current taste: minute made pink lemonade. yulk, no water. Current hair: down, straight, pink blonde and dark brown. Current clothes: pink silvers, black tank top with white shirt over, says somethin about mango's i guess.. and my swimming hoodie. exciting. Current annoyance: feeling hair on my face and i dont know where it is. gah! Current smell: outside smell. Current thing I ought to be doing: my college writing paper :X Current windows open: this one..right..[here] Current desktop picture: meh nothing. school computer. Current favorite band: oh jeez. there are too many. prolly something in my new pile of cd's im guessing. Most listened to: semisonic, yellowcard, story of the year. Current book: book of illusions Current cds in stero: coheed and cambria  Current crush: hm... Current favorite celeb: as always, johnny dep Current hate: i don't hate. except commerical free hours on the radio when they interrupt the music to do a commerical on commercial free music. gah! Current job: an ice cream jerk. +Last+ Last book you read: me and my typewriter Last movie you saw: benny and joon Last thing you had to drink: currently, lemonade. Last time you showered: this very morning. Last thing you ate: fruit snacks yum. Last person you talked to on the phone: mom, i think.  +Do i+have i ever+ Smoke?: no Do drugs?: welp, no i guess. Have sex?: nope. Have a dream that keeps coming back?:oh yes. Play an instrument?: lets see..i used to play the piano. and that was for like, 10 years. played the violin for about 8 years. gah, make it stop. Believe there is life on other planets?: it could happen Remember your first love?: yesm. Still love him/her: to some extent sure Read the newspaper?: sports. Have any gay or lesbian friends? humm i dont think so, no. Believe in miracles?: eventually. Believe it's possible to remain faithful forever?: is that not the point of marriage..? Consider yourself tolerant of others? depends. Consider love a mistake?: my experiences would point me to say yes, but real love is definitely not a mistake. Like the taste of alcohol?: i'm not big on drinkin :p but yes i suppose so. Have a favorite candy?: sixlets. mm yum. Believe in astrology?: maybe Believe in magic?: i wish Believe in god?: yes Have any pets: yup. Do well in school? meh. Go to or plan to go to college: yes Wear hats?: in winter and to baseball games. Have any piercings?: ears  Have any tattoos?: not yet. maybe eventually. Hate yourself?: no Have an obsession?: carmex. Have a secret crush?: yes of course :D Do they know yet?:well if they did it wouldnt be a secret. but meh, i dunno. maybe, maybe not. Collect anything?: tickets and alot of old stuff. i like to think that ive got an old soul. Have a best friend? sure do Close friends?: yea those too Wish on stars?: only shooting ones Like your handwriting?: its ok i guess. Care about looks? not really  +Love and stuff+ First crush: shh shh shh. First kiss: major shh shh shh. Single or attached?: single Ever been in love?: yes. Do you believe in love at first sight? most definitely. Do you believe in "the one?": most. def. Describe your ideal significant other: pure connection.  +Juicy stuff+ Have you ever played a game that required removal of clothing?:yes. Have you ever been intoxicated?: yes. Favorite place to be kissed?: my uht...lips..and jawline. painting=great. Have you ever been caught"doing something”: nope. tease?: no Shy to make the first move?: sometimes...  +Are you a+ Wuss: i can be Druggy: no Daydreamer: this is my life. Freak: freaky deaky Dork: yes Bitch/Asshole: no  Brat: no Sarcastic: very Goody-goody: i think that might be how people see me. which is a big no-no. Devil: no  Shy: yes. Talkative: when ive got somethin to talk about. Adventurous: sure Joker: COMEDIAN  Name::ashley Age:: 17 Date of Birth:: feb 3 Location:: minneapolis Gender:: wooman Occupation:: student and ice cream maker :D Screen Name::pluermoo Email:: skittles0387@msn.com Description Eye Color:: green and brown Hair Color:: brown and pink and blonde Weight:: disclosed  Height:: 5'5 Piercings:: ears  Tattoos:: eventually Shoe Size:: 7 ish Wearing:: clothes. der. Currents Listening:: dredg Eating:: nothing Feeling:: okay... Family Parents:: yes i have two Siblings:: older brother Pets:: one Divorced?:: i'm a little young.... Music Favorite Band:: many many Favorite Song:: still too many Hated Band:: meh, i dunno. im not big on the boy band thing.. Hated Song::  all the naked lady pimpin ones Best CD:: aw toughie Worst CD:: i dunno favorite? radiostation:: radio is stinky Music TV Station: mtv i suppose.  Favorites Color:: green Food:: cupcakes TV Show:: the oc School Subject:: chem Animals:: doggies Movies:: benny and joon Books:: anything by paul auster Cartoon:: family guy Drink:: water Holiday:: 4th of july Scent:: beach Pizza Topping:: cheese and nothing else. Board Game:: candyland Video Game::anything racing Number:: 3 Cereal:: cap'n crunch. or kix: kid tested, mother approved. Dessert:: it doesnt matter. Ice Cream Flavor:: mint chocolate chip Disney Character:: i dislike disney. Place to Shop: anything cheap. and vintage works too. Pastime:: music Teacher:: nada Childhood Toy:: hummm, i dunno. Amusement Park Ride:: i like rollercoasters Candy:: sixlets Magazine:: cosmo Season:: fall Sport:: baseball Bedroom Wall Color:: lime green and blue Posters: a lot pictures if they count Sheets: stripes # Pillows:: 1 # Blankets:: 3 Size Bed:: room enough for...two? lol Share a room?:: nope Snore?:: na Drool?:: yes :X Stuffed animals?:: na Either Or Coke or Pepsi:: coke. classic. Donuts or Bagels:: not really either. Day or Night:: night  Heaven or Hell:: heaven Coffee or Tea:: neither Hamburgers or Hot Dogs:: hot dogs at baseball games, burgers elsewhere. Hot or Cold:: hot Winter or Summer:: summer Spring or Summer:: spring. Operas or Plays:: plays Read or Watch TV:: tv i suppose CDs or Tapes:: cd's DVDs or VHS:: ...either Old or New:: both Shorts or Skirts:: skirts Colored or Black and White:: either Mexican or Chinese:: chinese Commercials or Informercials::infomercials Bikinis or One Piece:: bikinis Sandals or Sneakers:: doesnt matter Dogs or Cats:: dogs Black or White:: black Ribbons or Bows:: noodles Chicken or Beef:: either Cars or Trucks:: trucks Popcorn or Pretzels:: popcorn Picture Frames or Photo Albums:: either Candid or Posed:: candid Pens or Pencils:: pens. unless mechanical pencils. Opinion Recording Industry:: sucks right now President Bush:: ok. Controversial Music Artists:: really? Religion:: dont have one. Homosexuals:: do whatever makes you happy i guess Abortion:: womans choice. so, mr president, back the fuck out. Death:: always present  Random Words Sponge:: bob Yellow:: card Marshmallow:: camping Dog:: cat Cat:: fish Cruel:: mermaid Phone:: booth Rainbow:: bright Animal:: house Queen:: rocks Chocolate:: chip Trivia:: alex trebeck Sandy:: feet Soda:: machine  Have You Ever: Told a Secret?:: yes Broke a Bone?:: no Got into a Fight?:: not a physical one Plotted Against Someone?:: mayyybbaayy.... Been on TV?:: yes Been on the Radio?:: no Been in a Mosh Pit?:: yes Been to a Concert?:: yep Taken Drugs?:: yes Drank Alcohol?:: yes Broken the Law?:: maybe Been to a Rodeo?:: AHHH! i guess i havent found the right person to coughcoughdocoughcough a rodeo with. which is something i hope i never find, thx. Been on an Airplane?:: yes Came Close to Dying?:: yep. once or twice here and there. Terrorized a Babysitter?:: no Snuck out of the House?:: yes Smoked?:: yes Been to Camp?:: yes Won a Bet?:: yep Won a Trophy or Medal?:: yes Thrown up in Public?:: no. peed? yes. Bowled a Perfect Game?:: never. i dont think i even toss the damn ball right, which says alot about my skills. Stayed Back?:: [from where..?] Gotten Perfect Attendance?:: no Loved Someone?:: yes Random Three Things Near Computer:: cd player. notebook. that is all. Hidden Talents::baby cry Worst Movie:: uhm...i dunno. cant think. Best Movie:: benny and joon Drive?:: yes Sky Dive?:: would like to Believe in Bigfoot?::yes Lochness Monster?:: god yes. Yeti?:: haha friggin mountain man Other Random Monster?:: meh. no. Rooms in House:: several Afraid of Roller Coasters?:: nope love em Believe in Some Higher Power?:: god i suppose. Own a Pool Table?:: nope. Wished on a Shooting Star?::yes. Best Halloween Costume:: welp..when i was little i think i was a dalmation every year about until the age of 6.. Carry Weapons?:: no Ideal Way to Die?: in my sleep Way to Release Stress:: typing in this godforsaken piece. Trendy?:: in my own way. Artistic? yes Untie Shoes Before Taking Them Off?:: no  Strong?:: meh. Last Email:: alex Last IM:: charlie Deep Sleeper?:: very. Story Tellerer?:: i like telling them, yes.. Best Quality:: i would like to think that i care alot about feelings. seeing as though i know how i feel most of the time... Greatest Accomplishment:: pulling myself through shit. Best Feeling in World:: being thought of. Worst Feeling in World:: not needed. Bikinis or One Piece:: on me? pffft. bikini i suppose, as to not look like im 5...  did you read all of that? that took me 2 class periods to fill out, damnit. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my day has ended on a very high note. i like it when the little things make me happy. not only were there 20 minute classes today, but i left early to get my mm favorite Punch Pizza. talk about yummay. and then i went to barnes and noble. for my love of bookstores and such, you know how we do. went back to my house..cleaned out my car except [doorbell hold on] now my trash has been put into katies trunk. hmm. drove around a little bit. then went to practice. 6 hours. it didnt feel that long though, which was also good. i was pondering how the hell i would be able to make it through. no worries. it wasnt that bad. and then mmm i got to use marma's shampoo thats makes me think of my childhood, and that also made me happy. then my brother picked me up from practice..which made me happy seeing as though i dont see him all that much anymore. and then. my moms picking me up mm cupcake mix yay with  chocolate frosting that i will ever so excitedly bring over to the team sleepover tomorrow. woot woot. cupcakes are my favorite. chocolate cupcakes are my favorite favorite. and charlie,  you made my day . no im serious. there isnt anything i love more than getting 35 fresh exciting new cd's..except maybe the previously mentioned chocolate cupcakes..but you get the point. AND it was a double the pleasure because i like paper bags and that black tape reminded me of my childhood as well. seeing as though i used to play with it all the time because it would stick but you could rip it apart easily. so thanks for the awesome package. yay. :D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D:D im not sure how to say thank you enough...  its been a good day. gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it does.  life sucks. but at least there is saturday. yes, saturday will keep me breathing for now. someone said i was beautiful today. too bad it was me :X i digress. and will now end this blog with a pathetic little depressing song that i love. so, booyah grandmother. [cue pathetic little depressing song] which just so happens to have a lot of charm to it. i love it.  All of the king's horses and all of the king's men. Couldn't pull my heart back together again. All of the physicians and mathematicians too. Failed to stop my heart from breaking in two. 'Cos all I need is you, I just need you. Yeah you got the glue so I'm gonna give my heart to you. I had a premonition, a movie in my mind, confirming my suspicions of what I would find. It followed me to L.A., down to Mexico, came in through the back door at the start of the show. Still all I need is you, I just need you. Yeah you got the glue so I'm gonna give my heart to you. Oh was a perfect day. Oh in a perfect way, you know, something had go, you left me high, you left me low. Now as I lie in pieces, and wait for your return, the sun upon my forehead it burns baby burns baby burns. An eye on all my horses, you've slept with all my men. I'm never gonna get it together again. Still all I need is you, I just need you, I just need you. Yeah you got the glue, so I'm gonna give my heart to you. Yeah you got the glue And there's nothing I can do. Yeah you got the glue So I'm gonna give my heart to you.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Goodnight Moon, goodnight mittens, goodnight socks and kittens, goodnight green eggs and ham.. okay okay maybe i got a few of those switched around with the clever Dr. Suess..but i digress. the point it, Goodnight Moon is a great book. infact, one so great that i have now titled and continued to write about as i begin to get off track. i promise im back in the saddle again i swear. what i am trying to say is that alot of things reminded me of my childhood today.. there was this smell when we were on our way to mmmm mexian buffet after the play mmm..it was kinda sweet but now i cant remember. it just kind of, triggered my thoughts and i went back for a second. and its not the acid i swear because i havent tripped off that for months. :X and then there was mara's shampoo after practice. that reminded me of the old SLP rec center looker rooms. i guess one might think that looker rooms and/or gyms represent the smell and godforsaken feeling of being trapped in a sock [coughcoughmaracoughcough] but it was good smell. a nice, clean, unsock smell. kind of fruity. and then i got to hear of mara's horrible story. and when i say horrible i mean like walking in on an old man while showering nakkie...which so happens to be what happened to her. hot. and that also triggered the thought of me loosing my mom in Walgreens..but thats a different story for a different time. and then. anna got mad at me in practice. said i was spoiling her [annoying] fun of dropping the tapper and then swimming to it and picking it up, repeatedly. i think i actually deserve a thank you on that one. and then i made fun of the retard stairs in the shallow end. muah ah ah. theres just something about big, yellow, plastic stairs that get me everytime. oh jeez. this, is getting long and quite sickly. and now i will leave you all to whither on the vine! until tomorrow when i update..of course...  :D   *bows*ash
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i like how i was really scurred today at practice. no honestly, really scared. coach bust can be a real big loser sometimes. she intimidates me. and i guess if you have been keeping up with my postings you will know that when people intimidate me i become shy. and i really like when she bitches at me and says that i should be real embarrased with my swimming at this point and then i slid my goggles on and sink under as my eyes swell up with tears...yeh i guess alot of us do that. and it makes me laugh. anyway..all my routines are written so its a start.. :X my stummy hurts right now. owie. i got a feildtrip tomorrow yay. mm a play and then some mexian food. yummay. and then practice. booooooo. :'[ an then home. and i also really like how i dont have a car right now. ive been gettin the shaft with this car. no me gusta. im depressed. my boobs hurt ow. i have a really big bruise on my knee from when i ran into my door :X my hair feels like straw. at least ive got dem cd's to look forward to, right? maybe? yeah.   goodnight  moon gusgus  [thanks for the comment. me gusta.]  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the reason why i...  listen to music: i guess it seems like there is a song for every emotion that i have. it helps me get through everyday shit that is my life. wake up every day for school: i dont have a choice have the friends i have: they are there for anything, and can relate to me in more than one aspect of life. but they are different enough to keep things interesting. love the way i love: because if i love you i do anything and everything to make sure you know it. am optimistic: im not. id like to be, but too many things have influenced me to think other ways. am pessimistic: because thats the way my life tends to go. am contradicting: because im a scatterbrain and usually dont make linear statements.  am so hard to figure out: because my emotions have a mind of their own. am different: because thats the way i like to be. different. hate myself: because sometimes i dont understand even myself. love myself: because when you know me like i do, you will too. [how was that for a contradiction, eh?] hate people: they dont tell me like it is. love people: they are the best escape for the harsh brutality that is my life. interested in ______ : science and psychology. it provides exploration into how things work. i figure it will be a challenge considering lord knows i have no idea how anything works and why these days.  my parents... hate me because: apparently im not what they want me to be. love me because: ive got more personality than anyone they know. are idiots when: when they cant understand who i am. are wonderful when: they let me leave the house. err buy me things too. show that they love me by: obvious signs of affection. they are: funny they make me: laugh cry, hide myself in my room until i can leave. they help me: get through some of the toughest situations.  why i'm afraid of... the world: im not myself: im not my family: they will never really understand me. my friends: im not humiliation: because, its humiliating expectations: i dont meet them reputations: im not the unknown: because it is unknown the dark: not the end: not the degrees of my personality:not i'm happy because: im not happy right now. except looking forward to this weekend. i'm sad because: my life sucks right now i'm angry because: my life sucks right now i'm depressed because: my life sucks right now i'm suicidal because: i think suicide is selfish but justifiable i'm homicidal because: im not i'm afraid because: i dont want to be by myself i'm shy because:people intimidate me. i'm outgoing because: it makes me feel like i can do anything i'm brave because: it makes me feel like i can do anything i'm cowardly because: i dont own up i'm funny because: thats who i am. suck it. :D i'm likable because: you tell me? i'm despicable because: i just dont give a shit the one tiny thing that could change your view on me forever: you dont know me until you make the time to.  my greatest fear is of _________. being by myself. right now included. the thing i love most in the world would have to be _________. music. the reason i have guilty pleasures and continue feeling guilty about them is because: i dont feel guilty about it.. if I could change one thing about myself, i would: more outgoing and not be so afraid to make mistakes. not be such a pussy. if i could change one thing about the world i would: get rid of judgments.  when i die, i'll miss...  this the most: the sun. music. some people. this the least: certain people and situations that really sucked. worry about: nothing not even think about: anything. if i were trapped in a burning building and had everything that i could ever want available to me, and i had thirty seconds to make up my mind on what i would do right before i had to die, i would..: kiss you  what means this to me... love is: needed hate is: unnecessary fear is: what i have risk is: always there triumph is: domineering happiness is: splendid deception is: horrible lies are: unnecessary society is: judgemental failure is: always present life is: too short death is: a final escape sadness is: seemingly always there. truth is: great.  anything that has occurred to me while i filled this really long thing out probably fits into this category: reflections on myself include: i need to make some changes. or hope for some really good ones sometime soon. reflections on my friends include: they are my life personified. reflections on my family include: i cant forget where the heart is. reflections on society include: has too many stereotypes reflections on living include: i need to start doing a better job at it  some of them i left from emily. because they were just too splendid to erase. splendid.   gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after a long and very busy night of scooping ice cream and filling out lists on this here blog im thinking i might take a little break from those. i made 12.40 in tips last night. by far the most ive made thus far, mind you. summer is going to be busy there but whatev. im a thinkin i may get a second job just for shits and giggles. you know how we do. i mean, i cant work the corner for the rest of my life :D anyway..im going to be pickin up my florida pictures today yay. im thinkin that ive got some nice shots  of me and steph and that one guy on the beach that looked like a dark chocolate bar. and yay for all of the parasailing pictures that turned out. and woo hoo the 50 year old Ty Pennington, im sorry hannah. muah ah ah. :x weve only got like, i dunno. 30 something days left of school? i can not wait. ive got so much planned for this summer its not even high-larious. i have nothing more to say. my apologies.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. First Name: ashley 3. Middle Name:marie 4. Hair Style: shoulder length choppy layers dark brown with bleached chunks and occasionally a little pink and green when im feelin it. you know how we do. 5. Eye Color: green with brown chunks. 6. Height: 5'5" 7. Location: minnesota 8. Birthday: feb 3. 9. Zodiac Sign: aqua 10. Do you have a girlfriend/boyfriend?: nope. 11. Do you have a crush?: as always.  Favorite... 1. Favorite Animal: mm i like manatees :D 2. Favorite Sport: baseball, tennis, hockey. 3. Favorite Color(s): yellow black and red 4. Favorite Friend(s) Offline: i dunno, the patniz i guess 5. Favorite Friend(s) Online: there really is only one person i talk to online these days..soo...:D 6. Favorite Song(s) fascinating new thing 7. Favorite Movie Quote: say hello to my little friend 8. Favorite Store: bookstores. 9. Favorite Feeling: loved 10. Favorite Shoe: the stiletto heeled bitch boots with faint cowgirl stitching that makes me giggle 11. Favorite Scent: i like the smell of coffee. i like the smell of clean laundry. i like the smell of rain and ocean and fresh flowers. im a girl, what can i say. 12. Do You Wear Make-Up?: lipgloss, mascara, out the door. 13. Which is more important, personality or looks?: personality 14. What kind of personality do you like in a guy/girl?: laid back 15. Do you move fast or slow in a relationship?: slow ..i guess. 16. What is your idea of the perfect guy/girl?: ugh, i could never answer this honestly, realistically. i'll be wrong. 17. Would you ever ask someone out?: if i were afraid of them getting away. 18. Do you prefer blondes or brunettes: um, i dunno. 1. What is the first thing you notice about someone?: their voice 2. When's the last time you cried?: well i-i..i whimpered today at practice.. 3. What do you want to be when you grow up?: happy 4. Do you sleep with stuffed animals?: no 5. Do you want children?: yes. 3, a boy being the oldest. i dont really like little girls. but if i have on you better count on her being smacked around a little. no offspring of mine are going to be little shits. 6. How far have you gotten?: west - california. south - florida. north - canada. east: raleigh NC. but based on the question above and proceeding this question im not sure that was the answer they are looking for. :X 7. Do you like someone right now?: yeah 8. Do they know?: do they ever 9. Do you have a best friend?: yes  Within the last 24 hours, have you.. 1: Had a serious talk?: mmm prolly 2: Hugged someone? yes. 3: Gotten along well with your parents?: meh. 4: Fought with a friend?: yes  Do you like to.. 1: Give hugs?: i....am not a big fan of body contact, thx. 2: Give back rubs?: now i do have to say that i give a mean back rub like its no bodys business. 3: Take walks in the rain?: aww.sappy stupid couple shit. but yeah, on accident. it wasnt supposed to rain. i like walking right away after its rained. when everything is so...fresh.. 4: You ever have that falling dream?: frequently and it scares the noodles out of me 5: What is on the walls of your room?: green stripes 6: When you chew gum, what kind?: i usually run out of gum really fast...seeing as though i always need to be chewing something. but i guess: mints though. eye-watering strong ones! 7: Do you use chap stick: yup  In the last month have/did you.. 1. Drink?: mmm no i-i-i-dont think so. 2. Smoke?: nope. 3. Drugs?: nope. 4. Have Sex?: pfft. nope. 5. Made Out?: mmm, in the last month? it was a little before that i think. 6. Go on a date?: nope. 7. Go to the movies?: indeed 8. Go to the mall?: oh god. stupid mall rat, what can i say? i get bored.. 9. Realized you hadn't talked to someone you wish you had?: yes :( 11. Been on stage?: no thank god 12. Been dumped?: no 13. Had someone be unfaithful to you?: no 14. Watched The Smurfs?: no 15. Hiked a mountain?: no 16. Made homemade cookies?: yumm and yes. 17. Been in love?: who knows anymore  More stuff.. 1. Are you popular?: hell. no. 2. Are you pretty?: fuck if i know 3. Do you have your own phone line?: no 4. What is your favorite word to say?: spina bifida  5. What is your favorite phrase to say?: wanta fanta 6. What are you doing right now?: drinking my smoothie. since i found an old piece of crusted food on my spoon. yulk. 7. What song are you listening to?: running blind. 8. What are you wearing?: black work shirt and some comfy pants  1. Cold or hot?:cold so i can cozy up. 2. Lace or satin?: lace. satin seems so cheap porn 3. Blue or Red?: red 4. New or old?: depends. usually old. 5. Rain or snow?: rain 6. Give or receive?: i always say give. but lately i think i have received much more than i've given. 7. Wool or cotton?: cotton 8. Rose or Daisy?: daisy 9. Private school or public school?: uhh..public 10. Chocolate milk or plain milk?: chocolate yum my favorite :D 11. Celsius or Fahrenheit?: F 12. Spring or Fall?: fall 13. Inny or outty?: inny. outties are sooo gross. 14. Now or then?: now 15. How many fingers am I holding up?: .... 16. Scent?: lily of the valley 17. English or Math?: english 18. Bath or shower?: shower 19. Bedtime phrase?: hm.. none 20. Self-stick or lick?: lick 21. Cursive or print?: print 22. Do you like surprises?: very much so. 23. Paranoid or Cautious?: cautious 24. Heights or Crowds?: crowds 25. Half-full or half-empty?:half empty. lord knows im a pessemist. 26. Top or bottom?: top 27. Do you/Would you dye your hair?: yes, i do but only on the bleached parts. 28. Speeding or running red lights?: ooh, speeding :X 29. Gold or silver?: silver 30. Bad habits?: criticism 31. Piercings?: ears 32. Erogenous Zone(s)?: oh, BRAIN :P 33. talker or listener: listener. unless its something im passionate about. 34. Snore or talk?: oh god. talk. 35. What do you wish you'd done?: shut up 36. Fetish: n/a 37. Do you have one of THOSE voices?: eh....i dunno, you tell me. in my head it sounds ok.. 38. Jammies or naked?: jammies. unless its a sleepover.. oh, i jest. 39. Neurotic or psychotic?: neurotic like whoa 40. Do you talk to yourself?: yes 41. Will you ever do one of these again?: obviously.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is the last thing you watched on TV? band of brothers  WITHOUT LOOKING, guess what the time is 3:55  Now look at the clock, what is the actual time? 3:53  With the exception of the computer, what can you hear? the shower and the pipes of godsmack  When did you last step outside? What were you doing? about 10 minutes ago when i came home from katies and synchro  Before you came to this website, what did you look at? charlies list  What are you wearing? jeans, socks, underoos,  a shirt and a hoodie.  Did you dream last night? yep.  When did you last laugh? about an hour ago  What is on the walls of the room you are in? mah paintings.  Seen anything weird lately? does my reflection count  What do you think of this quiz? genious.  What is the last film you saw? band of brothers.   If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first? cds.  Tell me something about you that I don't know: i can imitate a baby cry like its no bodys business.  If you could change one thing about the world, regardless of guilt or politics, what would you do? no more clocks.  Do you like to dance? ive been known to get jiggy wit it on occasion  George Bush: ass.  Imagine your first child is a girl, what do you call her? ruby may..or jersey  Imagine your first child is a boy, what do you call him? jake  Name Four Bad Habits You Have: im too shy, too pessimistic, i dont like to work and i can have a short temper  Name Four Things That You Wish You Had: more cd's, more relationships. i dunno what else.  Name Four Scents You Love: kirra, rain, clean everything and the ocean.  Name Four Things You'd Never Wear: anything with the name hollister, shit, snow suits with suspenders,   Name four things you are thinking about right now: creative answers, how i dont want to work, waffles, and a phone call.  Name Four Things That You Have Done Today: woke up, drove to practice, swam, made a bazillion phone calls.  Name the Last Four Things You Have Bought: (Food not counting) some clothes, a pen, gas and gum.  Name Four Bands/Groups Most People Don't Know You Like the rolling stones, guns n roses, ac/dc and rob zombie  Name Four Drinks You Regularly Drink: water, chocolate milk, diet coke and lemonade  yay for these. because i like 'em.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. What do you keep under your bed: dirty mags 2. What do you keep on your nightstand: an orange bear from alaska, cell phone, alarm clock, a pink tin with pennies in it and some carmex 3. What CDs that are in easy reach:i dont really have any within reach. they are all put away in this really kewl cd case that grabs them for me and schtuff. yep. 4. What stuff do you do every morning:i get pissed off because im tired, then sleep until about 7:15. crawl into the shower get dressed dry hair and off on a jet plane by 7:40. 5. What stuff do you put on your face every morning: eyeliner, mascara, carmex 6. What stuff do you have in your handbag?: phone, wallet, massive amounts of pennies, cologne samples from pac sun mmmm some carmex and an extra change of clothes :X 8. Longest time you've stayed out of the country and where?: mexico..pfft for like a day. in tijuana. 9. One thing you're grateful for today:the ability to start over when needed. and i guess some people that make everyday a little bit easier. 10. Favorite high school memory?: i have too many. i guess having the uncontrolable giggles in class. those good days when you see someone in the halls and realize that youre still smiling like 5 mintues later. yep.. 11. What's your dream wedding?: i dont really think about the wedding, more like the concept. 12. Favorite quote?: i wish i was as invisible as you make me feel. err..i wish i was as invincible as you make me feel. that last one was modified by charles. 13. What are some of your weird preferences?: i dont know how to answer this one. 14. TV character you want to be? : stewie 15. Weird sleeping habits?: i dream lucidly. 16. What's your favorite song right now?: view from heaven 17. Give a line from any song: so here i go scream my lungs out and try to get to you, you are my only one. 18. Disney songs known by heart: i dislike disney very much. they give kids false hope that the world is somehow more perfect than it will ever be. and for that, i dispise you disney. 19. What's in your wallet, and how much money: license, ulta card, panera values thing idk, northwest card, some synchro things, kirra samples, a devil sticker, coins, movie ticket stubs, twins tickets, and about 200 dollars give or take a few. 20. Your favorite pair of shoes? birkies  21. First five things I'd splurge on if I was a billionaire: cds. 22. What are three of your favorite cartoon characters?: stewie, goofy, and porky. 23. Magazines you read on a regular basis?: seventeen and cosmo 24. Things you wear daily? : pretty much always jeans. in the summer, skirts. t shirts i guess. underwear? eh. sometimes comando is fun too. :O :X just playin. 25. Movies You'd Watch over and over again: willy wonka, clockwork orange, band of brothers, jaws. 26. Five bands that you couldn't live without?: incubus, taking back sunday, dashboard, apc, hoobastank. same as emily. but there are a many more. 27. One thing you could spend the rest of your life with?: this one person. 28. About 5 years ago I: i was 12. and still in the 12 year old ugly stage. About 2 years ago I: i was 15. hoping for change, and never got it. About 1 year ago I: i was 16 and thought i knew how i wanted to live my life. 29. Today I: actually know how i want to live my life and desperately seeking the guy that wants to play mini golf with me. 30. Tomorrow I will: be the same as today..i suppose... 31. Five snacks I enjoy are: nature valley trail mix bars, mountain best,  cheeze its, fruit snacks and water 32. Five games I like are: solitare, paintball, the question game, monopoly, and cribbage 32. Things I can't live without: music, music, music. select friends. music. oxygen. sleep. 33. Five things I'd buy with one thousand dollars: music, an ipod, some books and a new cd player. 34. Top locations I want to run away to: 1). this one place 2). chicago 3). florida 4). rome 5). your house.  and im spent.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sometimes alls you need is a little change to make it all better. i got my hairs cut today. i really like it. emily was kind of an inspiration, but not really as its the same hairs cut i had in the start of the summer. and now on to more [useful] information.. today was a really gouda day..i mean, the whole not having homework in more than one class kinda rocked..plus it was free burrito day today at chipotle. im not a real big fan of burritos de chipotle but meh. it was free, i was hungry, and ashley doesnt pass that up. is it gross that after that we ran over to subway for free cookie day? yep. anyway. got back to school, went to the meet, we won, woo hoo. im quitting next year, goddamnit. ran home, got a check, ran to the mall, got my hair cut came home checkout the status of the Twins whom i will gladly be seeing tomorrow evening with my bobble buddy yay upper G.A. here we come! heres what stephanie said to me tonight: [sn witheld] pluper m o o (9:06:24 PM): and i got my hair cut tonight! pluper m o o (9:06:30 PM): its really short. i like it though. [stephanie] (9:06:31 PM): butch? pluper m o o (9:06:36 PM): lol [stephanie] (9:06:40 PM): i knew u'd come around pluper m o o (9:06:43 PM): hahhahhahahhahah [stephanie] (9:06:54 PM): i mean... [stephanie](9:07:06 PM):    ohh man. so steph, when are you going to pic out your  tuxedo  for prom, eh? ;)  good times. i love our sense of humor. its too bad most people dont get it..  goondite gusgus lmao.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think its really pathetic that ive somehow still managed to want something so bad and its really not even there. sad. yep. a many thanks for the phone call from sea saw..i think ive got some plans to hit up north sometime soon. and i hear that she has been talking to someone about me... :x is that good? i dunno. thats the problem. but i hear my g-ma was excited to get my postcard. i feel bad that i never see her but im so different than every one of my relatives. what can ya do. i did some thinking today while taking out the garbage. it reminded me of the sunday i came home from florida. and it made me sad. so now im in a sad mood. and practice blew ass. anna, shut up. today was  bad day. no likey. and you just made it worse. not anna, you. i like how everyone is talking about prom. oh, the hooplah. make it stop. because, frankly my dear, im getting pretty sick of it all. maybe if i was a senior and had a date and/or boyfriend all would be well with the world. but we all know thats just hogwash anyway.  i really like my vocabulary this blog. nothin like chewin the fat with old friends. hit me up love, everyday. 867-5309  goondite gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ive inaugurated a new reader on this little journal here. say hello to everyone, cat. >.  ive got quite the list going now. yay. and im in college writing. boredom has set in. this is such a slacker class. yep. its like that. correspond later-----we shall...   gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its amazing how many people you can meet while reading at caribou.  i hit up the library tonight. 8) ive been itching at getting a couple of these books for what seems like forever now and instead of dishing out 60 or 70 bucks i decided to see what i could find else where. didnt find all of them, but now i have more than i need for my spare time reading. i used to read alot. allthefrickintime. thus far, i havent read in quite sometime and i really miss it. i like being able to burry yourself in a really good book. and i like things that really make me think. whether it be a movie or a conversation. i guess miraculous things tend to get me going. and i like hearing stories. and i pretty much only watch documentaries now. i want someone who is going to want to watch documentaries with me. yep thats what would make me happy. and someone to have an actual deep, meaningfull conversation with. thus far i have neither. im down 2 strikes. nevertheless im excited and/or pumped to read these books. ive heard err read some great things about them. i saw something funny today in us history. it made me think of something, then made me think of a conversation, then made me think of someone, then made me think about how much i would hate it if someone ever did that to me, then i thought that pfft like hell i would even get that far in the first place, and then i was sad because now i have realized that i dont even have anything going for me to even be  humiliated . but i digress. its funny how guys in cars can make you laugh when they pull up next to you, listening to the same song as you, and singing along to it..just like you are. that made my night. oh metallica.  listening to system of a down gets me pumped. i want to learn to play some mean geetar or something. naturally i would also settle for the Amazing Triangle anytime. i used to play that or the little finger tamboreens in like 3rd grade music class. ick.  goondite gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i like how its only monday. and ive got a bunch to look forward to for the weekend. but i hate that i am missing i want a famous face right now. because i hear that there is some kind of hermie on there tonight. te he. ick. today was actually a very light day. nothing to stressful except the make up work and such which will never get done. hahaha. and i hear that  stephanie picked up the florida pictures. you know, the ones with just me in the frame with my beast of a suitcase [hey it was large and in charge what can i say] and me doing some kind of...face....in BOTH of them. yes, plural, there is more than one god forsaken picture. no me gusta.  but i AM excited to see the ones with us in the wet suits :O :X sick lol  very excited though, very excited. im going to have to get some of these twins game lined up for me and my bobble buddy. get those good times-a-rollin again. yay for baseball. no yay for mientkiewicz and his bush on his chin. thats a no no. im not a real big fan of facial hair. but what ever toots your horn, i guess....  this is getting gross. goodbyes. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's a beautiful sky tonight and if you were by my side then we could share it but you are gone. So come at me with your moon and burn me in the stars cause nothing matters anymore. If I could only see you now for about an hour maybe just a minute just to ask What has she got that I don't have? Is it her brown eyes? I know blue eyes get boring but I'll wear dark glasses all the time and hey if you want me to, I'll take a knife to my own bright eyes. If I could only see you now for about an hour maybe just a minute just to ask what has she got that I don't have? Is it her brown eyes? Well, I'll give you a thousand reasons that tonight  you should grant me this one wish. Like the one year of my life that I gave to you and now you put me through hell. You break me up. I should hate you, but I can't replace you in my heart. Why am I so pathetic? I don't get it why you won't return my calls. Can't you look at me once? And please if you got a minute, enjoy this lonely sky with me. It'll swallow us whole if we only let it. If I could only see you now for about an hour maybe just a minute just to ask what has she got that I don't have? Is it her brown eyes? Well, I'll give a thousand reasons  that tonight you should grant me this one wish. Like the one year of my life that I gave to you and now you put me through hell. You break me up. If this sky's going to eat us then I'd like to be digested  into a million pieces with you.  I'd love to be scattered to hell with you. To hell with you.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate it whenever i see something...or someone..and want something so bad. didnt actually ever think that i ever needed a boyfriend. but i figure i would be so much happier if i did. and the thing is..i meet alot of guys. from a lot of different places. but nothing ever goes anywhere. and it makes me sad. and i tend to not understand the difference between me and most girls. and when things happen that i dont understand, im double sad. and i guess i just dont get it. its like everytime i meet a guy im never on the same page as them. but when i want someone or something, its never there. i dont like it at all. im 17. i want a boyfriend. i want someone thats going to return feelings as well as give them. i want someone thats going to want to make the effort to understand me. if everyone else can find someone...why cant i?  my ears are still ringing from last night. homework calls.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the night has come and gone so fast...ive been looking forward to tonight for about a month now and its all over in 2 stinkin hours. nevertheless, i had so much fun...after all i always do.   i had synchro this morning at 8 fucking 30 in the morning. to just sit there and eat my donut that i thought i really wanted...until i spit it up like an hour later. no fun. and it didnt taste any better coming up. got yelled at a little by coach bust and that was that. got home, got ready, chatted online as always...had a nice little run with the answer every question with a question game that i so fatefully blew..tis all gouda. ran over to ridgedale with my drankin patna but didnt see anything worth while..so we skid over to southdale so i could check out those cool ipods that both emily and meghan have..and i also saw something else of emilys but i will have to talk to her about that one :X after a long fit with these stoooopid strap buckle things on this certain undergarmet i was going to wear, i purchased some 1.99$ scissors. now im thinking, ok. scissors are meant to cut stuff, no? so wouldnt it make sense that there would be some sort of..blade...in them? yeh. dont fool yourself. because these ones didnt. they were just...plastic pieces...and it pissed me off. found some better ones, cut the shit off, and picked up porker #1. changed in the car like sluts and ran over to said destination for yes, a fun time. it was weird. in a really really good way. and atiekay finally got a little taste of it. muah ah ah yay :D ahhhhhh man. i had the best time. i hope you did too.  so...any lan parties go down tonight? :P fill me in.  my mom only buys this generic kind of pop now. instead of Mountain Dew...its Mountain Best  wtf? gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mission accomplished today, on some aspects. im still missing the vital link though. MOA was busy holy mother of pearl. walked around a bit went into some stores and such...spent a nice chunk of my money left over from florida and talked to the Vans guy again. he always suckers us. but this time we opted to not stay in there for so long....:X  ive got my 12 bucks for tonight. yay. although im not as excited. i mean i am, but from what they have said im not sure of what to expect. its okay though. theres always tomorrow night for it :D  i wish someone would write a song about me, one in good clean fun. i think i would like that.  im going now gusgus 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      college writing is a bust. and im never going to get anything done in here with my partner in crime. shh shh shh.  joe mauer is out for a month. *tear* what else could possibly go wrong with them in the first week of the season :( its okay though because as long as we have cootie and our posters alls well.. and people need to learn how to update blogs and/or live journals. because i like to stick my nose in other peoples lives. and i can perfectly justify that, because as long as i dont have a life, i can live vicariously through yours. some people are just plain great writers. me gusta. and i think ive found a way to hack...hack into...shh shhh shh it hasnt happened yet, all i need it a zip code. *angel face* im excited. its thursday, which is like a friday, no? because weve got this long weekend. and if i see yet aNOTHER goddamned marshmellow PEEP im gonna fuckingflip. i dont like peeps. at all. no tastey good.  but, ive got some things planned for the weekend and no synchro tomoz [sick] so i get a jump start at it. woot. woot.  im bored. and its only 12:15. thats it. one more hour and a test and im gone. home. to come back online for no reason because no one will be on because everyone is still at school [i said that all in one breath]. so thats it. oh happy day.  scatterbrain. not the song, me. gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and isnt that the truth. god.  i hate school. i honestly motherfuckingdo. and i hate home. i hate italot. i dunno...maybe its because of all of those motherfucking comments all the time. im annoyed. thank god for this llloonngg weekend. par.tay. right.  motherfuckersynchroissomotherfuckinghardrightnow.   im tired. that is all.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tis the season for something to actually live for...ahem, baseball has begun. and last night was home opener. oh, the memories of last year.  jaque jones slurred speech and larry. oh larry how you gave us so many chuckles. [tee hee] and who can forget about steve erickson? dem polar bears at 5 in da morn. cell phone reflections, oh lordy. but we lost. and i DO remember that.  so last night.....i know i know, i was about to lose hope. its not often that i do that, but they were down 0-4 up to the 7th inning. twas quite dry on the twins side. i think we had like 3 hits. kind of pathetic for my twinkies. but i digress. because with that NICE walk from mauer [hubba hubba] and some hits by cuddyer with a nice crack by the Bosskie to left field really put us on the map. so i was happy. and im impressed with Nathans solid pitching, too. Rincon had a nice close. i liked yesterday, i likeditalot.  11 innings, well done boys.  im in love with joe. coughcough[mauer]coughcough speaking of, JJH, you are an ass. yes, you are. i think i will recap on spring break at a later time. yessum, a later time. theres just too much to type. call me scatterbrain. thats weird.  thanks for the comments you left. youre a pal.mmmhmm thats enough of that. i want to go to all the twins games this year. i want season tickets. but i can not afford them. please take me. kthx.  amtrak has finally departed. ashm      
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.kissesarefree.blogspot.com  its a new day. out with the old, in with the new. ^aka, new blog. see you there.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      god i dont even know what the hell to do anymore. and im so fucking mad right now. and im sitting here shaking. and my skin is all tingly and fuckin shit i dont fucking know what the hell to do. when im sitting here fucking hyperventalating because i dont even know how to sit here and fucking explain myself to anyone. i want someone to talk to fucking A i do. i need my old friends that actually gave shit about anything that had to do with my life and who would actually think and care to ask how i was doing. i want my friends that i could just fucking call up any fucking time i wanted to and they wouldnt care. i was those back. i want them to not sit there and nod their fucking head but cause they dont understand what the fuck im saying. sakjhfiudsahflkjsdhfkjahdsfjkhskjdhfjskdhaflkjf djfsahjskdhfjklsadhfjhdsfjkhsdjfhdsjhfjshdafjhdsjfkhsdjnjkhfdjskhfdjhdsfkjhdsjfkhsdjnfjksldh fjsadytisduroiewsdnf,msdnfsiudhjsdfjsdf. and after i got all worked up, sees asthough i blacked out and something really is fucking wrong with me. i want it all to go away i want it all to fucking stop and i want my friends to be there and so far im pretty much down three. fuckjsdhfjisdyhfjhsajvhs.   fffffffffffUCK.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      theres something so comforting about reading coodies diary. :P ohyes, and seeing a little picture of joe mauer with his mother at the annual mother-son formal. im sorry. thats weird. i get real excited, too, about posting with this new format.  yep.gah.ive got modest mouse stuck in my head. and hot hot heat too. i hate coming home and smelling of ice cream. its a sickening smell. quite nastay. im investing in an ipod.  when i get the money, yeh. its been too long to not be able to listen to anything. i think im going to mexico. and florida again maybe. and katies cabin fo sho. conan was funny last night. the bells gonna ring. what a scatterbrain, i tell ya.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       :[ 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lookie! new blogger. yay. :P
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just. i just dont know. i have nothing to say, because whatever i do type will most likely make me sad.  so i think im just going to type what i feel in terms of lyrics.  Between an overload of information and a striving for a pure dedication I find myself looking for the exit sign.  see your pretty face in the sunshine in the morning after staying up all night..  I  want to wake you just to hear you   tell me it's alright and all I want to be is too much sometimes for me..  good morning baby  I hope I'm gonna make it through another day  good morning baby  I hope I'm gonna  make it  through another day  see the stars and all the planets  fly the great wide world and have it all  yeah better get a ticket better get in line  I'm praying now for beautiful weather   take a car and drive forever   but I'm only ever sitting at the traffic light  and all the world to see is too much  Sometimes for me  Good morning baby  I hope I'm gonna make it through another day  good morning baby  I hope we're gonna make it through another day  and when you rise you'll find me here  and see myself reflected there  a little room becomes an everywhere.  are those right? they were from memory but my memory is fading by the minute. so shoot me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its the only way to eat it. yum. left over. nice and cold. tonight started off alright...but progressively got worse. it was good after synchro, good after gettin ready [no Sally Hansen problems this time, mind you] it was even good when me and my dad went out to grab a bite to eat. it was good up until we were in the parking lot. god. i knew it wasnt gonna be like last weekend. i think i need a break from it. too much in too little of time. and i swear, he. is. retarded. its cool and all. like, the situation and everything. but....i dunno. his friend is a skeeve. a skeeve who wears jean shorts with knee high socks and little sneakers. gah. then! ohh we felt really bad. there was this nice looking clearly intoxicated young man leaving...and falling down the stairs. i felt bad. we watched him stumble around and eventually fall over in the parking lot. obviously in need of assistance..my drankin patna and i booked it out of there and helped him. it gave me a warm feeling inside. :) and then..uht..he was gettin his car keys out. oh-ho-ho-hell no, mister. we made sure he could get a ride home. that was about the highlight of my evening thus far. and ive got work tomorrow. blah. and mucho tarea.  sugsug
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the title seems appropriate for this evening. even though i had to modify the lyrics a titch bit.. went to see the talent show tonight. its weird, and quite obvious what people are your friends. it just seems so..unnecessary. but whatever, right. from what i saw the talent show blew. maybe it was all of those singers that really got me ready to leave. i dunno. coulda been Tim on the piano...he was good though, yep. left and went to ridgedale for obvious reasons that of Big Bowl and their lettuce wraps yumm but they had a 30 min waiting period that i really wasnt going to sacrifice my hunger for. we got followed. by a nice little group. and let me tell you, offers to fuck me up the ass dont just come around every corner. [literally] but what can ya do. we were stunned, shocked, and ready to hit the mall up sometime soon.. ran to fuddruckers. yum. i love their malts. and burgers. and cookies. and guys that work there :x oh the stories. my milk shake brings all the boys to the yard...da de hum hum la da daaa... ran katie back and now shes off rocking in a rocking chair hahah for her church thing...you know...those damn Rock-A-thons. oh jeez. and then ran to target. ilovetarget. and uhm. it seems as though i like to randomly flash my rear end to those that walk behind me. its not my fault though. there was wind. and the skirts are kinda short [some might say...too short? see previous blog]. and i cant really tell when they are being lifted. until, of course, i hear those whistles... oh god. im sorry if my bottom flashed you tonight.  gusgus
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today blew. i got pissed really easily. i just wanted certain people to please, please just shut the fuck up. plzkthx. nonetheless, the day didnt get any better..seeing as though we had a swim meet. no longer have the option of being conference champions like um..we have been every single year since St Louis Park synchro has started. how terrible. and then, fucker, i get talked to by the coach...on the means of my..skirt..being too short..? uhm, not really. tis very mild to everything else you see today. and katie was wearing the saME skirt! wtf. and yew only say something to me, fucker. fuck you. fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuccccccccckkkkkkkkkeeeeeeeeerrrrrrrrrrrr, no. im not doing it next year either. and now im worked up. and i really need to cry. people sucked today. and by thinking about it im in a pissy mood. when i lick my skin it reaks of chlorine. same after i work too. make it stop. gah!    GG
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Four baseball fans are mountain climbing. Each climber happens to be a rabid fan of a different MLB team. One fan is from Chicago, one from Kansas City, one from Minnesota and the other from New York. As they climbed higher and higher, they argue more and more about, which of them is the most loyal to their particular baseball team. As they reach the summit, the climber from Chicago takes a running leap and throws himself off the mountain yelling, "This is for the Chicago White Sox!" Not wanting to be outdone, the climber from Kansas City throws himself off the mountain shouting, "This is for the Kansas City Royals!” Seeing this, the Minnesota Twins fan walks to the edge and yells, "This is for baseball fans everywhere!” He then pushes the fan of the New York Yankees off the cliff.  Go Twins! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think the school blocked some blogger sites. you know..my list of about 20 that i check every twenty minutes to see if they have been updated. yeh. today was long as h_e_double hockey sticks. let me tell ya. i was falling asleep in mr millers class, too. but not really. he just likes to look at me when i take a really long blink. whats the harm in that? obviously much..because he felt the need to hit me with his pointer stick damnit. >:O synchro sucked. as usual. and weve got a meet tomorrow. tropical dress code pffffft. which also means that i am going to be missing the friends finale. damnit. and i missed the OC tonight AND real world on tuesday damnit. damnit. i ran to target. got a few 'hollers' from a few fellers. it wasnt flattering though..it was just kind of like a skeevey arcade thing i guess. and i swear my whole us history class was there. whoa. ran to ridgedale. caught up on old times.  hes not as bad as usual. :X but it was only for a little bit. i think too much of certain people is overwhelming. and now ive got homework to do. damnit.  gg
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate being the one that invests all of their time in someone. invests everything...everything the person is. into this one being, who doesnt give a rats ass. i hate being the person that thinks theyre doing the right thing but yet everything finds a way to screw itself up. I hate obviously caring about people who really couldnt give a shit about me either way, i hate not being able to make sense of anything. i hate being the one that notices all of the little things about a person...all of the little good things that make them who they are. i really hate that. i hate emotion. i hate being the person who needs someone. i hate being the person who wants to feel needed. i hate all of the stupid stuff that makes me sad. i hate IMing people first. i hate waiting and waiting for a reply. i hate not being noticed. i hate having the things i do not be noticed. i hate being the person who would do anything to be someone but it isnt mutual. i hate being the person that wants a valentine but didnt get one. i hate being the person who always gives out valentines to everyone. i hate seeing couples. i hate wanting to be one. i hate when people dont understand why i think like i do.  i hate feelings. but i really hate when they arent returned.  what a hateful blog.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Theres nothing like getting all excited to go into first hour for the sole purpose of being able to listen to my music and bury myself in my head phones. But damnit, somethins wrong with my cd player now and  tis no gouda. im not even prepared, either. ive got no back ups. this is it. its gonna be hard getting through the day with nothing to listen too. gah! ive got like 3 study halls, too.... i have to work tonight. woot. made 7.73 yesterday in tips. talk about ms. money bags. yeh. its just going to be the drankin patniz tonight. i wont be home until 11. just in time to be really pissed because im extra tired. which means i wont be able to get online. ah the horrors. ive come across some really knee slappin funny blogs lately. from people that dont know i read them..[te he] :D we have 27 days of school left. 27 days to do meaningless shit that wont help my already shitty grades, for shits sake. shit. shits gonna hit the fan when the units get my grades. im bored. emily is gone. which means i could actually be getting shit done. ive opted fo real slacker mode. im slacking off...alone. thats kind of like the losers who get drunk alone. hm. i wanna play frisbee. or tennis.  oooo minigolf. where are some go karts around here...i wanna do that too. i could go for some dr pepper right now. and panera :X let me see if i can find another survey thing... eureka! LAST PERSON WHO... x. Slept in your bed: anna. i wasnt in there too, mind yew. x. Saw you cry: katie x. Made you cry: you x. Spent the night with: katie and anna on saturday. x. You shared a drink with: my brother x. You went to the movies with: oo havent been to the movies in a while. x. You went to the mall with: myself x. Yelled at you: Uh yeah, that'd be an affirmative on the maternal radar. x. Sent you an email: uhm tyler x. You kissed: :X lets just say someone on saturday.  HAVE YOU EVER... x. Said "I Love You" and meant it: Of-fucking-course x. Gotten in a fight with your pet: Does simply whacking it count.. x. Been to New York: nope x. Florida: yessm! x. California: been there, done that. x. Hawaii: nope but i had plans to at one point... :'( x. Mexico: for a day x. China: too many people. x. Canada: of course. x. Danced naked: by my lonesome, yes.  x. Dreamed something really crazy and then it happened the next day: uhm idk. x. Wish you were the opposite sex: god yessum. x. Had an imaginary friend: actually, never really did. i thought kids with imaginary friends were weird and kidding themselves, while setting up a life of unfulfilled requirements and mere disappointments.  RANDOM x. Red or blue: Red x. Spring or Fall: i like both okay. x. Are you bored: gah yes. thats why im doing this dipshit. x. Last noise you heard: pat pat pat pat pat. that's me typing. x. Last time you went out of the state: a month ago or so x. Things you like in a girl/guy: a connection. x. Do you have a crush on someone: yessum. x. What book are you reading now: book of illusions. x. Worst feeling in the world: not needed. x. What is the first thing you think when you wake up: Fuck. x. How many rings before you answer: i dunno. depends on how fucking far i have to walk to answer the dammned thing. x. Future daughter's name: baby girls are brats. x. Future son's name: cambria. err....iowa :P x. Do you sleep with a stuffed animal: I found them to be a burden... they're always falling off and are so odly shaped you can't really get a good enough hold on them. I squeeze my pillows instead. x. If you could have any job you wanted, what would it be: I'd probably have a band just for the fuck of it. x. Are you a lefty, righty or ambidextrous: right x. Do you type with your fingers on the right keys: no. i have my own system. x. What's under your bed: Random shit.  x. Favorite sport to watch: baseball. x. Current Age: 17 x. Siblings: 1 x. Location: minnesota x. College plans: umd... x. Piercings: ears x. Boyfriend/Girlfriend: nope  EXTRA STUFF x. Do you do drugs: meh x. Do you drink: :D x. Who is your best friend: drankin patna for sure. x. What kind of shampoo and conditioner do you use: herbal. what can i say, i have the urge... x. What are you most scared of: being ultimately alone. x. What clothes do you sleep in: tshirt and shorts..i dunno. x. Who is the last person who called you: joe x. Where do you want to get married: anywhere with my husband is fine. x. Who do you really hate: people who stare. gah! x. Favorite number: 3 x. Been in Love: but of course. x. What type automobile do you drive: ford somethin or other x. Are you timely or always late: always early.  x. Do you have a job: yes. x. Do you like being around people: depends. x. Best feeling in the world: having connections. wherever it may be. x. Are you for world peace: It'll never happen. x. Are you a health freak: pfft. i would die for fruit snacks.  STUFF x. Have you ever loved someone you had no chance with: uhm.obviously. x. Have you ever cried over something someone of the opposite sex did: Are you kidding? That accounts for like 85% of what I cry over. x. Do you have a "type" of person you always go after: there seems to be a trend of fuckers fucking me over. x. Want someone you don't have right now: yes. x. Are you lonely right now: not as much, but still a yes. x. Ever afraid you'll never get married: yess :( x. Do you want to get married: yess. x. Do you want kids: 3.  FAVORITE x. Room in house: mine. x. Type(s) of music: rock/punk. x. Band: Currently Coheed and Cambria x. Memory: saturday. x. Day of the week: saturday. x. Color: black white, red green... x. Perfume or cologne: guy smell. x. Month: july.  IN THE LAST 48 HOURS, HAVE YOU... x. Cried: no x. Bought something: Yes. x. Gotten sick: No. x. Sang: Of course. x. Said "I Love You": yes x. Wanted to tell someone you loved them: Yes. x. Met someone new: Yes. x. Moved on: In a sense. x. Talked to someone: Yes. x. Missed someone: Yes. x. Hugged someone: Yes. x. Kissed someone: yes. x. Fought with your parents: hhmm nope. x. Dreamt about someone you can't be with: duh. x. Had a lot of sleep:never enough.  X the ones you have done:  (x) been drunk (x) smoked pot (x) kissed a member of the opposite sex (_) kissed a member of the same sex (_) crashed a friend's car (_) been to japan (_) ridden in a taxi (_) had anal sex (x) been in love (_) had sex in public (_) been dumped (x) shoplifted (_) been fired (_) been in a fist fight (_) had a threesome (x) snuck out of my parent's house (_) been tied up (sexually) (_) been caught masturbating (x) pissed on myself (_) had sex with a member of the same sex (_) been arrested (X) made out with a stranger (x) stole something from my job (_) celebrated new years in time square (_) gone on a blind date (x) lied to a friend (x) had a crush on a teacher (_) celebrated mardi-gras in new orleans (_) been to europe (x) skipped school (_) slept with a co-worker (_) cut myself on purpose (_) had sex at the office (_) been married (_) gotten divorced (_) had children (_) stripped at a party (_) literally crawled to your house drunk, even if just from across the street (x) jumped off a bridge (x) gone surfing (x) had a mullet (x) peed in public  phew. i liked that one..  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a hottie. holler. porker night turned into room full of grinding hottie night. me likey alot. he was hot too, damnit. yum. i wasnt much of a fan of the slobber across my face though, thx. :D no complaints though, no complaints. 0:) yay drankin patna and justin.. that was cool too. thanks for the water. _  ive got so much homework its not even highlarious. ive gotta do 45 notecards and a discovery draft. and ive only got 4 more hours to do it. plus i had the homework from work..pfft fuckit. that took me a long time, too. _  twins lost...? gah. its ok. radke wasnt exactly badke yesterday. [ohh dad] i was thinking that we havent seen andrew at any games so far.. _  only like 25 more days of school or something _  last night was muy exciting. thats all ive got for now. sorry for the shitty blog. _  goodafternoon gusgus
     
    
</post>


</Blog>