<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight was a very good night.  At some point, Adm.'s supposed to get home. This is good.  Tonight was also the first night that we took the boat out this year!! Yes, we're about a month late. Believe me, I would have voted to get the boat out in April if I could.  Things actually went pretty smoothly. Dad had me drive to Kwik Trip with the trailer, that was interesting. If you've got a trailer, you have to find two consecutive pumps open. This was at 5:30, 6 at night. We had a lot of fun there. *eye roll*  Got in the water smoothly. I was the first one in the water this year!!! And I was the first person skiing!! Mark, if you're reading this, we got new skis. They're more designed for high performance - our previous ones are for learning the basics. We still have them, I'm using them to learn to slalom. Which I also did tonight. Right now I'm learning how to control it more, but I'm getting a lot better at switching from two skis to one. One wipeout, they take a lot out of you. I have this rule - unless someone else is clamoring to come out and ski, I don't go in after a wipeout. I never go in until I'm ready to stop. The exhaustion from a wipeout does not rule my skiing time.  It's so amazing, being on the lake. Last year I used to be this dark, shadowy person all the time, and being on the lake made me drop all that and forget it, and just have fun. This year, it's that I stop the acting, stop pretending, and just have fun.  Denise's event is the kneeboard. Mine's waterskiing(always has been, but I dominate on tube, too), but Dad wanted me to give it a go after she was done. Eh, sure, why not? I still had yet to slalom then (I had tried the new skis first - still learning what I can and can't do with them. Note: I canNOT jump the wake edge. If I do, I will flip sideways and fall and smack my hip on the end of the ski. Really hope that doesn't bruise.) So, in one night I learned how to get up on the kneeboard, I actually did get up on the kneeboard (two separate things), I learned how to control it and steer it, and I went out of the wake with it. :D Had one wipeout, but as you go much slower with a kneeboard than skis, it wasn't all that bad. You're also a lot lower, so it was kind of just this sideways half-flip double roll, slip out of the straps thing.   I dropped a ski!! And I stayed up for maybe thirty seconds on one!! It was so cool. Whenever I'm trying to balance, I start counting. I do the same thing when I'm walking fences at FW. Just in measure-counts, usually to eight. Or the way I'd count if I were dancing.   After the above-mentioned wipeout, the really nasty one, I was just worn out. Denise was too cold to go back in, so I went once more on skis, dropped down, and Dad turned the boat off. He let me swim without my life jacket, which I like. The lake is just kind of home in a way I like. I feel like the real me there, without the darkness, without the acting. I'm just too much Amanda to have room for any of that.  So, I swam for awhile. Getting out of my vest, I really feel free in the water. I was laughing after a bit, and I said to Dad, "The World is my Bathtub." Floating, treading - man, I have to get to the pool sometime. I kind of wanted to dive down, but I was so tired I thought I might not be able to find my way back up.   We explored some ends of the lake we've never tried before. Got the boat stuck once. We were checking out a lot of the lake homes. There's one I really like, because it looks like a family actually lives there. It's really pretty, but the structure of it - you can look at the upper windows and think, "Hey, that might be one of the kids' rooms." For most of these houses, it's all about being beautiful and impressive and gorgeous - but you can't really picture anyone living there all the time, just going there for vacation.  I am sunburned, but I think that's from lawnmowing. But between the sunburn, the wipeout, and the candy Denise shared on the way home, I am exhausted, and going to bed.  Dreaming of lakes and trees and wind and sky...and nothing else. Sunset over the hills... 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mom got home last night. I heard her in the kitchen when I woke up, and I just smiled without thinking about it. I like it when Mom's home. Especially after she's been gone for a weekend. She had a race in Chicago, and she was a day late getting back. I think Dad was a little worried about her.  She brought back some prints from one of the art museums she went to. I have The Starry Night. I still have to figure out where I'm going to put it.  Plans for my room keep getting pushed around. Bleah.  I finally ended up waking up around 9:30, went upstairs around 10ish. I know Sid and I were talking late, but that's kind of late for me to sleep. I have to start signing off at 10:30.  Croc and I were talking at one point. Actually talking for a few minutes, not just trading comments. It seems that one of his past girlfriends has found someone new. It's kind of weird - you move on, you're dating someone new, but it still hurts when you realize the person you love(d) is with someone else now.   My sister accused me of hypocrisy on this one. After Eric and I were an item, the Admiral started dating someone new, and it hurt. It would seem that she thought I didn't think Adm. hurt at all when Eric and I got together.   I'm wondering when things changed. I used to sacrifice everything I could, and try to do everything I could to make people happy. Actually, I'm wondering if it changed at all. I still do the same thing, but not with as many people, and I don't always look for the problem the way I used to.  I think that was partly because someone accused me of invading. If I learned nothing else from my mom, it's the right to privacy. Then again, this contrasts with wanting to really get to know a person.   What is my purpose? Why me?   Nothing special, your number just came up. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling fairly content right now. Just watched Prince of Thieves, and sang along with Bryan Adams. We played a medley of songs from this movie for Honors Band, and the sax solo on "I Do It For You" was amazing. I want the music. I want the music.  Somewhat less than happy now. Sheetmusiccatalog.com does not have the solo I want for Alto Sax. Phooey.  Today's shaping up to be a good day. I have the house almost to myself. This is very good. The weather's fairly decent. This is also very good. There's a chance I can get a lot of stuff done today. This is excellent. Mark comes home on Thursday, Eric and I got to see each other last Friday, and Jackie and I might be able to finally get together this week.   I'm trying to figure out why I told Dad Jackie and I were getting together, which is true, but I didn't say anything about Sid being a major part of our plans. There was an incident awhile ago that my dad heard about and didn't really approve of his actions in, but that was months ago. Maybe it's just because Sid's one of the guys, and it didn't seem like a good idea at that moment in time. I think Dad was kind of worn out or something.  It's kind of odd being friends with the seniors. We tend to forget that we're all different ages, so it seems like we should all be going through the same rites of passage at the same time.   Anyway, I have time to dance (which hasn't happened for about a week and a half), practice (week), and get some exercise (three days), and get some work done!! Carpe Diem!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Firstly, I am starting to wax poetic again. I just described Croc's voice as surprising, a little higher than you'd think it would be (almost all of our communications are online, so the few times I have heard his voice, I blink and check again that it actually came out of Croc's mouth), and that he usually has a ghost of a laugh hidden in it somewhere. As though he's either not giving voice to a laugh, or it was there and is gone now.  Of course, I said this TO Croc. I say stuff like this to myself all the time. Croc is not exactly what one would call the poetic type. Flowing, silent warrior type. Actually, every time I try to typify anyone, I end up very confused. Then, after the confusion goes away, I'm very proud of my friends for having too many dimensions to easily typify.  Someone tried to typify me last week. It was something like, "answer five questions, and I can figure out what category you belong in". What kind of a student are you like? What do you do in your spare time? What kind of music do you like? That sort of thing.  I say they just didn't have enough categories. *smirks*  Says the girl who has been listening to "Savages" from Pocahontas, "Dear Jessie" by Madonna, "Be Still" and "Cornelius" (one of the top twenty in Amanda's music) by the Newsboys, "Why God" from Miss Saigon, a techno remix of the theme from Titanic, and now we're on "Wipeout" by the Surfaris.  Cool.  Secondly, I am a little tired. My face feels sunburned, and I had another normal shift today. Interesting that a "normal" shift is eight hours, but a "long" shift is nine.   I had a dream last night. I know that's what started the oddly poetic mood, but I don't remember what it was about. My mind's in someplace cool and green, shaded by trees with the floor hidden by ferns, and I think there's a stream nearby, but I can't remember the dream.  Of course, now my cat's feeling affectionate and has determined that she needs to be on my lap. Eric has made me somewhat less sympathetic to their constant plight of having to get through doors and that sort of thing. Something along the lines of, if you can get a paw through it, you can open it. And she knows she can, she would just much prefer if I opened it for her.  She just gave up in disgust. I think she's sulking under the bed. In about two minutes or so, she'll be back out again, working at it.  A shame all the interesting parts of my life have been declared secret, and so do not appear in this blog. *sigh* Woe to monkeys.  "Oh, great. Irresponsible monkeys."  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Eric came over tonight. I think it was sort of random - we had been batting around the idea of getting together (as always), Mom's gone this weekend for another race, and when we were getting shelving and other things in Roch, I asked Dad if we could rent Prince of Thieves.  (I am a bit of a Robin Hood fanatic. Little known piece of trivia no one knows unless they knew me at twelve in the woods.)  So, after spending a few hours raking (and Pippin playing wild Jungle Cat in the high grass that's left), Eric called. So I asked if he could come over.  Yay. ;)  It was nice to see him again. He's got new horror stories from the third graders, and he smelled like wood smoke, which is nice.  So, after he left, I was pretty warm-fuzzied, and feeling elated and girlish at once. Then I learned that, as Mom is out of state this weekend, ride won't be happening. So, I most likely can't go to something I promised Sid. At least, I think I promised. Memory's been a bit iffy lately. Major letdown - I was really looking forward to seeing him again, and I think he was really anticipating it, too.  I feel really bad now, and really, really want to make it up to him.  First impulse was to call him, but he usually works late certain nights of the week. Bleagh. Amanda is smart. So, dashed off a quick note, and halfway through it noticed that my family had once more (yay, thanks family!) dropped my mail off on my desk. Something else from the U of Montana, Navy, glance up - oh....  Got my ACT scores.  Went into mild shock. They're actually pretty good. In fact, they're on the "really good" end of "pretty good". However, I can't help feeling like, with my friends, it doesn't quite make "good enough".  This is the problem with knowing J.T. and the Phoenix reasonably well. See, some friendships fluctuate in how close they are. And if you're on the high end of one fluctuation during an early part of last summer, they happen to "casually mention" their ACT scores to you.  So...I want to go do a morning run on the 2 1/2 mile loop tomorrow around sunrise, but instead, I have work.  And then I get to let my best friend down.  But I'm still happy somehow inside because I got to see Eric again.   And I'm in elated disappointment and shock over my ACT scores.  As Mark would say, "I need a drink - and I don't drink."
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I met two guys today. For the sake of the pointless anonymity that must ring true with all characters who Amanda somehow felt mattered - Jason and Steve. Which really don't suit them, but whatever.  I was working in Red Wing again. Which I muchly like. There's the free food thing, there's the being-paid-for-ride-time...but most of it's just the people there. Everyone's a lot less tense. And we laugh more. Okay, and RW is a lot slower than Apache. More welcoming atmosphere.  Jason's apartment is shared by himself, Steve, Jason's brother, and Jason's friend. So, Jason and Steve know each other fairly well. It was just a lot of fun working with them, riding with them. Jason's car was a major topic of discussion, also during the ride we went over Everquest (their social life), Steve's katana (that interested me)briefly, hats - mostly a lot on Everquest and the car. It was kind of funny - I had been planning to sleep most of the way there (another thing I love about RW - I get paid to sleep!!), but I really didn't want to miss much of the banter.  They're a lot of fun to work with, too. I had my thirty-two with Steve, and we got to talking about a lot of stuff. I had been pretty sleepy for the first hour or so, and then perked right up. Wiping up a spill under the coffee machine, remembering doing exactly the same thing last year, and hearing Marshall (store manager) glance at it and say, "Looks like Justin had a food fight and lost." For some reason, it was really funny the way he said it, and it made me laugh again. I was a little weird for most of today. Got two major cases of giggles. Jason and I were talking a lot while he was running and I was handing out, and I don't even know what about. Larry was working at RW - it was good to see him. He was everybody's favorite manager at Apache - now he's everyone's favorite there, too. During break, I glanced at the door of the breakroom once to see Jason stalking one of the other guys - with a mop. Like the Grim Reaper, really, that deadpan, except he was grinning.   Steve dated me. Comes up with the little date sticker machine, leaves a sticker on my shoulder while I'm making a lemonade and thinking about making the diet coke, "I dated you." I'm concentrating, and I hear his voice (my first impression of Steve was that he was kind of cute in a way that made me laugh - I met him yesterday after work and he was doing lobby. First words to me? "Do you have anything you wanna throw on the ground?" I was eating outside, and he seemed to be in a pretty good mood about doing lot.), and my brain just goes, "What??" So, that's exactly what I said.  I still have the sticker on my shoulder. :D  We were talking about "How Jason went weird" on the way home. Apparently it was when he decided he didn't care what people thought of him. Then we got onto "How Steve stopped being normal" - apparently he started wearing household objects to school. Something like a mouse, or PS2 controller, around his neck as a tie, and that sort of thing. He's from JM, Jason's Century. He showed me his ring, let me see it. The light in Jason's car was flickering so much, I had to ask what his last name was. It was great, we were all laughing.  It was kind of funny, because sometimes with guys I want to be friends with, I get kind of shy or feel like I have to "act" a certain way. We were just clowns from the McD crew - there wasn't any acting, we were just goofing around.  We got back from RW an hour earlier than we were scheduled to, so the two gave me a ride home. Jason, "I've always wanted to see Byron." We dropped off the other girl who came with us at her store, had a little fun with directions, and got things sorted out after a few minutes.   On the way into Byron, we were talking about the McD's that's supposed to be put in here, what's happening with the five in Roch, and what effect it'll have on our jobs. Facts as of now are that 1)Broadway needs a lot of renovation work done. 2)19th St. is or was blocked off because of the highway project. 3)The people who work at these stores need to be able to work someplace. As it was, every store got a few 19th St. people, and Broadway's going to happen soon. But, the original plan for Broadway called for the Byron store to already be built. The Byron store is not, in fact, already built. So, Broadway's going to be dispersed among the other Rochester stores. Everyone's going to be overstaffed if this happens. Which means everyone's hours will be cut. Which means that, Courtesy Corporation will no longer have to pay certain people for full time, as long as they can cut everyone's hours to under thirty a week. So, it'll be more cost-efficient for McD's to have more employees, if they're paying all of them 5 whatever instead of seven whatever.  I really wish I'd asked either of them for their screen names. It was a lot of fun, and they were really nice. (Actually, Steve was surprisingly nice. Apparently he's been well-trained in courtesy. :) ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Started to feel a lot better yesterday. No head weirdness or dizziness. All I've really got left now is the sore throat and coughing.  Kept waking up during the night. Or rather, what I believe is night. Whenever I want to get up early, I leave the shade up. As I've been trying to get a full amount of rest the last week, it's been staying down, and it's very heavy, so I usually have no idea what time it is.  I have this thing about clocks, all right? The whole system worked fine until Mom decided she liked the one we had in the den, and moved it upstairs. This happens to be the clock I rely on, because one of my programs kills my computer clock, my alarm clock's display is rather smallish, and it's right out through my door.  And yes, I have two other clocks stored somewhere in my room, so I could haul one of those out. I have this thing regarding what time it is, though, and I don't like to have any reminders of it inside my den. Outside is just fine, we can let time pass all it wants in the real world.   Does anybody really know what time it is? Does anyone really care?  We've gotten cable, it would seem. Or, to be correct, "extended cable". TV really isn't my thing so much - movies, yes. TV, no. So, I don't care too much. Except for getting to see reruns of some shows I used to love.   I have one sister who could be referred to as a "chameleon". Gracie and I are all about being our own personalities, clearly defined as unique characters. Needless to say, it disgusts us that we share the house with someone who's cliquey and trendy and does whatever her friends are doing or want her to do. Okay, so we're worried about her losing her identity, or, depending on which friends she's with, getting hurt.   This is not to say that I don't love Boo. I'm fiercely protective of her, there are times when she's the only one who can make me smile, and when I'm feeling lousy, she almost always wants to help or be with me. She used to think I was the coolest person she knew, and wanted to be just like me.  Anyway, right now she's out watching Tom and Jerry. An amusing show in itself, but rather pointless. Which is great after a hard day, but first thing in the morning, come on.   Getting better means I have the energy to have a mood, but I don't feel great enough to make it a good mood. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Been kind of sick the past few days. A lot of tiredness, coughing, and dizziness when I stand. Sore throat, too, but that's something we're used to.  The pixie cough (no relation to The Pixie) came about through a bout with pneumonia last year. Generally, I tend to think I'm okay until the pixie cough starts. It's like my body's forcing the air back out, and the resulting cough is pitched quite a bit higher than where it would normally be.   Supposedly, I have a low voice. I don't know. Whenever I hear it recorded, it's lower and more mature sounding than I tend to think it is. It's said that people are usually surprised as to what their voices actually sound like.   I've been told twice by people in drive-thru, and by a few managers, that I have a really nice voice, or very understanding, or something like that. This, of course, takes me totally by surprise. Pleased surprise, but total surprise.   I'm in choir, and I enjoy singing. Part of singing rather requires that you're singing the right notes. So, how is it that, if my voice is lower than I think it is, it's possible that I land on the notes I'm aiming for?   Should probably go get some fresh air, sunshine, exercise, all that sort of thing. Whee. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Skating is gliding and flowing. I'm not exactly of a graceful, willowy build. The most flattering and accurate way you could put it is that I'm built like Nani. Lilo's sister. Which, on her, is cute. But sometimes I think I was just supposed to be born on skates. I'm a thousand times more graceful, I have fun playing around with them, and every movement is an expression.  Unlike the tripping over carpet things I do at home.  I'm more intensely aware of things. You're watching first the pavement for bumps and sand and changes that you react to before they happen. Secondly, you have a sense of where the things around you are - this is more innate, react subconsciously to it than really concentrating. Third, you're planning out your next path, and keeping in mind the possibility that there will be a car there.  Cars are not, in fact, one's friends when one is skating. There are two intersections that I have to choose between if I'm going anywhere in Byron. Well, anywhere east of my house. I was once almost mowed down by a semi doing something stupid at one of these, and since then I'm antsy about it. I sort of have to swing wide into the lane of traffic - which is a lot busier in the summer than during school.  So, aware of the pavement, how my skates work with it, the sounds my skates are making, slightly reacting to subtle changes, flowing and gliding, and the edge of "Hey, I could get smacked if I do this."   Thanks to a friend, I've been doing less of the "could get smacked" and more of the "might get smacked" endeavors. Apparently he wants me mostly alive for some peculiar reason. I believe he finds me amusing.   Today we swung by the Swordmaster's home. K, I was with Carla. Haven't seen her for awhile. We spent quite some time discussing tails. And some stuff about males, but tails was more entertaining.   Ran into Tim on the way over to the Swordmaster's. Actually, he was running up to us, which is unusual, because Tim is not what one would call athletic. Swordmaster was nicely indifferent to us, as always. He's always either indifferent, or hostile. In my case, it's usually hostile, but he and Carla are friends. Interestingly enough, after spending half an hour with the Swordmaster, we both felt better. We speculate that it's something about striving so hard to be liked, and not being met with a boot out the door. After this, we went to Han's. Han is a lot more tolerant of us. Found ourselves marveling at the Y chromosome again (length of pipe inspires him to make a shooter so he can blast an earplug across the yard six different ways. Why? Y chromosome. Has to be). We played with Han's toys again. He let me have some fun with his bass, and showed Carla a lot of the fun stuff one can do with his keyboard. We are both jealous. Carla had to go home, I went over to see if the Phoenix was up. Spent time talking with her, got her to smile again, she's been a little down lately. The Phoenix is normally always smiling, and I rather prefer this.   So, all in all, except for being kind of sick today, today was pretty good. Except now I'm being bothered to go to the pool. Bleah.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If no one knew your age, how old would you be?  I looked at myself in the mirror the other day. I had this really cute twin ponytail thing, and it made for a more sweet and innocent looking Amanda. One of those "everybody at the party" questions - what kind of music would or do you have in your car? Mine's kinda all over the place for what I like to drive to. I'm actually having responsible moments now. I get fascinated by storms, and want to go out and play in them. I have some inner darkness, and sometimes I like it. I play Jazz. I dance.  What determines how old you are? How old do people think you are? How old are you?   I'm supposedly the one who matures later than everyone else my age.   Is there anyone else out there who's my age? Would I like them, or would we fight all the time? Does it matter?  Maybe age doesn't matter.  My sister has a problem with this - that adults have more rights than she does. I know there's something at the root of this, but I'm not sure what it is. I thought it was just a given - more privileges, due to more responsibility.   Everyone's on me to grow up faster. I'm supposed to "act my age". But don't grow up too fast, don't lose what's important. Just make sure you're not being immature.  If anyone bothered to really pay attention, maybe age doesn't matter at all. My best friend is 18. Eric's is 23. Or maybe we just pay attention to increments of time that are far too small.  My life is the span of someone else's yawn. And something else has a lifespan of the time up to my first rite of passage.   I see you. Not as often as we used to. Shows you time matters to one of us, if we're not as close as we used to be. You've gone through quite a few rites of passage since we stopped spending so much time together. I had your birthday memorized, still know which week it's in.   How old are you, if no one knows your age?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I have past writings in my notebook from this year. From time to time, I'll post them with their dates, or try to guess from the basic content what the date was. This wasn't one I dated, and normally I'd just fold it in with some of the others on Random, but it still applies in some strange way to what's going on.    Tell me what matters.  I knew what mattered to me. I pursued what was important to me. Yet it wasn't until I started to lose those that I realized I had to know what mattered to you.  "What's so important? What have you got here that's worth living for?"  Despite all my rage I'm still just a rat in a cage. Makes more sense than anything else right now. I want you to see me, to notice me and understand something's wrong. I rail and flail, start to cry, threaten to die. And you in your lab coat glance up, and check off that #42 is responding appropriately to the stimulus. I'm exactly like every other rat, no matter how much I race around.  "Is there peace in immortality? Peace in death? I wish that you were different. But it is impossible to exist without opposition in life and death."
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another good  urlLink point .  Spent most of today "cleaning my room". It gets on my nerves when people assign me projects I'm already working on, and set new rules other than the ones I have. As in, getting this done a week earlier than I had planned. All they really want is for this place to LOOK clean. Doesn't matter how organized stuff is, whether or not it's truly put away. It just has to LOOK clean.  Well, my dresser and my desk need to be dusted, and my hamper looks like it's going to be sick (which isn't surprising, considering some of the stuff I jammed in there), and a vacuuming wouldn't hurt, but hey, the room is clean.  Mom declared that it had to be clean in here by the time she got home, or I couldn't go over to Eric's tomorrow. Dad said by three. Technically, the floor was clean by three. I still had stuff on my chair (papers I didn't want to bother with), and the bed needed to be made. The room is most likely now acceptable by their standards, but they haven't checked it yet.   I'd think they could come up with a more original consequence than not letting me go to Eric's. That makes the whole thing seem so...juvenile. Then again, if I have to be told to clean my room, I probably deserve it.  Technically, I was organizing things. Okay, so the laundry all over the floor was similar to my dad's statement that my dresser threw up. I had been looking for a white t-shirt the other night, for a fifties thing we were doing with the leaders. As it turned out, I do not in fact own any plain white t-shirts.  Spent part of today playing with Gracie. Had the usual argument/banter about which of us will be playing Tenor in the Jazz Band. It'll be her, it makes more sense, but I'm still hung up on "One Band, One Sound" and sometimes caring far more about how the overall band sounds than how she feels.   Yes, I am scum. Sorry.  Had we two more tenors, I wouldn't care. It's actually not so much about her, just that our only tenor is a newbie, and doesn't have to be.   I want the tenor for pep, but she's got plans to use it in concert band, too. *sigh* We have these almost arguments (again, me no like confrontation) about encroaching on each other's turf. She says she doesn't want to play the alto, because I do. This I can completely understand. What gets under my skin is that she's playing sax. I realize she doesn't have a whole lot of options. In my opinion, she'd do great on piano - but we're already overbalanced on pianos in J.Band.   I'm also forbidden to play tenor, one of the school's tenors, for either. She hates being associated with me.   As you can see, these won't be too much shorter than Random's, but I'll try. Just for you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've had three arguments with my computer in the last two days. Two of these were after I'd turned it off for making me mad. I'm not sure if this is like yelling at the kid while he's in timeout, or taking out your rage on a dead body. At any rate, it doesn't make me feel much better.  The irony is that I like to write when I'm mad. And the only reason there are any used pages in my journal is because sometimes I don't have the internet to my room, or I can't log on, and I get desperate. I don't like writing as much with paper. Actually, I'd prefer it, if the computer was a block away.  My math/science/gov/German notebook has maybe seventy pages left in it. Half of these have drawings. Another third are writings that should have made it in here or Random Musings. Sometimes school makes me mad, and I feel better after drawing. You get caught up in what you're creating - you've got the energy. I actually started two drawings I absolutely hated last quarter - fortunately it was two weeks before the end of Math, so I didn't ever finish them.  My computer is possessed. There's no other explanation. I'm not saying it's possessed by demonic forces. In fact, I'm not sure it's so much possessed as inhabited. Something lives in there, I'm not sure I want to know what, and every three weeks, he or it gets bored, and starts screwing things up again. And this really gets to me, because my computer is no longer an innocent pawn in this whole mess. Rather, it has retaliated to its inhabitation, and started possessing me. Sooner or later, I'll have named it as I do my musical instruments. This will be the day one or more of you can come to my house, into the dark, dark catacombs of the basement, and try to drag me out of my room and put me somewhere safe. There you will try to convince me that dogs are atheists. And my computer will sit, alone, and hopefully off. If you leave it on, then another poor soul who likes dark caves will come inhabit my room and be possessed by it.  I've had these three arguments with the afore-mentioned machine sitting blankly in front of me, because the little troll I picture inhabiting it (who looks curiously like Jaken), has yanked a few things around again. I believe he is redecorating. And he is inconsiderate enough to do this whilst I am writing, and so confuse the poor evil little glowing box in the corner to the point where it suffers either an emotional or mental breakdown, and loses my work.  I already know I'm in trouble. I personify things every day, trees and my instruments and all that, but when the computer becomes its own entity, things are really messed up in here.  Which is pretty funny, actually.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It is so, so nice to be free.  It hasn't really registered yet that I'm free. Technically, I'm on shore leave from purgatory, but I don't have to find or do anything for them there whilst I'm out of their clutches.  Wir sind frei!!!  So far today, I have slept in 'til nine-thirty (this is as late as I ever sleep, unless I was REALLY up late. Last night I was doing things in/with my room until maybe eleven-thirty. I think Chai came in to wake me up - I didn't totally wake up, but I could feel her walking on me, the mattress where she walked, and once she tried to get me up by washing my cheek. That, or she likes my skin cleanser.  Force of habit has induced me to eat breakfast in my room - must break free of this. I always eat breakfast in my room, because I'm getting dressed at the same time, doing my hair, packing my bag, and it takes an extra ten minutes if breakfast is set apart from these activities. Now, I have time, it just hasn't sunk in yet.  And then there will be room-cleaning today. Hopefully. I have about four loads of laundry to do, although half of one of them is just all the stuff I brought home from my track locker. Much weeding out of stuff should take place over the next week. I enjoy this quite a bit.  Dad said it would be a nice day for taking out the boat, but we've got way too much work to do on it before it's lakeworthy. Also something to be enjoyed.   It's very, very nice to be free.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just needed to change a few things.  If you're reading this, there's a half chance you got it from my last blog. You'll probably thus know where my last blog was. If you are the kind of person who cares about history, this may make a difference. If you desperately need to check past archives and you somehow do not have the address, just ask me.  Changing a few things.   Not sure if we'll be using the aliases on this one. Kind of depends on the feel of it. I have one private that's usually pretty dark, and so we use the aliases on it. The other one was just random thoughts, so for the most part real names were used.   I should probably ask a few people what they think would be better. Ah well. As usual, if you've got a problem, talk to me before deciding I am a jerk and ranting for three hours. As entertaining as that usually is, I'd really prefer to spare you the stress.  Hmmm...anything else...like I said, it'll be a few days before we're really set into any kind of pattern here (me? pattern?), or even a feel, so blogging as much as I normally do won't be happening.   I have a suspicion that much of this will have a similar feel to Random Musings, but there were just a few things that, as I said, needed to change.  So, without further ado...
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's kind of interesting, that, when something happens to make you feel down, you can't really concentrate on anything that sits in the sunny side of your life.  &nbsp; Actually, nothing really happened. I was reading a book I hadn't read for awhile, and I had forgotten how it gets towards the end. I mean, I remembered the ending, but I forgot the whole atmosphere. She perfectly captured exactly what I was feeling last year - like I was trapped in a vicious cycle, and letting everyone down all over the place, and couldn't say anything to anyone without hurting them more. &nbsp; Right now, things are actually going pretty good. Yeah, my room's a mess, and my foot hurts, but other than that, I'm pretty happy. And if I keep saying that enough, I'll manage to put my mood back where I like it, because this isn't really based off of anything. &nbsp; I think I'm sending the book off on Bookcrossing, though. I've learned almost everything I can from it, and I don't want to keep anything like it around. &nbsp; Just...remembering how I let everyone down before. Really...really hurts. &nbsp; It's always been something of a mystery to me how anyone can really want to leave home. I always just decided, "Well, some people have totally different relationships with their parents, and some people have lousy home lives." I think I have a great relationship with my parents and my sisters, and I've rarely felt the urge to get out of here. I know I have plans to, but don't really want to yet. I'm perfectly happy and content to live my life as I do, living here. &nbsp; Which is kind of the problem. What happened is mostly based off of my parents and I both taking for granted that we had the supreme say in what I was doing here. I actually found myself thinking, "It's  my  life, and  my  relationships, and I don't care what anyone else thinks!!! No one else  should  have that much of an opinion, or tell it to me!!" &nbsp; Usually, anything along the lines of "It's my life, and I don't care what anyone else thinks!" is a warning that you're doing something stupid. I was clowning around with some friends, the way I always do, but my sister was there, too. Which I didn't really think about - my sister is one of my friends, too, and she's there with us a lot. What I should have thought about was that my sister hasn't been with us all the time, and so doesn't see me with my friends EXCEPT for lunch and the odd outing.  &nbsp; *sigh, blowing bangs off forehead* &nbsp; I'm kind of a flirt. It doesn't mean there's any kind of romantic inclination behind it, for the most part it's just a social game a lot of us play. And you don't really get to be good at it unless you KNOW how much feeling there is behind it. But I was flirting with three of the guys - one of whom is like my big brother, another isn't my type by any means, and another I've been flirting with for months, just clowning around. Didn't really think anything of it, checked with the girlfriends to make sure they weren't reading more into it than was there...just playing. &nbsp; If you've read Harry Potter, you've probably met Rita Skeeter. My sister can develop a similar attitude, sort of a gleeful, "Oh, oh, what is this?" that would make a great story. She's also remarkably talented at understanding where information will cause the biggest uproar. To a certain point, this amuses me with mild admiration. I like going for reactions, too - and the little reactions (that end with a shrug) are not the best ones. But every time she does it, she's using fact. Often, tailored-fact that is slightly recut to get a better reaction, but it's still based on truth. The truth was, I was flirting.  &nbsp; My sister has since decided that it's necessary to tell the people she thinks would most care. She doesn't get the pleasure of pointing it out to certain girlfriends, since they were already there, but, hmmm, parents? Oh yes indeed, that could be enjoyable. Oh, and boyfriend? My my my, this WILL be a pleasurable evening. &nbsp; (To the second - thank you so much for listening to my side of it after her. Thank you, thank you, thank you.) &nbsp; Usually the three of us have what would be considered an illegal pact, simply that sometimes we cover for each other, but we can always be counted on not to go out of our ways to snitch on each other. The exception being that someone's in trouble. I like to go on minimum details for this. Part of this is respecting that the perpetrator has enough clear judgment to be able to tell when the parents need to know something. Whether it's school-related, guy-related, punishment-related, just about anything - we don't discuss it. &nbsp; Perversely, the guys know that certain closer friendships in the circle mean that so-and-so tells everything in her relationship to other-girl, and the ones who are either smarter or less straightforward use this to their advantage. For example, if other-girl's boyfriend wants her to know something but is too shy to tell her himself, he'll mention it to so-and-so. However, if I want my parents to know something, I much prefer telling them myself. Then I can do my OWN fact-tailoring. &nbsp; Due to my sister's fact-tailoring, my dad decided it was "inappropriate" for me to ask Mark to come boating with us. After all, how would his girlfriend feel? And it's hardly appropriate for me to do anything with a person I broke up with less than a year ago, now is it? Pointing out that I've asked his girlfriend is not a swiftie - "if you have to ask, you should know the answer". No, actually, I'm asking because I happen to LIKE her and really enjoy being friends with her and not having her mad at me.  &nbsp; My sister is currently on semi-probation, which doesn't mean anything, except that I don't tell her anything anymore, unless it's something that I wouldn't care if my parents knew. The sad thing is, this is the kind of thing we used to do when  I &nbsp;was fifteen. *sigh* I'm trying to train her out of it, really I am. Interesting question is - what's she trying to train  me  out of? 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tuesday was, of course, the 13th. So, Eric asked me to come over. Actually, Eric asked me to come over like two weeks before then, and this was when it seemed like we wouldn't be able to see each other as much over the summer. Kind of like, "If we can only have one date this month, can it be on our "anniversary"?"  &nbsp;  We've been doing a lot more than I hoped we would be able to. It used to be that whenever we wanted to meet, we'd have to plan it a week in advance. The other night, we were watching movies and Mom just out of the blue came out with "Why don't you have Eric over?" It's been more random, and a lot more easygoing. I rather like this.  &nbsp;  After Panic Room, I'm even more definite about staying away from anything that could be described as a "scary movie". This is a shame, because my boyfriend enjoys watching scary stuff just to laugh at it. Unless, of course, it's a fantasy involving the co-star being male and wearing tight pants. THEN he's scared of it. Love ya, hun. ;)  &nbsp;  Well, had fun talking with Eric's mom in the car. Eric was in the backseat - hah. ;) I really like his mom, his whole family, really, but his mom's pretty cool to talk to. The first time I was over at his house, I was really nervous about his family's impression of me, and she just made it easy to relax. It also has the effect of me not wanting to do anything to get her mad, because I like her. Must remember this. Threatened to leave Eric in the car when we got there (child locks on the back doors), she said "Oh, I like her."  &nbsp;  There are little comments that you probably don't think about, that other people can really latch onto and remember.  &nbsp;  About a month ago, we got new furniture for our family room. This resulted in the moving about of some other furniture, like the "character" couch in the family room being put in the playroom (matches a little better there - color scheme red, gold, and white vs. slate/blue and faint pink), and the rather extremely beat-up floral print loveseat and chair from the playroom being put into the basement to deal with at a later date. These two have endured so much abuse at our hands. They're both really light, and get moved around a lot. Well, they were in the basement, and&nbsp;Eric was sitting on the couch for whatever reason and...well, with one thing and another, now it's in his room. There was a little bit of a tear in one cushion, and you can't flip the cushions over because it folds out into a bed. As he now uses it to get into his bed, or so he says - the tear has grown a little bit.  &nbsp;  He's also rearranged the tv and computer, so now his tv sits on his desk in front of the couch, and the computer's at the end of the bed. Great. *affectionate eye roll*  &nbsp;  But, we spent most of the afternoon on the couch. One side has the tear, which has grown, and has since been designated as "Eric's side". The other is usually George's, sometimes Amanda's, it would seem. George is Eric's baby. Gorgeous kitty, glossy fur, and beautiful markings. Rather largish, too. I don't think I could actually hold him, he's too big.  &nbsp;  I voted for El Dorado after shooting down the first scary movie. "Does it involve blood?" "Not really." Blood I can handle - pretty good about blood, as long as it isn't from gunshot wounds to the head. Actually, any fatal gunshot wounds bother me inexplicably - swords I'm just fine with. "Does it involve melted skin?" "Just at the end." "No."  &nbsp;  I have the soundtrack, don't have the movie. I used to really like it - wrote a fanfic about what happened to Miguel, Tulio, and Chel after they ride Altivo off. Bibo keeps popping up, of course. For the record, they have quite a fair share of adventures, get lost in the jungle, never really settle down in any one spot for too long, and in the inevitable really bad sequel, end up somehow crossing the Pacific. Yes, they bring the horse. But, at any rate - though he denied me permission to say all the lines with characters (a few major ones are all right; "We're both in barrels, that's the extent of my knowledge."), I got to sing all the songs!! Well, the ones he didn't decide to make me be quiet for. "Without Question" will remind me of being with Eric for quite some time, I think.  &nbsp;  After this comes the inevitable argument about what movie we should watch next. This lasted for quite some time.  &nbsp;  Here's where we run into a gray area - I remember this happening, I just don't remember when. I know it involved the couch, so it had to have been after the tenth. But somehow, I don't place it on the thirteenth as easily - it seems like it happened another night, before that. But, it couldn't have been the twelfth, since we went to the lake. And I don't really THINK I went over to his house on the eleventh.  &nbsp;  Anyway, back up a pace. I should explain that my dear friend and ex-boyfriend hates Eric with a passion. And according to him, it really isn't over him dating me. Not for the most part, anyway. He'd be just fine with me dating Sid - recommends it, in fact. *sigh* Anyway, he's known for looking for a decent excuse to kill Eric. Eric's response was that if he ever hurts me, then he can kill him, but, whatever.  &nbsp;  Last week, at the Watersports, I ended up slicing open one toe very badly on a zebra mussel. ("Zebra mussel" is like a curse word to lakers, except we don't use it to describe anything else. It's just a word that causes automatic recoil and...yeah. It's right up there with "nuclear waste". They're parasites, and they're worse than glass to step on.) I had been paddling in, not stroking, because I was bringing the skis in to shore. Normally, they're not a problem for us because we don't swim near shore in Zumbro. But, that morning was the first morning it had really healed over.&nbsp;   Whether this happened or not that night, whatever. We were just clowning around as always (just so everyone&nbsp;knows, he's no more ticklish than I am - he just doesn't know that), and he accidentally kicked me. Right on the first three toes of&nbsp;my&nbsp;right foot. It&nbsp;really shouldn't have hurt, I&nbsp;normally would have retaliated with fierce, vengeful silliness - but I&nbsp;yelped.&nbsp;I think he worries about me too much, he&nbsp;immediately backed off and asked "What's wrong?" very concerned and worried-like.&nbsp;I answered with a string of more ows, bit my lip with that scream-sigh I do when I'm trying not to yelp, and waited for the pain to go down. Gave him a brief explanation, I think I tried to go back to the previous battle, and then I noticed it bleeding. He directed me to the bathroom, I cleaned it up pretty well, band-aid, etc., go back to the room to find him...buried in his couch. All righty.   My boyfriend has the cutest wounded-puppy expression of anyone on the planet. Big brown eyes, very expressive eyebrows - the whole expression is just adorable. Always makes me want to hug him or make him smile. Anyway. I pulled the cushions off him, and he looks up with that. I'm kind of grinning, and gave him much grief over the injury. It hurt! Okay, and I like teasing him. I guess I could have been nicer.   After a little while, we were back to happiness and watching Bruce Almighty. I know we had supper before that, but I don't know if it was before or after the bleeding thing. I like eating at his house, because his mom's a really good cook, and I just like talking with her. Except, Mom's years of training (handed down by her father's constant "Shut Up and Eat") not to talk too much during dinner holds true. (Never does at home - I think this is because it's been drilled into me as "good manners", and at home I also tend to rock back in my chair, occasionally talk with my mouth full (also a way to scandalize&nbsp;Mom - picked THAT one up from my Dad), and be less refined overall. Anyways, so I like talking with Eric's mom, or rather, listening to her. The result of not talking the whole while we're eating is that I'm shy again for some time.   Anyway, so, watching Bruce Almighty. I hadn't seen the outtakes before - and I've never seen the deleted scenes on a movie actually be worth deleting. Eric groaned when I "asked" to see them. (I'm a little demanding sometimes.) Example: On Pirates, they just distracted from the storyline or flow of things - the scenes themselves weren't actually that bad. Outtakes were good, though. Scales of Justice.   About a week before this, I'd sent Eric a "We need to talk" note. I had monumentally bad timing...whatever. I think I blogged about it. Anyway, we were both afraid that we'd end up breaking up, but we actually bothered to talk about everything...and though I don't think we actually said anything that hadn't been said before, we're a lot closer now.   We had another brief discussion, just because...well, something happened with&nbsp;Adm, and since that incident, I've been really scared about getting close to guys. Khalid once grabbed my arms to apologize for running smack into me (I would have dashed back out to grab the next order, otherwise), and it was all I could do not to cry. I actually DID run back to the break room to cry after that. Close physical contact has really scared me in certain situations, and I'm trying so hard to trust Eric that he's not going to hurt me. Anyway, so, I ended up telling him parts of that, and he just held me, and it was okay.   I feel safer when I'm with him. I don't know why. I just do.   Mom had called, we agreed on her picking me up around ten, and that was about when I dashed downstairs in a manner of speaking. In my mind, it's that mom and Eric's mom are both going way out of their way (which they are at least physically, to say nothing of the time it takes) to drive us back and forth, and I really don't want to give her any reason to decide not to.   Mom and I were talking about driving to Dodge Center to watch the windmills at night, we ended up going home, watching Kodo drums instead with ice cream. We were playing "I'm Gonna Be" the whole way home - and the rest of the evening, I was trying to figure out what had happened that made me trust him so much more. I'm still not sure, I'm just really happy about it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has been a long week.  &nbsp; So, while I started this on the 17th, and finished&nbsp;at least part of it on the 19th, I'm going to date these on the days&nbsp;I wanted to write them.&nbsp;I&nbsp;have a friend who complains that my blog posts are too long as&nbsp;it is.  &nbsp;  Monday I did something I really should remember. I think it was pretty fun. Lake!! That was it!! We took the boat out to Zumbro. Eric came with us, and we tried to get him up on the kneeboard. I'm starting to think most of our watertoys are built for teen and not adult size, because we've had trouble with both the skis and the wakeboard, getting the guys up.  &nbsp;  I'm very hungry right now. But I have to wait, because Mom's making pancakes, and that's better than cereal.  &nbsp;  Usually, we like to go to Zumbro on weeknights. For one thing, the wind doesn't really die down until after six - choppy water is only fun to play in if you're trying to stay in it, not on it. For another, most of the yahoos are usually off the water by then. For one reason and another, this wasn't the case Monday. There was also a lot of trash in the water - high water last week had pulled down some nice logs and the like. We had to go way up the lake to find an area free of yahoos and trees. There was still a lot of trash, but nothing that would put a hole in the boat. The kneeboard goes slow enough to deflect a lot of stuff, and I'm okay enough on skis to be able to jig sideways if anything big pops up.  &nbsp;  I tried skiing - it was really rough for awhile. Did a lot of one-handed clowning around, just showing off, having a blast. Dad tried to get me to drop a ski, but the water was pretty rough - and I'm pretty rough on skis. That much friction, you know it wasn't going to go smoothly. I think I did one wipeout, and just fell another time. Wipeouts are the ones where people go, "Oooh!!!" "That one hurt!"&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  The waterski team was practicing, too. I was talking to one of the girls last week at the Watersports thing, and about half her family used to be part of it. She's one of two families in Freedom with six siblings. I used to really, really want to be part of it. For the most part, though, I've preferred doing my athletic activities solo.  &nbsp;  Speaking of yahoos on the water - a couple of 20-year-olds. I think I'm going to hate it when I'm in this age range, because they're the absolute worst for driving anything. It's like they don't notice anyone else around them. What might impact their vehicle, sure, absolutely - but...well, Denise almost got nailed with the kneeboard. Kneeboard!! It's half the length of a surfboard, little wider, and bright yellow!! It's huge!! You can see the logs in the water that are eight inches wide, four feet long, but you can't see a bright yellow kneeboard???  &nbsp;  There's usually a kind of courtesy on the lake between drivers. Just consideration for the other boaters - it's nice. We all give each other room, we take note of what people are doing and reduce our wake if it'll be a problem for them, we just watch out for each other. We've found other people's skis before, just haul it out of the water, hold it up whenever another boat drives by until someone claims it.  &nbsp;  A yahoo on the lake is a moron who doesn't notice other boats anymore than they would notice overlarge logs in the water. Same thing happened when I was skiing. Twenty-year-olds. Usually, when there's a pontoon on the lake, we give them a wide berth and slow down - they can't go more than maybe twenty, twenty-five miles an hour, and really don't need our wake to deal with. Anyway, we were up past the waterski team's territory, and I'd gone down after skis. Dad&nbsp;had tried to convince me to go to one ski, but there was a lot of trash in the water, and I'm not as certain of myself on one ski and how I could deal with extra waves, jigging sideways to avoid logs, that kind of thing. So, I'm down, Dad's circling back - pontoon. I had no idea pontoons could go that fast. We all know enough to make a point of holding up whatever toy we were playing with - because they're often bigger and more brightly colored than we are (especially three girls with dark hair - really blends nicely into the lake if you're swimming free without a life vest). So, I'm holding the ski mostly out of the water - turning a bit to make sure I'm out of the main boat lane - pontoon.  &nbsp;  I have a long rant about the morons driving, but they were going faster than pontoons normally do, which is their prerogative, and not noticing anything in front of them. Actually, odds are good that they would have passed me with ten feet to spare, but in the water, you give each other as much room as you could each travel in a few seconds of reaction time. Very scary when this doesn't happen. A boat going by you at that speed, that close, is like a car going by you somewhere between 40 and 55, five feet away.  &nbsp;  Okay, done with rant against lake&nbsp;yahoos and morons.  &nbsp;  We tried getting&nbsp;Boo&nbsp;up on skis. I was elected to help her in the water. Okay, and I really wanted to get back in.&nbsp;We had found one little side cove that was free&nbsp;of trash, and mostly free of other traffic - one&nbsp;fishing off to the side, but we&nbsp;stayed out of their way. It was&nbsp;so pretty -&nbsp;sun setting, of course, and the lake was finally calm.&nbsp;Jump out, swim over to her,&nbsp;help her get her skis on.&nbsp;Generally, my advice on&nbsp;getting up is composed of, "Pretend like your butt's made of lead. You have air in your knees, so they're almost floating.&nbsp;Try to keep your skis parallel, it's okay if they're not level with each other - just so long as they're parallel.&nbsp;Trust the boat to pull you out - it's 180 horse,&nbsp;you don't have to help it.&nbsp;Just lean back!!" She got up after a few tries.&nbsp;I was so proud of her, it was just really cool to see.  &nbsp;  They went way, way down the lake. And I'm not sure what happened then, because I was still in the water. It was one of the most amazing things I've ever done - I remember always looking at the water in Turtle Bay and other coves on lakes I've loved, wishing I could go out in it when it was so quiet, and not wanting to disturb the sunset on it. Now I actually was in it, without disturbing anything. It was probably 12-19 feet deep there, so it was as though there was nothing around me except the water, endless water. Holding me, surrounding me, supporting me, I was safe. I love being in the water - it's where I'm most at ease. I was stroking under the water, and my body's movements were making ripples in the alternating darkness and pastels of the sunset reflected on the water. It was so quiet - I felt like I was the only person on the world, no one else was shattering this silence. I was noting the rushes to one end, the sun leaving the sky, the woods around the cove, and most of all, the water around me. I could have stayed there for hours.  &nbsp;  Dad finally came back, and I think I was glowing. They tossed the skis out, and I got up. We have a few signals from boat to whoever we're towing, faster, slower, stop (well, stop, I just let go), and for skiing - how he's going to turn (you don't want to be skiing on the inside of a turn - makes the water and the rope act very goofy - it's a warning to be in the wake or on the outside), and more recently, that it's okay to drop a ski now. You can't do it where there's a lot of traffic, and you want to be near the shore. And I happen to prefer doing it on smooth water, but that's just me. Anyway, he gave me the drop-ski signal, and I thought about it, started the focus thing I do, and then realized that we'd be going across the main boat lane in another fifteen seconds. I think we ended up going around a major bend in the Zumbro, down by some of the more open lake-homes, before I did. And then, things  really  got fun. :D  &nbsp;  I've dropped a ski before - did it once last summer, maybe twice, but that was the first time I stayed up for any real length of time (the first time I did, everyone was watching me, no one was watching ahead  except  me - it was fall or hit the shore), and the first time I had that much control. I was playing around, just having a blast - actually had enough courage to start showing off. It was amazing.  &nbsp;  It took about five minutes, maybe more, to actually FIND the ski again. It had been just a little bit illegal - you're not supposed to tow anyone after sundown. Sundown is that the sun is no longer visible, not "but officer, there's still light in the sky!" Oops. I could see just fine - unfortunately, you couldn't&nbsp;really see&nbsp;the ski in the water. Which means that you probably couldn't see a dropped person in the water. THAT's why you're not supposed to tow when it gets darker.  &nbsp;  Eric said later that he was proud of me. Everybody, when they came back to pick me up and I got back in the boat, was saying it was awesome, I did a great job, but Eric said he was proud of me. I wonder if he knows how much it means to me to hear that. I always want to make someone proud of me - not to be the center of attention, but for someone to really be happy to know me and take pride in it. I did something right for once. Someone was actually proud of me.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Absolutely nothing to say today.  Well, no clear idea, anyway. A lot of ideas floating around. I haven't been charting my dreams as much as I should have been lately. Last night involved me being the counselor in a cabin with about four or five junior high girls. I like junior highers. Some pranking between my cabin and the one next to us, it seems there was a massive bookcase right in front of/over my bed. This involved the use of shaving cream and all of us waking up pretending to be guys. Which, of course, with us, meant pretending to think a lot slower, walking much more clumsily, and putting a lot less care into our general appearances. Then after laughing that off, we went down to the beach with some of the others. It was just me and my girls, but one of the other counselors about my age, probably a little younger, was helping out. The beach is pretty level, but short - retaining wall. Then a steep decline to deeper water.  There was something in there about flirting, and then finding Han and being surprised about running into Eric on the other side of the lake. They were trying to help - somehow it was conveyed that someone was drowning - but I was the only one who could go down or something like that.  I keep having dreams where I'm the only one who can help, or I somehow rescue someone. I think I'm just really wanting to make a difference in someone's life, really want to help, but I'm not. And, yeah, there's always a conflict of heart somehow, illustrates uncertainty about relationships, but that it's not the main focus.  For much of today, my subconscious has been sending images of a Dalmatian into my mind. Adult, doing that kind of bouncing prance that longer dogs are prone to, brown eyes.   Maybe we'll take the boat out tonight. Dad says if I ask anyone to come, it has to be someone in town - and Mom doesn't want me calling Mark. Fuss and bother. Actually, for the most part, I agree with her - he's been getting the impression I've been throwing meself at him.  ...  Called. Am now depressed. I kind of figured it fell under the "notable exception" - he's been asking to come boating for months, so, a few social codes are okay to skip over. However, it would seem he and his girlfriend (who I also wanted to call) are in trouble with parents and must stay with parents tonight. Blah.  ...  Eric can come!! I think. My parents misinterpreted my disappointment and slight depression over these two (PMS alert - woop woop!) as not wanting to go. For the record - there is very, very little that keeps me from wanting to go to the lake. Waterskiing!!  Should probably do something about getting ready. Laters.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well. THAT was fun.  My timing rather sucks, it would seem. I emailed Eric, something in the general "We need to talk" area...which was originally supposed to be calling him. Well, I was planning to call him when I realized that, hey, we needed to talk - and then I noticed that it was 2 am. Why do I have to do all my serious thinking at night? So, the plan was to call him when I woke up. Except, hey, heh, when you're up until 2, and your body always, ALWAYS demands 8-10 hours of sleep...you usually don't wake up at seven. So, I emailed him. Forgetting, of course, that Dad had promised that the two of us (me and Dad) would help with the watersports thing. By the time we got back and had the boat taken care of - it was after eleven. I can't usually call after eleven, can't check my email after ten. So, today, when I finally CAN check my email, he'd written back and asked that I call him no matter what time it was. See, this would have been really good to know the day before, but today, he'll be at work until tomorrow.   An old friend (in a manner of speaking) speculated that I must be a real bitch to date.   So now I feel really, really bad, and I really, really want to talk to him. But I can't!!   Oh, crud. We're going to be gone tomorrow night, too.  Saturday's all of the GND stuff. We were making plans to run into each other, anyway, but not until the afternoon.  *sound of intense frustration*  I need to talk to him!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I SERIOUSLY don't recommend reading this unless you've got nothing better to do.    Right. So, I jammed part of my right hand, and now I can't use it.  Well, I sort of can. I mean, for typing and all - not much effort required there. But picking anything up is chancy.  I blame this entirely on me wearing my glasses. Which is taking something that isn't my fault and making it into being my fault, but hey, it's my problem, so it doesn't hurt anyone anyway, right?  Sigh.   I'm not overly fond of my glasses. At the private school I used to go to, I was the only kid in the whole class with glasses. Then again, I was also the only girl with dark hair. Curiously, I don't attribute my whole scheme against the "midwestern blondes" to this, but rather my experiences in high school.  Wearing the glasses messes me up, all right? However, I happen to be so blind without my contacts that the chances of me making it from the bathroom to my room without some sort of visual aid are slim. I'll find my room, eventually. If I leave the light on or something. But I'll hit the ironing board and two laundry baskets on the way.  The incident with the needle in my foot has encouraged me to take slightly more care at night. That, or start cleaning my room and the playroom more effeciently. Take a gander at which one has happened.  Well, actually, the room did start to get cleaner. And sometimes I go out of my way to pick up the playroom. But not vacuuming. Which is, of course, the problem.   Actually, I think the immediate result after the needle incident was that I wore slippers everywhere for about a year.  Technically, my glasses probably aren't as powerful as I need them to be. And that's sad, because they're geekily thick as it is.   Almost done with the rearrangement of the room. Got furniture in place Sunday, spent most of yesterday fixing my drawer and making (yes, making - it seems that the 25 foot ethernet cable we had was in fact a crossover. We could either daisy-chain about three over to the new corner of my room where I've lodged my desk, or make a new one) the new internet cable from my sister's comp to mine. And rotating my rollerblade wheels. Eric came over at one point, we were planning to do the fireworks thing, but rain came down.   Not feeling terribly flirty. I seem to recall this being the sort of thing that made me wonder if the magic was going out of the Adm.'s and my relationship. Now I'm thinking we've just got some sort of chemical fun-ness from certain hormone cycles.  Sometimes I really hate being a girl, but it's considerably better than the alternative.  Which, as we all know, is being captured and androgynized by mutant squids from the planet Xerx, to be brought back to their world minus reproductive capabilities. Thus will they keep the human population in check, so as not to overrun Xerx and seize control of their military and bathroom facilities.  Which raises the question of whether or not squid actually defecate. I remember the dissection from seventh grade, and I don't think there's any way for anything to leave their body except ink. Which is highly unlikely, so evidently we missed something. In the science and biology classes (I use the term loosely - way too much fun to be a class) we ended up discussing how poop will either float or sink based off of the kind of bacteria in it. Squid are rather largish, but if all their defecation sinks to the sea floor, wouldn't this suggest that they're lacking in some sort of necessary bacteria?  Then again, not every life form requires every kind of bacteria.   Now I'm confused - is the plural of squid squid or squids?  I think it's squid when we're referring to the species as a whole. Squids when we're thinking of seven or so individuals.  Generally, that's how we establish sentience - when a species can think of itself as an individual. Take sharks, for example. They don't really think of why they're doing what they do. Little concept of past, no concept of future. They respond as their instincts dictate to each stimulus.   But how do we know this is the case? It's believable, certainly, if they don't do anything other than typical predatory activities. An acquaintance, Kevin, argues that the only true sentients are those that do things only for the purpose of pleasure. Dolphins are reputed to be the only species other than humans that have sex for other than reproductive purposes. But my cats respond to my presence by asking to be scratched, and seem to enjoy it. Unless this is somehow cleaning them, I can't think of any purpose this serves, except that it's pleasurable.  I'm not sure whether this is a quote or not, but last night at the table, Gracie comes out with, starting in a very poetic voice, "Oh, cat, you think you are so clean, but you are only covered in spit."  "Why should I try to leave my room? I am warm and safe in my cocoon."  Upon waking this morning, I was visited with an echo of a dream, and then proceeded to make up a rather simplistic poem along those lines. Not terribly impressive, but the whole thing amused me. Right now, I am secure in my cave, although hungry. I woke up late, got online to talk to some friends (partly involving a conversation with Sid that should be distantly on my mind for most of today), and went upstairs to get breakfast. That's when I jammed my hand in the dishwasher. Which I blame on my glasses. They affect my depth perception by making me think I have some. So, after wincing and yelping and doing the "AAAH I hurt myself ouchie ouchie ouchie!" dance, I came back here to writhe in agony on my bed. Then, after my hand went numb, I decided to get back on the computer and finish my conversation with Croc - which still hasn't happened - and complain to my blog and whatever poor souls read it about my hand. So now, I'm still hungry.  I've been eating a lot less lately, come to think of it. Kind of falling into that "food is optional" thing again. About two years ago, I was doing something similar, and thinking the same thing a lot of the time. Maybe life really is just a series of phases, most of them cycling.  And a few just surfing.   Awikiwiki, mai lohilohi Lawe mai i ko papa he'e nalu Pi'i na nalu, la lahalaha O ka moana, hanupanupa Lalala i ka la hanahana Me ke kai hoene i ka pu'e one Helehele mai kakou e Hawaiian Roller Coaster Ride!  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What happened to love?  I remember laughing with Jackie about who we thought was cute. I would laugh about her celebrity crushes, and she would tease me because I liked the "different" guys.   I rememember being dramatic without meaning to, so serious for twelve. I remember thinking N and I were going to get married, and going everywhere with him, putting special significance (in my mind) on everything he said. Remembering his smile. Taking it for granted that we could laugh and smile together. Thinking it'd always be like this, until we got married.  Now it means so much to me to honestly make someone laugh or smile.   I remember reading under the same tree by a white fence every week, hoping to see someone. I remember almost fainting when Jay wrote that he loved me. I remember the total shock from when you IMed that you actually did like me. I remember being able to make you feel better, being able to make you smile.  I remember being with you less than a week ago. Just resting against you, watching a movie. Love need not constantly manifest itself in the contact of a kiss. Just that we're together, and we love each other  I remember wondering when one character smiled at me or noticed me in the halls whether he liked me. I remember flirting to an absurd degree with one of my friends in Jazz Band. I remember thinking "what if this is love?" for four different people. I remember the day I knew I didn't have to ask for one. I remember your smile, and realizing that it hadn't changed in a day, but every day we were together, that love isn't something you have to ask.  I remember pain. I remember being hurt. I remember hurting you. I remember wanting so badly to make it right. I remember that I'm not allowed to love you. I remember refusing to let myself come anywhere close to falling in love with you. I remember being in your arms. I remember questions. I remember that there weren't answers. I remember going too far. I remember being content. I remember being truly happy. I remember thinking this would never end. I remember it ending. I remember everything I learned from you. I remember when your friend said I had made a difference in you. I remember being afraid of losing you. I remember taking you for granted. I remember knowing you would never leave me. I remember leaving you. I remember fear that I wasn't right for you. I remember that you deserved so much better. I remember wanting so much to please you. I remember making you smile. I remember you reminding me of what had happened a year ago. I remember us laughing about what used to be. I remember you trying to help me. I remember you holding me when I was scared. I remember telling you everything that had happened. I remember keeping secrets and trying not to let you know. I remember that I could never keep secrets from you. I remember that you were always there for me. I remember the times you would cry. I remember when you hurt me, and how badly I wanted to make it all right again.   And yet I'm afraid to look to the future and hope for love. I want so much for you to be there, my love.   "What happened to love?" What do you mean? When did it change??
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I've been on one long trip, still have to talk about spending the night at Roni's, the Valleyfair trip with friends, and then I'm going to Valleyfair tomorrow with another group, and then the day after that, leaving for a trip that will last three weeks. The day after this, I have a voice lesson, then a music clinic the day after that. Hopefully that Friday will be our last Valleyfair trip, because a lot of people have work Saturday, a certain person is leaving for the open north Sunday, and my sister and I don't get back until Wednesday (and all other committments for this week have been explained. Between the music clinic and being abused/ignored by J.T. and the pixie all day, I think I'll take the music clinic.) So, there's a lot I should be writing about...and instead, I'm going to tell you about Tammin.  Tammin is, pretty much, the exact character that I would choose to be my lover/associate in any fantasy story. Eric's going to hate that, but look on the bright side, love - I fantasize about nonexistent guys, instead of ones you know. ;) Generally, by anyone who understands fantasy, it is assumed that an elf would be a person's Chosen.  Little explanation about elves: They're perfect. They're immensely graceful, beautiful beyond all reason, intelligent (though not always wise), swift, blah blah blah, and on my personal requirement of all "acceptable males", they have an association with music. More to the point, they are sometimes powerless against it. Particularly gypsy reels. I am always susceptible to music myself, and I let it rule my emotions constantly. (This isn't exactly a rarity.) The problem with taking a perfect mate is that you yourself are rarely perfect. And, if it lasts, you're always trying to measure up to them, to somehow be their equal.  My Selkie character is involved with a Kelpie, just to make things really interesting, but the Selkie is quite a bit older than I am. At least four or five years, I should think, probably more like eight.  Tammin happens to hang out with the Sidhe. More accurately, he works on cars with them. Long explanation there, the whole thing's very funny. He is, in fact, a mage. With a much-beloved Mustang. A much-beloved and barely street-legal Mustang. Apparently, when you're a mage, and your friends are from Underhill, you can try a few things with your car that there  Human-mages in a decent age range are definitely worth paying attention to. And I like Tammin. He has a great sense of decency, is very trustworthy, something of a pushover, and rather immensely protective of those who have pushed him over. He can give way to his passions when he's angry (instead of clear-thinking and actually being able to  aim  his magic attacks), much like someone else I know. He has interesting tastes in music - we approve of anyone who doesn't just listen to pop. He has a fascinating sense of humor. He can swear in Elvish.  Physically, Tammin is rather thin and wiry, with longish brown hair, brown eyes (I always fall for the brown eyes, okay? The darker the eyes, the more I trust someone. Don't know why.), covered in scars from past attacks by the Unseleighe's pets (as well as the Unseleighe themselves, I think), and a quirky, crooked grin. If anyone sees him, do let me know. I should very much like to meet him.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>