<Blog>

<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl..im in victoria now, its so damn hot!!! except for the place im staying...it's really breezy there because it is right next to the sea, and u can see surfers, and parachutists and stuff..its really cool, hehe. yea fung, ill give u guyz my number when i get one, ifi get one, but i dont think it will be that cheap..brian, what did u do to ur mail?? lemmi guess...u changed ur password and 4got it and u also forgot ur secret answer...?? hehe... oh yea, ill definitaly cling on to u guyz, and ill try to keep in touch as much as i can ok, no matter what u say! bout the girls: today, i saw this girl in the mall, and i dont know what it was about her, but i really liker her...but just from her looks...hehe *shallow moi* THERE ARE SOO MANY HOT CHICKS HERE!! but all the hot gurlz are going out with the hot guyz so...thats crap..hehe, anyway, i gtg now so ciao 4 now!!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... just came back from johor... good to hear from you arin.... man we miss u loads... life here is never goin to be da same without u.... hey btw i think it should be damn cheap to sms us from there... if u get a hp line.... so give us ur number when u get one k =)... and yeah dont become daryl... even though i doubt u will.... daryl was a dick even bfore he left and he is still a dumbass.....  and btw brian might not be using his email for a while so dont mail him... just post stuff here.... if u wanna know wat brian did... ask him.... long stupid story  and make new friends dont hold on to us too much.... but dont forget us either.... and send us some pics of da gurls there....  anyway gtg sleep now... ill post summore stuff another time... ciao ppl
     

    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha tell me everything abt ur school when u have the time ..oh btw arin once u learn japanese u can help us traslate when we go to japan on our tour ;) hehe have a good time there and take care dude 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      dudes....man, u dont have to worrry bout me turning into daryl... u just have to worry bout me talking like this ' ichh luhhhve maghhell' (french accent if u dont understand)... anyway, i cant wait to travel round the world,and its ok that u didnt get the wah pedal, because my dad sed not to get it anyway.. hehe, k.. im sorry my plane didn't blow up, i really wanted it to though! grrr...i can't wait to come backeither, jac....but i dont believe how much my sister cried and everyone else...anyway...ig6tg bye byeb ye bye, ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey dude its good tht u arrived in canada safely ...  no prob for comin to the airport to see ya off ... haha we really wanted you to go :P hehehe jk jk .... hoped u liked our present ..hehe couldn't get you ur wow, wild , woah ( not sure) hehe padle.. we would have gotten it for u dude.. yea we are gonna make life fun for ourselves you better make you life fun too... but we are gonna travel the world!!! can't wait for tht :>.. it be cooll.. hey btw arin u better not change hehe.. don't be like daryl.... just be urself... haha we all miss you dude have fun in canada   PLZ take some pics of " panas ayam ayam " for us :P and good luck with them :>   cya dude 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yoyo arin ma man person dude guy. y didnt 1 of ur plane engine blow up so u could come back to malaysia man? i dun friend u anymore. introduce me to every hot chick in ur skool k? and every friend u haf. and every teacher. hope u enjoy skool on the 2nd. make lots of gurl friends ya? looking forward for u coming back altho u just left yesterday. neways....keep on posting on this site and tell us abt every single thing. cya btw arin, when i wanna post u click on the POST & PUBLISH button. not the POST button
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone... just arrived in  canada, its not cold at all here, and i never said it would be. im soooo sad bout leaving...jac, brian, and fung, im gonna miss u clowns, and thanks for coming to the airport yesterday wif me, i really appreciate that!! the second last day was cool, had fun in bukit kiara on the second last day wif the thunder birds and friends. im gonna miss all the fun we had in kl.... but u guys keep on enjoying before u dont have the chance to anymore k? school starts on the second, i can't wait.......wait, i can wait :'( i don't wanna go to boarding!! but i've seen loaddddds of hot chicks so far...Aactually there were only like 2 really hot ones....hehe. anyway, thats all for now, ill give u guyz all a call as soon as i can ok???? bye bye!  Arin
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hello everyone!! havent posted anything up in agggesss!! how has everyone been? pat... i really dont believe i talked to you yesterday although i was planning on callin you for so long...ask brian and fung.... hehe. Ppl.. bukit kiara on tuesday rite??/ u ppl gotta come... my last daY!! and im gonna take loads of photos and frame them up...one of me, jac, brian and fung, one of all the girls, one of me and mel if i can get one, one of family.... one of all of us!! hehe.... its gonna be cool mian! k, then when i meet the girl of my dreams, ill send u all a photo of her, and u r all gonna be sooo jealous, even the girls!...anyway, im going on too much, so talk later, bye bye, arin
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hiya! whoa..sori i totally 4got bout 4:am....i hope u didnt stay up all nite waitin. im reallll sori!!! how was de football match? haha..ah i got to no a lot more new ppl. so dats kewl :) haha..in my homeroom...theres only 4 gurls n 14/15 guys in de class...lol. but de guys r cool..so no biggie. well..i hope fung will enjoy his stay at k.b. n yah ill miss arin too. he called me up yesterday..i was soooooo surprised!!! though, it was gd 2 hear from him..missed him a lot. i hope we cleared stuff up..cos lately everyone thinks dat im pissed wif em..when im not..n etc. haha....anyways..i miss marc too!!! :( havent heard from him at all. well i juz hope he's fine n all. how bout u yong? u alrite?! its gd 2 hear from u...COME TO OMAN!!! when r u leavin 4 miri again? will u b able 2 get a pc? get jo 2 finally get n account! okie me g2g now...it's like 6:30am here...gettin ready 4 skool :D. byeeeeee!!! mwah..tc of urself n luv ya loads, pat
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo pat its gr8 to hear tht school was THE BOOOMB:P hehehe i m awake hehehe watchin football.. life is GOOD and bad made some new friends online and got tot know ppl better how abt u??.. fung is in kota baru ..and we are all goin to hang out on tuesday vefore arin leaves :'(   hope he has a good time in canada :> anyways cya online laters if ur awake :P 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey every1!! omg......1st day of skool was de BBBBOOOOOMMM!!!! :D but i think my ears r gettin deaf.....ppl yellin n screamin when they c each other...hehe. anyways, hows life ppl? yong again..ill get online at 10:00pm ur time. but than again..i can only stay 4 n hour..than i wont b on till.......4 am ur time again (i bet u wont b awake :P) okie..me g2g now..ill mail u a LOOOONG mail later k sweets. ciao! xox, pat
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ok im online now
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      loool......talk bout b'ball!!! it kicks ass..anyways..i get online at 6:00pm my time...which is 10:00pm ur time :) okie?? kewl kewl..anyways..yah i no jac..we always talk bout confusin stuff..but at least it's interestin :P..hehe j/k!!! anyways..wats up ppl?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heyy..any1 on??
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah...squash???!!! hahah .. ok pat i ll meet u online then we can chat just tell me th time and date  and i ll be there .. and i sent 2 e-mails to u and i already changed my password so don't worry ..and i don't arin fung and jac read ur mails .....trust me.. and chat to u next time i see ya online   ciaow and btw jac atleast get a better sport !! plz  :P  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hmmm......squash is a really kool sport. who plays squash? y so little ppl toking. we can tok about squash. there is lots of things to tok about squash.....the rules, the ball, raquets, court. anyways.....ppl, plz try to type stuff if u do af the time. we cant depend on brian and patrina to entertain us toking about confusing stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      wat? who's actin weird? who's confused? huh.......ok now im confused...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      get onlineeeeeeeeeeeeee!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heya..yep ill reply ur mail soon...we're over derek's house now..he sez hiya to everyone. n..oi i wanna appologize if josh was bein a jerk online..he gets protective bout me. dat cud b gd n cud also b bad in sum ways..but i still love de guy..owez will. anyhoos..yah i kinda guess every1 else cud read dis..so i wont b trypin anythin personal..dat cums in ur mails..i can mail u..u juz WONT MAIL ME BACK half de time!!!!!! :( though..i was thinkin, arin n fung n em knows ur password..so how m i spose 2 no dat they dont read ma mails 2 u..n dat u dont go on my account n read my mails while they're around!!! bout de pix..np :) ill post sum up of me n de GURLS soon..cos they think all de pix i have of em r bad..so they dont lemme post em up. especially a pic of sian..de gurl i sed dat looks EXACTLY like Maggie..cept wid a browny-blondy colour hair. i get online..definately at 6:00pm my time..which will b 10:00pm ur time. so dont sleep so early! man i miss u loads! listen..bout dis whole marc situation..im gonna leave it till nxt summer..till than nm will happen. i guess dats it 4 now..ill reply ur mails soon..n bout "choo-choo train" (where de hell did u get dat nick from????) anyways..yah bout her..ill summarize it.."be a MAN" :)!! g2g now..ciao!! luv ya, pat
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      y are u actin so werid or maybe i m jus confused
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yep?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pat thanks for  joinin hehe.. i already replied ur mail so reply mine asap cheerrs mate :P   and u need to tell me more stuff haha anyways don't write any personal stuff here coz other ppl are readin too haha just send as much mail to me as possible .. anyways tell me when u are coming online so we can chat :P ciaow pat btw thanks for the pictures
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey! well it's 12:50pm/am rite now..n i cant sleep :P im over at josh's house now..so i doubt im gonna sleep anyways...hey de pix i sent u guys of my friends here...de pc kept sendin de same pix n not de ones i added..so sori if it kept on repeatin......anyways...brian reply my mail!!!! take care!!! sweet dreams...nite! xox
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heeeeeey.....brian...de pix r cumin soon...so delete ur mails so it can fit
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yong..thx 4 addin me in......so um, wat now? :P
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo nothing to do, man is there anyone else in this site or am i like chattin to my self hehe........................ arin's party tomorrow!!!! yes man .. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      SHHEEEEEEEEEESSSSSSS SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO HIGHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ABOVE ME!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! hehehe cool songs dudes feelin like playing it hehehe if anyone knows the tabs or anything send to to e LPAZ and than YOU!!! hehehe so sup sup guys ... COZ SHE"S SO HIGHHH ABOVE ME!!!! ;P
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      good news... i changed my piano lesson to 10.30 in da mornin... so ill be finished be 11.30... which still isnt dat early... but normally i would still be asleep at dat time...hehe..... my exam... i dunt think i can change it... so im not sure if i can go to malacca...   And wats happenin tommorow... at wat time?... cause wtv it is... i might also have to pick up my pasport... which should take around 30min...at least dats wat my parents say... so i can onli turn up after 12... so it kinda sucks... but then again... im also normally asleep at 12... =P   oh and brian can u get ur mom to buy da stuff... cause i cant get it...  okay ciao for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahah cool stuff fung :> * thumbs up* hehehehe  okok if u can change ur times post it up lar .. ok ok and yea i am serious to bring jia weii hehe.. i have 4 free tickets to the water world and safari thing .. yea hahahahah ok i ll kidnap u :P  hahahah ok ok plans again  tuesday... i m goin to the drivin range at around 8 something ..  play golf until like 10 .. something ok ok  we need to call ppl . ok   ill put the ppl we need to call besides us ... ok  jon chay, dawn , fatin , elanie , em , verun , menz , greg , AND JIA WEII !! any body else just post them up... really i think nobody actuallys checks this sit out except us :P hehehe hmmm...  i have a feelin tht the gurls wouldn't wana come hehehe.. but we need to check anyways .. fung can u help me call some of the ppl.... once u called and got the answer just post it up ok??? we need to do this by today..
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi ppl... added some stuff again... well im havin trouble plannin for da week... got piano lesson on tues evenin... and piano exam on thursday at 12... so kinda sucks... but ill see wat i can do.. try to change da time and all... hope i can... ill tell u guys if anythin changes in my plan... oh and brian u can kidnap me if u want.... or else i can always just go after 12.30.. exam onli around 15 min... and i would also go with plan C if i can... o well gtg ... ciao for now.... btw seriously r u serious abt bringin jia weii?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      arin can't come because his dad is scared tht he will get sick .. so he can't come ... hahahahahaha ok i ll try to get jia weii .. if ur serious :P  heheh  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      brian....is arin coming to melacca with us or not? jia weii can come to mallaca with us. he'll make things fun
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah true jac .. i don't think anyone else even looks at the dam site heheheh.. ok ok ... so we are goin to do plan C ok ok .. so who else u wana ask to come???? i got some ideas..   ppl to come.:::     briana , jacalina , fung anus , arina , jon chay, dawn , em , elanie, fatin, ben teo , jason , menz, verun, jia weii ... hmmm... if u want anyone else or want to cancell anyone out just post it up!! and if u wana come just post something up sayin tht u wana come okok?? bagus.. hmmm wut else ...... its night time and jac is watch 102 dalmatians...    ok my plans for next week if u guys wana know.. which u prob wouldn't :P ok         monday  - nothing               tuesday - sleepin over arins                 wednesday - arin's party, sleeping over                                         thursday - melacca with jac and maybe fung                       friday - come back from melacca          ok i need to fit jia weii in there some way coz i promised him to gosomewhere       anyways ciaow if any ideas plz post :>   cheers mate 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      if we take PLAN C, who else will come to paint ball with us dude? neways....the only ppl who are actually typing in this site is brian fung arin chay and me. where's everybody else?
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo guys .. fung and jac.. are u guys goin to sleep over in arin's house on tuesday?? if u are i have A PLAN!!!!!... ok ok .. listen up ..i mean read up!! .. ok  heres plan A: first u guys come over my house and bermain bola sepak then from my house we go to arin's house by taxi.   PLAN B:  go to arin's house and help him move the drum set .. if he doesn't do it on monday..  PLAN C : come over my house and go to the extreme park and do paint ballin ;) so CHOOSE!!.  btw fung .. hmmm if u have paino exam...hmmm... i got a list of stuff ok ok  1:can u put the exam earlier?  if yes go to question 2, if no go to question 3  2: then we go after you finish lar 3: ill try to get my parents to make it later . if i get my parents to go later go to question 4, if NO!! then go to question 5 4: then we must come back later on friday 5: JUST SKIP THE DAM THING OR ELSE ILL KIDNAP U!!! heheheh  ok call me fung  cioaw cioaw
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung, what thing on the right?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey evelyone! im damn bored, sitting here in my office... i just wanted to say thanks to the thunder birds for the really really cool, and special keychain they gave me, it really means a lot to me... hope u guyz  enjoyed pirates of the carabiean, and no problemo for the flowers... now ur making me sound gay! it was from my mum! anyway, i said thanks to her many times for u guyz, and.....ya.  Ok, fung, what do u mean it is going to be soo different without me? i mean.. think about how different it will be 4 me, without all of u guyzzzz, :'( and by the way, i am going to miss u ppl... i love u *breaks out into tears* anyway... i haf to go, so ciao for now... ps: sorry for getting mad for trying to figure out what u guyz were doing.. hehe love Barney
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      and can someone tell me wat da  thing at da right side is supposed to do?.... i dunt really get it
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi ppl... hope u like da new title thingi i put in.... any ideas on wat else i can add?... and i could change da title if u ppl dunt like it..=P.. hehe...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys good morning =)   ok JAC......so therefor i need to do ma add maths hw ..DAm.. heheh jk .. need to do loads of work today.. hey fung finding nemo didn't take 10 yrs hehehehe ooppss took 3 years -2 years for the graphics and 1 yr for the idea ..so DUde Boi hehe.. ok ok wut else do i wana say..hmmm...... can't wait for arin's party :) goin to be great =) and does anyone know when fatin is coming back??  oohh yea if jac doesn't read my blog then i just want to say thank q jac for workin so hard on the thunderfriends blog :) haha and AGAIN I WANA say THank u to arin for the BUNGA BUNGA hhehe ..i know my malay sucks jhehehe... okok so anyways need to eat papaya hehe  ciaow guys 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      found a new skin. neways, the thing on te right does not work....nebody noes how to work it?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hi ppl... damn bored.. so decided to post somethin here.... Pirates of carabiean damn cool... got free tickets... so went to watch with brain... sorrie jac... couldnt ask u to come got 2 tickets onli... and arin is on church camp...  anywayz bset week of my life lar this week.... everyday somethin fun... from throwin stuff in da pool to jumpin in and out of LRTs... damn chun =).... And i would also like to thank arin for da very nice flowers he sent us... damn chun...hey arin, be sure to thank ur parents on behalf of my family.... thanx again...  man i cant belive arin is leavin... hey btw hope u like da present we got u... u got damn pissed of tryin to figure out wat we were doin..=P..... life is never gonna be da same next year... cant belive school is startin soon.... gonna be damn diffrent especially without arin... o well ....no more to write... so ciao for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      brian...we dun haf to cancel. we can go to arins party after add math tuition.  we go to arins thing at arond 12 or 1 lah. hey, i just realised u can u HTML on this  blogger thingy. .......neways....i'm trying to get new skins for this blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys..i  also want to say thank you to arin's family and ofcourse arin ..for the flowers.. and i can't wait for ur party heheh.. and  i hope u liked the present tht me,fung and jac got u .. mr kapor,, =) anyways jac..   we need to cancell add maths tution on wednesday coz of arin's party!!!.. so tell ur mummy plz hehehe... anyways thts all for now.. over and out  GF.. u know wut it means right???......... bagus =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi everybody. i just wanna thank arin and his whole family for the flowers. their so kind. arnt they? yes they are. i feel like crying. i also want to say lalala pohpoh.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HOWDI HO!!! man i have nothing to do and i m chattin to joel and listening to micheal learns to rock ..and theres thunder and lightin every where its like i am in world war 2 hehehe even if i wasn't alive then,.,,, or was I????!!! :P haha so sup guys any news ????!!! and jokes?!! Or is ur Life just PLAIN BORIN?!!!! IF IT IS CALL ME  ;) esp ..if ur a panas ayam hahahaha .. jk jk 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      lalala poh poh. hi guys. i'm feeling bored. theres nobody online. i am trying to past my time wisely. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo dudes! its dawn hahaha hope y'all enjoy your holidays! stay cool! =P
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEy Guys this is a promise to ALl of u here... i am goin to make my life intrestin and go for  adventureS,,!!! i don't wana live an ordinary life ..   LIVE LIFE TO THE FULLEST!!!! ADVENTURE!!!!! GO GO GO GO 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys, I just joined into this blog. Hahaha, mine is www.jonchay.blogspot.com Its about my life too! Yea it could be boring for you guys too, catch you up later, i needa update my blog. Cyaz  The LiGhTbUlB Lover
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      GOOOOOOOOODDDDDDDDDD MMMMMORRRRNING.!!! hey guys for new ppl .. here are our individual blogs .. for the thunderbirds = ) ....  i m not sure if the bold eagle and black hawk has one.. well mine is www.Mxtreme.blogspot.com,     jac's ruffryderz.blogspot.com but guys BEWARE ITS JUST ABT OUR LIVESSSS...sooo might be borin to u guys ; )   Cya Guys ..      GF........hmmmmmmmm tht doesn't look right.... ok ok green falcon ; ) ...hahah cya 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl.... bald eagle here.... last 3 days damn cool lar... and damn u ppl who threw me in da pool...hehe... =P well hope we do somethin like that again..... damn tired.... but im still up at 1am for some reason... well da fun for me is finally over.... my mom wont let me leave da hse for quite a while..... o well... too bad for me then......
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YO MAN... call me the Green Falcon ... i see u already met ma friends the golden phonenix hehehe.. there are 2 others the bold eagle and th black Hawk heheh .. together we make the THUNDER BIRDS!!!!!!!!!!! ooooooooOOOOOOOOOOOhHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH yeaaa
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi this is the golden phoenix(jac). for those who are new to this like me.....this is where u just type anything like crap dung shit poo. when u feel like wrting stuff then come write. anyways we hope u enjoy ur stay with the thinderbirds and friends! ROCK ON PUNKS! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo guys .. today was COOOLIN .. man first time we did soo many excitin things hahahahah hope there will be more to come ;)  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi, im a new member of this  place, and im like cool surfer dude type... i got long blonde bob marley style hair. i like boobs
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      testing 123....this is the GENISIS of the THUNDER BIRDS and FrIeNdS!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey fung could add more links...... like the newcastle site or fhm (just a thought) ;D
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung.....can u figure out a way to make a link to our archives. i wanna look at our previous posts and i'm sure other ppl would want to too. u can edit our archives site by goin to settings if u didnt already noe. only our most recent posts can be seen now.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yea brian....go to low yat plaza....its very cheap stuff there.....hehe. wussup dudes and dudettes. lets add more ppl to this site. but add ppl tht we like lar ook? wut do u guys think. it gets a bit boring here so i guess we add some more ppl. post up ur ideas
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Brian i see u want to buy a thumb drive, go to low yat plaza instead.... its very cheap stuff there.... i got my 256 usb 1.1 thumb drive for only RM 150...  oh yea and fung do u still want to share the 24 season 2 thing?.... rite nite all :D
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      today is such a crappy day....crappy crappy crapppyyyyy dayyy!!!!  -eLaniE-
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha hey chay dude i think thts enough of the jedi..s stuff :P hahah  hey u know arin called me this morning BUT I WAS IN THE SHOWER!!!! NOOO.. what kinda friend am I?!! hey arin sorry mate i was in the shower but thanks for callin ;) hey today is Pitcha's birthday ..happy birthday! hmm.. but first needa invite her.... ahh ok ok and it was greg;s birthday also.. haha cool main.. so wazup guys..??!! hey fung wei u goin to the club right? after gym then me and u can go to pyramid to buy the pen drive for computer studies :>..ahh hey i feel like eatin roti canai..for some reason .. ok ok thts all cya cya  Green Falcon
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      To all you Jedis out there!!! The code shall be followed to be in the Jedi Academy: There is no emotion, there is peace There is no ignorance, there is knoledge There is no death, there is the FORCE...  hehheheh
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ohtayz guyssss...so post and publishhh okiezz..haha...linkin park have gotten kinda weird since thier last album..no offensce to n e one..i mean they are okies and everythinggg but is it just be or did theri first album sound alot better then their second? n e wayss...ARIN!! get u ass back here!! haha...oh well...knock ur selves out guyss...im outttt :D   -LuV- -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yea one more thing.. if u guys have problems just say it lar :P then we can go beat them up MAUAHAHAHAHA jk jk we are peaceful follow the code of the jedi hahaha  cya
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yea its true but lets hope we invite only friends and not some random ppl :P. haha u hurt ur back ?! haha so did i the lower part haha well today was kinda  good day.. fatin told me tht they beat the ppl they were playin( no idea who) hahahah.. and i asked one of them ;) THEY ARE HOT DUDES!! ..nah just jokin arin's hotter ;P so anyways they told me tht they were trashed hahah and tht gis have a good team haha so thts good. one more thing lets hope we can beat them again tomorrow and CHAY forget aobut her comon dude feel the facts flow with the force and COMON dude haha cya cya  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl.... good to know that we r attracting more ppl.... da site is called thunderbirds and FRIENDS =P... emphasis on "Friends"..... anyway... yea man... we won football today... hurt my back... dunno how though... dunt really think it was football..... and arin.. cant wait for december man... we must go melaka this time...=) and chay just forget abt her man... it would be better off.... trust me... and well abt da birds pictured... ill change them this weekend k...  anyway...cya ppl for now....buh bye.. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl....its ben..... i heard that the linkin park concert is only 18 and over... does anyone noe anything?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahah hey elanie u need to press post and publish to post it on the site  JUST REMIND EVERYONE OF U GUYS!! esp ARIN :P hahah wattapp?? hmmm... we won soccer TODAY!!! after a VERy long time... maybe our !0m skill is comin back :> haha yea anyways its a team game.. seems like the site has ppls now so thts kinda cool .hahaha so dudes and dudettes .. whats my name!! haha sorry nothin else to say :P.  u know johan suddenly is actin dam kind to drew haha hey anyways ciao dudes  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guyss...eLanie hereee...wattaapp?! can u believe that i couldnt register my name becoz someone already had it?!! i mean!! thats my name!! haha....oh welll... muahz -Luv- -Elanie-
     

    
</post>

<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hehehehe.....i dunno wut is going on here. anyways.....who wanna go watch linkin park?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yea MAIn and guys remember we still need to plan our trip around the world :P remember we promised and we cant break promises hahahaha.. haha forget about leon lar haha and mel :P.. haha and i m still a long way from playing for malaysia ..DUDE u know whats our problem in soccer every lunch time ??!!!! WHERES THE LOVE?!?!WHERES THE TEAM SPIRIT??!!! thts where we go wrong dude :P we are the 10 M warriors muahaha .. and i think fun will be able to go with her haha so dun put him down and with the prom thing .. guys are really cheap skates lar hahaha no offence guys but seriously we are suppose to buy the tickets hahah but as i said boys are cheap skates hahahaha.. and about the play... hmm.. we must get our star guess ;) kapoor haha  we can call it " JAC STRIKES BACK" muahaha and ARin's our hero ;) and i can be yoda :> :>  haha ok guys gtg cya dudes
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thats cool, you guys can get a apartment, live side by side and stuff, sounds really really kewl!!! Yea, it is love at first sight. She likes Leon cause of the accent, looks and stuff lah. Anyway, walaooo i knew brian will be able to represent Malaysia man! I have trust in u man! Brian BOLEH!!! (or tak boleh lah...) I know who fungs gonna ask too. I sense the disturbance in the force..... yesss......... that girl is gonna be asked by sumone b4 Fung.......... fat chance man! Dude, isn't the guys gonna have to pay the tickets for the girls? (thats why most guys go ALONE) At least they can still dance with the girl right??!?! But if ya want it a very magical night. Then u go with the girl lah! Yea man! I like my lightsaber stuff. Brian, this year's play, maybe we can put up a saber fight!!! And I can construct a lightsaber and install a rod on it!!! Sounds intresting eh? Hhahahaha, imagine this man.... Brian, Fung and Jon Chay: Stunt Coordinator/REAL JEDI KNIGHTS!!! Hahahha, anywayz, gotta get back to work man. Ciao dudes! Peace out!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha dudes we are like a big family ;P hahahahaha.. next time we must get an apartment together guys our own episode of "friends" hahahahaha...  ...yesterday went to em's house was quite cool dude then went to chay's house and had a light saber fight haha ..    so hows everyONE?! tomrrow another week of school ..soo much hw lar. ANYWAYS real madrid lost to velencia ( dun know spellin) haha 2-0 and arsenal beat newcastle 3-2 OH YEA .. haha go arsenal !! u know wut?? we shuold get more good friends to come and write on the stuff .....oh hey arin did i tell u i m playing for a soccer CLUB!!! haha its cool sponsored for adidas and we get our own buss and everything haha.. remember we must bring malaysia to world cup ;) and jac as our coach haha ..  so anyways ppl one more thing.. about mel.. hmmm... i seriously dun get something how can mel like some1 is 3 weeks hmm.. haha maybe love at first sight haha yea. anything else i wana say.....hmm.. nothing much thts all.. OH arin btw WE miss YOu dude!! .. four of us makes up the THUNDERBIRDS !!! haha   and i wana ask some 1 to the prom but the force is tellin me tht she will say no :  ciao dudes and dudettes .. take care and peace out 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha, u obviosly didn't read the blogs last time ;) yea, i'm over meiping now. I'm a new guy man! Jon Chay! Ain't no Jonathan Chay no more!! Thx to brian, fung, ppl who helped me. Brian did the most lah, frankly. And now i'm a new person. If u so happen to find out who i like, arin, plz don't get mad or sumthing. I know it feels weird, or it doesn't sound right. But yea, i can tell u how it happened and all next time man. Leon? He is a pretty good guy. Lets hope mel made the right choice. Anyway, won't u come back b4 prom starts? if you do, maybe u could come to the prom too! I'm sure everybody wanna meet u again.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey everyone... im glad to hear from u, jon, uve been quiet, anyway, i  hope that got will answer whyatever u prayed fot.. and who did u ask to prom?? tell me tell me? u over that girl yet... ? k, anyway take care and bye bye haf fun at prom!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl, I'm back in track for Blogger ;) Sup guys. Good to hear u again Arin, hope you'll cope with everything there. They're right, the thunderbirds have a missing piece and all. Can't wait to see u again man. Anyway, yeap! Leon is going with Mel. Hahaha, sounds like i'm cursed right? dealing with the fact that got turn down so many times... Anyway, last night i was in church and i prayed to god outside the church. Something happen... when i finished, a bulb just off. All the bulbs except this bulb is off. Sounds weird or stupid but its really cool. You should have seen it man. Anyway, i can't tell u wut i prayed for. But its really magical. Again, can't wait for arin to come back. Hope to see u again. Ciao man. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dudes!!! i am still here... its just that im not there!! and btw, ill always be here and part of da thunder birds! anyway....u guyz haf to introduce me to leon.... don care bout zaid..hehe, cause leaons going with mel.. and tell him that i will kick his ass if he doesnt treat mel well at prom... hehe..but he has to be a cool guy... and ya, anyway.. what happened to faisal..? hey who are u guyz going to prom with. u know what wud be cool... if fung and em got back together again..that would be sooooooo good! k, anyway... i know like ppl from like mexico, and they are really funny.. hehe.. anyway, i gtg  bye bye take care and stuff
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl..... yea prom is comin up soon.... and i got no one to ask.... so it kinda sucks.... and brian who u thinkin of askin?.... anyway.. school seems to get more borin everyday.... and its sure diffrent with out arin... onli 3/4 of da thunder birds left.... well got nothin else to say =P.. cya ppl
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys .. and kapor good to hear from u thought u forgot about us :P hahaha hey anyways.. ur welcome jit.. and updates  welll.... its true every1 likes mel.. ok now leon is goin to the prom with mel .... ziad is goin with steph.. and hahah who are u guys goin with???... im thinkin of some 1 but i dun think she will say yes though.. hmm anyways been goin to loads of soccer traning 4 times a week.. hey arin .. u done any fishing over there ???!!! and dude u need to send some pics of ur friends and gurl friends :P hahaha.. ok ok just keep writin stuff. and one more thing chay is pissed of coz mel is goin to the prom ith leon ..hmm... its not a big deal chay ...   anyways cyaq dudes
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung i think the red looks good too. newasy...wussup guys....i just got back from school and i have nuthing to do. i'm going to play football later. ummm.....oh well cya
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey arin... good to hear from u =)... and good to know that ur gettin on really well in school.... we miss u so much.. damn lonely... and hard lar this year... im hardly in any of brian and jac's classes... so im like alone.... da teachers and da homework are also not very pleasent... but overall not too bad... and man u wont belive da number of ppl starting to like mel... damn weird lar.... those ppl include jon chay and menzie.. and others....  Anyway brian, jac adn chay... wat is jit tim tokin abt?... i dont seem to know wat is goin on in da world anymore....  And yea did somemore changes to da site... i think blue looks better though.... okay... cya ppl for now....
     

    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo arin. no wonder u didnt come the the site for a long time. anyways....gr8 to noe that u r adjusting to ur skool well. HEY ARIN! so wut changes in ur life haf u made? oh welll.....i've got nuthing else to say other i miss u. hehe. post somore stuff ya? cya
     

    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hello evelybody...sorry i havenn't posted for so long...busy gone for an out trip(camping) i went saiiiiiling! it was so much fun... like on the boat, if u looked up, u could see thousands of stars up in the sky.... me and some friends were lookin up and talking and stuff bout like how it is good to make a change in life ,because withoput changes in ur life, you wouldnt really get anywhere in life... ya u know.. so its not that bad. k, boarding life isnt that bad.. actually it's pretty cool! u get to hang out withaall ur friends all the time... ya..  and  yesterday was so cool! i was like walking down to the feild with some ppl, to where everybody was... and suddenly someone says Hey Arin! then everyone is like HEY ARIN!!! then i was like .... 'hey cool' ppl know me...hehe, anyway... school is pretty easy, but its boring lah, how bout u guyz... what happened about fais??  hey yong! did u get that mail frop pat saying something bout lay off and three chicks and whores and crap... pretty freaky.. anyway, i gtg now, bye everyone, take care...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl....just wanna tnk brian for addin me on this site. Well...not much to write abt today..except for the fact that i nearly got 1 damn week detention coz i forgot that stupid info on that village by the sea..well...who cares anywayz.....dunno wut to say when i meet ribena..sigh..brian, jac and jon should noe who i am talkin abt.. Anywayz..write more laterz
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yay.. auto bold works.... now everything ppl type nomatter wat it is (bold or not)... would be bold.. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl....added summore stuff.... nice to know that ppl atually come here.....and brian i think i can auto bold da text.... should i try?..... anyway wassup ppl... not much hw today... so got sometime to do this... and is everyone goin to prom?... and brian who r u thinkin of askin?....
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       hahah wah loae soo late dude dude ... haha i didnt know anyone else read the site :P .. ohh well we are more famous than we think ..hahahaha... so anyways its no reason to not write what we feel ..right !! ya MIAin.. hahaha anyways soccer traning was fun.. piggy bank jason :P.. scored 1 goall!! yay.. well not tht happy :P.. soo tired i have like soccer traning like every day :  hahaha and i m still thinkin about prom i dun think the gurl i wana ask out will say yes :  one more thing.. hey fung if we bold our words it will be easier to ready :>   cya guys  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hahahha! why the hell did u call fais my name in the first place?!?!?!? Nice background u got for this website man. Goodiee! sorry, i didn't post up any messages at all, so yea. Really great effort u put in this web fung. Anwayz, its 11:30 gotta sleep now. Ciao guys
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... i actually found out that ppl do read this blog.... like fatin and faisal... cause faisal got pissed at me for callin him chay and he read it bcs fatin was readin it... anyway.... SORRIE FAIS...  and for all u ppl who read... please post soemthing up...   And yea i think my background is too dark.... should i make it lighter....   anyway arin... hope life is cool for u... we r stuffed with work here.... and eya brian is right.. we should at least go out once every 2 week if not every week.... okay gtg now.... ciao ppl
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      nothing much i have soccer training at 6:30 and i need to finish all my hw quickly.. oh shit i just remembered tht tomorrow is wed .. soccer training under 15's hah anyways wazup?? cya tomorrow 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo sup yall! heheh.....how come only brian and fung comes to the site. there is no point saying tht anyways....cos ppl still wont come to the site and wont read this. oh well....sup brian...and fung. and arin.....come to the site dude. how r u? reply now.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       cool stuff fung " thumbs up" me and fung walked back from sportsunlimited hahah cool lar about 3 - 4 hours walk .. haha had fun  dun wana write everything coz its too much.. well anyways me and fung and the ppl were talkin about school and stuff and i think we should like go out like at least once in 2 weeks and enjoy ourselves .. coz theres soo much pressure and i dun wana be crazy :>.. anyywayss soo much hw to do.. goin to do it tomorrow .and jedi knights 3 is cool been playin it most of the time.. hmmm.. what else .. everyone is in sarika's party thts y there is no one online so tht kinda sucks.. and everyone is talkin about prom .. i know fung is goin but i dunt know if jac is .. hmm.. jac are u goin to the prom this yr ?   anyways got to go.. and fung good job.."soo clever one :P " over and out and one more thing we need to make the font stand out in the background  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung, the site looks gr8 man. do somemore! heheh......anyways....since the site looks good, wee need ppl to write on it too ok? so post anything u want to post even if it is rubbish. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppls.... as u can see... did summore changes... gonna do more later.... but dunt really feel like it rite now.....o well.... we dunt seem to postin much stuff here.... wat happened....???.... and hey arin.. hope u havein fun over there... we all miss u loads.... and i mean loads!!!!.... damn borin nowadays without u... =(... anyway ... ciao for now... buh bye
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      nvm bout fais....just let him be. yes. uh huh. yea baby. neways.......hey arin. wuusup ma nigger dude guy! how're u? i hope u didnt forget us already. i noe u wont forget us. i think. oh well, how skool dere? is it like a cool surfer dude kind of thing? or is it a boring harry potter skool. take care of urself there ya? eat lots of cabbage there. i heard the cabbage there is very nice. ummmm........post ur reply sooooon. we really misss u. guess wut. its september! tht means ur coming back on december! tht means we only haf to wait for another 3 and a half months! oh yes! ok.....now i gtg. cya ciao avoir cing tao teh WEEE WEEEEEEE!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ya maiN... dunoh whats wrong with him lar... BUt nvm dudes ... so sup guys ,,, so much hw these few days ..and only FIRST WEEK!!!!!!!! hey guys tryin out for under 15's football on wednesday ..and btw what cca's are u takin ?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yea... faisal is turning into chay... nah jk jk...chay is better than him... faisal is just being weird... and hateing da whole world all of a sudden.... and arin... did u get in da football team?... hope u did... wait did u try out in da end?... well hope life is great there for u... school is kinda stressful here.... shit load of hw on da first week... =(... anyway... kinda got to ciao now... so cya ppl..
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo VEE DUDE. how are u ? when are u goin for ur camp ?? hey arin are u the best in soccer over there??!! oh yea arin u need to press post and publish not post.. coz we cant see what u have written :P.. hehe do u have a gf pver then oh yea btw there are 2 new guys in ur class.. ziad and leon.. man i have no idea whats wrong with faisal he keeps havin these mood swings. .. anyways got tot ciao   Cya guys .. keep cool n WHATS MY NAME!!!   i m the coll chi wa wa ..oh yea :P 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      dude! im online rite now... hey, u know what... i kipped rugby yesterday cause i had to go and try out for a soccer team... but i didnt go in the end...and ppl here are crap at soccer, not as good as ppl in our school, but the rugby is really good! i mean im probably the crappiest t rugby...hehe, anyway, ill try to mail here as much as i can... and i gtg now, so eeryone take care, and have fun in yr 10, bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yay! arin injured himself! now he can come back to malaysia to see the doctor! YIPEEE!!! neways....hope u recover alin. how e u mian....how come u dun come online anymore. oh yea....u haf skool. neways...i gtg now cya
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... its in the middle of school, and im sitting in the library with some ppl using the com... i have nothing better to do! fung.. yea, ill go to melaka, don worry... hehe, i have rugbbby today!  and im gonna get my ass kicked pretty soon.... i already have an injured shoulder, and both my knees are screwed too.... k, i gtg, bye bye take care and all... 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl.... its cool that u got to met loads of ppl there arin... and hot chicks too ;)..  over here... schools starting quite good.... there is 2 new guys in our class and no gurls=(... damn.... o well... scored an own goal today in fottie today =(... headerd it da wrong way.... and we will call u... definately... but we have to get a whone card first.... so maybe next week.. =).. really miss u.... cant wait to december... this time we would make it to melaka okay... anyway... ciao for now... have to go study... and at least get off da pc... cause my dad is scoldin me
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      helo everyone.... guesss what, i went bowling today! and i got the highest score! 120pts.. hehe, anyway... i met loads of new ppl today, alot of them are from korea and hong kong... thats cool, korean chicks are hot! and i met 2 twins from hong kong in yr 11.. they r cool too, they are bonita and um... something else..  hey pat, how come u dont mail here anymore? i miss all of u like crap... and glad to hear that the bet is still on. hey, brian...post some pics up ok, and ill try too... k, i gtg help my m um do the dinner, bye bye bye ...take care ppl. my phone number is (from malaysia) 0012505197199, thats all, get a calling card, but dont ring from 10-12 in the morning ur time ok, ciao xoxoxo xxx xxx ... bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha man arin take some pics of the gurls lar..:P hey dawn told me tht will be a new gurl in our school ..hahah... man i was lookin through my sis pics then i found the adverts tht we did :P remember "100 PLUS " hahahah dam funny ... i wana post up some pics on the site ... hey arin btw whats ur phone no. ? need to call u atleast once a month :P  hahaha.. keep informin us about stuff ..and yup the bet is still on ... all the money in our wallets at the time :P hahaha AND THE FEAR FACTOR BET !!!! i won :> hehehe.. got to go look at more pics   hey arin dude.. we all miss u :> so cya in december  and ill see everyone else in school tomorrow :>   Ohhhhhhhhh Chi wa wa   cya guys  \ /                <>   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys.....try to thinkof some links we can put on this site
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ho arin..wussup dude. hope u like ur new skool and new friends and your new girls. oh yeaaaa.. btw, when u wanna post on this site, u click the POST & PUBLISH button. not the PUBLISH butoon k? neways....skool starts tomorro for us. just cant wait mian.....i wanna see JULIE! tht was random.......the bet is still on man. ummm.....keep on posting on this site ok? cya 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      AHHHHH... finaly! a computer...it feels all smooth and nice...donkey! k, first day of shcool was sit boring, especially when u dont know anyone... but two hot chicks came up 2 me and this guy, jeff and asked for our names..and we were too bur to remember theirs... :P one was called marriel...hehe, anyway its saturay today, and i just went to the guitar store and the guy was too scared to teach me haha... so he sed he wil teach me blues... weiird huh? btw.... ppl here suck at soccer mian, excep for the year 12's theyr 12's are not as good as yr 11's in gis...   k, boarding school can be fun, and it can be shit! sometimes i just sit in the room and think and think and think.... bout u guyz, and what u could be up 2, and i just wish i uld b there! :'(. we have to sleep at 10:15, and 10: 45 on week ends..but the cool thing bout boarding is thatu can go out with anyone any time u want, and go and do stuf and stuff...! but we r not allowed into the girls rooms! that suks! oh yea guyz, thanks for the wah wah wow woo pedal mian! and i got fung wei's amp! hey guyz im just gonna mail here for now ok? unless it is personel stuff i haf to say 2 ppl...  hey jac, AAAAAHHHHH BOO BOO, AH GOO GOO to u 2 ok....i miss ur boo booness.... go lickatitsdickpissshit... it rhymes... cool AYE.. hey pat... i found out u have a canadian accent...ask brian y..hehe 'im going oot,'  'i'ts all aboot'...hehe u guys probably have no idea what im talking boot... hehe, oh ya...u know i have rugby 4 times a week! monday, tues, wednesday, and thursday! and it is for 2 hours each time! tiring huh?   hey jac...is the bet still on with u ad brian that u wont get a girlfren this yr? i bet u will...somone like chae won.... ok, that was random..hehe, hey when does school start?? and pat, how is school..and everything... ? ill give all of u guys a call again asap ok??  but i think i 4 got ur numbers........hehe, jokin, just being like dar*l...he's a dick... hey, il be back in december so make sure all of u are here ok??!?!?!?!?!?! or ill....umm..do something...ya. k, ppl here are gererally quite nice...but not as good as in kl... : (... im talking but frends here...  anyway...  gttg do stuff, so u all take care and dont change!! miss u all, bye bye...luv u, all the babes! ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys back from miri i found new meaning to life : ) ooohh yea ok whats up..?  pat i already helped jo get an e-mail account just go check ur mail... hope u guys had a gr8 hoilday and i can't wait to go back to school : ).. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      AAAAAHHHHH BOO BOO. AH GOO GOO! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl.... just came online.... cause im bored:P... hey arin heard u called faisal today... he called me up for some reason to tell me that... and brag abt how he was da 1st person to tok to u damn weird... but i was busy... so didnt listen to him.... anyway pat... my email is tai_fung_wei@hotmail.com....   hey and arin... since ur school started... tell us wat its like there and stuff.... man and school gonna start here soon too... sucks lar.... its gonna be damn diffrent... being yr 10 and all... especially without arin.... gonna be damn diffrent.. =(.. well i got not much else to say... so cya ppl for now.. bye
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      sori i seem to like de word "damn" a lot......:|
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl..sori 4 not postin up here 4 ages! how is every1 doin?   lol...aaaaaaaaaaaaaaa yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong yong aaaaaaaaaaaaa...etc....yong i miss u like heeeeeeeeeeellllllll!!! y didnt u juz cum down to miri wif me when i was there! only now than u wanna go! stupid bastard...grrrrrrrrrrrr!!! i swear i can juz........argh!!!!! lol...actually im not dat pissed off as im makin it sound..but trust me..i am pissed at u!!!! keep me updated on jo! knowin her...she probably sed sum stuff bout me when u went there!!! aiya...i no her too well. hmm...BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! - dont worrie...i didnt type dat over n over again...it's called copy n paste. i actually do have a life to live :P hehe..j/k........ok u have to call me! or ill call u..ill like get dad to call ur dad...n juz snatch de phone from him to talk to u. lol...yah i wish! we'll well c ;D. hmm..wat else..oh yah..BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! BRIAN I MISS U!! hehe..ok nvm dont wanna start dat again..luv u loads!! tc of urself..xox. oh n of corz send ma regards to ur family k?! tell stez to mail me...not fwd's but e-mails :) thx! p/s: do me a fav..nxt time i take u to a mall to HANG OUT..do not..i repeat..DO NOT go to a book shop!! :P  anyways...hey arin..hows u! im glad u're keepin intouch!!! hows life goin since i last spoke to u?! u went online yesterday but than got off in a split second! :( i didnt get to say hi or anythin. oi wat hot chicks u all talkin bout?! u sud check out de guys...god damn!!!!!!!!!!! i swear they're amazing....though sum of em can have de worst attitudes...hehehe. yah fine..send de pix of gurls to de guys..but sum hot guy pix to me n fatin la! lol..tc & missin u loads! kiss kiss  fung & jac: hiya!! hows it goin? damn..fung gimme ur email add!!! i cant seem to find it on my msn list..i have it on..i no it's there..but too many ppl lah :(!!!!! n u dont mail me anyways!!! tc & missin u!  hey does marc cum on dis site? if he does........................STAY CRAZIE, STAY SWEET..BUT MOST OF ALL -----------------> STAY IN TOUCH!!! which u havent been doin lately. apart from de fwd's..i dont read fwds. but thx 4 de last one..it was real sweet. ok now i g2g...tc!! LOVE YA! mwah..ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      say hi. then say my name is arin. yup yup. neways.....remeber to take pics of the gurls dere and send it to us ya? and send us pics of u too. with hot chicks next to u. btw, 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      school starts tomorrow!! i dunno what to say 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahhaha, camp was dam chun man!!!! I like my group's play, it was cool. Anyway, Andrew Richards was very cool, Hahhahaha. I made a new friend! yay! Anywayz, great job ppl on everything they did in this camp!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hehe..damn..real sori..jakob 'felt' like writin dat.. n yes he's gone mad.. anyways..u guys have fun campin! brian....i didnt dat mail!!! :'(
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      camp is 2moroeeee..haha...omg!! this will be our last camp...damn mannn...haha....oh well..hope ya'll have loads of funnn if i dont see youu!!! :D:D 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha yea i cant wait for camp!!... hahaha still need to pack my bag today..and i feel sooo tired :P for some reason haha too much roti canai ;) haha 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i just can wait till camp. today was gr8 day. the fact tht we had double periods of soccer. i hope we get to do that more often.   we should haf more ppl blogging on this site. the people who are invited and never write anything should start to write atleast a few sentences. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yea the hoildays were gr8 except for some days tht i did nothing but played ps2 and computer but besides tht it was GR8! camp is comin sooon cant wait! Oh btw thanks for the presents guys :> i bought a new bag :> :> YAY!! hehehe me fung and chay are gonna prefrom in church on saturday im dam scared :P!!!  Oh btw kapor i got ur certificate for scuba divin ;) come back soon so tht i can give it to u yea? :P haha anyways ciao dudes 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz... damn da holiday is over... like tomorrow... =(... o well... sorrie never said anything for quite a while.... stuff kinda busy.. even during da holiday... if im not out... im doin hw... =P... cant wait till december... arin's comin bac... =)... =)... =)... yay...   anyway holiday wasnt so bad.... brian's bday... greg's bday.. go megamall... go pyramid with brian... go jamming... quite abit of stuff for a week... also upgraded my pc... damn chun now... 770mb ram... damn chun... hehe....  cant wait till next holiday... dunt feel like goin to school on monday... and shit got so much hw... but yay.. camp is on wednesday... bunking with brian... so its cool... jac is with ben.... dat kinda cool also.... cant wait... hehe...  okay.. got no more to say... ciao pplz
     

    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey arin dude man yea no way Surfer dude :P  haha everything is cool just watched run  down with fung WAy it was COOlin dude :> haha dun worry arin everyone will be here waitin for U!!.. haha get a mob to wait for u in the airport ;) hehehe yea i m goin to prom ..fung is also but jac isnt haha   take care dude ciao 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEY EVERYONE!! how are all u guyz?? so brian.... good that u won ur soccer tournament thing... anyway, how is everything else.. school and stuff. its pretty not bad here... hey, ill ive u guyz a call one of these days ok? so u better be at home!!!  hey, are u guys gonna be in kl in december?? cause im coming back on about the 14th or seomething... u should be rite? u guyz going to prom?? when is it?? k, anyway i gtg... ciao take care, bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YEs queen shoulda won :P but crest was better hahahahah jk jk queen was Gd ..what are u guys goin to do this hoilday?.. i wana goo some where ill prob need to plan something with fung haha .. ARGH my whole body hurts !!!! just came back from a soccer tournament GOT FIRST PLACE OH YEA!!.. felt good to win :P  hmm. what else to say... my parents are in genting highlands watchin the salsa thing..and CHealse VS ARSENAL TONIGHT BE THE OR BE ....SQUARE YES... ARSENAL ROCKS :> :> hehe also manU vs Leeds dun bother watchin tht match u already know leeds are goin to kick ManUtd's ass boy! yea ! .. ok ok thts enough.. and btw theres no one online now and days dudes we should like all come online at 7 or something :P  haha anyways ciao caio chiwawa  BT as In BTBy as in BBB as in BTB as in CT as in GF :> 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      sports day was so much fun....haha....chancellorrrrrr rulezzzzz!!! hahaha n e how...stupid queen have to go and try and beat us!! the best!!! no wayy mann!! hahaaha oh well...cheerleading wasnt too bad today....got to miss abit of english ;) haha..mr.moss was singing in class again...imitating Whitney Huston :S oh well...who else thought tht cheerleading queen sud have won?!?!?!!?!?! i mean they were so good...if only they didnt break tht stupid rule...no flipping ppl in the air and they flipped alina...they weren like original man..and im not even in queeen!! haha..and chancellor sudnt have gotten last!!! damn..haha..oh well...toodlez..   -LuV- -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      apa spaming? haha ok ok jac .. soccer teams have their own games :P  haha im soo tired and i m coming to school tomorrow ..cheer leadin first period i think .. and oh btw pictures hahahahah i look so bad in pictures :P .. well its mid term break next week .. hey fung u wana catch a movie or something ? and we can makan japanese in mid valley hahahaha :P YUMMy yes main .. ok ok guys ciao ciao hey jac u comin to sports barn for gregs thing ?  out and over   Chef Tain 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh i see. anyways.....heared tht linkin park concert was awesome. now i regreted not going. i also heard tht they did not let camaras in so the guards took away the camara batteries...hehe. i found out tht real madrid has their own video game.so does arsenal. so does man u. so does juve. so does chealsea. so does liverpool. so does aston villa. so does inter. so does leeds. so does barce. so does ajax. hahah they all have video games now. (http://www.codemasters.co.uk/clubfootball/)check. also max payne 2 is out! gtgt now cya
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      IIIIIIII AMMMMMMMMM SOOOOO SCARED !!!! SPORTS DAY !!!!! NO! YES! OF COURES AIN..Wwhat is tht about man? Oh yea ISEE .. OFcourse know .. is THT the thing which was in ur bag?!?! .. Oh yea i remember   ciao cioa 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh yes. hi arin wussup dude. hows it going. kool man...ure hafing fun at ur skool. so when r u gonna take pics of the girls and send it to us? i haf a really bad coughing problem.....and now my ribs hurt cos i haf been coughing to much. neways..... sports day tommorw. i'm not gonna make it. i just farted really loud. hey arin....can i ask u a question. are the people there taller or shorter than me? heheh.they must be shorter rite? and i bet u r like the tallest. just cant wait for u to come back. i'll be waiting at the airport. gtg n0w cya
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahahhaha ok ok ok :P ... hey fung WEI! what is this tht brian changes his mind easily !!! :P hahaha i mean... when i say i will do some thing i will!!! so u shadap lar :P hahahahaha..will today kinda sucks FOR one thing i m DAM close for getting kicked off the under 18's team coz i m injured and couldnt play a match.. and secondly ...today... is tuesday and thursday is sports day ;(  but i dun mind coz i dun think i can run anyways :> haha.. hey arin dude great to hear from u .. well fung wei is just sayin that nothing has been happening ..BUT!!! ofcourse there is something haha fung wei likes another gurl :> so ill tell u when i call u .. yea jac is sick jason is sick.... and i m running out of things to say.. LInkin park is comin to kl.... and PROM..yes yes yes PROM!.. haha ..  ok cya lar 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hahahahhaa, thats right ppl. My tuition teacher is Mr. Chay!!! And I get it for free... But the other ppl won't lah! Except for my sis.... Anyway, his fees are unreasonable. right now i'm negotiating about changing price. Damm expensive. Oh well, at least i get it for free. Oii, first class tuition u know?!?! Anyway, I want another graphic card... but i might gonna hav to buy a cell phone tomorrow from James... a nokia 3350. Gonna check it out tomorrow. I might buy it, might not.... oh well, gotta go guys, ciao!! Peace out!! Rock on!!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl..... wassup?.... well u cant really answer dat so i dunno wats da point.... hey arin... miss u man... dunt miss da borrowing though... =P.. im broke again... and compared to last time... im borrowing money now... not lending ppl... probably bcs i have to pay for my lost phone.... dats just mean dont u think.... well man things seems damn cool for u there.... ur not really missing out on anyhting here.... we barely do anything anymore....all in diffrent classes.... and brian we should at least try to keep ur with our adventure a week thing or at least every 2 weeks and bring jac along too... prom is comin soon... yay.... but then... ppl say its in a crap hotel this year... and jac says he is not goin... and well brian says he is not also... but he well.. changes his mind quite easily....  well although days pass quite fast here... tuesdays suck... its onli fast after tuesday..... hate tuesdays.... science 4 periods... and then later me Loo... but he is getting better.... and well maths sucks too.... hate add maths.... and brian did u know dat jon chays tution teacher "mr chay" is actually his dad =P.. abit weird eh...  anyway ran out of stuff to say... reformatiing my pc now... damn annoying... send for repair and they screw up my pc.... and brian i got a new graphic card... same as urs hehe... =P...  cya pplz....
     

    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone! how is school and everything?  am i missing out on a lot?? so does time pass really fast there, cause it passes too fast here! its like it takes one day for the whole week to pass.. its kinda cool, because then ican see all of u guyz faster in december... anyway, so are all of u in the football team?? im  the rugby team but i dont feel like going to the terainings anymore.. i just like the games because u can pound ppl and stuff.. and u get smoked too.. hehe.. coach is always like 'Tackle low!' and 'ruck ruck ruck!' its kinda cool, but the problem is that it takes up too much time- 4 times a week for 1 and 1/2 hours each time.   girls: all i haf to say that hell yeah, im happy wif the girls! lemmi see.. 8 girls hugged me yesterday 4 no reason at all : ) hehe.. they are hot too... hehe, but id rather be back home no matter what...   hehe, im not at home to borrow money from fung wei anymore.... but u know what is crap?? u cfan go broke really fast here if u dont be careful, because there are no parents here to stop me from overspending too... and ive got a debit card- it's like a card where u can getr money from atm machines... its cool... but im using too much money!!!!   Prom: so who u all going to prom with.. and who do all of u guyz and girls wanna go wif?? mian! i wish i was back home... anyway, how is jon chay and his girlz? hehe... oh yea... dawn suddenly sed out of the blue : ' me and jac are going out!' then i was like coooll! then she sed just jokin... then i was like 'damn!'   Haloween: it is big here! everyone is talking about it and stuff, and there are gonna be trickertreating..its so cool, and we are gonna have a haloween dance, which me and my friends are gonna go to and leave half an hour early and go out and find the chickadies! there are soo many dances here, like 1 a month for some reason or the other... pretty sweet AYE?  k, im gonna go now, because im gonna cut my hair and dye it brown.. its gonna be wicked! k, so take care guyzzz talk some time, bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      its FRIDAY!!!!! eeeek....haha....omg!! i cant  believe tht its already fridayyy....and schools over...and im so happy...hahaha...i had to do my stupid physics test today during lunch and ms.tan left the room and left ME with MS.THIAGA!!!! and she fell ASLEEP!!!!!! haha..so funnnyy...me and some other dude was in there and she fell asleep!!! the dude was like hey do u noe how to find the deccelatration? and she wakes up...haha...so funnyyyy....i flunked the test though...oh well..i can always make up for it on the next one,..and the one after tht and the one after tht :S haha Laterz, muahzzzz...  -Luv- -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha well its true theres nothing wrong with being random but dun be random here :P u can go random fung wei's house ahahahah .. yea i need to pay u back 3.70 haha 4 dollars lar haha ok ok tomorrow well just came back from soccer traning not that tiring today coz like everyone was sick .. mr currie didnt come coz he's sick so really we didn't do much traning :( i wana and i needa run !!! hahaha yep its a friday tomorrow :>  and fung wei haha u can ask anyone u want i dun really care :P hahaha i dun feel like goin to prom ill just go to jac;s house hahahaha or canada :P to visit arin haha.. so fung just forget what i told u this afternoon or yesterday or the day before :> hahaha tell me when ur goin to do it though ;) i wana vedio tape hahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha... nothin wrong with being random..=P and yay tomorrwo is friday... if i was abit blur.. i would still think today is tuesday... seems damn fast.... goin to va with jac and ben.... no idea wat we gonan play there.... im going broke...running out of cash... i go broke every week nowadays.... o owe fatin money for my meal at buddies.... and ill pay her bac when i get money form brian and verun..=P.. and brian if u read this.... can u please put my macromedia mx cd in ur bag and bring it when ever.. cause i need it... for edinting da blog format....  and prom is coming up... who u ppl goin to ask?... i was thinkin of askin someone... but then brian want to ask... damn weird... lar.... but then found out brian wanted to ask someone else... so i dunt understand anymore.... o well... cya ppl for now... got like a shit load of maths hw.... and english corsework... and history... i can go die tonight.... ciao dudes
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo guys do me a favor and dun post random stuff ( jac and ben ) :P hahahaha yea so dun yea? ok ok well tomorrow is a friday tht is quick and next weeek is sports day : 

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha i agree maIN this week is fast and i mean fast but next week sports day :  did soo bad for my chem exam MAN I SUCK !!!! haha well soccer is gettin beter though gettin back the groove :P haha now i get pissed off again when we lose :> :> thts a good thing :P.. hahah COol man u can come to my bday ( if u couldn't i would have slapped u lar ) hahaha so fung who are u goin to the prom with? 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      and jac its cool how u got da rules thing to keep comin up... might get annoyin after a while though
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahha.. ben who allowed u to start suspendin ppl from this blog...=P  hey ppl... seems like i havent been here for a while... man... had so much stuff to read.. and catch up on.... brian..  definately will come to ur bday =P.... and jac ill fix da link this weekend.. maybe in ur hse...  anyway wassup ppl... week seems to past so fast.... and i mean damn fast... thought today was tuesday..... hehe..... and brian abit too late abt ppl not knowing this site.... after inviteing so many ppl.... u cant just start kickin ppl out.... to those who read..... also post lar at least.... no point just reading... and if u dunno how... call up jac... i have no idea how to add ppl... =P  damn got history essay to write now... but i have to go makan dinner first.... man i dunt like hw.... seems to get so much now adays....  and brian da concert thing is on da first week of november....... so better go jam soon... and come up with a new song if we r goin to....  anyway... ciao ppl gtg makan now... cya buh bye  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      RULES 1. U must be a Newcastle United fan 2. Swearing must be included in every sentence 3. U must like food IF YOU ARE NOT CAPABLE OF FOLLOWING THE ABOVE RULES, YOU SHALL BE SUSPENDED FROM THIS BLOG. BEN TEO....heheheh
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh i swear
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha nice jac :P but i do mind (sorry guys ) i think we already have too many ppl .. i mean some ppl dun even post up stuff.. so i dun want it to become like the GIS2005 site.. like only some ppl say stuff.. SO >AS  I DIDNT SAY ..too many ppl already..we can disscus this in school tomorrow and also i dun want many ppl to know about this site hahaha 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      RULES 1. No bitching about people 2. No swearing IF YOU ARE NOT CAPABLE OF FOLLOWING THE ABOVE RULES, YOU SHALL BE SUSPENDED FROM THIS BLOG. JAC TANG....heheheh
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i dun really mind inviting mez and greg....u guys mind? 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey hey guys.... im screwed man.. i have not even started my f-ing english coursework.. excuse my rudeness.... oh btw i was wonderin whether we could invite like menz and greg to join :)..... hey gtg guys .. i have to try to start on my english.... rite laters ppl.... oh yeah nice rules jac
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      \hi again......fung, i did the links to the archives but the first link does not work. i dunno y. can u try to figure out. thanks
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo....wussup guys. just came back. today was okay...normal day just like evry other day. so.....hows life? i dun haf much hw today but i haf to study for physics test tomorrow....oh well see u guys tomorrw at skool. bye
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha ok ok .. well.. i hate tuesdays ..but today was kinda downing *sigh* but its gettin better :P yea main .. no one make the FRENCH MAIN Sad ;P hmm.. hey guys do u wana come to my brithday??? on the 20th this month.. no ideas what to do yet but it will come to me hahaha 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yes yes yes yes yes YES!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha i would set something up for u guys but i have a soccer  tournament this saturday ..so sorry guys ,, but on the bright side my birthday is  comin soon so we all can play soccer ;) ill go think up some ideas for the party.. haha.. maybe sports barn maybe ill book a feild , maybe i can have my party in MCDONALD'S :P haha or buger king all of us get get one for those cool hats man :P ahahah .. ok ok  one more thing.. i have this question.. so i need u guys to say either YES! OR NO!.. ok ok ??? easy ?? easy?? thank U very much... now i need to study for my chem exam ciao dude  The FRenCh MAin 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ARGHHHH..... today sucked man...... rite need to think postive.... anyways r u guys free this weekend... i wanna play futsal.... someone plan something... 'nudge nudge... hinting at brian'... rite gtg ppl... god bless... cya
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey dudes.. thanks jac the trip was great haha lost 2 drew 2 :P no skill one hahahaha but the games weren't tht fun it was what we did between the games was cool.. we arrived at like about hmm.. 10:30 i think so then we went to the hawker(i think) store haha ..man OYSTER so dam cheap :> 4 ringgit haha me, adzim and brian choo ate sooo much maIn haha adzim also tau pow hahaha and brought back to the hotel ;P.. well shawn brought his ps2 so like all the guys were in his room playin the "winning 11" haha man dam funny lar.. and u know it never I MEAN NEVER !! stops raning in penang 4 days in a row.. can u imagine tht haaha FREEZING COLD DUDE MAIN! + the wind.. haha me, joel and justin used the bbq thing to warm our hands ;P haha dam weird.. but over all it was gr8 came back at 1:30 this morning .... and u know i m SOOOOO STUPID i didn't MAKAN CHAR KWEY TOew :  ps. i have no idea how to spell char kwey teow..i think. :P
     

    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys and gals....wussup.....just came home from dinner. i had curry fish head. yum yum.  neways.....how's everybodys week? wus it interesting? i haf to work with tht poo poo head susanna in drama. dammit. i hate her. oh well.....i guess thts just the way it is. sooooo wut r u guys doing this weekend. brians in penang. gd luck in ur soccer matches brian. gtg now cya
     

    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppls... today sucks... done alot of maths hw... and i mean alot.... well dats abt all dat sucks abt today... econs was really borin though... and so was lunch break...  and yay we got another.. member... man im damn bored... just finished my maths... im so happy now... but i got nothin to do.. =P  and brian im not sure if im stayin bac tomorrow... im goin to VA with ben.... wanna come?... or could always go after makan... but need to ask ben lar.. cause he is sendin me home.....  and u ppl seem to have ur weekend packed... so i guess brian our adventure atleast once a week isnt gonna happen... and jac.. how come u always never go anywhere... stay at home onli one?....  and chay dont be bothred with VB.. although i didnt go to VB today... they didnt do much.. well didnt do nothin at all.... so dats jsut weird.. cause mr loo was never in class... he was teachin his yr 11s  anyway ppl... gonna go to sleep now.. actually kinda late.. ciao
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl, yea, jit and i went to buddies, but we just went to get a drink and came back. I wanted to see someone doing chearleading. But jit wanted me to go to buddies for a while. When i came back, that someone dissapeared. so i went to music room cause she's there doing choir, so i waited outside. But she didn't turn up.... for some reason.... anyway, i was using Jia Weii to see if she's in choir room. Hahahahhaha!!! So yea, i didn't go for VB programming either. Was waiting for her. But couldn't talk to her at all. Nvm lah, but i can't afford to skip another VB programming... Maybe i will next week. Don't know lah! G2g guys, ciao ppl
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys, just finally joined this thingie... so how's school and everything??? ooooh ooooh anyone going to the LINKIN PARK concert???!! can't wait for it!! oooh la la anyways, better start on hw again. take care bye
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yo. we didnt go for VB.....we went to Cambrigde thing. it was okay.....neways....yes tomorrow is friday and it is super duper fast. oh well, thts a gd thing. i'm going to times square on sunday! yipeee....jst cant wait to go the the theme park! so......gtgnow cya
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha i only injure ppl when they talk about my mum :P hahaha thts when i get mad and u wont like me when i get mad :P hahahaha so fung and jac hows VB class and jon chay and jit how was buddies ? i saw u guys goin to makan makan ;) hahaha hey guys can u PLZ stay back tomorrow :> coz i m leaving at 3 to penang and i wana makan with u guys :> just before i go ok ok? i need to do my hw fast coz i needa go at 5:30 so just post up stuff if u guys can go ok ok ? and u know wut?.... tomorrow is friday isnt tht just super super super super super super fast or is it super super super super super super super super super fast ? :P hahaha ok ok lar gtg ciao ciao   Rock on. YEsss
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz.... yea brian u do play quite rough at times.... can really injure ppl.. hehe... =P...  Anyway... abt da links yea i can addsome.... or alot.... just tell me wat u want me to add  and jac... da archive thing is damn hard to put on this page.. da most i can do is make a like to da archive directory... which i would do another time.... anyway.... if u want to see previous post u can just go here for now... http://thunderfriends.blogspot.com/thunderfriends_archive.html  anyway ciao ppl... just found out i got history hw to do... cya....... buh bye
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah dude dude dude haha chat about stuff lar if ur bored :P hahhaa hey fung sorry dude i can;t come to the club on sat.. im goin to penang. daIam. not dalam. :P u know wut??? i got a yellow card today :> ..mAin tht guyw as fakin dude..i dun injure ppl tht badly. muahaha or do i?? hmm.. i sae.. u know i was thinkin about all the stuff we guys did ..haha remember the interview :P hahahah jac plays the box hahah:P man tht was a gd day. I MISS ARIN! dude get ur chindian ass back here :P not being racist always do tht to arin hahaha   ok o ciao guyys
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh i see
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i was bored so went a did a whole bunch of quizes and decided to post them up here instead..i have no clue how well this takes html....soz if they take a long time to load and soz if they take up soo muchh room...peace out...muahz  -eLaniE-    Morpheus    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       ! You are Most Like A Ruby ! Passionate, in control - and very sexy. You tend to be more dominant, and people long to possess your wild nature. People find you fun, and a real live wire. You're most like a Ruby because people simply can't take their eyes away from you - your bright captivating nature draws people to you. Congratulations ... You're the sparkly fun gem everybody craves.    urlLink   ?? Which Precious Gem Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     oopsies..please bear in mind tht most of these stuff arent really real...they are just for fun      You're Most Like The Season Autumn ...  You're warm, and the most approachable. You have that gentle prescence about you. People can relate to you, and find you easy company. However it's likely you've been hurt in the past and it has left you scarred so things can become rather chilly with you at times. Being the third Season in, you're mature, trustworthy and loyal to your friends but prone to depression and negative thinking.  Well done... You're the shy and sensitive season :)    urlLink   ?? Which Season Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       Rainbow    urlLink   ?? Which Natural Wonder Or Disaster Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You are Envy! Wow... what a dreamer. Always wanting what you can't have, and always dreaming of having more then you do. It's not the worst sin, and we're all guilty of it - but you take it to the extreme! You are prone to depression, often from things you can't obtain. Be a bit more positive, you have a lot that others want too - so don't sit there being all green! On the positive side, you tend to be a smart person - and can often achieve the goals you set yourself. Congratulations on being the overall harmless, and pretty normal one of the 7 deadly sins :)    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Seven Deadly Sins Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    haha..im envious of other people :S haha...   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I  am a cow
     

    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha i will take pics :> HO HO HO yes .. yea i think u should make a page just for pics and comments : ) i mean "I" hehe haha yea we go watch lar cant wait i dun really think its a good idea to pick him up ... coz i think he wants to hang out with his parents for a while and i dun wana disturb them..u get it .. cool hehehe tomorrow's a saturday :>  ciao guys  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz... yay its friday... so fast..... was thinkin of makin a pictures page for this blog... where we can post like pics up.... but then... who here takes pictures?... so was wonderin if i should make da page... all in favor say i... and brian lets all go watch da LOTR marathon.. with arin when he come bac.. he will be bac on da 14 or 15... wanna go airport to pick him up? he say ask his dad for details.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hehehe so waZap guys ??? today was ok but i was sooo sleepy this morning :P haha dreamt of puppy rottweilers dam chun hehe so u guys wana go catch a  movie or somethin ??? i wan go watch the lOTr marathon :> hehe cioa ill write more laters 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      merry christmas to you toooo. hilary duff CD looks dicky man. my brother dreamt of dinosaurs tooo. i watched tale of 2 sisters yester day..shit scaryymannn! i was to afraid to continue. u guys should watch it. but watch it with a whole bunch of ppl. i watched it alone dueudeded. i was shivering the whole night man. anyways....im scared now.....going to sleep . bye
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys tomorrow is school. haha u know today feels like christmas :P haha my mom is puttin up the tree and playin christmas songs *sigh* im soo happy today :) done all my hw yesterday night haha oh yes.. and i dreamt of dinoraurs last night haha strange! ... its goin to rain again hoho oh yeai remember i have tution today.. daIm haha but nvm lar haha i dun wana go to school maIn haha iwana stay home and relaz :) oh yea u know wut?? i m goin to buy the hilary duff cd :) OH yes the song for christmas !! hehehe   MErry Chirstmas Guys !! :)  HO HO HO HO    [[B]rian]] - ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey hey.... wassup ppl... today wasn't too bad... toked to arin on messenger in da mornin... finish downloadin 2 cds... Blink 182 and LInkin Park Live In Texas... and jac is right da blink 182 cd sucks da first time u hear it... but it gets better.... Linkin Park is jsut payin all da old songs again.... and i also finished most of my hw today =).... not bad for a day stuck at home =P okay gtg now... ciao dudes
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      donkey me now! wussup guys. hi arin! hows it going? anyways....blink182 album kicks ass. it might suck the first few times u listen to it but u will realise the beauty of it. so so...just cant wait till interhse and swim gala. oh yes. uh uh uh. yess. oooooooooooooo babby. hubba. get jiggy with me. im busy noe so ill catch u guys latersss.   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      donkey!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey GUYS selamat hari raya!! sing with me guys ..."selamat hari raya ta da da ta da da....." hahah dun know the rest of the song :P hahah yea lar jac wouldnt be here .. DaIm we cant to the thunder brids thing :( hey wei we must take loads of pics then can post it on the site ..if its possible .... i m goin to jusco laters to buy some stuff and go buy some new games :> hey u guys wana go swimmin on wed? will faisal be here?? haha hey wei y not go do something lar??? go watch a moive or something haha  i know what u can look forward too :P haha u can look forward to 1:  watchin lotr marathon 2: playin soccer in school and 3 the most important one .. to see me maIn ;) ho ho ho ho LAugh with me guys HO HO HOHO ...yes way :P  and one more thing thanks for th advise dude ill think about it.. today looks like ANOTHER good day :) goin to buy more fish stuff again also need to do work ..and maybe later play soccer a bit with my bro.. so tell me if u wana go to the club on wed  coz i m goin for a swim might even go today if i can find goggles :P haha ok ok thats enough ... goin to say this one last time :> Selamat hari raya guys !   BYE BYE !  over and out  Mxtreme 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      cool arin posted... =)... missed ya man... hows u doin over there?...cant wait till u come bac...can go melacca this time.... i would be here... not goin to nz anymore...sucks that jac is stil goin to china though... btw ppl i changed my phone number 78761206... anyway Brian seems to be havin a much more intersetin life than me =P... i spend my day sleepin cause i had a headache after playing football... for me time seems to be passin extreamly slow.... damn borin lar everyday... nothin to look forward to da next day... not even prom... doesnt seem that interestin anymore...  its 12.30 at night.. im not sleepy cause i have been sleeping... brian im guessin u wanna ask fatin rite?... if so.. i think u should go ask her... even if she says no... i think she might say yes though.... no harm in tryin....  goin to try to sleep now... ciao dudes...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      aiyo arin press POST AND PUBLISH!!!!! hahaha how many times must u make the same mistake :P haha.. anyways everything's great and kapor ill call u on prom night ok ;) haha just be awake btw ill waste fung's credit hahahah MUAHAHAH yes way.. haha today looks like a fine day doesnt it ?? goin to bermain bola sepak laters with the "guys" haha .. so u guys know something ... times passes soo fast man to think of it prom is comin sooon.. haha plus my Vee is comin back so thts cool. but jac and fatin wouldnt be here :(   we should like gather ppl and go somewhere lar ill try to plan something and not to forget we are suppose to go to  melacca.. cant wait maIn.. Argh haha thinkin of prom..!!! i wana ask her!!!!! yes way... ofcourse : ) hahah goin to buy some fish stuff for my pond/ fountain : ) hahah so cya guys laters   over and out  --- Capt America  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey everyone... havent posted anything for a long time... how is everyone??and.... i gtg.. bye bye... take care ill call sometime
     

    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey pplz!... wassup... yay.. holidays started =D.. onli for 6 days... but its still cool.... And the justice league was really cool too... we palyed damn well..  it was damn cool =P... we were just unlucky... we couldv'e won.. =).. o well too bad... try again next time =P...  and if someone reads this bfore monday... r we gonna go paly footsal on mon... cause im not sure...  ciao dudes
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys! haha havent posted anything for a loong time haha .. well just wanted to say thanks to everybody that supported the JUSTICE LEAGUE!! hahahah and i also want to say GOOD JOB! to   everyone tht played : ) haha so what are u guys goin to do in the hoildays ??   and to all the ppl tht  celebrate hari raya ,,,, SELAMAT HARI RAYA .. :> :> !!!  HO HO HO HO HO   BT 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ummm....sure ben sure. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YEA
     

    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HAHAHHAH...ben ben ben. i cant imagine him sitting by is computer typing poopoopop until it became 11280 characters long. he must have been damn bored. or damn sad. hahah. anyways...i think bens learnt a valueble lesson. so so...sup guys. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppls some more minor changes to da blog... hope u guys like it... anyway... post seem to be getting less and less... this site is dieing =(.. should try to post more.. =P.. anyway todays been crap... gotta cold... didnt do nothin... better go sleep now... ciao pplz
     

    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hehe... sry ppl..... so its saturday and im damn tired after open day and mid valley... arghhh soo bored.... neways today was quite cool... didnt do anything much for bio and mid valley was ok... couldnt get tickets for revolutions so had to settle for brother bear :P.... dunno what was so sad abt the movie that menz and greg kept goin on abt it... i didnt think it was sad but damn funny.. hehe... lang and i couldnt stop laughing... need to take my shower now ok... gdnite guys... and sry again abt the 'popopopopopopopopopopopoppopo' word thingy
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl finally fixed da blog.... found out da problem wasnt in da html at all... hehe... stupidly it was ben... he wrote a very long word"poop"... it had 11280 characters... it was 4 pgs on microsoft word...=P... forced da blogger so become too big... so from now on i suggest da longest word ppl should write is maybe.. 100 characters... not 11280 characters ben =P... you can split up da word thought use space bar everynow and then make sure its not more than 100
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tuesdaayyy...mann..still ages and ages and ages more till fridayyy...ahhh bio and history test on thursday...suxx dunnit?! haha damnn..oh well...laterrrr....   Muahz -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guiys haha tuesday wasnt tht great was kinda pissed off until Computer studies ..then i became happpy hmm..... thts weird : ) hahaha so are any of u guys goin the futsol tournament??? cant wait MAIN!!! and prom is comin soon also!! i need to get my dress ready!! Oh - ma-- Goid! heheh tomorrow is a wednesday and i have to redo my maths coz i think i got loads wrong so i need to figure out how to do it!!and i think tomorrow will be a gooooood day : ) haha k ciao ciao  Bt peace out \ /
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEY AGAIN. Its another tuesday and a long way till friday. Ahh got tennis lessons today and i cant believe manchester beat liverpool. Probably they biribed the refree. HA HA and it was fluke
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEY PEOPLE.  Just decided to say something since i am so bored. Livepool is going to play Manchester United. Liverpool is going to kick ass. Matrix revolution is out and i heard it wasnt that good. I cant see yet because i havent seen any of the matrix. But i am going to see the first one and then matrix reloaded and hope that matrix revolution is still in the cinema. I hope you people enjoy your weekend!!!!!  Verun
     

    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      its the freaking weekend baby im gonna have me somee funnn..haha..this songg rockkkssss....haha....prom is like abit more then a month awayy...whoooaaa....damn man..it seems too fastt....oh well...i am soo glad tht this week is up!! my godd tests everywhere...and historyy and bioo test next week...damn damnn...i dont have a clue about anything in bio..oh well....have a great weekend guys!!!   muahz -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      whoops... k, ill start my poem again u asking me who? im going with melanie woo, i dont care if she has a flew, but i know leon is poo, and my train goes choo chooo!!!!! hey everyone! how are u??
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      u asking me who?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      im going with me
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey dudes life is gr8! prom is comin soon and i have  a 4 game ban : ) NO/!..im soo happy today :> finished all my hw !! oh yea yea yea yea .. so guys who are u guys goin with to the prom/?..
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys and gals. hows life
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      gangbang
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi guuuuys  camp was kool guuuys. but it was tooo short guuuuys. i hope we can go again guuuys. and nooo school tomorrow guuuuys. i dun want to go to skool guuuys.   bye guuuys
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      camp wasnt too bad..it was too short thou..it was like we just got there and then suddenly we were going back..oh well..it was kinda dissapointing for our last ever camp!!! haha..oh well...ms cheah sed she'll try and talk to mr.llyod and ask him if we could have another after our exams and all...oh well....damnn..school on mondayy..oh welllll....rapellling was the bomb!!!! haha....  muahzzzz..laterrrsss.. -eLaniE-
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks man, I like the play too :D Brian's play was good too! I like the soccer part and the DJ part, it was really kewl!!!! OK, i hav to get back to my work, forgot all about it!!! Ciao ppl!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha yea maIn camp was coooool ..esp stayin in the same apartment :> haha it was soo fun... now i cant stop sining numb :P aiyo!!.. hehe i wish we could have stayed longer..and yea andrew is cool MAIn hehe we were suppose to have tug of war!! but no time!!.. oh yea chay btw ur play was coolin hehe ok ok ..more ppl need to type stuff :>   hehe ok ok ciao ciao  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ahahaha sure u dunt :P ho ho ho anyways happy new year guys! and selamat hari raya :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha... well humpin teddy bears is not wat i do jac.. =P
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i noe wut u can do fung. go and hump all ur sisters teddy bears! itll be fun
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey... seems like a llllllllloooonnnnnnnnggggggggg time since i came to this site... hahahaha... and jac does seem really bored =P... come bac early lar... and we can all go hang out.... o well brian use XtremeFT looks coller =P... and im damn bored too... someone gimmie somethin to do, which doesnt involve books =P... sick of books... dunt wanna study...   and its new year's eve tomorrow... 1 more day of 2003.... time flies... =)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hhheeeelllloooo...i am soo boreddddd...damn only a week left till school...i havent done any homeowrk yet...haha...enjoy whts left of the holidayzz dudessss..:) muahz  -Elanie-
     

    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha jac maIn u must be really bored :P i think u have a hiddent talent ;) hahaha hey jac the team is now narrowed down into 2 names Mixed Fc and Xtreme Ft haha anyways! happy new year guys :) and i think jac will be able to see arin yea.,.. so hows everyone ? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys wussup. as you can see rite now i am pretty bored. yes i am. you see one day was was walking with my grandpa along the riverside and we saw a huge CD. we then turned into cows. me and my grandpa, we both love grass. u see, i like sweet grass. grass which is sweet. u get wut i mean? my uncle, whom is a goat like grass too. i think thats is how we are realated. yes i think i am bored. i would now like to write a poem. here it goes.  i haf nothing to do so suck my tau fooos i dont think that is koool so ill go wear my shoe i walked 1 mile to the loo and saw the hottie rikku i turned around and there was another hottie there tooo it was melanie wooo but i wanted a kangaroo that is why i went to the zoo this place u see it smelt like poo maybe it were the cows that went moo moo so maybe ill just do it with YOU!!!!  i think that was preety kool dont you? i mean it written by mr loo. so lets all say boo boo. ciao ciao   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys christmas is over :( BUT! the new year is comin :) oh yes hehe we have one week left of hoildays i hope eveyrone is havin fun. i jumped off a speedin buggy hahaha but it wasnt THT fast! well thts what i thought but then when i jumped off the next thing i know i m rollin on the ground hahaha well it was fun anyways hehe lotr is cool watched it ALONE thanks to mr tai fung wei.. ditchin me at the last min :P haha i wana watch peter pan! it looks cool :) arin is leavin next week.. tht kinda sucks haha atleast hes still the same :P hehehe HOw was Everyone's christmas??! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah MERRY CHRISTMAS EVERYONE!!! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      SUCK MY TWINKLE WINKLE
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I FeEl LiKe SiNgInG!! Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell rock ...Jingle bells swing and jingle bells ring....snowing and blowing up bushels of fun...now the jingle hop has begun! OH YEAH! Here comes Santa Claus!here comes Santa Claus!right down Santa Claus Lane!vixen and Blitzen and all his reindeer are pulling on the reins! MERRY XMAS TOMORROEEEE! HOPE U GET WONDERFUL PRESENTS! CIAO CIAO NOW! Frosty the snowman was a jolly happy soul, with a corncob pipe and a button nose  and two eyes made out of coal.........................  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      happy christmas eve guys and guylings
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hahahahahaha MErry Christmas guys :) tomorrow is christmas !! Oh yes haha there are sooo many presents to open i cant wait ! and u guys better remember to get me presents ;) hahaha ..kiddin :P have a good christmas guys and i wished it snows in malaysia :P hahah   silver bells :) BYe  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      MERRY CHRISTMAS COWS AND COWGLINGS! HORSES AND HORSELINGS! SKUNKS AND SKUNKLINGS!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      jingle belllsss!!! hehe jusssttt want to wisshh everyoneee a meerrryyyy x'massss and a happy neww yearrr!!! :D :D :D *muahzzzzzz*  -eLaniE-
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      bonjour.... it's me again.. i just wanted to say that i love u all...*MUAX*!  FROM: WET ASS
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEYYYY EVERYONE IT HAS BEEN A GREAT WEEK! and there are two more to come i hope everyone is having a good time, because i am! i jsut wanna stay here and never go back to canada....anyway.. bye bye ciao ciao 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Good mornin :) its almost christmas ..Oh yes ! hahaha i wana watch lotr !!!1 cant wait and spy kids 3d !!1 i need to satrt doin some work :P .. the melacca trip was soooo cool maIN haha i enjoyed it alot esp the water slides and the bikes thingi !! haha we still have 2 weeks of hoildays! hehe evie left so thts kinda sad :( anyways got to do some hw :) BYe bye   Over and Out  :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz.... a week of holiday is almost over... and it was damn fun... all da parties... and goin to melaka.... except for a borin saturday... coudnt have been a better week... =) miss jac though... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i wannnaa go and watchh LOTR:-ROTK!! i was going to buy tickets todayyyyy but i couldnt coz of the stupid stupid linesssssss eeeekkkk hehehe...WELCOME backerooss arinnn!! rights thts it laterrrrrss 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys ! haha prom was Cool :) enjoyed it alot man haha everyone looked great! SO HOT MAIN!! :P ;) hehehe river dance was the BOMB!! u should see their feet maIn ... So fast!! hahaha have a good hoilday everyone :) and arin is back haha goin to melacca with arin, fung, and faisal on wed ! cant wait haha,,, who wants to go watch LOTR 3 ??!!! just tell me when u guys are free the we can go lepak lepak ;)   Bye! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      prom is finishedddd..i thought last years was better.,..but this years wass funnn tooooo...haha in a ood way...the room was tiny thou...too tiny!! haha next year we are sooooo sooo sooo going to make it soooo  bigg!! hahaha oh well....next year a big dance floorr!! haha arin coming back 2moorreeee im going janda baik 2moroee damn man..its going to be solddd that meansss no more fishing mannn...oh well...haha...im babbaling now so ill stop :P :P :P Laterrrssss muahhhzzzz 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey pplz wassup?... prom is over... and im in brian's hse... abt to go home... soon... =(...  prom was kinda cool... but it kinda sucked at da same time...food sucked... dance floor damn small... keep whackin into ppl... well at least i got to dance with 'someone' =P.... i guess prom bacicly sucked but being with friends there is still quite cool.....
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha so what if nothing special happens on ur birthday :P haha its still ur birthday~ "thts already special right ??! ..ofcourse im right  ;) hahahah it prom night tonight~!! excited :> HO MO yes way hahahah anyways cya guys  and plz say something lair  Brian 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yay my bday today.... doesnt seems that good though.... probably bcs i just woke up and im kinda sick =)... but then... nothin really special can possibly happen today anyway... its a tuesday... and tuesdays suck... o well better get to school now =P
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      - hey arin.....happy b'day! n thx again 4 callin me all de way here ;D im glad u're havin fun there :D..keep it up n maybe c ya nxt summer.. ciao hun! xox  - ola brian..check ur mail..i juz replied it..n it's pretty long..its mainly bout de soccer tournament we had here..okie g2g now..tc of urself & keep in touch.. luv ya, patty
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday Arin:>!!! Oh yes!! Christmas is comin Soon :>!!! HO HO HO HO yes way c  cya guys in school tomorrows Cheers maIn 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahahahahahhahaha yep yep i did hehe MAin we won a soccer tournament today! the first of many i hope :P hehehe u knw the thing i really cant wait for!?? .. Its christmas !i love christmas maIn all the presents and turkey and Yummm... oh yes ehehe Prom can wait maIn hehe ;) christmas comes first! haha hey guys is there any soccer thingi this saturday??  swimmin gala on monday .. dam scared lar! need to train!! ARin's birthday this SUnday! magical 7 ;) n MR TAI FUNG WEI TAN"S birthday this tuesday RONALDO 9 oh yes hehehe and I m goin to DISNEY ON ICE ON SUNDAY!!! yay1 : ) cant wait ho ho . and river dance on the 14th : ) hehehe  anyways CATCH U LATERS WEEKENDERS !  Oh yes   Brian TaIn 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha... brian u got mixed up between tuesday and monday... football was on monday and we got our report on monday =P.. o well.... anyway...got so much stuff to look forward to next week.... my bday... arin's bday comin up soon also..=P... prom.. end of school... =).. damn cool... and tomorrow is mufti day.... and arin is comin bac durin da holz... =D.. so many cool stuff... =P too bad still have to study for a few days... guess thats life... hehe....
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      i noe u r but wut am i?!?!? akunamatata. amma. im sure
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YAY! MUFTI DAY!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      GOOD MORNIN!.. WAX UP?!!! hehehe its a tuesday night and i m date less... :P hahaha tryin to sound american-ish:P hehehe GOOD ONE!! ho hoho yes ... soccer was cancelled today and tomorrow is table tennis :> so its kinda cool plus we miss thursday coz of mufity day!!!! and we got our reports back today.. mine was opk ok lar what did ur parents think about ur reports ?  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yea ill do da picture page thing over da holiday.... dunt really feel like makin it now... too lazy... =P and yeah brian i guess we r not goin to pick arin up then =P
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wait i forgot to say..... From MR VEERAPEN
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEY HO HO HO... i am going snowboarding tomorrow!!! i cant wait, anyway.... how are all u guys? when is your next holiday so that i can call u? and stuff... hey, so where are awe going to go for our world tour afer collage? i think we should all go to mexico and like south america, and then we should go to africa and ride the poneys... and then we should go watch fishes playing american football in a fish tank! hey yong, by da way, i found a guy who remindes me of you man... is name is dominic! and sometimes the stuff he says is like am i talking to brian or dominic... its coool mon! and jac and fung wei... i havent quite found a jac and fung wei yet... but anyway it doesnt really matterbecause there cant be anything better than all u guyz! s0o.... WAAZZapppp???!?!?! i catch up wiyh you guyz later! ciao 4 nowwww
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz... happy chinese new year.... cant wait for u to come back arin... =).. but then time passes slowly here.... o well.... hows everyone doin... hope u guys had a great chinese new year..... =) take care pplz... 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEY EVERYONE!  GONG XI FA CAI!!!! how are u all?? im missing all of u, im listening to a really sad song now, and i feel like crying because i wanna go home!!! :'( i dun haf  holidays... no fair!!!! anyway know what i realised, time passes really fast, so it is probably not going to feel very long till i come back! anyway... wussupp?? i am going for a ski meeting now so ciao ciao!! bye  mr veerapen
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey GUYS maIn wheres everyone dude??? anwyays happy chinese new year :) have a great new year and .....study hard ???? hahahahaha  cya guys take care enjoy ur holz   mr B 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      likee i sedd it'sss okkkkaaayy batman!! haha...dudes!! have a great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great great & Wonderful Chinese new yearsss!! haha.... Dontt forget me when ur getting all ur ang pow ;)   -E- ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yo yo dudes and Dudlings :) hows is everyone??? theres NO ONE POSTING UP ANYTHING ANYMORE!!!!! alamak lar hehe anyways chinese new year is comin sooon :) everyone better get me ang pow ah ;) remember GET ONE FOR BRIAN :) cheers and thanks Q ho ho ho .. u guys up for watchin a movie?? and sorry elanie for not tellin u   MR B 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      heloooo. everyone.. it is 6 15 at nite here... i decided to come online and say hi to you guyz's ... so hi! how are all of u? and how is your futsal team? hey.. imagine riding poney's and playing football...ooh, imagine if pigs lived on trees...haha.. fung wei, we should go freeze some fishes..hehe, i feel like im talking to myself when im typing... its soo weird. i cant download msn on this computer! its so annoying!! anyway, how is schoooool? i wanna go back to kl! and see everyone again.u know when i went back, i felt like i never left, and when i came back here, i felt that i was new! it waas soo weird man...hmm.. i still taste that last ramly burger in my stomach... hmmm yumm... and and :'( i wanna go backk!!! anyway, i gtg and stuff... so ciao ciao!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah... hey... i am in hong kong air port now... i didnt get yo say bye to jac... so byr jac... and stuff... fung, i hope ur thing is ok.. and ur back... thanx for letting us come tp ur house i have a thing for ypur sister...hehe.. jac wyhy did u go home so fast?? k.. i gtg, flight boarding now.. ciao... take care... i love all of u!!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys long time no post maIn ! hahaha hows schoool??? how are is the new year ???? DUDE! we need to post more stuff up laIr hahaha hey main arin is leavin tomorrow dat sucks .. main hes like my good luck guy for football :'( today was pretty cool all 4 of the thunder birds were in school at the same time :P haha well it was fun.. jac went home like once i reached the car park, went home with fung wei today coz i had no transport back so did faisal and arin :) me and arin bullied fung wei sooooo badly today :P hahahha we were slapin his back and throwin sand on him ho ho hoho sounds evil i know haha maIn.... arin come back soon dude :) great to see u again, glad u didnt change ..except for ur height lar hahaha have a good flight and cya next time :) i love u arin :( hahaha   yong yong  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAPPY NEW YEAR!!!! pplz.... a day late... but realised no one said happy new year here =P
     

    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz and arin, just wated to know if anyone knows wat time we can call arin... tried a few times... but keep gettin his answerin machine  please post times if u know... 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello...:)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yi ping
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh Yi PinG..... harder
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys. hey arin.. sup sups up ??? dudes?? im good how's canada?? its it like cold and stuff?? hows school? got a gurl friend yet? the site is like dying maIn ... i have no internet i m writing this from the school libary during geography.. dam boring lar.... hey you know this gurl in year 8 A.K.A Yi Ping.. ho ho ho ... hey arin when are u comin back to kl dude? anyways i gtg  cya thunderfriends ... Ciao like bye bye :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ello everyone! how is everyone, hey ben and jac and everyone... howz it going mon? havent spoken to u guyz's for so long... when is ur next holiday?? im going to new york for the next term break.. it should be fun, but i want to goooo backkk homeeee!! lala doo doo, anyway.. i have to go now, ciao.. from me
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello guys. wussup. how is everybody doing? well, im doing okay. yes. uh. uh. hi.   oh yes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello guys. wussup. how is everybody doing? well, im doing okay. yes. uh. uh. hi.   oh yes.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi arin
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wat abt... SUPER hot chinese boys with glasses... thats me 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi dideley ho neighbour! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey ho everyone! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      whoops...i meant hot chinese boys with glasses....thats me.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      chinese boys with glasses... thats me
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello. how is everybody guys? i  am in computer studies class.. `and im really really bored. anyways.... sup arin! wut is up ma man dude?!?! hows the chick diggin over there? remember to ask hot chicks around if they wwant chinese boys with glasses.  soooo i gtg now ciao
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      NO
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys.. the site is dying maIN... so how did u guys spend valentines??? ho ho ho
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HeY YAAaaAA........
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hehe...am sooooo boreddd...am in Dt right now which suxx...wish i neva took it hehe :P heyy arin!!! hehe hope ur good and having good fun! :D laterrss -Elanie- 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey arin whats UP ?? dude how was snowboarding? well valentines dance is on friday and u know wut???? ho ho ho ho ...no... yes ... hahaha i m in the computer lab now during PShe..:) how is canada? is it like snowing?? and faisal says Hi we are in PSHE now and it is boring..
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey pplz... this site is dieing..... =P  Hey arin... wassup... hows stuff over there?... when u gonna come back for holz... =) stuff over here seems okay.... abit on da borin side soemtimes... but still da same...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      very good maIn
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEy bennnn!!! how are ya man..?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys... wat is up?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes be there at 10
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      can i come?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi friends. so guys saturday is on same time, same place.. if u noe wat i mean.. haha im ben and i think im funny  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi arin 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEY everyone man, ow are u guyz's im sot sure when im coming back but  probably not for a long time, but we will keep in touch lah... anyway, i got to go now, so bye bye everyone.. haf fun at school BYE BYE
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey GUSY!just wanted to say well done to everyone who played softball :P haha anwyays trainin is on this saturday!!! cant wait maIn and arsenal drew with chealse which isnt that bad :) yes! we need to kick some asses maIn  peace out [\/]   brian tan 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      GD MORNING. THE MOON IS SHINING TODAY. THIS TELLS ME THAT THE SUN ISNT SHINING. HA          HA          HA          HA. im so funny rite?!?!  anyways, real madrid will win tomorrow. arsenal will win too. but newcastle............ummm..........hi ben. wussup?  rite now i gotta go. see ya guys. tune in next time, same jac channel, same jac time. THE MAN OF ALL MANS THE MANIZER
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Correction it is the UEFA champions league quater finals and arsenal r gonna lose... Newcastle is going to win the UEFA cup guys.... oh and i need to know who can come on sat... and wat time do we set it... ok ok i gtg now  BT
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys long time no typin typin :) hows everyone ?? there is soccer trainin in ben's school on saturday thanks to ben T :) anyways hows life ppl? i think we should go to melacca for 1 week in the end of yr 10 if anyone wants to go with us just tell me ?  hey arin when are u comin back to malaysia?? we should go to another trip when u come back. like the melacca one.  tomorrow morning is the arsenal vs chealse match !! first leg of the UEFA championsleague semi finals WOW!! i know guys its amazing !! go arsenal ! anyways i gtg now i m in computer studies with the other 3 birds of prey cya dudes Peace out  BT  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ya mon!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      holy goo goo jiao i look so tiny and puny and small and opposite of big. haha all the memoriesss... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      bonjour mes amis.. cava?  je suis dans ma tauntes masions! et je suis visite mon cousins!  haha... heylo everyone! im in new yorkeyus right now visiting ma cousins and it is very fun! i went to manhatten today, and i saw ground zero!- its the place where the world trade center used to be.. its just a big hole in the ground! and then i went to timee square, and i saw da empire state building and stuff and stuff and stuff... there are so many orang hitam in new york man... they are all like so down in the hood and stufff.. and they come up to u and they are like hey bro... wsup? and because i am brown they are like hey nigger.. haha, they are cool. aNYWAY... how are all u guyz?? must update me with all the  news lah! i am very bored with my school life right now. and maybe next month i am not going to be in boarding school anymore, because my parents are going to come and live in canada next month.. :'( i wanna go homeeee!! cya guyz...ciao
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      newcastle 4 - 1 real mallorca
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      heya guyss...was looking through some pictures on my computer and came across these i took ages ago of u dudes..haha...thought ill post them up here :)                     if these dont show..hehe soz :P u guys look so small..hehe...  -elanie
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well well well what do we have here..
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ohh ben ben ben u toking abt uefa cup? well i hope newcastle will do well but i dun think they would. their gonna face mallorca rite? newcastle gonna lose. they will go down. down down down. even if they win this round, i think they will be knocked out the next round etc etc. anyways, i just wanna say that real madrid  WILL  beat bayern munich eventhough they are without  CARLOS , ronaldo and raul. well we will just have to see TOMORROW!!!! and i think arsenal will thrash celta like sh*t tomorrow too. so so, RO is getting abit like a routine game and is kinda boring now.  from J         T        Jac      Tang        Justin  Timberlake        Jit        Tim        Juggly Tits
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      :)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello......... i would like the emphasize that i was talking abt the UEFA cup not the Champions League maIN... newcastle is in the UEfa cup while ARSEnal and madrid are in the champions league... and yes... madrid could possibly win the cl but dun forget teams like MIlan and united are still init... they also played shit agaisnist munich last week and were lucky to come away with the draw...NOw to Ragnarok... i would like to thank myself for and the hard work and time wasted i put into this very aDdcitive game...and one more thing..."hi"  from ben T bye guys
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well hello guys wut is up?  i think newcastle will bw knocked out no doubt about that. so will arsenal. real madrid will be the team kicking ass if u get what i mean. look at them! their doing soooo well.....unlike newcastle. and the players in madrid do not have weird accents and voices like arsenal. anyways....abt ragnarok, i would like to thank fung, benT and chee meng. I luv u guys. now i would like everybody to say "carpet". ok  from jac tang
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha newcastle are goin to by knowed out of the UEAFA CUp soon dude ;) haha but arsenalwill still be in :) u dun need to worry about arsenal hahaha.. well in ragnarok . i jusrt wana say thanks to all the people ( just ben t, jon chay, jac) for all their help :' ( im base lvl 10 and job lvl 8 YES!! soo close .. thanks chay for the weapon ho ho ho .. tomorrow is a friday !! oh yes! and guys i was thinkin do u guys wana go to langkawi?? and one more thing....hmmm....  well... i would have to say negative ...  im so lame lar .. anyways  :)  cya guys .  BT 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys.. waZZup??? well im really really really bored rite now ok so thought i would come here and post...Hi... im feeling damn low rite now becos i got 50% for my hist. test :p... anyways newcastle beat valerenga 3-1 last nite and we advanced to the 4th round of the UEAFA cup MaIn... YEs i gtg  yours sincerely, bean tea... haha NO
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey.....everybody has their own 'from ................' ill make mine too  from jac tang  so creative rite?!?!?!  from jac tang
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      call arin like at 6am. i think. i dunno. hey brian dun u wanna learn VB during holz? where u planning to go?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey Guys! me and fung wei are goin to plan a trip man .. during the end of year holz... :) so do u guys know any good places where u guys would wana go??.. hjo ho ho anywasy arsenal roks maIn..! and ...hmmm..... raganarok rocks man..:) im level 8 / 7 YES!   gtg cya guiys  Green falcon 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      2.00
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i visit the site! in fact i visit the site the most! i am a true thunder bird! that is why i should be leader! anyways hi. brian why u thinking of changing the time? and man u lost to pompey hohahoha! well, they wont be winning the premiership this season. real madrid are doing crap too those losers. ok  hi ok bye
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys no one visits this site anymore :( anyways guys i am thinkin of changing training every saturday to later in the afternoon. what do u guys think? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ReAL mAdRiD 0 - OsAsuNa 3  fLuKe
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ARSENAL 0 - NeWcAsTLe 0
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      fLuKe
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ARSENAL 4 - LIverPool 2 !!!! YES ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hhaaha hey guys :) its the hoildays ! yea maIn.. arsenal lost to manUtd daIM maIn anyways thanks ben for letting us use ur school to play soccer. and we should go watch a cool movie this hoilday :)   have a good hoilday guys   -De Bat 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oooooh. now u can blog using EMAIL! ooooooooooh. just send to ruff_ryderz89.thunderfriends@blogger.com
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        test test 123 
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yea why is your name BARNEY?!?! i duno. ooh who lives in a pineapple right under the sea? grrr....maths was so hard...hi...lucu. okay blogger looks so futuristic.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      haha.. why is my name barney?
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      helloe.. how is everyonnnneee?? im am so bored dright now, and then the bogger came to ma mind and i was like holi moli, i ave to write something.. so now i am writing something.... to say hello and stuff...and i cand wait till i come back in DECEMBER! i hope the soccer tournament went well and stuff... ok, i have to go now, so take care, i love u all BYE!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys long time no blog ho ho ho .. hey arin thanks for callin me dude. we all miss you here back in Kuala lumpur. :) man.. its almost the end of the year. and almost the end of schoolin in malaysia. :( ill miss you guys when i leave school dudes.. anywyas the tournament is this saturday  .. Oh yes!! cant wait :P haha hope i dun screw up .. tomorrow is  wednesday.. yes .. not such a bad day lar . arsenal is goin to play on saturday!! if they win or draw they went through the entire EPL without being BEATEN!! they are the unbeatables .. ho ho ho anyways cya guys tomorrow ..   [B]rian :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey all....  arin.. hope its fun livin in your own house soon.... with your own pc... to come online and tok to us =P  anyway found out somethin cool in google.com.my... trysearching for "fungwei" and click pages in malaysia then...click im feeling lucky...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo yo arin sups. how does it feEL tO be LiVing with ur parents?! Is iT like WOW or WOAH?!  I AM NUMbER 3. ThE 3
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HELLOOO!!! how is everyone, my parents moved here!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha... jac's the best. hey, i think the best thing woud be to meet in africa.. cause africa is the place to be! nyway....a hem, i went to the beach today and came back and played a lot of guitar with this guy who plays very good latin guitar... tres bon, if u know what i mean... i like big butts.. and all these ppl came to my house for house warming.. it was clazy! oh ya.. and i havent called anyone for so long, so if u guyz get a phone call at a weird hour... its gonna be me ;).. anyway.. PEACE for noww....   ARIN V was speakin
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ohhhh...hi ben. hi arin. hi brian. hi fung. maybe maybe we can all meet in africa since it is equally as far from malaysia and canada i think. OR mayber we all look at the moon on one specific night and start toking!!! HO ho HO! OR WE CAN JUST COME ON MSN! or WE CAN CHAT HERE! get iT?!?! okay. sure. funy. no.  hi guys. tonight is the nite when i lose my virginity to an amazing girl. wish me luck!!  hi guys. i am an old saggy balled woman.  PEACE  JAC TANG
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys.. havent posted here for very long.. neways tonite is mid summer nights dream.. oh cant wait...MELANIE uh uh...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey u guyz's... hey, u should go to the states to study laaa... so much mor fun than all the other places.. hokay, anyway... it is like summer and stuf and i might rent a boat for the summer, and go fishing and water skiing... fun stufff.. are u guyz gonna be studying for igcse's all summerr or december??
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha we cant watch troy in the cinemas coz it was like durin the exams and stuuff plus its like over 18 :P but its reallllly cool though :) i m goin to miri for  like one week can go fishin :P YES!! haha U KNOW WUT GUYS?!? me and fung were thinkin hows goin to melbourne to study??? coz we should go to someplace where we can stay together man :) like old times ho ho hoho   Bt out {>} 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dun worry man, im not going anywhere either.. it gonna be boring, but im goig to get a eally black tan because it is so hot over here.. for canada, like 30ish degreees... anyway, troy is such a good movie, y dont u guyz just watch it in the cinemaa.. its so good, i dont even lke brad pitt, but he was really good in troy, anyway...gtg.. peace! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      mother. i'm not going anywhere during summer. it will be VERY VERY boring. study study study gb gb gb. GET WHAT I MEAN?!?! where are you guys going?! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey dude y are u barney :P haha same here man we need to make this site alive again ho ho ho SO so SO So so so arin dude how was ur exams results?? hope they were good.. and we won soccer yesterday .. yes 8 -3 maIn so i have to say it was not bad not bad.. im downloaded troy but it isnt clear tht sucks i really wana watch it..its dam cooool..:) wut are u guys goin to do in the summer break???   BT out {>} 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      KACHING! YO YO. I'm gonna start writing in this site as much as i can now! wussup ARIN. HOW IS LIFE? cant wait till you come bak in DECEMBER. then we can spend some QUALITY time together...dum dum dum.   Football match tomorrow. just can't wait. GUNBOUND.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yoholomo! howz u guyz's? im bored so im writing here.. no one writes anymore!! :'( anyway... peace!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey yo u guyz... i finish school in 6 days! oh my good i cant wait! i just did my english exam and it was the hardest thing ever! u know what im sayin yo diggity doag. guyz.. i have the best idea ever! all of u sjhould come to canada this summer.. now that is such a good idea! hey, all my furniture for my house has come and it looks soo full! ill send some photo's soon... anyway i have to go study for geography! so peace! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahaha... im sure u would have plenty of fun this summer jac...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes i just cant wait too! we can all be like "GANGBANG GANGBANG GANGBANG!" then ms krenca wil be like "STRIP STRIP STRIP" then i will be like "YES YES YES YES" then we all go to a huge gigantic bed and do STUFF GET WAT I MEAN?!?!?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i think i'd rather come here and write stoof... hokay so.. u guyz have exams now? when do u finish school? i CANT WAIT TILL SUMMER HOLIDAYSSSS!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha nice ad jac :P hey guys .. came back from miri it was greeat :D how are u guys ??? are u guys cool or cool cool cool or just cool less ..if u get what i meaN haha holz are passin quite fast :'(  which sucks and my leg still hurts ..anyways who wants to go to Mv on thursday?? i invited quite a few ppl already :D 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i understand youuu....ho hoh oh 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i understand... weird hi tech computer talking ppl.. ahh. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yeah... its true tht its a crappy mp3 :(&nbsp;only can hold freaking 32mb.. unless i find another MMC&nbsp;n it needs&nbsp;to be frm IO Data.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I need to get to pc fair asap.. wassup ppl?!? my hols r as boring as hell 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ya jon CHAY. u should listen to the smart boy master fung wei. okay. im just wrting nonsence so dun read what ever i post.    &nbsp;  la la la la. im bored and i wanna go back to skool.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wtf.... 250 bucks for such a crap mp3player... even a 128meg pendrive/mp3player is cheaper... so jon dont rip ppl off.... hahahaha.... and wat a crap place to try to sell something jon.... how many ppl actually read this... post it up on gis2005 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      no its okay jon chay. are u okay jon chay? jon chay is okay. chay okay? no its okay chay. but why? beacuse jon chay is okay. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Obviously he knows ritee?!?! yeahh, DFD is Data Flow Diagrams. I havn't start on tht either, just finished interviewing user only :(&nbsp; Did u know u're suppose to put it in dialog form so show prove of analysing?? Fung knows already... Can make up dialog lahh, no worries, who wanna buy a 32MB Mp3 player? selling for 250 only!!! Cheap Cheap~! (hope i didn't turn this forum into somekind of pasar malam =D )  {J}on {C}hay 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes i know. did you know? 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      u know u can remove ur own admin status 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      mother kiap kiap. make me ADMIN LAH!!!! what did I DO?!?!!?  anyways. yea jon whats a DFD? isit DATA FLOW DIAGRAM?!?! well if it is, i havnt done that yet. GUNBLADE. WHAT ABT BLADE GUN?! hi. come guys round up and lets play gunbound! 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      whaddyodoodle.... im sooo lost  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jon wats dfd?  and i havent started my project yet 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wuts wrong wif buying a gunblade? problem is finding one. Like i wanna be mr.loo's pet student crap. I don't, pretty much hates his stupid quotes and all. Jac, did u do DFD for ur project yet?Brian... is enjoyin in miri.. wut bout u fung? 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      where are you at fung?  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahaha.... jon chay wants to buy a gunblade?... hahahaha.... dat cool meh?... the lionheart sword looks sooo much cooler... y dont u try to find that on ebay...  and how on earth can mr loo get pissed at u jon... ur his friggin pet student.. hehehehe.... "if jonathan can do it than everyone can... " dats wat mr loo said rite... hahahahaha  and abt the computer studies project... dont worry jac... i dont think anyone has got very far... 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       oh yeah, fung i found a gunblade in ebay =D!!!! problem is tht its the size of a dam letter opener and obviously is used for a letter opener... can't find the actual scale of one... :(  {J}on {C}hay 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      h3y guys~! errm.. obviously fung's one is the best larrr... (lansi..) Anwyay, you guys started on ur CS project already? I just got a new one so i had to start all over again!! :'(&nbsp;&nbsp; Think i got mr. loo pissed, oh well don't care bout him lah.&nbsp; Hows life ppl?! Or hows your holss?! Brian is prob. in Miri now... lucky him. Ciao guyyyss  {J}on {C}hay 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey brian and fung, i was just wondering where u guys are at ur computer studies project....cos im still doing my problem description. tell me if u are way ahead or not. okay? peace.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      okay guys u are all admins now. sorry for the damage i have caused. u see, there was an evil spirit called yaktu. this spirit possesed my body and tried to take over the site. but i had enough stregth to take my body back. yea. PEACE 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i think someone else should be the judge.. like ben or jon chay or something.. yes, no?  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im sorry guys but did i hear something? well, i am the admin after all so i say I WON THE LOGO CONTEST. im in 2nd place and in 3rd place tooo so too bad guys. fung i have to say, that ur logo is of poor quality. arin ur logo suxs too. bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ok guyz.. i think i won the logo contest... here it is a ok! &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey, ppl... i think that oth are reallly cool logos... ill be posting one up sooon... and ma dad sez hi, and come visit and stufff. hahaha  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
             hi was bored and decided to create something better than jac's logo   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fung~! It ain't my fault u hav a crappy broadband connection!!! Yeahh, Jac u shud hav used photoshop or sumthing. looks like u did tht frm paint! Let btby n fung be admin larrr Fung! dam u for getting me addicted to FF lah!!! N yeahh... i can't find the cd, so i needed u to dl! =D thx!!! belanja u something later lahh!&nbsp; N my palms still hurt... all ur fault man! I'm dam confuse on the other ppl who they r... Alritey, gotta play games. Ciao guyys  {J}on {C}hay 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OIIIIIIIIIII JAC!!!! why on earth did u take us off admins?... and brian is right ur logo is ugly u could have at least used photoshop....  anyway i worte a realli long random borin post yesterday but the stupid thing didnt post... and i blame jon chay's FF8 download for scrweing up my internet.... damn u jon... everywhere i go also page cannot be displayed...  buh bye... and make us admin again please jac...  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          hahahahahaha tht logo is U_G_L_Y just like ur..... :P haha comon lar jac make us admin again Y u soo bad one = ( btw nice speech man haha &nbsp;     
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Well, beacuse I am LEADER, i present you the logo of thunderfriends.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bloggers of Thunder Birds &amp; Friend(s), I hereby announce myself, Jac Tang, the OFFICIAL administrator of this site. I have demoted the other 3 admins for absolute no reason at all but I promise you that I would lead this site to a better future. I will keep my annoucemet short and end off my saying HAPPY BLOGGING. Jac Tang. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wassup ppl?! Yea larr, hols are pretty boring these days. Lol, fung and i hav nothing to do. Dam xian. Brian, i hav&nbsp;ur add math revision bks, i'll give it to fung tomorrow ya? N fung, if u read this, remember to bring FF8 disc 3 tomorrow~!!! So i have something to do this comming week =D ciao guyyss 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          YO yo yo yo guys ..havent been bloggin for a while .. how are u guys ??? and hows ur holz?? is it like ...COOOL... or is it like yea.. ok&nbsp; .. haha goin to miri this monday yay!! cant wait guys ..... hoiildays are kinda borin lar ! i want to play football.. =( anyways gtg cya guys  peace out {>}   bye &nbsp;      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    check ot the NYPD truck with the new york crazy POlice with the crazy gunsssss.. holi moli..crazy&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hayalolomodo, u know what? i love the drink mango juice... tasty and smooth like a baby bottom.. so, everyone, yes i know i look cool with the glassees.. hahah no, anway it is time to say bye and hi at byhi..byE BYE 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      daryl wats the point of emailing when u can just tok here.... and when u say send pics... u mean here or email?... if here... go download the program form  urlLink www.hello.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey fellas, supp arin..yea im good (really cold).. oi fung until now u still don e-mail me a...ayo this 1 la  urlLink darylt@ggscorio.vic.edu.au &nbsp; newayz how do u send pics man? i got to run now ciao darsd 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      but what if the pictures are not cool?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      whoa cool pics arin.... the bithday one was soo long ago... we look so small.... and u look damn cool in the picture with the sunglasses...  so how everyone's holiday goin...? 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi daryl how is ur life mate 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guyz, hows home...school here is pretty good now...hope u guyz havin fun on ur hols..im so board now im tryin to do my visual communications graphics designing now...its so hard..so supp all. coool photos !! ok this is it 4 now...ciao dasdg 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      KEY to MY hole CAN be FOUND in BEN'S pants. hi guys, we look REALLY tiny in the pictures man! SURE. no.  bye  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey yong, do ya like the sound- stage crew photos... haha, remember when that guy became the leader, when he just joined.... err so pissing off, and we didnt show up to the meeting and that crazy woman with saggy flat tits- mrs krenca got sooo angry.. haha and she was like UR FIRED... then we were like u cnat fire me! i quit! haha... no oh randomness 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys .. nice work on getting the pictures up fung wei.. how are the holz ?? hope they are COOL anyways i gtg add maths tution &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i think so too....im blue, if i were green i would di, if i were green i would die, if i were green i would die. yes ok, no but i thot it was the telephone wire who did it 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why helloooo there jac why helloooo theregh dense foliage, momentary flashes of lightning illumining the night sky, open window panes hurtling violently
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys in my opinion, i think keira knightley is hot. not that hot but she is hot. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      YES i think that IS you. What do YOU think?!  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    guyz.. i want to ask a question.. is that me ?? cause i dont think so &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    hey here is mine and fung weis birthday!!!! 2 years ago... yr 8 it think, wah... seems so long ago... what the crazy!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    haha oohhhhhh good days, good days&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ok fine LAAASSST ONE&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ho ho, its the guy with the fro.. haha, ok, il stop doing th crazy stuuff now, ok bye&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    say hello to mR hamster!!!... yesz, now i dont have to go online to go to le blogger.. yes.. no, but yes!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    hey lo&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      NICE PHOTO DUD i wanna know how to put photos, but u r never onlineeee!!! lala.. summer days, drifiting away.. dooooab 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      then too bad 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      what if i have seen it? 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
             for those who hasnt seen these    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yay i did it.... figured out how to add pics u need to put this in ur post  ask me on messenger how... cause i cant do it here.... when i type it out... it puts a picture...  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
            testin     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      how was sex? hey anyone know how to upload pictureS?? dum dum dum. i tried but dunno how.  GET IT?        
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey people~!!! I finally gotten my blogger to work. Not badd, new stuff lately. Didn't use this for a dam long time. So wassup ppl?~
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAppy bithday.. ya i agree with jac, daryl... u should mind ur language, we are young ppl, and we dont like to hear things like that.... and dont call us assholes u australian racist person to black ppl... like al of us... hany way.. hapy holidayz everyone! i want to have sex now, ok bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      plz plz mind ur language young man. daryl, we are trying to make this blog as civilised as possible.  &nbsp; happy holidays to you too elanie. &nbsp; you know what i realised? next month, august 11, will be the official 1 year anniversary of this SITE!!!! and the day after that is MY BIRTHDAY!!! im SOO exciteD!!!. no. gtg sleeping now PEACE. &nbsp; JACSTER 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey dudes..its holidayzzz..haha...have a great greatt summerr! :D   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      soz sent 2ce dadef wazzup 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guyz, gurls, guygurls &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; supp all, im in oz now (boardin school) its fukin cold down here man....all u assholes so lucky 2months hols and im doin school, its warm there... i feel so jewed!!!! my god footie training is not good 4 times a week considerin u do beep testiin and endurance....so hard!! Too bad i couldn't see everybody last round... times runnin out u guyz so lucky 1 yr left i got 2!!! anywayz i gtg do some work now b4 the weekend hey every1 e-mail me @  urlLink darylt@ggscorio.vic.edu.au &nbsp;cool web peeps (hi every1 especially the guyz) (and gurls) (hi arin i luv u muah) byebye dassd&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey mans and mans. whos going to mv wif ben and shit today?  suck it like a litle ball bouncing. can  we play futsal tomorrow?! becos i want to. can we? can we? yes i think so too.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MY FINAL FANTASY X GAME FROZE.... AFTER A FRIGGIN BOSS.... AND I PLAYED AGAIN... AND IT FROZE AGAIN.... so annoyin... beatin a boss twice and the stupid game hung twice... i need a new cd...   HAHAHAHA... i think im addicted.... anyone willign to donate a FFX international cd?...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys, WHATS Up??!??! last day of school today man!! i want to go fishin tomorrow YAY !! man man man what can we do for 6 weeks ??? study? football? FISHIn?? eating?? watchin tv? for you see if the moon touches the earth at the correct angle and the water washes the sand at the excat moment when the fishes jump out of the water...... yes.... hahaha  anyways guys BYE BYE 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      can u feel the beat?!!? bom bom bom bom bom. can u feel it!?!!?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      SCHOOLS OVER.... and hmmm... cant tell if i am happy or sad... both i guess... brian was rite... it would get very lonely not seeing everyone everyday... but not needing to study everyday also kinda cool...  so should i be happy or sad?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      u know what guy... happy last day of schoool! im bored... hmmm, oreo's taste goood... went to the club today, went swimming.. rally fun... and the stuff, anywyay, it smells really bad right now cause i did something... hey im joining this crazy rowing team thing.. its gonna be coool.. i hope oh ya, someone say happy bday to fatin for meee wait, nevermind, ill call her la.. its ok, BYEBYEBYEYE i love u very smooch and i cant wait till june, and what i mean by febuary is december.... ok bye
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wow...im fighting wif a teacher. dum dee dee dum. u guys post so much man. so shall i. but for u see, what if i can't?ahhhhhh. yes. ever wondered why piss comes out from your dick instead of ur ass? mmmm. anyways, i wanna play footbaall with yr 8s. do YOU?! you and you?! anyhoooo hiiiii. arin arin arin uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh. yes. i think so..... u noe guys, i haf this firend who's name is guy. he has many guy friends. and i am one of them.   dum dum dum. tomorrow is the last day of skool. yay. wow. amazing. i wanna watch king arthur. it looks kool. for u see all king arthur movies are kool. today was a good day because i had many experiances. both wet and dry. big and small. okay PEACE OUT. A-town. WHAT ABOUT B-CITY?!?!?!?!?! HAHA. no.  THE MANIZER, WAC JAC TANG WANG aka 'the little thing' aka 'everthing black' aka 'PETER'
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahhaa cool dream dude ;) and most of the time ur dreams come true except for some weird ones :P haha its fatins b-day tomorrow IS IT AMAZINLY FAST!!! and just to tell u guys i asked fatin out on the 15th of july which is tomorrow WOW!!! hehe anyways arin wish u were here main ;) then the thunderbirds can go watch a movie together :D haha ok guys i m goin to get changed  take care and see you guys soon   Bt out  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wah.. soo bussy, fungg the site looks like crazy awesomee.. and like it is sooo cool and the stuff and i am eating cereal now yumm tasty... i wanna go back and play soccer with u guyz's... i missss those daysss. i cant wait till someone invents the teleportion machine... then ill be like everywhere at onece... what the crazy rite... holi moli... anyway... the thing is i had a dream rite.. whrre we were all together, and there were my canadian friends and u guyz, and  all met each other AND, just for the record, BRIAN was going out with fatin in my dream, and u know about my dreams rite.. they are the truest dreas ever... and fung and jac and fais got in a fight with some of the teachers in ma school... it felt sooo real! any way... gtg to ma frends hooose.... bye bye.. peace!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have a suggestion lets go watch king auther on thurday after school... we finish at 11.... so we got like alot of time to watch... and malls wont be crowded... and crap have to get somethin for fatin... =P.. suck at presents... hahaha... wat to buy... anyone wanna share?...  anyway brian holidays still can see friends wat... i think... organise outing somewhere... and if anyone does make it at the begining of the holz else i wont be here...  and footie trainin... why not... we need somethin to do during the holidays rite... football once a week would be cool.. and we still have to play the year 8s my brother keep buggin me... brian when u wann aplay them?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha hes the TECH maIN :P hehe school isnt tht bad lar wei :) enjoy the company ie all the friends we have :P coz durin the holz we are not goin to see ..err.. some ppl hahaa besides mr reeeves is leavin man :( well lets all have a moment of silence for MR REEEVes hahaha :) to one of the best teachers i know ! what are u guys getting for MS FAtin ? ?? BTW do you guys want soccer trainin durin the holz?? or do u guys wana stay home and study :P haha OK i wana watch king Arthur this weekend :D haha ok guys   see ya all tomorrow except arin :P PEace out   B T
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi all... seems that brian asked me alot abt puttin pictures here... or isit onli twice o well... since im the technician i will have to figure out how.. =P... cant be too hard... anyway can u guys like send pictures of urself to my mail or something... and if anyone has a pic of me please send.. cause i dunt have...  anyway cant wait till the end of school.... 2 MORE DAYS!!!!!!! YAY... and 2 parties tomorrow... and 1 test =(... and 2 more lessons with ms thiaga =(.. dang....  and another 4 with ms kunahlan.. shit the more i think of what i have left... the more i dunt feel like goin to school...   well got eng hw to do now... ciao
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      in my opinion, i think the site looks better now. maybe that is because of me getting sick of the old template. due to technical difficulties, our very own technician, fung wei, has helped us improve our site. PEACE. did u noe that in an average day, an average sized cow eats and average number of 10 milion average sized leaves? but does it? or does it not? give it a think. hmmmmm. i think so. PEACE. ziaaaaa. hi. MY DICK IS GETTING BIGER AND BIGGER as i am looking at a picture of jonchay. yes. that is me. and i am me. and you are not me as you are you and you are not me as i only can be me for i am me. GET IT? okay. PEACE is all i want for the world to be a better place for my childeren and my childeren's childeren. and of course, ur childeren. as they are your childeren and not mine. OKAY. I AM SPAMMINGGG. SPAM SPAM SPAM luncheon meat. is tasty. PEACE. if u want be to shut up, just post it up. all complaints are invited. PEACE
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WOW this site really looks good fung :) now we just need pics of ourselves :P haha man 2 more days of school LEFT!!! WOW!!! and fatin's B-day AS WELL. ! its A M A Z  IN  G haha we are goin to  eat KFC and pizza hut tomorrow .. YAY i also have a party after break haha IS anyone goin anywhere durin the holz??? or is everyone goin to stay home and study ;)   Brian Tan OUT  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys... ok fung i promised nothing longggggggggggggggggggggeeeeeeeeeeeeeerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr than 59 letters.vso anyways school finishes on thurs..wooohooo but i still hav coursework. ok  bye, peace out, ciao, seeya, bb BenT =]
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl... redid the site... had abit of trouble with the template... please especially jac and ben... maximum characters in a word is 59... so dont go   ziaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  hahaha... had to cut 3 "a"s of ur words to make it fit.. hehe....  if u like the oled template better... i can put it back.. but not just yet... cause webspace is down... this woudl ahve to do for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      africa jac?... hahahahaha....  anyway.... wassup ppl?... cant wait till the end of school.... 3 days left...and there is no more futsal competition or prefects work =)... gettin tired nowadays.... yay.. then we get to go and have fun... and i can play final fantasy for as long as i like... hehehe... anyway sorrie about the background.... stupid ppl scrwed up my webspace.... hope files r still there... else ill have to add again.... and are we realli goin to do our end of year holiday... lets change it to after year 11.... or was it oledi after yr 11... and our first stop can be canada... and from there arin can follow us.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hello, my name is abu.. and i love to eat baboons on a stick
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahahaha jac u dam sick man :P why africa???? isnt it like very hot there ?? haha hey guys where do u wana go for a hoilday???? we can like arrange STUFF and we can all go for a hoilday together MUAhahaha.. hey fung wei! it isnt THT bad sittin in the front row u know :P hahaha its R_E_L_A_X_I_N_G ! hahaa anyways guys peace out    BT  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yes WE will ALL go TO africa. TO see THE hot CHICKS in BLACK. hi all. ziaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa wussup guys, hows everybody. hey arin go to www.gunbound.net and dl the game and play it and get addiected to it so we can PLAY! PLAY PLAY PLAY! u guys are the apples of my apple pie.   bye PEACE DAWGS. NIGGA LUVERS. BLACK MAN IN THE HOUSE. BRUDDA IN THE HOOD. fo' shizzle my nizzle. haaaaa yeaaaaaahhhh . CATCH YOU GUYS LATERS!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      guyz... if u all go to melbourne... u know what... thats so cool, cuase then there will be 3 of u and daryl.. then ill be in africa, and well visit each otherrr... ya... hey jac, the dancing hamster still works.. and i still find it soo funnyy... like ya... anyway.. gtg bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hie... sorry for being dead for a while... spiderman was okay... brian loved it with the front seats.. I got headache now... cant wait for holidays.... so sick of school.... and arin ur room damn cool lar... can see u got all the gis yearbooks there.... and cool speakers... =) and the dancing hamster... hope to see u soon when u come back.. cant wait... and would like to visit u over there someday  jac daryl saw this site.. and wants to join... i got no idea how to do that oledi though  and about the background... ill fix the problem soon... once i get my webspace working again...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey u guyz know the stuff with the place and the thing and the person? AHH...  summer days drifted away doooooaabb of the summer nights oh wella wella wella ddum.. grease lignting baby!... peace!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys hehe sure arin ofcourse u can come ;) sometimes i can see the background sometimes i cant jac... anayways tomorrow is SOCCER TRAININ WOW! yes i know .. 1 year passed really fast remember when we were foolin around in ythe lrt station thingi?? hehe cool man   Bt out 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi guys, hi arin sure u can come tomorrow! just cant wait to see you!! and u're room is nice and sexy. can fit 10 chics in there. neways.. i still haf problems wif the site. cannot see the background. isit just me or u guys too? PEACE
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok, im coming this saturday to watch spider man... hey u guyz know i left about a year ago almost.... its so like clazy and stuff...peace 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey GUYS! i bought spiderman 2 as well :D my bro plays it like 24/7 maIn hehe iw ana watch spiderman 2 this weekend who wants to come ???? btw theres train this saturday ok??? ill just sit and tell you guys what to do hehe .. :( i tore my ligament man!!! it sucks need to use crutches!!!1 argh ALAMAKMAL.. fatins birthday next weeek WOW its really fast man One year has passes already! haha anyways cya guys   BT 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey GUYS! i bought spiderman 2 as well :D my bro plays it like 24/7 maIn hehe iw ana watch spiderman 2 this weekend who wants to come ???? btw theres train this saturday ok??? ill just sit and tell you guys what to do hehe .. :( i tore my ligament man!!! it sucks need to use crutches!!!1 argh ALAMAKMAL.. fatins birthday next weeek WOW its really fast man One year has passes already! haha anyways cya guys   BT 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      isit just my pc or is the background for the site not there? hey arin go get spiderman2!! its the best game!!! u can swing and swing and swing lke uve never swung b4!!!! its suppppeeerrr webelistic! get it!?! hi. oh dear.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      lalala..... the spiderman game looks cool i wanna play itt!! hey did u guyz's know the simpsons have an albumm.. im listening to it right now... its so cool! hey fung and brian and jac... when i come back we haf to jammmmm im gonna bring ma guitar back! im learning blues and stuff... clazy... anyway, haf fun in the holidays, bye bye swing swing swingggg PEACE!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahahaha.... faggots now... wanna kick me out..... o fine...  btw r we watchin spiderman this weekend?... abit confused... trainin is on rite
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh i thought there wasnt training this sat?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yes!!1 Finally jac is gone :P haha j jk Football trainin is on this sat then we can watch SPIDER MAIN 2 :D ..it cant be THT bad jac right ?? ANYWAYS this site is alive again and i think we should kick fung wei out since he never post anytihng ! MUAhahahahaha ...ok :P 2 more weeks of school left.. fast man..gtg guys  BYe!   Bt tan mei foong GET IT! 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Y hello. i would like ya all to know that tomorrow is thunderbird golden pheonix's B-day so i would like to congratulate with a hONOURy thuderbird Cheer "TWIT TWIT TWIT TWIT" hahahaha :P  Wow it has been almost one year .. since this site was made :'( im soo proud!!! hahaha i would like to say to u all tht it has been an honour to be friends with u and i would gladly fall in battle for u guys ! haha peace {v}  the Green Falcon :D 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      happy birthday birdie.  where is everybody? how come no one posts anything up?! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My fellow thunderbird pals i would like to annouce that our thunderbirds and friends site will be turning 1 year old in 2 days!!! im sooo excited!!! hi. we should all have our own little message to honour our site. i will start:  "well i would like to say happy birthday to you thunderbird. i so proud of you. i have seen you grow from a little bird to a big bird. get it? that beans u have grown.peace out." 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh yes i feel you on that one. thanks brother. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      jac, ill send u some hoe's and some bling bling cause i know they like that in the hood.. yes, no, peace!  -Ak- 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      is PATRICK VIERA coming to REAL MADRID? 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha... jac did i get u a present last year... i dunt remmeber... i hope i did... dont worrie i would get u a realli cool present this year.. even if ur black... need to think of something first though.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      its okay if u dun get me a present. im kool. coz im black. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha jac y do u want to be black :P from now on we can call u BLACK JAC GET IT ?? GET I???? HO ho ho FUNAY! yea ok .. so whats up guys ?? jacs B-day next week .. WOW thts amazing haha hey jac this time ill get u a better present :P not like last time i got u a cheap jedi outcast Cd hahaha anyways peace out peace out@  BT bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      whassup ma chigger... welcome to the kampung 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hows your mother 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys, for some reason i feel like being black. so im gonna start acting black. and when i grow up, im going to micheal jackson's plastic surgeon and ask him to turn me black.  peace out yall. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      SHUT.. i meant how non of us are going to stay in malaysia  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i stayed in malaysia. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ahhh hayo.. i dunt believe we are in yr 11.... carazy! yes, well, its weird how none of us actually stayed in malaysia....aha do u know if u guyz are going to the same school in melbourne?? 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      no 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      why hello there... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DAMN.. yeal 11 is soooo sooo soon... we are gonna die =(... and life aint gonna get any easier... and when we all spit after year 11... i realli wonder what life would be like.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
              GOOooood MOoorrriinnnin i want to play football lar!! my legs need to run and my total 90 111 needs to score some GOAls MAIN!! AMah haha how are u guys ?? we have 3 weeks of holz left :( tht sucks maIN hey arin hows your holz?? is it like fun and stuff??  holz are ok lar ..sometimes a bit borin though.. scared tht year 11 is comin so soon and im goin to miss u guys when u leave :'( haha        BT B T                 
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha.... nice oral sex thingy..       *sniff* *sniff* no mv for me 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      me me me... i wanna go.... hahaha... brian who u invited oledi?... thursday at 11 ya 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>