<Blog>


<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        First Roundtable!   Ok. This is the first Roundtable about Taker/Angle. And a lot of other stuff. I mainly asked the questions to Drewcifer because I consider him one of they few people that understand wrestling in a way deeper than just thinking they know what they are talking about (like me) So without further adieu...the roundtable  Peter -- First off do you think that Taker deserves a shot?  Peter -- why or why not?  Drewcifer -- hell yeah he does Drewcifer -- Taker has been solidly behind the Mcmahons through thick and thin Peter -- yes he has, and through all his matches where he has jobbed for people (Cena included) he should dang well win the title next week  Peter -- But if he does win it...that is another story  Peter -- as a mark who do you think would win this match?  Drewcifer -- he's not going to win the title next week Peter -- why not?  Drewcifer -- Taker is contyent in his role as a locker room leader... Peter -- good point  Drewcifer -- plus everyone loves angle Peter -- I never really looked at it that way  Drewcifer -- Angle is going to take the belt all the way to Wrestlemania Peter -- if you were the Undertaker next week, who would you more than likely look to come from the back? Because with WWE these days nobody will job for anyone anymore  Drewcifer -- keep in mind that next months PPV is a RAW only thing Peter -- ah yes  Peter -- didn't Raw have the last one before summerslam?  Drewcifer -- Besides, Angle has everyone's respect in the back Drewcifer -- no, Smackdown! had the last one Peter -- But say by hook or crook Taker wins the belt at SD! next Thursday....and then what would happen?  Drewcifer -- won't happen Peter -- you sound so posative  Drewcifer -- I'm betting on some sort of run-in from brock or slow Drewcifer -- or both Peter -- why would they take out taker though? have they formed an alliance? are they going to take out taker then go after angle?  Drewcifer -- hard to say Peter -- lets look farther down the line, like say to Mania XX...and lets say that Angle is going to hold the title  Peter -- and he fued with the obvious norms of SD! main events....lesnar...pig slow....taker...do you think that we could see another fatal 4 way elimination match like at mania 2000 (mania 16)??  Drewcifer -- honestly, I think they're going to build up to Angle/ Lesnar for Survivor Series and do it again at Mania Drewcifer -- in the meantime?  sure Peter -- have Angle and the Undertaker had any feuds in the past?  Drewcifer -- Angle/Lesnar has the potential to be one of the greatest feuds of all time Drewcifer -- Taker/Angle? Peter -- i heard someone say that it could possible be as big as the hogan/andre feud of the past  Drewcifer -- none that I can remember Drewcifer -- I said that Peter -- maybe armageddon hell in a cell..but that involved so many other guys....the immortal HHH....Rikishi...Rock....and Austin  Peter -- ahh yes....you did didn't you...or did you?  Drewcifer -- Austin!! Peter -- lets skip shows here for a second....(yes austin)  Peter -- what is your opinion on the IMMORTAL ONE.... eveyones favorite dillhole Triple H?  Drewcifer -- Hell YEAH!!! Peter -- ha ha (in case you haven't figured it out...Drewcifer is a HUGE Austin fan)  Drewcifer -- honestly? Peter -- yes honest  Peter -- keep the profanitly a little low though...what if some kid reads this....  Drewcifer -- the thing is, back in the day, when I was your age, pedro, I hated Ric Flair Drewcifer -- He would never loser his title to anyone Drewcifer -- as I got older and became more educated about wrestling Peter -- I think I might know where you are going with this  Drewcifer -- I realized that I loved to hate Ric Flair Peter -- (good point)  Drewcifer -- which is why he was so over Drewcifer -- and now HHH is the same way Drewcifer -- except I'm a little more educated in the inner works of wrestling these days Peter -- like HHH is Ric Flair in some ways...do you think that having Ric by his side....the WHOOOO 16 TIME CHAMP!....makes anyone 'love to hate' Triple H anymore?  Drewcifer -- but I hate HHH just like I hated Flair back in the day Peter -- how about the Hair on Nash? I have wanted to blog about this forever!...what do you think about it?  Drewcifer -- I'm really not concerned about the hairdo's on the guys... Drewcifer -- now a Trish/Victoria hair vs. Hair match... Peter -- WHOA!! That would be a nice one to see! I'm sure all the fans would love it  Peter -- ok...Closing Comments?  Drewcifer -- I'm marking out for Brock Lesnar Peter -- explain  Drewcifer -- I think he's the future of wrestling Peter -- like another Hogan...or Freddie Blassie type even?  Drewcifer -- along with Rey Rey Peter -- I think that Rey is getting old....how old is he do ya know?  Peter -- like 30s? Drewcifer -- If the writers use them correctly Peter -- then again Terry Funk was doin some moonsaults at age 54 for the WWE (then wwf)  Peter -- yeah like in WCW they had Rey Rey run with Nash and almost win the belt  Drewcifer -- I think rey Rey deserves a run with the title Peter -- so do I  Peter -- maybe just maybe in the future do you think that he acutally will?  Drewcifer -- I'd love to see a Rey Rey angle match Peter -- already happened my friend  Drewcifer -- for the title, I mean. I'm talking about a Main Event Peter -- ah...sorry...I was going to say almost one year ago at SS 2002 they met Drewcifer -- I remember Peter -- can you recall who won the match?  Drewcifer -- Angle Peter -- ah yes...angle lock correct? Im looking it up now. Peter -- Hey you are right Drew! You really really know your stuff when it comes to wrestling!  Drewcifer -- then again I'd alaso like to see Booker T, or RVD run with the title as well Peter -- ok well with that nice long rant about Rey Rey, Booker T, and RVD...I think I am going to close the Roundtable...Peace
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Smackdown! 8/28/03    I've been having computer issues tonight, so I missed the first segment of Smackdown!.  Actually, I had it on mute while I was on the phone with my tech geek friend.  I saw Eddy Guererro and John Cena seeiming to have a promo-fest...apparently they're going to have a match later.  I also missed most of the Rey Mysterio-Nunzio match, which sucks because Rey Rey is one of my favorite wrestlers...anyway, Rey Rey won.  Up next is Benoit- A-Train...In the middle of the match, Albert pulled off the turnbuckle pad.  Benoit then hit a German Suplex and a headbutt from the top rope.  Prince Albert kicked out of the pin and ran Benoit into the exposed turnbuckle.  Benoit kicked out of the pin attempt, the ran A-Train into the steel.  Crippler-crossface and a tap and Benoit wins.  The replay shows he had his foot on the rope though.  Back from commercial break, A-Train jumps Benoit in the back with Rhyno's help and knocks Benoit out.  Meanwhile, someone has stolen the tires off of Eddie's low-rider.  He gets into a shoving match with the FBI until APA breaks it up.  When did Guerreo become a face, anyway?  HERE COMES THE PAIN!!!  Lesnar struts out to the ring.  He still gets a good pop from the fans.  He proceeds to tell the fans, "SHUT UP AND SIT DOWN!"  He proceeds to throw a tantrum because he tapped out at SummerSlam and calls it a fluke. "I'm not a quitter, dammit!"  He proceeds to put over his SummerSlam match as something that will never happen again, and demands a re-match.  Kurt Angle appears on the Titan-Tron and begins to mock Brock in an obvious pre-taped segment.  He calls Brock a "whiny little bitch".  Angle is obviously borrowing from Flair's book and overusing the "Whooo!" thing.  Out of nowhere, DEAD MAN WALKING hits and the Undertaker comes out.     Taker proceeds to preach the rules of the yard..."You were in front of the line, now you go to the back of the line.  And it's been a long time since Big Evil's had a title shot.  You got a problem leaving the yard, I'll be glad to help ya!"  Which brings the Big Slow to the ring.    Paul Wight still can't handle a mic to save his life.  "I'm 7 foot 2 500 pounds..."  BORING...he claims he's the #1 contener when Angle's music hits...  YOU SUCK!!   Angle says he doesn't give a damn who he faces.  he says he'd love to make Brock tap out again, then turns to the Undertaker and says it would be an honor to make him tap in his yard.  He proceeds to insult Show's body odor when Steph's music hits.  Steph is calling the shots tonight and makes a triple threat match with Taker, Show, and the Pain.  Back from commercial, Cena rhymes about how he never touched Eddie's car.  (My money says Chavo did it...)  Anyway, Cena's music hits, and he's got a tire from Eddie's car.  Before he can bust a rhyme, Eddie jumps him.  Cena gets busted up early.  (Now I realize why Eddie is a face, they're in El Paso; Eddie's hometown.)  Eddie does a good job of dominating the match, until missing a dropkick, when Cena takes over, briefly.  Eddie goes right back on the offense, only to find Cena was playing possum.Eddie throws in the tire that Cena brought out...while the ref was throwing it out, Eddie smacks Cena with a chair, then goes for the froggy.  Cena rolls out of the way and we go to commercial...  Back from comercial...Cena has full advantage, but misses the pinfall.  He pulls off a nice press-suplex, but Eddie kicks out again.  Cena slaps on a sleeper-hold but Eddie comes back, and Latino Heat fires up.  Eddie reverses an FU, and goes for the pin, but Cena kicks out.  The crowd is firmly behind Eddie.  Cena hits a low-blow and gets disqualified.  Then he wraps his chain around his hand and abuses the hell out of Eddie.Cena pulls the tire in the ring and FU's the US Champ on it.     Word Life.  Anyway...they're putting on the highlights from last weeks Brock beatdown on Zach Gowen...And HERE COME'S THE PAIN!  and it's a Big Bad Show tonight...(rolling eyes) DEAD MAN WALKING!  Apparently Show and Lesnar are in cahoots for this match.  But Angle comes out and takes his place next to Tazz and Moron Cole.  And then a commercial.  (this is the first time I've ever typed out a play-by-play wrestling thing, and i gotta tell you, my fingers are getting sore.)  Brock and Slow are double-teaming Taker.  Big Slow just pulled off a very nice suplex on Taker.  Amazing!!  Big knows how to do a wrestling move...anyway, Brock and Show get into it until Taker gets back in the ring and takes care of business.  Brock goes for an F-5 on Taker, but Slow, breaks it up.  He goes for a chokeslam, but Takerv turns it into a submission hold, which Lesnar breaks up.    The action spills outside the ring.  Brock puts Taker up for the F-5, but Taker jumps out and throws Brock into the ring post.  Big Slow comes up from behind and whacks Taker and Lesnar with a steel chair.  The we go to commercial...  Back from commercial...we have Big Slow and Undertaker in the ring, with Brock writhing outside until he breaks up a submission hold that Taker had on Slow.  Undertaker choke-slammed Brock, but Brock kicked out.  WOW!!!  Lesnar pulls off a beautiful vertical suplex on the Big Slow.  Taker breaks the count though.  Brock turns around and F-5's Taker, but the Slow breaks the count.  Big Slow goes for a top rope Choke slam on Brock, but Undertaker breaks it up.  Undertaker goes for a Last Ride on Brock, and Taker gets the three count!  Undertaker is facing Kurt Angle next week for the WWE Championship!  As the show goes off the air, Undertaker and Kurt Angle stare eachother down....    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Summerslam?    I was honestly expoecting something shocking to happen at Summerslam.  I figured Triple H had a groin injury,  and was near  to his wedding (real life wedding that is) with Steph, that he'd drop the belt.   I had figured he'd drop it to Jericho.  Instead...  HHH does the least amount of wrestling possible in the Chamber match and wins it.   I got no problem with Goldberg jobbing...in fact, I'm glad he did.  I llike the idea of Goldberg having to face HHH in a "must retire match" at the next PPV.  I hope Goldberg loses.  And I think he will.  Bill Goldberg doesn't do house shows.  He's only there  for TV.  My guess is, they're going to build up to the next PPV, and then Goldberg's gone.  As far as the rest  of Summerslam?  As an Austin mark goes, I enjoyed the Shane/Bischoff match, but I was hoping for a bigger bump on the end of Shane-O  All I could think during the 'Taker-A_train match was"please find a way to trade Undertaker to RAW and let him feud with Kane"  Speaking of Kane...  I'm all for his push and all, but for the love of Jericho, quit burying Rob Van Dam.   RVD has the potential of being the next mainstream breakout star of wrestling.  The only three others who have made that feat were Hulk Hogan, Stone Cold, and The Rock.   For the love of Sammartino, WWE, give RVD the push!  And as far as Brock vs. Angle goes...this feud is better off without any McMahon involvement.  These two have the potential to eclipse the Hulk vs. Andre feud.  Brock Lesnar is a monster, and in his very short time in the WWE, he's become one of my favorites.  Angle has become universally recognized as one of the best.     I hope the writers are smart enough to push the feud to WrestleMania XX.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        No Raw or SD! for me   Grrr. I didnt get a chance to tape Raw last night. Seeings how I dont have cable to watch Raw, or UPN to watch Smackdown, I am getting mad! Stupid Smackdown! is being replayed on a local channel on Saturday nights. But now they are starting to air some crap on the Kansas City Cheifs during that time slot. So that means that there is no SD! for me either! During the summer I would go over to Jadie's and watch Raw every once and a while. But now I cant!...Dang...now I'm mad...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Summer Slam Match Outcomes   1)  Raw Heavyweight Title  - (Elimination Chamber) Triple H def. Shawn Michaels, Goldberg, Kevin Nash, Chris Jericho, and Randy Orton 2)  SD! Heavyweight Title  - Kurt Angle def. Brock Lesnar 3)  US Title  - (Fatal 4 way) Eddie Guerrero def. Rhyno, Chris Benoit, and Tajiri 4)  Raw Tag Team Title  - La Resistance def. the Dudley Boyz 5) Kane def. RVD 6) The Undertaker def. A-train 7) Shane McMahon def. Eric Bischoff 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        The Roundtable(s)   None this month. Sorry all.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Summer Slam Matches   The  matches as announced are  1)  Raw Heavyweight Title  - (Elimination Chamber) Triple H (champion) vs. Shawn Michaels vs. Goldberg vs. Kevin Nash vs. Chris Jericho vs. Randy Orton 2)  SD! Heavyweight Title  - Kurt Angle (champion) vs. Brock Lesnar 3)  US Title  - (Fatal 4 way) Eddie Guerrero (champion) vs. Rhyno vs. Chris Benoit vs. Tajiri 4)  Raw Tag Team Title  - La Resistance (champions) vs. the Dudley Boyz 5) RVD vs. Kane 6) A-train vs. The Undertaker 7) Shane McMahon vs. Eric Bischoff
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        First Blog   Hello one and everyone tonights PPV is the classic Summerslam! Last years SS rocked majorly! but I dont know about this one. It should be good. But we will see. It is a joined PPV with both Raw and Smackdown! on one show...who knows maybe fireworks will fly
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...with the very few tag teams that have graced my presence these very few years that I have been watching professional wrestling...I'm going to say what I think. Even if it is a crappy tag team in Drew's eyes. Oh yeah...and Drew...I'm not a geezer either...I'm far from it, about 15 years farther away than you!!!   #1--The New Age Outlaws ("The Road Dogg" Jesse James & "The Bad Ass" Billy Gunn):   These guys were gold. As I recall my first time seeing them was on the Monday Night Raw, right after Mania 14. They were to face the team of Chainsaw Charlie (Terry Funk) and Cactus Jack (Mick Foley...for all you fools out there). This was not just going to be any simple match. Ya see the stip was, the night before they fought in a dumpster match. The Outlaws lost...getting sealed in THE WRONG DUMPSTER. Therefore, the titles were vacent and were to be defended on that particular night. The Outlaws won it, while also becoming part of D-generation X (already with Triple H, X-Pac, and Chyna). DX then became my one of my favorite groups.ever.   #2--The Dudleys (D-Von & Buh Buh Ray):  These guys have done it all. They are the only tag team to win all of the top 3 tag titles of the moder era, ECW Tag Titles (9 time champs), WCW Tag Titles (1 or 2 times champs), WWF/E Tag Titles (5 or 6 times champs). Is there anything about these guys that you can hate? One black and one white guy; what a combo! These guys are funny, and they can kick some major @ss too!!  We Want Tables!    #3--The Road Warriors (Hawk & Animal):  To directly quote Drew - "Only because you can't mention great tag teams without mentioning them.  'Nuff said." Plus I didn't even like these guys, and they still made it to number 3 on my list!   #4--The APA (Bradshaw & Ron Simmons):   Drink Beer or Fight!  These guys were nuts! They were fighting everywhere. Bars, in the back, in the parking lot, and they even had good ring skills. These two were fairly decent by themselves...but together, they made quite the team. They are even the guys that Vince looks for to put some guys in-line that aren't doing their job right!   #5--(tie) The Headbangers (Mosh & Thrasher) and Owen Hart (RIP) & Jeff Jarrett:  The Headbangers were pretty funny, and awesome to watch. They pulled off some great tag team moves. Like something simple, such as powerbombing your partner...onto your opponent lying on the ground. They had so much chemistry in the ring. It was nuts. I also loved the way they would taunt their opponents. -- Jarrett and Owen made a really fast ride to the top as a tag team. They won the titles from Ken Shamrock and the Big Boss Man on Raw one week. Boy did I hate them...but man I loved Debra! Their title run fell short just a few weeks before the tragic death of Owen Hart. Rest In Peace.   #6--The Two Man Power Trip (Triple H and Stone Cold Steve Austin):  These guys didn't seem too tough to beat, if faced by the right tag team that is. But alone these guys were top notch power houses. They ruled the wrestling world, and still do. Together they made a nearly unbeatable group. Austin was already the Heavyweight Champion, and Trips was the IC Champ too. I cant recall if they won the tag titles at that time too...but I know that they held them at one point or another. Because they lost them to Benoit and Jericho.   #7--(3 way tie) Kane & Mankind, The Brothers of Destruction (Kane and Taker), and The Minestry (Taker and Big Show):  All of these guys weren't together for too long (a few months to a half year), and they weren't anything special, but I think that they deserve to at least be mentioned. They were all forces that were not to be reconned with!  There are so many mediocre to good teams that I could mention. And remember I dont have too much experience with tag teams either...so bare with me!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tag team wrestling today is nothing like it used to be.  These days there are very few "real" teams.  (The Dudley's, Benjamin & Haas, seem to be the rare exceptions.)  Back when I was a young lad  Jesus, Drew, you're not even 30 yet...quit acting like such a goddamned geezer , we had tons of "strictly tag teams".  So without further ado...   #1--The Midnight Express ("Sweet" Stan Lane & "Beautiful" Bobby Eaton):   This team had the coolest music, one helluva manager, and some of the smoothest scientific moves for a heel tag team.  Jim Cornette would always hit the ring first to introduce them, cuz no ordinary ring announcer could do them justice.  "Ladies and Gentlemen, get ready for the greatest tag team ever, twin brothers from seperate mothers..."  and stuff like that.  My favorite memory of them was seeing them defeat Tully Blanchard & Arn Anderson for the NWA tag team belts. I think I became a fan of theirs when they began their long, drawn out feud with the Rock n' Roll Express, who were nothin' but a couple pretty boys who deserved to have their teeth kicked in.   #2--The Road Warriors (Hawk & Animal):  Only because you can't mention great tag teams without mentioning them.  'Nuff said.   #3--Demolition (Ax & Smash):  This team still goes down in history  as the longest running Tag Champs in WWF/E history.  At first, they were considered the Fed's cheap ripoff of the Road Warriors. And to be fair, they probably were.  But over the months, they were able to gain the respect of fans like myself and the writers with their pure brutality in the ring.  It took a chair shot from Arn Anderson (there I go mentioning Tully & Arn again) to end their year and a half title run.  They would have a couple more turns with the belt though.   By the time they brought in Crush as a third member, it was pretty much over.  But it was great while it lasted.     #4--(tie)The British Bulldogs (Davey Boy Smith & Dynamite Kid) and the Hart Foundation (Bret Hart & Jim Neidhart):   I consider this a tie because they were the top two teams in thier time.  I always enjoyed their matches.   #5--Lex Luger & Barry Windham:   This was a relatively short  lived team, but one of the loudest pops I ever heard at a live show ever was when they beat Tully & Arn for the tag team belts.  I still have pictures of that match somewhere.   The team broke up a few months later when Barry swerved on Lex, joined the Four Horsemen, and  handed the belts back to Tully & Arn.    #6-- The Mulkeys...just kidding...   #6--Tully Blanchard & Arn Anderson:   Of course I was to get to them.  I didn't realize what an impact on tag team wrestling they had until I started writing this thing.  Seems like a lot of my favorite Tag Team moments involved them in one way or another.  Either as members of the Four Horsemen in NWA, or as the Brainbusters in WWF, their no-nonsense, hard hitting style made them one of the best tag teams ever.  It's also worth noting that they were the first team to ever hold both the NWA/WCW and WWF tag team title.  (The Road Warriors were the second).   #7--Rick and Scott Steiner:   This was back before Scott Steiner bulked up and became The Genetic Freak.  Back in the day, Scotty was the master of all forms of suplexes, and practically invented the Frankensteiner (aka Hurricarana).  Scotty was the high flyer, while Rick "The Dog-faced Gremlin" was the brutal mat wrestler.  I'm sure they had a match or two with Tully and Arn, but I can't think of any off the top of my head.  (They were also the third team to hold both World straps).    I'd include the Dudley's on this list, but seeing as how they have plenty of life left in them, there's still a lot of history for them to make.  Also gaining honorable mention are the New Age Outlaws, The Hardyz, Edge & Christian, Beavis & Butthead (oh, wait a sec...),  and The Brothers of Destruction.   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Drew! You want to call me Wee Wee in front of the dozens...AND DOZENS of readers out there!?!? Well I'll show you!!! Also keep in mind, like Drew said, that I am half his age...about. Therefore, I have only seen a few greats in my day. I haven't been watching wrestling very long either. Maybe only about 5-6 years.   #1--"The Heart Break Kid" Shawn Michaels--  This guy was the whole reason that I began to watch wrestling in the first place. I flipped on the TV and saw someone superkick the Undertaker, put him into a body bag. Prance around like he was the biggest of all the big-shots and then do some really neat poses with some cool fireworks. I loved everything about HBK. The nickname, how the ladies loved him, how athletic he was, etc. etc.   #2--Mick Foley (aka Dude Love, Cactus Jack, and Mankind)--  Is there anything really special about how this guy taunts?  Nope.  Okay how about his awesome physique?  What physique??  Hmmm. How about his ravishingly good looks?  Uh...no!  So what makes this guy so special??? The fact that he spent his whole life trying to get into the Fed. He wrestled in High School gyms to start his carreer. After he got better, he went to Japan and wrestled. In Japan he had his whole body torn apart. But he kept going til he made it ECW, then WCW and then finally to the Fed. When he won the title I went nuts. I went to school the next day the BIGGEST Foley fan ever. I have both of his autobios and his new book Tietam Brown. This guy is the best!   #3--The Rock (Rockey Miavia)--  What can I say about the Rock? This man, next to Hulk Hogan, has had one of the best carreers in the history of the business. When you were supposed to hate him...you still liked him. Then when you were supposed to like him...you loved him. He was the first 3rd generation "superstar" on the Fed's roster. And what a stud he is.   #4--Bret "Hit Man" Hart--  I didn't quite start watching wrestling in time to see Bret in the Fed. I tuned in just as he was leaving. And what a shame it was. I have seen about 50% of the matches Bret has been in and they are classics. The very first Iron Man Match. The first Ladder Match. He was a tag champ, IC champ, and a world champ...and thats just the WWF/E! His feuds with his brother and with Austin were among the top 10 feuds in the history of WWF/E.   #5--Owen Hart (RIP)--   What was so great about Owen Hart?  Well...hmm...lets see here. There wasn't a whole lot that was too great about his wresting style, or his out of ring abilities, or how well he could handle the stick (microphone); but the way that these not so great attributes meshed together made an excellent entertainer. He also had a bad gimmick as the Blue Blazer, which eventually led to his death, but despite that he made it work. Just for the record, from what was said on the special Raw episode dedicated to Owen, I take it he was quite the ribber and quite the family man. I really would have been honored to shake his hand, or just to even see him live.   #6--nWo--  Hmmm...can I do that? Can I just make the collective unit there one of the Hall of Famers?... Well...Im pretty sure that  I JUST DID!  These guys were studs. And Im not talking about Vince's lame redition of the nWo. Im talking about nWo Black and White (Hogan, Nash, and Hall). These guys could really raise some hell in WCW. They kicked ass and took names day in and day out! I didn't really quite understand the nWo Black and White vs. nWo Wolfpack, but that is probably just because I didn't watch WCW all that often.   Noteables  Chris Jericho, The Undertaker, Triple H, and definately Steve Austin!  How is that Drew? Something about this last couple of years opted me to bump Triple H off of my list. I really think that if I took this last 8 months away he would be right up with HBK and the Rock. He was one of my favorite wrestlers...but now what can I say? He is getting a little selfing with the strap.I say you whip out your best Tag Teams of all time...   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This is actually Peter aka Pedro's blog, but I've totally hijacked it, not so much out of boredom, but for my love of wrestling.  Pedro needs to post in here, besides bitching about his lack of cable TV.  Keep in mind, dear reader, that when Pedro was born, I was his age.  Nonetheless, that's  no obstacle for two guys to talk about wrestling.  Right?  Right.  Anyway, this is where I list off my All-Time favorite wrestlers, and then encourage Peter to weigh in with his own takes.  (Come on WeeWee, I know you got it in you!)  So here's my All-Time Drewcifer Hall of Fame List:   #1--Randy "Macho Man" Savage  -- OoooH Yeah!!  I became his biggest fan in 1997 when he was in Wrestlemania III against Ricky Steamboat.  He went on to become a face after that match.  What really made me mark out for him was when was the following November when he was wrestling Honky Tonk Man for the I-C title on Saturday Night's Main Event.  The Hart Foundation interfered and Honky ended up bashing Macho up against the head with his gitaur.  Elizabeth (RIP) ran backstage and brought out the Hulkster.  Anyway, Savage and Hulk ended up forming an alliance, and come Wrestlemania IV, Savage won the WWF World Title.  Of course it led up to an eventual Hogan/Savage feud for Wrestlemania V.  No matter.  In 1989, I was lucky enough to see a Savage-Hogan match in Winston-Salem, NC.  There's only one wrestler who has made me mark out as hardcore as Randy Savage did..which brings me to #2...   #2--"Stone Cold" Steve Austin -- WHAT? I'm still doing that bit with people...Anyway..I stopped watching wrestling for a few years, pretty much because I was married with a child and all.  I kept up with all that was going on in wrestling through 3rd party sources.  I was told by a guy that I worked with back in '98 that Stone Cold Steve Austin was arrested for beating up Vince McMahon.  I had no clue that Vince was involving himself in storylines.  I decided to tune into RAW to see what was going on and what I had been missing for a couple of years.  At the top of the show, Stone Cold comes out, starts drinking beer. flips off his fans, and he gets to beat the hell out of his boss.  That's the ultimate American Dream, right there.     #3--"Mr. Perfect" Curt Hennig (RIP)   Not so much I can say about the guy.  He was the AWA Champ before dropping the belt to Jerry Lawler (Yes, the King).  When he came to the WWF, he had a series of vignettes where he nailed a three-pointer from the top of the key  (swish) , putted a 50 foot putt in the cup, hit a homer over the Green Monster, bowled a strike, won at chess, he was absolutely perfect in every way!  He had a couple reigns with the I-C title.  I loved his attitude going into the ring.  I still emulate it to this day.  When I walk into work, I don't swat my gum away, but I strut like he did, back in the day.   #4--Ric Flair -- I spent many a year hating Flair.  Back in the day, I used to go to the monthly NWA shows at the Greensboro Coliseum where you could get in for five bucks.  The main event was always Flair vs. Lex Luger, or Sting, or Terry Funk, or whoever.  Flair always managed to cheat to win.  I always walked awy from those matches at the Coliseum cursing Flair.  It didn't occur to me until recently that that was the way a heel champion was supposed to do things.  It's fitting that nowadays that he's more or less HHH's manger.  If you're going to have heel champion, then you have to have a guy that people love to hate.   #5--Hulk Hogan -- Anyone who was a wrestling fan in the '80's and claims they didn't mark out for the Hulkster is a liar.  Hulk Hogan made mainstream Pro-Wrestling (sports entertainment) what it is today.     #6--Barry Windham --Hard to believe that I would pick him, but he was the first wrestler I saw who could snap off any type of suplex in the books.  This guy could have wrestled  me  and pull off a good match.  His push with the Four Horsemen was abruptly derailed by Arn Anderson and Tully Blanchard jumping to the Fed in '89.  Windham soon followed suit and went to the Fed as the Widowmaker, but that gimmick fell flat.  I'll always remeber Windham as the heel who would come out to the ring with the big black cowboy hat, and the chaps.  He had that loner, Johnny Cash thing going on.  Nevermind what he looked like, Windham was like Kurt Angle in the ring.  He could have taken my cat and make it a great match.  Pedro?  Bring on your favorites!   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">Comment   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually, I picked most of the Unforgiven card.  With a couple glaring exceptions...  Lest's re-cap my picks...   Test vs. Scott Steiner: Yep..called that one.  Only Stacey accidently whacked Big Poppa Pump with a chair. Either way, the angle is set.  Look for them to be competeing with the Dudley's soon.   Lita & Trish vs Gail Kim & Molly:   Well, I was correct on which team would win.  Look for Lita to shake off her ring-rust and take the title by Survivor Series. The women's title is like an ex-girlfriend of mine...everyone gets a turn...   Spike, Devon, and Bubba vs. La Resistance and Rob Conway in a Tables Match :  Somehow, this ended up turning into a title match and the Dudley's ran away with the Belts.  Okay, so my pick came a day early.  What the hell.    J.R & King vs. Al Snow & Coach:  Man did I call that one wrong.  Not to worry though.  Give it a few weeks, and our regular announce team will be back.  The problem is, during this time, I will be looking forward to Smackdown! for Micheal Cole's insightful views on wrestling.  Scary, aint it?    Christian vs. RVD vs. Y2J for the I-C Title:  Called this one, didn't I.  Next Monday, RVD takes on Christian for the I-C title in a ladder match!  RVD may or may not win the Intercontinental Title next week.  What we can count on is a big time feud between the two going into Survivor Series.  Smarks underestimate Christian, but he's really done well as the I-C Champion.  Christian is no Macho Man or Mr. Perfect, but he's making the I-C title important again.  Time was, when I was young (forgive me for geezing out, here)  the Intercontinental title belonged to the second-best wrestler in the WWF.  When Ricky Steamboat won the belt at Wrestlemania III , that really elevated that title.  Christian and RVD have the potential to have a series of great matches, ala Savage and Steamboat.  Let's see what happens.   Kane vs. Shane-O-Mac (Last Man Standing Match) : I called it, but the next time Shane wrestles, can he top that?  Shane is no Mick Foley, but he pulls off the Mick Foley moves on a rare occasion.  Let Shane disappear far a while..and let Kane get a title shot against Golddust...I mean Goldberg.   Randy Orton vs. Shawn Micheals:  Everything I read has indicated that wasn't the match that it could have been.  Anyway, Orton won, just like I called.   Goldberg vs. HHH  When I made my picks, I forgot about the stipulation where if HHH got disqualified he'd still lose the title.  Not that it mattered.  I'm still stunned that Trips would job cleanly to Goldberg.    I still say that Kane gets a run with the belt before HHH comes back. Look for a short reign by Goldberg before he bolts to Japan.  This is just purely my opinion, and that's all.   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">If You got something to say, Give me a Hell Yeah!!     LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">If you got something to say, gimme a HellYaeh!  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, I'm going to skip buying this PPV.  A) I'm broke this month, and B) Very little about this card excites me.  There's two matches that I'd like to see, but the main event holds little interest for me, and I can keep up with the realtime results for free by reading  urlLink PWTorch .  Anyway, a lot of the card is pretty predictable, but just for shits and giggles, bear with me as I play Fantasy-Vince, and fantasy book this PPV:   Test vs. Scott Steiner:  The stipulations for this match are that if The Big Bad Booty Daddy wins, he gets Stacey Keibler's services back.  If Test wins, he gets to not only retain Stacey, but gets to make Big Poppa Pump his personal hookup.  Thus far, Steiner's run in the WWE has been a flop.  He could really benefit from having a heel run with Test.  I could see the pair having a pretty decent feud with the Dudleys in the near future.  Holla if ya hear me!   Prediction: Test wins with his arms on the ropes.    Lita & Trish vs. Molly & Gail Kim:  What really weakens the Women's division is the fact that every single one of them has at one point or another held the Women's strap.  It's time to bring Nidia or Dawn Marie over to Raw and inject  some fresh meat into the division.   I got your fresh meat to inject right here, baby!    Anyway, all horniness aside, Lita has been out of action for nearly a year and a half.  She's bound to be a tad rusty, and Gail Kim thus far is a horrible worker.  Therefore it's incumbent on Molly and Trish to carry this match, which I have no doubt they will.   Prediction: Lita wins with a Litacuranna on Gail.    Spike, Devon, and Bubba vs. La Resistance and Rob Conway in a Tables Match:  No way The Frenchies win this one.  This is going to be a pure crowd-pleasing match.  The second the bell rings, the crowd will be chanting, "WE WANT TABLES!"  I'm predicting a Dudley squash here.   Prediction:  Dudleys put all three opponents through tables and win the Tag Belts on RAW.      J.R & King vs. Al Snow & Coach:   First off, I would have never even booked this match, or the whole ridiculous angle to begin with.  This slot on the PPV could have been well served by a Hurricane/S.H.I.T vs. Mack/Henry.  Oh well...this is also a no-brainer.  My only question is, Who's going to call this match?  Stone Cold and Bischoff? (Hey, there's an idea...)  Prediction:  J.R. punks out Coach in a major way, and gets the win.    Christian vs. RVD vs. Y2J for the I-C Title:   This match is one of the one's that tempts me to buy Unforgiven at the last minute  (must...resist...urges...) .  This is also one of the most intriguing angles going in, and has the potential to carry on for a couple months into the Survivor Series, with many possibilities.  It's no secret that I'm an RVD mark.  RVD definitely deserves to look good after his long, drawn out feud with Kane.  Jericho needs to be competeing for the World Title.    I'm looking for him to be a non-factor in the finish.   Prediction:  Christian cheats to pin RVD, and they carry on a feud to Survivor Series.   Kane vs. Shane-O-Mac (Last Man Standing Match):  This is another match I'd almost pay to see.  Kane has been on a monster run as of late, but anyone who has watched WWE for the last four years knows what Shane is capable of in a match.  Look for Shane to pull off a move that makes the crowd chant "HOLY SHIT", only to see Kane "rise from the dead".  Kane has the most momentum on the RAW roster going into this match (except for maybe Jericho).  Look for Shane to vanish again.   Prediction:  Kane whips ass.    Randy Orton vs. Shawn Micheals:   I'd pay to see this one too.  ( I didn't say that!  Tell me I didn't just say that!  I am NOT BUYING THIS PPV!)   Orton has been playing up his "Legend Killer" gimmick very well, lately.  HBK has also said almost everything but "To be the MAN you gotta beat the MAN".  This has all the potential to be an awesome match.  Look for THE man (Flair) to be a factor in the outcome. Orton's performance in this match will make or break his WWE career.   Prediction:  Orton with the pin and goes onto bigger things.    Bill Goldberg vs. HHH for the Ten Pounds of Gold:   This match  should  be a no-brainer.  Trips is about to get married, and go on his honeymoon, plus he needs to rest his various injuries.  All indications are that he will drop the belt.  Stay with me here... Last Monday's RAW kept doing those "Believe the Hype" highlights on Golddust, err, Goldberg.  No question, Goldberg wins the belt, right?  Sorry, I have a different prediction.  (After all, I'm fantasy booking here, right?)  The stipulation is if Goldberg loses, he has to retire (or go to Japan).  I figure Goldberg will stick around for a few more months at least.  However, there are a couple factors to consider.  First off, WWE is not going to put the strap on a guy who refuses to work house shows.  Secondly, Trips won't job to just anyone, and in the WWE backstage hierarchy, Goldberg is just another anyone.  Still, HHH needs to drop the belt, however briefly...   Prediction:  HHH loses by DQ, therefore saving himself the title, and Goldberg gets to stick around .   I'm not done yet!  Based on my booking, tomorrow night's RAW is going to be a must see!  I peer into my crystal ball and see Stone Cold putting Trips into a title match with....KANE!!  Kane destroys the Champ (setting up an injury angle) wins the belt and gets to run with it for a couple months.  It'll be interesting to see how right or wrong I am.   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If you missed Smackdown! Tonight, you missed two five-star matches given away for free.    As I hunkered down for Hurricane Isabel to put some smackdown on me (I live in the DC area, and we've been warned all week long of the impending apocalypse that was Isabel...what a gyp!   Nothing happened here.  After I spent the afternoon digging trenches in my backyard so my basement wouldn't flood, taped up the windows, put batteries in my flashlight and radio, set up candles within arm reach, stocked up on beer and smokes...nothing!   Tropical Storm  Isabel is nothing but a cocktease!  But I digress...on to the show!)  The show started out with a ton of hype for the Iron Man Match between Champ Kurt Angle and Challenger Brock Lesnar.  In the history of the WWE/F, there have only been two other Iron Man matches, HHH vs. The Rock a couple years ago, and Bret Hart vs. Shawn Micheals in their classic Wrestlemania encounter some years ago.  The announcers were also hyping the fact that this was only the third 1 on 1 match between Brock and Kurt (the other two being WM XIX, and a month ago at SummerSlam).  But before the "Match to End All Matches", there was a tag-team encounter between the Champs, Shelton Benjamin & Charlie Haas vs. Los Guereros (Eddie & Chavo).  For rookies, the World's Greatest tag team have been wrestling like seasoned veterans for the short time they've been around.  Tonight was no exception.  The match lasted roughly 25 minutes with complete non-stop action.  Both teams threw their hearts and souls into the match.  The Guereros won the belts at the end, but after the match, both teams got a standing ovation from the live audience.      Eddie is now the US Champion, and one-half of the Tag Team Champs.  I'd love to see an angle where he decides that he looks so good in gold that he challenges for the WWE Championship.  Triple-Crown Champion?  I could see it.  Eddie is  that damn good!   Anyway, up next was the Iron Man Match.  For those of you who have never seen an Iron Man match, here's the rules in a nutshell:  The match goes for 60 minutes.  Whoever has the most falls (pins, submissions, DQ's, or countouts) at the end of 60 minutes wins the match.  Micheal "barely smarter than Coach" Cole was handed a memo in the middle of the match saying that should it be tied at the end of 60 minutes, UPN would allow them to go into overtime.    Anyway, to start out the match, Brock played the heel coward, by jumping out of the ring and threatening to get counted out.  (This reminded me of Ric Flair's heyday as NWA Champ, pulling similar stuff.)  Angle won the first fall by DQ when Lesnar clocked him over the head with a chair in the middle of the ring.  Lesnar apparently knew what he was doing, because seconds later, he F-5'ed Kurt and got a fall.  Two minutes later, Lesnar went up 2-1 over Angle by using Kurt's own Ankle lock.    Next thing you know, the two are on the outside of the ring and Lesnar F-5's Angle on the steel ramp (HOLY SHIT!!  HOLY SHIT!!).  Lesnar rolled into the ring ahead of the ten count and went up 3-1 over the Champ.    After the commercial, there was some back and forth action, then Angle came out of nowhere to hit an Angle Slam and score a pin.  3-2 Lesnar.  Then comes a lot of reversals.  Angle goes for a German Suplex which gets countered into a possible F-5 which gets countered into a possible Angle-Slam which gets countered into a possible...you get the point...anyway, Angle manages to put on the Ankle-Lock, but Lesnar doesn't tap out.  After Brock gets up, he goes for the clothesline, but hits the ref.  Nothing like a ref bump at this point, especially when both are getting falls on eachother.  With the ref down, Brock nails Angle in the head with the belt, revives the ref, and gets the three count.  4-2 Brock.  The next Holy Shit moment came when Lesnar was outside the ring threatening to toss the stairs in when Angle does a baseball slide into them and bonks Brock in the face and he rolls in two successive back somersaults on the steel ramp (you had to see it, trust me...).  Then there's a commercial break, and when we come back, we are informed that Lesnar scored another pinfall on Angle from a superplex.  (Why in the Blue Hell on a  TAPED  show did they have to have a fall during a commercial?   anyway, Lesnar is up 5-2 on the Champ.  Would Kurt Angle be able to battle back?  After more awesome counter-wrestling on the outside of the ring and then inside, Lesnar counters an Angle-Slam attempt into a DDT, but Angle kicks out. Lesnar hits three release German Suplexes.  Angle got hold of Brock with a belly-to-belly and narrowed it to 5-3, Brock with less than 20 minutes to go.  After some more great counter-wrestling, Kurt managed to wrap on an Ankle lock and get Brock to tap once again.  5-4, just a couple minutes to go!  With just 20 seconds left, and Angle losing 5-4 with the promise of an overtime, he applies a hardcore Anklelock on Brock.  As the clock ticks down to it's final seconds...  Brock doesn't tap out.  It's over and Brock Lesnar is once again WWE Champion.  What a night!  And for free!  I've been a wrestling fan for 20 years, give or take, and I have never seen matches like this given away for free on TV like tonight.  This year alone, I estimate that I have spent roughly 250 bucks on PPV's and haven't gotten this quality of wrestling.    After tonight, I highly doubt I'll be getting Unforgiven this Sunday.  I may wait until the next Smackdown! PPV, or even wait for Survivor Series in November.   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have not watched Raw and/or Smackdown! in quite some time. Over a month maybe. I have not even the slightest clue what the frick is going on. The only way that I keep somewhat in touch with it is by way of  urlLink WWE.com . I hope that I can at least get a copy of the PPV's or something. I am going bonkers without my wresting fix!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Nice Post Drewcifer   Yeah. Those moments were all pretty stupid. I want to touch up on one of those moments that could have possibly been a classic and produced an awesome new match for the "fed". Remember when Al Snow and Big Boss Man were feuding and after pepper (Snow's dog) died? (he was actually kidnapped in Ames Iowa (about 100 miles from here)) Well then they decided to have a match called the "Kennel from Hell". I personally thought that this match was going to be awesome!   Why is that Peter?   Well now. The match was going to be the original Cage surrounding the ring. With the Hell in a Cell cage around/over top of that. Then in between those two cages there were going to be 2 or 3 rottweilers. You had to escape the first cage and then proceed into the empty space between the cell and the cage, fend off the rottweilers, and escape the cell. Sounds pretty sweet huh?   HELL YEAH!   WRONG! The dogs, who hadn't been exposed to so many people, spent most of the match just pooping and peeing all over ringside. And when the match finally ended nothing happened. The dogs didn't go after anyone between the cages. They just ran around and barked and released their bodily fluids all over. THAT WAS STUPID!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The Dumbest things I've seen as a professional wrestling fan   This last Monday's RAW Episode featured Kane having Shane-O-Mac shackled to a ringpost.  Kane then pulled out a pair of jumper cables and a car battery.  Kane attached the jumper cables to the Shane-O-Nuts, and zapped him off of the battery.   My first thought was,  "How shocking!"   Then I realized my brain was punning me....  The segment was saved by RVD running in to make the save and beating the crap out of Kane.  Thank gawd.  It was almost about to become one of the dumbest things I have ever witnessed as a pro wrestling fan.   What are some of the dumbest moments you've ever witnessed as a pro wrestling fan, Drewcifer?   Why thanks for asking!  There was, of couse, David Arqutte's run as WCW World Champion (which was the final nail in WCW's coffin, ask anyone), but WCW doesn't count here.  I remember a few years back when the Hardcore Title, and hardcore wrestling was a big deal in the Fed (whenever I refer to "the Fed", I mean pre-lawsuit-change-WWF-to-WWE days).  Anyway, Al Snow was the Hardcore Champ, and was feuding with The Big Bossman.  At the time, Snow had lost his "Head", so instead he was coming to the ring with his chiahuahua.  Then the doggie vanished.  So Bossman takes Snow out on a quest to find his dog.   Over the course of a couple weeks, Bossman decides to serve Al some homecooked beef stew.  As Al was chowing down on a dish that he was selling as MY-T-TASTY, Bossman reveals that Snow was eating his own doggie.  DUMB!  Speaking of Bossman...somewhere after that, he was feuding with The Big Show.  Show's storyline was, at the time, his father was dying.  And howww courageous Show was, for continuing to wrestle in the name of his dying father.   Except Bossman was interupting Show's matches via the TitanTron, taunting him with vignettes about how he was stalking his dying dad.  At last, as RAW came on the air, Jim Ross announced that Big Show would not be appearing because his father had died the night before.  The next Thursday on Smackdown!, they were going to air scenes from Papa Show's funeral.  Sure enough, during the burial, Bossman showed up with a tractor and hauled the casket off.   DUMB!!!   What else was dumb, Drew?   What, you want more?  Okay...Doink the Clown, The Ding-Dongs, Edge & Christian wrestling as Los Conquistadores (to their credit, they did beat the Hardy's for the tag belts in that match). the current Super Hero In Training (S.H.I.T) Rosey...  Remember the angle with Mark "Sexual Chocolate" Henry and Mae Young?  Mark was addicted to sex (who isn't?), but when he hooked up with 80-year old Mae Young, he was...ummm...hooked.  Anyway, over the course of time, Mae announced she was pregnant.  Here's the deal:  I like to suspend disbelief while I'm watching wrestling, always.  Make no bones about it.  But when they decided to make Mae young pregnat? At 80?  It wasn't even one of those things where I could say to myself, "how are they going to play this off?".  No, it was more of "please end this crap".  And after a few weeks, they finally did.  The Dudleys put Mae through a table...EMS came out and wheeled her into the back, whereupon she proceeded to "give birth" to a mannequin hand!  DUMB!!!!    I was going to mention HHH bonking a mannequin corpse as well, but I think you, dear reader have heard enough for one day.   Actually...no Drew, I haven't....   What?  Okay fine.  Wasn't even over a year ago when Kane was feuding with HHH.  Trips claimed he had some damning evidence of Kane committing murder on a gal named Katie Vick.  Kane claimed it was a car accident.   Then HHH pulls out his video coverage of Kane at the funeral home.  To every viewer, it was blatantly obvious that is was HHH in a Kane mask, that proceeded to crawl into the casket and make sweet sweet love to the corpse.  DUMB!!!  Actually, now that I think of it...Kane's electrocuting Shane-O's grapefruits doesn't seem to rank as high on the Dumb-O-Meter after all....  Close though.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      By now, everyone knows about the death of Hawk.  He died in his sleep on Sunday, October 19th.  Word is, he had been having heart problems for over ten years, some would speculate having been caused by years of steroid abuse.    Joe Laurenitis, AKA Animal, Hawk's longtime tag-team partner said that neither he nor Hawk had done steroids for over ten years.  Animal says that Vince McMahon beginning to test for steroids was one of the best things to happen to them.   Animal swears that steroids had nothing to do Micheal's death.    Regardless, the wrestling world has once again lost one of it's legends.  I remember seeing the Road Warriors on TV for the first time years ago.  They would come to the ring in their face paint, huge spikes on their shoulders, with "I am an Ironman" by Sabbath playing.  This was in the era before gimmicks truly caught on, and these guys were certainly unique.  The first time I saw them in person was in 1988 at the very first Clash of the Champions in Greensboro NC.  They were in a barb wire match with Dusty Rhodes against the Powers of Pain and Paul Jones.  I think that was my very first brush with "hardcore" wrestling.  Hawk and Animal showed up on RAW earlier this year in a one-shot deal, wrestling Kane and RVD.  When they came to the ring, I have to admit, I marked out huge.  Sadly, after the match was about three minutes old, it was obvious that the LOD were mere shadows of their former selves.  RVD and Kane managed to carry the match and make it look decent enough though.  All in all, it was great seeing the two together again.    I read that recently Hawk and Animal did an indie show in Chicago to commerate 20 years of tag team dominance.     urlLink ProWrestlingTorch.com  reports that there will be a tribute show on Nov. 1st at Birch Run Michigan, followed the next day by a fund raising breakfast on the 2nd, with proceeds going to the family of Hegstrand.  Laurenitis plans to be at both events.  Thanks for the memories, Hawk.  The Great Wrestling Ring in the Sky just got a whole lot more hellacious.  LinktoComments('MANUAL')    urlLink Comment     
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont quite know the whole story but Drewcifer is absent from the face of the earth it seems. Not on IM, IRC or even posting. Its quite sad. I miss his huge rants on pro wrestling.  Onto more important matters.  The latest PPV. I hear it was quite a smash! Maybe its just me but I think that Smackdown has not only better story lines (well...they are more practicle at times) but they also have better wrestlers by far. No doubt. Absolutely...you have Angle, Lesnar, Big Slow, Haas and Benjamin, Cena, Hardy, Los Guerreros, Taker, Edge (although he is nursing a neck injury), Ultimo Dragon (where is he by the way...). Need I rant on more?  Smackdown far superior in the talent department!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Man...as if being away from pro wrestling isn't bad enough, Stu Hart just died. From what I understand he was 88 and had an elbow infection of some sort. Then that hospitalized him and turned into pneumonia, and the rest is just history. I am really sad for what has happened and I hope that Bret isn't taking the news too hard.  My thoughts and prayers are with the Hart family. Bret especially.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hell in a Cell was and is a great concept.  Whoever came up with the idea was a genius (that's my way of calling Vince McMahon a genius without naming him directly). I enjoy a good Hell in a Cell match, but I don't want to see the concept overused.  And despite what you say, Pedro, I happen to like the Chamber of Elimination.  That's another concept I'd like to see done on a rare basis.  So anyway, here's my favorite Cell matches (I'm old and senile, so forgive me for not having the dates or PPV's):   Mankind vs The Undertaker:  C'mon...I think this is everyone's favorite Cell match.  Foley risked his freaking life in that match.  Jim Ross' commentary still rings in my head (along with several other voices, but we won't go there...).  Not only did Foley go off the top of the cell into the announce table, but he managed to battle back and climb the cage again only to get thrown though the top onto the mat.  I remember as soon as he hit the mat, a bunch of officials and EMT's hit the ring thinking he was dead (or something).  That wasn't scripted, it was pure shoot.  Foley was fine though and finished the match.  Pure classic.   Cactus Jack vs HHH :  This was Foley's retirement match, and boy did he go out in style!  Being thrown on a pile of thumbtacks, getting whacked with chairs, etc.  I hope when I retire from whatever I do, I can go out with that kind of bang!   Undertaker vs Brock Lesnar:  The reason I mention this match is not so much that it was a special match, but that it truly signalled the fact that Brock Lesnar is the real deal.  He had won the belt from The Rock a few months before, but I still wasn't sure about him.  In this match, he took everything Taker threw at him, got bloodied, battered, and abused, then showed up for work the next day.  That's when I knew Brock was here to say, and was truly a special wrestler.  (Was that a run-on sentence?)  All this Hell in a Cell talk reminds me of the NWA's War Games matches from back in the day.  Maybe I'll write about some of those someday.   LinktoComments(' ')    urlLink  ">Comment    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HELL NO! They aren't a myth. As a matter of fact, I have seen just about every cell match, and they are pretty dang  good...every one of them. But some were pretty bad.  I guess what I am trying to say here is that some cell matches were quite a bit better than others. Before I go into this too much I would like to ask Drew to name his top 3 or 4 cell matches. This does not include the crappiest match ever (elimination chamber...because cell matches are cool...and chamber matches...well..they just suck!).  So Drew? Step up? What are your favorite Cell matches of all time??? Are we due for another? If so who should be in it and why?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, looks like I picked half the card.  I certainly have done better in the past.  Oh well...  After seeing (most) of tonight's RAW, I can see a few things down the road...  Stone Cold's team lost, meaning Austin was fired from his job, leaving Bischoff to run rampant all over RAW, right?  This afternoon, I was thinking that after The Rattlesnake was done with his book tour (and c'mon, that's really what this whole thing's about, right?) he'd show up on SmackDown! to be a foil for Paul Heyman.   Then, after watching RAW something else dawned on me...  First, Bischoff fires HBK.  Then he fires Lita.  (And what a great angle that was, by bringing Matt Hardy v1.0 back into the fold...poor Shannon Moore.  Now he has nowhere to go but OVW.)  I'm seeing a scenario where over the next few weeks, Bischoff either firing folks, or forcing others to quit (RVD comes to mind...you know Orton is going to get the I-C strap soon.).  Then, creepy things start happening.  I dunno...masked wrestlers jumping the heels in the ring, unknown assailants trying to run over or "cause accidents" in the back.  Stuff like that.  As it progresses week by week, we find it's Austin and his fellow fired folk trying to take over.  I think that'd be a great angle, don't you?  OOOH! OOH!  I KNOW!!   The group could be called "REVolution"!  (I just thought of that...)  Also, I'm shocked, SHOCKED that HHH would job to Gill..., um, Goldberg on two straight PPV's.  Aint that some shit!  Actually, I see some good coming out of this.  Seeing as how Trips has mowed down and buried everyone on the RAW roster, letting Goldberg run with the ball may not be such a bad idea after all.  Already, we're seeing the start of a Kane-Goldberg feud, which is overdue if you ask me.  I say, let Goldberg bury some talent for a little while Paul Levesque-McMahon plays backstage politics.  This may be an oppurtunity for some fresh storylines, something which RAW has seriously been lacking.    Also, I shoulda known that Kane would have something to do with Undertaker's dirt-nap.  There's your Wrestlemania XX Hell in a Cell match right there.    On Thursday, I'll post some SmackDown! post Survivor Series ruminations.       
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets total it up here shall we???   HHH vs. Goldberg  Drew said: HHH win Peter said: HHH win  Outcome: BOTH WRONG!   Vince vs. Taker (buried alive match)  Drew said: Vince win Peter said: Vince win  Outcome: Both Right!   Team Lesnar vs. Team Angle  Drew said: Team Lesnar win Peter said: Team Lesnar win  Outcome: BOTH WRONG!   Team Austin vs. Team Bischoff  Drew said: Team Austin win Peter said: Team Austin win  Outcome: BOTH WRONG!   Molly vs. Lita  Drew said: Molly win Peter said: Molly win  Outcome: Both Right!   Kane vs. Shane (ambulance match)  Drew said: Kane win Peter said: Kane win  Outcome: Both Right!   Bashams vs. Los Guerreros  Drew said:  nothing  Peter said:  nothing   Outcome:  None    FINAL SCORE!!!!   Drewcifer:  3 of 6  Peter:  3 of 6  Oddly enought I thought that I had picked Team Angle over Team Lesnar....but I guess i didn't....a tie isn't that bad....but 3 of 6 is....and i thot there was supposed to be a cruiserweight match....but  urlLink wwe.com  didnt have any info on it.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      >  GOLDBERG RETAINS, AUSTIN GONE, TAKER BURIED  - With all four members of Evolution down, the World Heavyweight champion Bill Goldberg managed to survive the Survivor Series by defeating Triple H clean. Orton, Batista and Flair - and even the sledgehammer - tried to interfere but Goldberg turned the tables and beat them down with the sledgehammer until he decided he doesn't need it to eliminate Triple H. A spear and a jackhammer later, Goldberg was declared the winner, retaining his title.  In other matches, the show opened with Team Lesnar vs Team Angle. Within a few minutes three members were eliminated. Cena and Benoit ended up the survivors after Cena FU'ed the Big Show. Yes, that's right, Cena got Show in a fireman's carry and turned him over; Molly Holly kept her women's title by defeating Lita. Not a bad match, but usually the women perform better; The ambulance match was next with little wrestling and a lot of hard stuff. Shane hit his usual high spots, including a coast-to-coast off the top of the ambulance. Kane was on the receiving end of a sick shot to the head from the ambulance door with no protection. Kane tombstoned Shane on the concrete to finish him off; The Basham Brothers managed to keep their titles as well after Chavo hit his uncle with a shot to the head while doing a spinning DDT. Shaniqua received a frog splash form Eddie and some spanking from Chavito during the match; Team Austin vs Team Bischoff followed with HBK stealing the show sporting a crimson mask while doing his thing. HBK had the match won after Austin stunnered Orton but Batista interfered, did a tiger bomb on the former champ and Orton covered as the unconscious referee came to his senses. After the match Austin said goodbye in a cool TV moment. Oh yeah, he also beat down Coach's @ss; The final match before the main event saw Undertaker losing the Buried Alive match vs Vince McMahon. McMahon bled from the first 5 seconds of the match and lost tons of blood. Just sick sick sick. McMahon got pounded during the match until it was time to get buried, when Kane came out from the truck after an explosion. Kane then beat on 'Taker and McMahon dumped the dirt in the grave site to get the win.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      >  TICKETS STILL REMAIN FOR SURVIVOR SERIES  - The American Airlines Center will not be sold out tonight unless tickets get snatched at the box office prior to the event. As of this writing, $300 seats that come with the commemorative chair in the first five rows are still available for purchase. Not good news for what usually is a hot crowd in Texas.  Drew check it out!!!! there are still seats available!! isnt this awesome! .....  ...... wait.... why is this awesome?  Hmmm I dont know, but if I had any chance what-so-ever to go to a WWE event I would because the atmosphere is awesome. Jeez, and I thought that Survivor Series was a big event!  (info courtesy of  urlLink www.wrestling-online.com )
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      >  SURVIVOR SERIES TONIGHT  - Live from the American Airlines Center in Dallas, TX., RAW and Smackdown! present WWE Survivor Series on pay-per-view. The card is as follows: Booker T, Rob Van Dam, Dudley Boyz & Shawn Michaels vs Chris Jericho, Christian, Scott Steiner, Randy Orton & Mark Henry; Kurt Angle, Chris Benoit, John Cena, Hardcore Holly & Bradshaw vs Brock Lesnar, Nathan Jones, Matt Morgan, A-Train & Big Show; Goldberg defends his World title against Triple H; Lita goes for the Women's gold against champion Molly Holly; Undertaker and Vince McMahon battle in a Buried Alive match; Tajiri vs Jamie Noble for the Cruiserweight title; Shane McMahon goes one on one against Kane in an Ambulance match.   My Picks???  Team Austin wins Team Lesnar wins Trips wins again (whoopty doo) Molly wins McMahon buries Taker alive Jamie Noble wins Kane klobbers Shane-O-Mac and wins it easy  (info courtesy of  urlLink www.wrestling-online.com )
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       (I was 3/4 of the way done writing this column when some error occurred with Blogger.com and erased everything!  Now I have to write this all over again...dammit!  I have really bad carpal tunnel, for fricks sake.)    ONCE AGAIN , it's Thanksgiving time, and Mr. Turkey said, how very careful I must be or HHH will make me lose my match...or something like that... Anyway, since I have to work late this Sunday, I'll be missing our beloved annual November event.  Therefore, I'll just book the thing myself.  Why not, right?  We WWE viewers are a lot smarter than the writers, or so we'd like to believe.  Whatever the case may be, I'm going to play Drew McMahon (or Vince McDrewcifer, take your pick...)  On with the show:   Jamie Noble vs Tajiri (Cruiserweight Championship)  -- I hear that Jamie Noble is an above average wrestler.  You'd never know it though.  Since he first came in along with his "longtime girlfriend" Nidia (boy, they never mentioned that on Tough Enough), he started out feuding with The Hurricane, then before that angle ever achieved fruition, Hurricane jumped to RAW.  Noble got to run with the Cruiserweight title for a bit, then he went on a long losing streak.  He then swore he was going to bring in "Cousin" Nunzio to help him out.  The Nunzio/Noble angle went...well, nowhere.  (How in the  BLUE HELL were we supposed to buy the whole cousin angle with the Italian New Yorker and the West Virginia redneck anyway?)  Noble floundered around on Velocity for a bit until he discovered that he inherited 64,000 bucks from his dead aunt.  He bought Nidia a fur coat, then we heard what from that angle?  Then he got into this whole group sex thing with Nidia, Torrie, and Chuck Palumbo's former boy-toy, Billy Gunn.  That storyline had a great potential until Mr. Ass did what he does best, and that being laid out with an injury.  (Why the WWE doesn't release their second most oft-injured wrestler is beyond me...and yes, I did say "second most"...more on that later.)   So now Jamie Noble is getting another push, this time in a Championship match on one of the most prestigious PPV's.  So the outcome?  You guessed it:   Tajiri wins via pinfall.    Lita vs. Molly Holly (Women's Title)  -- FINALLLY...LITA HAS COME BACK...with a bit of ring rust.  Trust me, I'm a total mark for Lita and no chance in hell I would kick her out of my bed for eating crackers (let alone  this  cracker).  Lita had been on the shelf for well over a year with an injury she sustained while filming an episode of Dark Angel.  Anyone ever notice that the episode she appeared in was the final episode aired before the show got cancelled?  What?  You never watched the show?  That's right...neither did most of America.  The good news is Lita's back and RAW is a happier place with her.  Let's not discount the fact that Molly Holly has quietly been doing a great job as the Women's Champ.  She went from being a down home southern gal to Hurricane's sidekick (smells like S.H.I.T. to me) to the gal she is today.  Last time I fantasy booked a PPV, I mentioned how the Women's Title gets passed around like a $2 whore...since I'm fantasy booking here, I say Lita gets screwed out of a sure victory, and somehow ends up in a feud with Trish Stratus come WrestleMania time.   Molly wins with the help of Gail Kim.     Kane vs Shane McMahon in an Ambulance Match  -- What is up with the McMahon family anyway?  Last month, we had a PPV match with Vince vs. Stephanie, now we get to see a PPV with not only Shane wrestling Kane in an "Ambulance Match", but Big Poppa Mac  in a "Buried Alive" match with the other Bother of Destruction.  In any case, let's hope the Shane-O-Kane feud ends here.  In my fantasy wrestling FEDERATION, Kane would be the monster heel going for the title against Goldust--I mean Goldberg.  Look for a lot of no-selling by Kane, followed by a huge bump-gone-wrong by Shane, and a  Kane victory.    Undertaker vs. Vince McMahon (Buried Alive Match)  -- I've already ranted enough on the McMahon Family hogging the spotlight, but I will say this:  Ever since the Austin-Vince feud, it seems that any wrestler who has been around for the long haul has to at some point have a big money match with Vince.   Wassupwitdat?  Think about it.  Ric Flair, Hogan, and now Undertaker.  This match is so easy to book, I'm going to bet a month's salary with Pedro on it.  For the last 3 years, Undertaker has dropped his Deadman gimmick in exchange for the biker/husband/American Badass/big-dog-in-the-yard persona.  Taker is also  reaching the twilight of his full-time career.  No question what happens here.  I may be wrong about everything else I'm writing here, but  Vince buries Undertaker alive .  You don't see or hear from the Undertaker for months until possibly No Way Out, or around then, when The DeadMan retuns.   Team Lesnar vs. Team Angle (5-on-5 Elimination Match)  --  I love the idea that WWE is bringing back the old school Survivor Series match.  for you young folks, it works like this: Everytime a person gets pinned, they're elininated from the match.  The battle goes on and on until one team gets totally eliminated.  Lucky for us, there's going to be another Survivor match, 'cuz this one is going to be a stinker!  On one sidewe have the Champ, Brock Lesnar, The Big Slow, a mystery partner,  Matt Morgan (?), and Nathan Jones(?).  The other team consists of Kurt Angle, Chris Benoit, Farooq, Bradshaw, and Hrdcore Holly.  Before I make my prediction, I have to ask this:  Why are Holly, Nathan Jones,and Matt Morgan (whom I've never even heard of until a week ago) in a big time PPV event, yet there's no Rey Mysterio, Benjamin& Haas, Eddie Guerero..etc.  Somthing is stinkin' in the state of Connecticut.  I don't even have a prediction for this match...lets just say for fun that  Team Lesnar wins when Brock is the sole survivor after a tainted victory over Angle.    Team Austin vs. Team Bischoff (5-on-5 Elimination Match)  -- Now this is a match!  This has been built up well over the last month.  If Austin's team loses, then Stone Cold has to quit as Co-General manager.  If his team wins, then his "No physicality unless otherwise provoked" clause is out the door.  Tell me again what Bischoff has to lose here?  Oh, that's right.  The writers didn't bother coming up with anything more intrigueing than that.  Not to worry though...this is going to be the showstoppa match of the night.Team Bishoff boasts Y2J, Christian, Big Poppa Pump (your hookup), Sexual Chocolate Mark Henry, and Rndy "Legend Killer" Orton.   I need a nickname like that, but I don't think the ladies would swoon over "Sexual Vanilla".  Team Austin has my main man, if you can dig it, Booker T, RVD, The Dudleys, and HBK (you screwed Bret) Shawn Micheals.  Aside from Mark henry, all of the participants involved are true main event caliber wrestlers.  I would actually pay for an entire PPV just for this match and watch it go on for two and a half hours.  The cream of the crop is in this match.  And since Bischoff has nothing to lose, watch his team lose.  My guess sorta goes like this:  HBK pins Mark Henry with the sweet chin music, Steiner beats Devon, then beats Bubba, Booker T pins Steiner after the Dudleys send him through a table, Orton beats Booker T, RVD puts Christian away, Jericho beats Micheals, and  RVD is the sole Survivor after beating Jericho .  That, by the way, is pure fantasy booking...no way it's going to finish like that...   I'm done right?   There's one more match, Drew.   WHAT?   Oh yeah...that thing...I did say somthing about the most oft injured wrestler in the WWE, didn't I?     Before I jump into the next, and hopefully final paragraph, allow me to wish Paul Levesque and Stephanie Levesque, nee McMahon on their nuptiuals last week.  And to celebrate his newfound life as an official McMahon, what do you think Paul Levesque, aka, Hunter Hearst Helmsley is going to do?  Go to Disneyland?  Stay in a Holiday Inn Express?  Save a ton of money by switching to Geico?  Get swarmed by some bees whilst drinking a Stacker2 Y2Stinger?  Hell no...   HHH vs Bill Goldberg (World Heavyweight Title)  --  C'mon...did you really think Goldberg was going to hang around that long?  There's a chance that he may stick around long enough to do a match with Stone Cold at WrestleMania XX, but who knows...if I'm wrong about the outcome of this natch, then Pedro can choose whatever punishment he wants on me!    HHH takes the 10lbs of Gold back.Goldberg vanishes.   There you have it.  Tune in next week too see how right or wrong I was...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      zz
     
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I go into yet another long-awaited column that all of my loyal readers demand, I gotta give a shout out to my boy Pedro, aka Peter "The dry-wall eater" Stockdale, aka Weewee...  My computer has been virused all to hell.  Therefore, until I get this shit fixed, IRC and all of my IM's have been uninstalled untill I can cough up some dough to have a professional grade firewall coming into the house.    Anyway, to my main man Pete "The Sneaky Cheat", I want to say "Thank You" for giving me the oppurtunity to distribute my wrestling drivel around the world, via this blog.     Now shut up and read on, you sick freak...   In 2004, I want to see:   Shawn Micheals get a lengthy run with the World Title : Man, that last RAW show of 2003 gave us an awesome Main Event between HBK and HHH.  The ending may have been a bit controversial, but it truly elevated Shawn as the #1 babyface on the RAW roster.  Talk about your comebacks.  He was supposedly done after his back surgery in '97.  When he came back part-time last year none of us expected him to be anything more than a p/t player.  Not only did he get a brief run with the belt at the end of last year, he's managed to pull off incredible matches with nearly every heel on the RAW roster in '03.  His match with Chris Jericho at WrestleMania XIX was so good that my good friend Xine, who was at my place that night even got off the computer long enough to watch it.  Micheals is back and let him have the ball while HHH is filming Blade III.   More attention given to the US and Intercontinental Titles:    Back in the day, the secondary titles were nearly as big a deal as the World titles in their promotions.  Now that WWE has both titles in two brands, let's make it a real competition for those straps.  Instead of passing around the belts like a drunk girl at a frat party, let's make it a big deal to win that title.  On RAW, they're starting to turn the corner by making Randy Orton's IC win a big deal.  SmackDown! could really benefit by having Chris Benoit and John Cena feud over the US title as well.     Less McMahons:  'Nuff said.  It just occurred to me that the New Year was rung in a few minutes ago.  Isn't that something?  I spent my final minutes of 2003 and my first few minutes of 2004 writing a wrestling column.   Obviously, 2003 was a rough year for yours truly, so send some good karma my way for 2004.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Rookie of the Year:   Quite a few guys and a gal came up this year from the minor leagues.  We saw Zach Gowen, Gail Kim, Spanky, Orlando Jones, and others come up.  Im going to reserve Matt Morgan for next years consideration.  Im going to award the Kurt Angle Rookie of the Year Trophy to two men:  Shelton Benjamin and Charlie Haas .  These two guys have a legitimate background in amateur wrestling.  Shelton was Brock Lesnars college roommate, and Charlie Haas was the runner up for the NCAA championship the year Lesnar won the National Championship.  Kurt Angle proved right off that a sucessful amateur wrestler can pull it off in the WWE.  He paved the road for Brock Lesnar.  Now we have two more guys with successful backgrounds in amateur wrestling.  These two gentlemen have put on awesome matches with a number of tag-teams, including two MOTY candidates versus Los Guerroes.  Both of them have the potential to break out on their own, given a proper gimmick.  I can see them main eventing against eachother  at WrestleMania XXV.   Tag-Team of the Year:   It pains me to see tag-team wrestling be a mere shadow that it once was.  There have been a few bright spots this year, though.  The Dudley Boys had a great run after reuniting, and Im guessing theyre not done yet.  The Bashams showed up on the scene, and theyre looking to be a force to be reckoned with.  The Worlds Greatest Tag Team has been wowing me with their abilities as well.  The rest of the year has seen cookie cutter teams like RVD & Kane, and GoldDust  & (my main man) Booker T.  However, the winner of the Strike Force Tag Team of the Year Trophy goes to  Los Guerroes,  Eddie and Chavo.  Theyre teasing a break-up and a possible WrestleMania XX match, but theyre exploits in 2003 were worth watching.  Not only the lie, cheat & steal gimmick, but their abilities in the ring.  They put on not one, but two matches that were candidates for MOTY vs. Benjamin and Haas.  I hope their matches against eachother are as awesome as their matches with eachother.   Breakout Star of the Year:  Word Life!  I wasnt writing for a wrestling blog last year.  But if I had, I would have handed this award to Rob Van Dam.  Therefore, after the way RVD has been treated by the WWE, Im afraid to hand this award out to the guy I think who burst from out of nowhere to capture the wrestling fans attention:  John Cena.       Angle of the Year:  So many good angles saw fruition, while others died an immature death  Kane vs. Shane McMahon was a good one.  So was the rise and fall of Chris Benoit.  Not to mention the evolution of Evolution.  That angle, if booked correctly, will carry into 2004 as one of the best angles since the days of the Four Horsemen.  But the Angle of the Year for 2003 was easily between two non-wrestlers.  It was the fight for control of RAW.  The N w O angle of the year award goes to Stone Cold  Steve Austin vs. Eric Bischoff.    Those two fought each other verbally and physically for most of the year.  Hell, when RAW was at its weakest, storyline-wise, Austin engaged Bischoff in a Pie-Eatin contest, featuring Mae Young! (Those aint puppiesthose are bassett hounds).  Biscoff got the best of Austin at survivor Series, but we all know that Stone Cold 3:16 will be back soon.    Match of the Year:  I saw some awesome matches this year.  (Oddly, none of them involved HHH. ) There was a ladder match on Raw between RVD and Christian which I consider a second runner-up.  The first runner-up would be the match between Chris Jericho and Shawn Micheals  at WM XIX.  The hands down winner of the Ricky Steamboat/Randy Savage Match of the Year Trophy goes to  Brock Lesnar & Kurt Angles IronMan Match.    Read back a few pages in this blog and youll see my commentary on that match.  The best part about that match was that it was on free TV.  Now that RAW and SmackDown! Are alternating their PPVs, one brand has to put a better-than-great match on TV every other month.  And finally we get to the top trophy, the Bruno Sammartino Plaque for Wrestler of the Year:  And the runners-up are, Hunter Hearst Helmsley, Whiskerbiscuit Bill Goldberg, Kurt Angle, Rob Van Dam, Kane, the Undertaker  And the winner is   Brock Lesnar.   Brock managed to carry on his monster gimmick, but also prove that he wasnt just dumb muscle.  He showed us that he could wrestle a match with the Big Show, and still pull off a pure science match with Kurt Angle.  At WrestleMania XIX, he botched his shooting star press, landed on his head and gave himself a nasty concussion, but still managed to pull off the finish as planned.  I dont know if Brock can be a breakout star like Stone Cold Steve Austin or Hulk Hogan were in the mainstream.  But for my money, Brock Lesnar is the best thing going in Professional Wrestling today.       
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my good lord! I clicked the link that drew posted and listened to this Piece of crap. This is pretty pathetic and stupid! Randy Savage should just go smoke some weed and take some more roids.....and maybe get his vocal chords checked out....did he have a TERRIBLE case of bronchitis when he was young? He has one heck of an odd voice...  Good lord Macho Man. You are almost as pathetic as....ya konw what....i cant think of a good enough insult....ill let drew do the macho man bashing!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Booker T. vs. Mark Henry  --  Mark Henry getting a push? This is bogus. Why does Henry deserve his fat ass to get a push? Honestly, the last time he has gotten this good of a push was maybe when he and D-Lo were beating up the rock a few weeks before the PPV Rock Bottom in 1999. But never-the-less.  Look for Mark Henry to pull away with a sneaky victory.    Trish Stratus & Lita vs. Chris Jericho & Christian  --  Do you really think the alpha-male canadians can lose this match? YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT!!!!  Stratus and Lita win either by DQ or outside interference    Randy Orton vs. RVD (IC Title)  --  Orton has gotten a huge push by WWE and rightfully so. He, one day, will probably be the next HHH....ok maybe not. But he is very good in this story line. Look for  Randy Orton to take out RVD    Batista vs. HBK  --   Uhh...isn't HBK a jobber now?  Oh! no he just doesn't win on PPV anymore....thats it. Since his 34th comback about a year-and-a-half ago, how many PPV's has he won...maybe 4ish...at most? Besides Batista is a monster. Look for  Batista to dominate    Tag Team Turmoil  --  I have not seen enough to get a good estimate of who would win this match. But just for the sake of saying so....just for fun.... look for  Mark Jindrak & Garrison Cade to come away with a surprise victory!    Goldberg vs. Kane vs. Trips (World Title)  --  Why oh why has this belt become a joke??? WHY!!!!!! Who cares. Just because I dont care and I want to finish this blog entry.... Goldberg retains just to lose to Kane the next night.   This PPV will have its ups and downs....ending with a HUGE DOWNER! ...... uh...  thats all i guess...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I start my tirade, as it were, I have to comment on one thing.  And bear in mind that I have been a wrestling fan since the mid-80's...and I have seen a lot of PPV lead-in's...plus, in the last few years, I've been reading a couple wrestling websites...  I'm totally lost.  HHH is in the main event of Armageddon, in a Triple-Threat Match with Kane and Bill Goldberg, yet Trips hasn't even shown up in any way, shape, or form on Spike TV.  Not only that, but JR and the King have made no attempt to even play HHH's absence on something.  We're just supposed to accept that he's in the main event at the next PPV without having done anything, let alone tape a promo.  One would almost think that he's married into the McMahon Family or something...  On to the show: (This is purely one drunken idiot looking at the card and saying how he think it would be booked.  I accept no responsibility for any of my dozens  AND DOZENS  of readers placing bets with their bookies)   Booker T. vs Mark Henry --Say it aint so, Book!  Lemee holla atcha, playa....Last April, you were in the main event at WrestleMania.  You da man, Book!  You're my favorite guy on the RAW roster.  Why they burying you?  Especially against a punk like Mark Henry.  I wanna see yo' ass bust this one out, cuz you my man!  I got this guy in urlLink  PA named Elvin  who calls you "Loser T" that I wanna prove wrong.  See, Elvin been drinkin' too much of tha Hata-Ade.  Pull that win out...do it for this white crakka brutha!  Take a heel turn after that, it's all good...just don't let that playa-hata Elvin bad mouth you.  B'lee dat!   Trish Stratus & Lita vs. Chris Jericho & Christian  --  All this for one Canadian Dollar.  This storyline has had a decent buildup that I was enjoying until my mom came in while I was watching RAW.  She saw Trish on the TV and said, "Oh my lord, she looks just like Krishna!"  Krishna is one of my *ahem* friends down here in Atlanta, and I'll be damned if my mom wasn't right, but if Trish had a bit more junk in her trunk, she'd be a dead ringer for Krishna.  (I ought to give her a call...).  Anyway, I'm seeing a Trish heel turn.  She's sooo going to hook up with Jericho.  I feel like a teenage girl watching a soap opera (The days of our RAW?).   Randy Orton vs. Rob Van Dam  -- RVD is da man!  Most WWE fans love RVD!  I am a total mark for RVD!  RVD is going to lose the I-C title to Randy Orton, and I will be royally pissed if the time of the match is 4:20.   Batista vs. Shawn Micheals-- The behemoth from DC is destined for great things in the WWE. He needs to work on his mic skills a bit, but his wrestling ability is awesome! My gut sez Batista wins after a heroic effort by HBK.  However, upon further reflection, perhaps it will be Micheals (who beat Jericho against all odds at WM XIX) who put Devon's former Deacon in his place.  I call this one a tossup.   Tag Team Turmoil: I love this concept!  By random draw, two teams start out, when one is eliminated, another comes in and so on and so on... The Dudleys are the defending Champs going into this.  The other five teams are:Mark Jindrak & Garrison Cade, Val Venis & Lance Storm ,Hurricane & Rosey, Test & Scott Steiner, and Rene Dupree & Rob Conway.  This should be quite the spectacle to watch.  Look for Test and Big Poppa Pump to be your hook-up at the end.  And that should do it for a great PPV.  See you all next time!   ummm...Drew???   What?   You forgot about the main event.   There's a main event?  No way... Wait!  Don't tell me!  The Rock & Sock Connection vs. Shane and Vince McMahon!   Nope...   Awww crap...I actually have to write about this, don't I?     Yup     Goldberg vs Kane vs HHH for the World Title--   Ever seen two men in a ring trying to wrestle eachother but won't sell eachother's moves?  I've seen that a few trimes.  What I have yet to see is a triple threat match where all three contestants are non-sellers.  This should be, um, great?  Trips hasn't even shown up on TV for the last two weeks to lend this main event any credibility.    That alone would almost lead the purest cynic into thinking HHH is getting the gold back.   Might happen, noway to tell these days.  I say it goes one of two ways...Kane gets the strap and runs with it briefly, or Goldberg hangs on.  It all depends on how Bill's contract negotiations work out.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      WrestleMania XX is supposed to be  THE MOST ELECTRIFYING EVENT  in sports entertainment history.  Live from it's birthplace in Madison Square Garden!     Hey, Pedro...how old were you when the very first WrestleMania took place in 1985 at MSG?  Nevermind, don't answer that....   The original  urlLink WrestleMania  was the biggest gamble ever made in the wrtestling industry.  Vince McMahon jr. was betting everything on taking his newly bought enterprise nationwide, and if it hadn't been for Mr. T, he may well have failed.    But we all know at this point that The Higher Power, Vince, has suceeded quite well since that great gamble in 1985.  And come this 14th of March, 2004 AD, we'll see the 20th installment of the true Grandaddy of 'em all.  From what I understand, Vince usually starts planning the next WrestleMania about a month after the previous.  Meaning for XX, Vince had something in mind as of last May.  If only our weekly RAW and SmackDown! shows were so well booked...  Usually, they like to start the WM Countdown at the Royal Rumble.  Who knows whats in store this year.  I have some guesses though...   Did you expect anything less?    Kane vs. Undertaker  -- Of course this is a foregone conclusion.  I was originally thinking that it would be a Hell in a Cell match.  Then again, I'd like to see those creative geniuses come up with something new and more brutal.  Like a barb-wire-flaming cage match, or something.  Rest assured, it'll be a gimmick match.  let's hope it'll be something we've never seen before.  And then there's the deep speculation...  Goldberg's contract negotiations are up in the air from what I've read, but let's assume for the moment that it's all bullshit.  If Golddus..Goldberg sticks around for a WrestleMania paycheck, he'll face Brock Lesnar.  As a Lesnar mark, and a Goldberg hata, I would love to see that match.   John Cena  is getting a huge push, and I gotta say, I'm diggin' it...sucka!!!  Word life!  My boyz going to WrestleMania/and his opponent there aint no savin' ya/ Jericho might say your're an ass clown/but Cena's gonna beat ya down/it don't matta who stands toe to toe with word-life/John Cena's gonna beat them worse HHH's wife/It don't matta who steps around cuz they aint it/Cena knows it stanks cuz he's  THA SHIT!!!   They say Bret Hart is going to be there.  We also  KNOW that Shawn Micheals is going to be there.  Could we possibly see a handshake and a hug over the Montreal Screwjob??  (I'll write about this in the future, but the Montreal Screwjob was the most genius work ever pulled...).  They say Hulk Hogan will be there.  As well as the Macho Man Randy Savage.  Back in the day, I was the ultimate MM mark, but now he's just pathetic.  Have you heard his new rap CD?  No?  Well, shit,  urlLink click this link , clear out the popups, and let the Macho Man tell you what you need to do, oooh yeah!  Kurt Angle's neck may prevent him from ever wrestling again, but I hope he'll at least make anther WM match, perhaps against Shelton Benjamin.  Shelton is just a winning gimmick away from being The Next Big Thing.  I'm rambling here, Pedro.   Ask me about WM XX after the Royal Rumble. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      No posts in almost a month and I haven't seen wrestling in nearly 2 months. Once again allow me to rant on how much I hate not having cable! But im done with that rant....  Wrestle Mania is a while away and I am already itching to see it! I am gonna ask Drew (the Guru of wrestling) to predict 3 matches for the PPV....and he already did one on Nov. 18th.....Taker vs. Kane in a Cell.....lets see what Drewcifer says....
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all I watched Velocity tonight, and liked what I saw. I was totally in the dark about what I was about to feast my eyes upon. I saw Hardcore Holly beating Big Slow in a street fight (highlites from Smackdown! anyways), and I also saw Los Guerreros breaking up. Looks like a good time. Too bad I have to miss it.  By the way all Drew has carried a load in here for a while, therefore I gave him a couple weeks off for vacation :)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes you got it! Sunday night isn't just for Heat. It is also for Smackdown. According to my local listings, Smackdown is on promptly at 11:30 on Ssunday night. It used to be the local WB station would tape Smackdown off of UPN then play it on Saturday night at about 8ish depending on prior programming. But that ceased a little over a year ago.  Now alas I have my Smackdown back! I was the biggest fan for Smackdown. Everything on that show was awesome. They even had a TLC match on there that was awesome (Im talking about the one between Edge & Christian, the Dudleyz, the Hardyz, and Benoit & Jericho).  So since I have school the next day I usually just stay up until about 12:30 AM and then go to bed. For the most part I miss the best parts (seeing how most wrestling cards climax at the end of the show).  But lately I think that Smackdown has taken a turn for the better with the lottery. Getting Dudleys and Booker T on a trade and then getting RVD from a lottery pick. I think that RVD is supposed to be on Smackdown anyways...he just looks like a Smackdown person. And plus with Lesnar leaving...there is a pretty big void to fill. I think thats where Drew's Main Man comes into play. Booker is gonna dominate! He will be the next champ I know it!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I tried like hell to get out of work before 7PM tonight, but it just wasn't in the cards.  When I did get cut, you've never seen a dude haul ass like this dude hauled ass tonight.  We're talking around just a tad after 9PM when I clocked out.    The Hooter's across the street from where I work shows all the WWE PPV's, so that's where I went.  I apparently had good timing.  Just as I walked in, I heard the glass shatter and Stone Cold's music hit.  I had arrived just in time for the Lesnar-Goldberg match.  (I hadn't heard the  urlLink Lesnar rumors  until after I got home...)  Lemme tell you, Hooter's was packed.  And full of rowdy wrestling fans as well.  Of course, they were all marking out huge for ol' Whiskerbiscuits Goldberg (he lives in Atlanta).  I for one was stunned at the easy win that Goldberg got, considering he's leaving WWE for Japan after WM.  Then again, so is Brock.  Who knew?  (He'll be back...)  Anyway, I'm not going to recount the entire card here.  You can go to  urlLink PWTorch  for the full blow-by-blow.    When the Old School Undertaker came out (and man, did he ever slim down?  I swear that's the slimmest I've ever seen the man.  I guess that's what happens when you're buried alive and only manage to rise from the dead 5 months later)Hooter's went nuts for the Dead Man.  I was a bit disappointed in the quickness of the match, but hey, what do you expect from a man who's spent the last five months dead?    I was pleased with the Eddie Guerro-Kurt Angle match.  I haven't mentioned it here, but I've been saying that I want to see Eddie run with the belt for a good while.  Along with Rey-Rey, he can really help pull the Hispanic audience into WWE.  Plus, if there's any man who deserves to be WWE Champ, it's Eddie.  Wait...There's one other guy who deserves to run with the title...   BENOIT!  BENOIT!!  BENOIT!!!  My hat goes off for the Canadian Crippler.  Talk about a "smart" wrestling fan marking out to HHH tapping out to the Crippler Crossface.  I spilled my beer.  All of Hooter's went nuts as well.  The next PPV is Backlash, and it emanates from Edmonton Alberta, which happens to be the hometown of who?  You guessed it...Chris "The Rabid Wolverine" Benoit.  Looks like I'll be headed up to hooter's in a few weeks!  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The last time I was at an arena to see some professional wrestling was in 1989 in Winston-Salem, NC to see Hulk Hogan beat Randy "Macho King" Savage.  That was a long time ago...  Years later, I decide, "Damn the cost", I'm going to check out RAW, which would be broadcasting live from the Arena at Gwinnett Center, down the road from my house.  The show was billed as being from Atlanta, but in reality, the show emanated from Duluth, GA.  But who's looking at a map, right?  I call my regular cab driver and he picks me up around 5:45PM.  I tell him I'm going to the Gwinnett Arena.  He says, "You're going to see that wrestling?  I just dropped one of those lady wrestlers off at the arena."    "Who?"  "I don't remember her last name, but her first name was Stacey."  "Keibler?"  "Yeah, I think so.  Nice legs, she was staying at the Fairfield Inn."  "You mean to tell me that my ass is currently occupying the same spot that Stacey Keibler's ass was five minutes ago??"  And that was pretty much the case.    Anyway, I got to the arena right before 6PM and headed straight to the box office.  The cheap seats were sold out, but I could get a $32 seat that was still available.  I snatched it up. (Turned out it was a good buy as the arena sold out shortly thereafter).    I grabbed my seat around 7-ish and was amazed.  I've been watching RAW all these years but had never seen the set in person.  My seat was 13 rows up from the floor, parallel to the announce table.  I was at the edge of the stage, and couldn't see the Titan-tron, but oh well, I was there.  The setup truly amazed me.  Anyway, Howie Finkel comes out and announces some dark matches, which involves jabronies getting a tryout shot.  Those matches were okay.  Then we got a couple Heat taped matches (Spike Dudley vs. Renee Dupree, and the Dudleys vs. Val Venis & Lance Storm).  Then we went live!    And before we knew what was going on, the glass shattered, and Stone Cold Steve Austin hit the ring to talk some smack!  Man, that was awesome!  Then Vince came out to yell at him, and it just went to (oh) Hell (yeah) from there.  I'm sitting in between a couple of guys who were 18 or 19 who had never seen a wrestling event in their lives.  I hadn't seen one since they were toddlers.  So we were all marking out.    Further on in the show, Rico came out to introduce Stacey Keibler and Miss Jackie when Kane's pyro hit out of nowhere.  Let me tell you.  From where I was sitting, those flames burn hot! (Not to mention scared the living shit out of me...).    Ditto when My Man, my Main man, Booker T. came out with his flames a'jumping.  That pyro burns 13 rows back.  I'm sitting parralell to King and J.R. and thinking about how they manage to endure it every week.    Anyway, it was an awesome show.  It ended with Mick Foley challenging Randy Orton, Dave Batitsta, and Ric Flair to a 3-on-2 match at WrestleMania.  All of us in attendance knew who it was going to be, but that still didn't stop the house from popping HUGE when The Rock came out sprinting and helping Mankind beat the crap out of Evolution.    (A side note...I was hovering a bit by the merchandise stands.  People were asking for Evolution T-Shirts left and right.)  So the live show ended with Rocky and Mick sending Evolution up the ramp.    Then we hear the glass shatter, and Stone Cold Steve Austin comes out to the ring.  He grabs a mic and says, "I'm sorry to ruin your moment, I know that you and Mick Foley are special friends..."  "WHOA WHOA WHOA!!," The Rock says, "EVERYBODY knows, The Rock likes that POONTANG PIE!" Then he continues, "But, um, speaking of the streudel...how you doing, Lillian?"  Referring to Lillian Garcia, the ring announcer.  Rock brings Lillian into the ring, and Stone Cold decides that everyone should sing a song.  Meanwhile, some drunk dumbfuck decides to jump the railing and gets jumped by security.  Security has to struggle like hell with this guy to get him back over the railing (no, it wasn't me..).  The Rock says, "Hey, don't be rough on the guy, he's wearing a Stone Cold T-Shirt!"  Stone Cold turns to Rock and Mick Foley with Lillian Garcia at his side and says, "Doesn't Lillian look lovely?  I almost proposed to her the other night."  Rock says, "Why didn't you?"  "Because I ran out of beer!"  At which point the beers started flying left and right into the ring.  Mostly for Steve, but Lillian was chugging them too.  At one point, Mick, Rock, and Austin had Lillian on her knees while they were all pouring beer down her throat and all over her body and elswhere... Then Austin got down on his knee in front of Lillian.  Rock was getting ready to leave the ring when Steve said, "No, Rock.  I want you to be here for this.  You're a good friend of mine."    "Lillian...Will you..."  "...get me another beer?"  Mick Foley went on to acknowledge the fact that he lived in the Atlanta suburbs during his WCW days and pointed out that Austin also lived in Marietta during his WCW days (the crowd popped for that, of course).   In the end, it was Austin with beers galore in his hand making his way up the ramp. On each end of the ramp, he's saluting the fans the only way he knows how, and smack his beers together.    Man, that was awesome.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay I dont even think anyone reads this anymore. Just cuz Drew is the only one that posts in here it seems. Last sunday (when the smackdown! tapings are on at my house) i missed smackdown because the stupid local TV station went nuts and played reruns of crap over and over and over again...but oh well  Hopefully the next time wrestling comes through town I can get a ticket. I missed it last time it was in Ames and I was pissed!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Great American Bash  is tomorrow night. I will have some (if not all) of the matches listed and have my picks up as well. Maybe if he gets around to it, Drew might too. We will see.  This pay per view is looking ot be one of the best ones that  urlLink Smackdown!  has had to offer this year I think. Although I wont see it live, I will probably see it sometime next week. I have a friend that tapes almost all of the pay per views for me :)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know who watches much Smackdown! anymore here...but I sure as heck do and I love it! Its on at 11:30 P.M. on Sunday night into Monday Morning. I just thought for now I would address the Texas Bullrope match before The Great American Bash airs on Sunday (when I will watch the final Smackdown...and watch my friends tape of it on monday sometime)   Eddie Guerrero vs. John 'Bradshaw' Layfield  Texas Bullrope Match: Stipulations. Two superstars are tied together by a 'Texas Bullrope'. The bullrope is nearly 10 feet in length, and has a cowbell in the middle of it. You must wrestle your opponent with no disqualifacations (hit 'em with the cowbell or whatever) with only one way to win. Drag your opponent and touch all 4 turnbuckles.  This type of match you would think that JBL (John Bradshaw Layfield) would win simple as pie...but I dunno. I cant decide whether or not they will have JBL win it, and gain some heel heat...or to have Eddie keep the title (which I think they have run him as the champ for WAY too long...) and find a new rivalry to pursue...   My prediction:  JBL comes out victorious in a huge bloodbath!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish Chris Jericho would bring both of these men out on The Highlight Reel, just so he could tell them both to  "SHUT THE HELL UP!!   Apparently it all started with the recent publishing of Ric Flair's book, "To Be the Man..." (which I want to read, but haven't as of yet.)  Supposedly, Ric stated that after Bret Hart beat him for the WWF Title (just prior to his return to WCW), Bret was not a draw for the Fed.  Supposedly, Ric goes on in his book to slam Bret on just about everything.  Like I said, I haven't read the book yet, but I do read a lot of wrestling websites, and the debate has been raging on and on and on as to who was better:  Ric Flair or Bret Hart?  I thought about sending my thoughts in to PWTorch.com or PWInsider.com, but I decided that I'll just state my piece here and only here.  That's right, you lucky Dojo reader!  You get an  Exclusive Drewcifer Perspective  right here for free!   Now let's see...  The very first time I saw a Professional wrestling card live was on March 27th, 1988 in Greensboro, NC.  It was the very first Clash of the Champions, televised live on Superstation WTBS.  (For you younger reders, this pre-dated WCW.  It was still Jim Crockett's Mid-Atlantic Promotion, about a year before he sold his interest to Ted Turner, who then created WCW.)  That date was significant for two reasons:  It was the very first Clash of the Champions, aired on live TV, and going on at the exact same time was none other than WrestleMania IV.    In 1988, not everyone had cable, let alone the chance to get a 19.95 PPV event.  (Yes, in '88, WM cost a mere twenty bucks.)  I was upset two weeks before the event that I would not get to see the World Title Tournament at WM (like I said, we didn't have cable)...but my mom bought me and her main squeeze of the time tickets to Clash of the Champions.  It was a nice consolation prize, I thought, but it turned out to be even better.  I was a big time WWF, Hulk Hogan, Macho Man Savage, Brutus "The Barber" Beefcake fan at the time.  I also watched Mid-Atlantic Wrestiling on TV, but pretty much considered it a minor league to the mighty WWF.  Anyway, I went to my first live wrestling event on that March day in '88.  And I'll be damned.  What an event that was!  I saw Barry Windham and Lex Luger beat Arn Anderson and Tully Blanchard for the NWA Tag-Team Titles, The Road Warriors (LOD)& Dusty Rhodes wrestle in a barbed-wire match against The Powers of Pain & Paul Jones, Midnight Express vs. The Fantastics, etc...  But the match I'll always remember was Ric Flair vs. Sting.  It was their first ever encounter for the NWA/WCW Title, and they went to a 45 minute draw, the end of the match having Ric Flair in the Scorpion Death-Lock (aka-Sharpshooter) and the bell ringing at the time limit.  Having been a total mark at the time, I was totally impressed with Ric Flair's performance, even though I started hating him more.  It took me nearly a week to find out what happened at WrestleMania IV. (Believe it or not, there was no such thing as an internet back then.)  Around the same time Ric Flair was going "Broadway" with Sting, Randy "Macho Man" Savage was winning the 14-man tounament for the vacant WWF Championship.  Not only that, but Bret "HitMan" Hart turned face in the 20-man Battle Royal that led off WrestleMania IV.    In August of that same year, WWF made it's debut at the Greensboro Coliseum, a long-time stronghold of Jim Crockett's territory.  WWF didn't just throw their mid-card talent, they went all out.  The main event was Hulk Hogan vs. Andre the Giant.  It was a huge event at the time.  (I was sorely disappointed when I got there to find that it wasn't being taped or televised, but at least I got to meet Leapin' Lanny Poffo--he autographed my Hulk Hogan shirt.)  Anyway, The WWF soon started running semi-regular shows in the Greensboro-Winston Salem area.  The NWA/WCW were running monthly shows at the Greensboro Coliseum.  On the day of the NWA events, you could buy an upper-deck ticket for five bucks, and that's what I did once a month for almost a year.  And Ric Flair was always the Champ, and I hated hated, HATED him as Champ.  He'd always somehow manage to cheat his way out of losing his title, either by having the Four Horsemen interfere on his behalf, of getting himself intentionally disqualified.  And yet, I'd go back the very next month in hopes of seeing him lose the title.  Bret Hart came into his own glory a bit after my time so to speak.  By the time I hit my senior year of High School, I suddenly found myself occupying my time with Cross-Country, and my first real girlfriend.  (Trust me, if I had to do it over, I would have told her, "I love Professioal Wrestling, and I'd really like to stay home tonight and watch this new show called RAW...")   Anyway, my wrestling viewership waned for a year or so, and my attendance at live events went dormant for nearly 10 years (last March 1st at RAW).  After I started collegein the  fall of '93, I was hanging out with trouble...I mean a nice young lady in her dorm, who somehow had cable, we were watching some movie on USA, and an ad for RAW came on with Bret Hart holding the Championship belt, saying not to miss the next Monday night RAW.    I was stunned!  I asked, "When did Bret Hart win the WWF Championship?" (I knew Randy Savage had beaten Ric Flair at WrestleMania that year, and that Flair managed to win it back).  She was like, "HUH?"  and I was like "Oh yeah..nevermind..."  Anyway, in the intervening years ('93-'98), I kept loose tabs on Wrestling.  I managed to see most of Diesel's reign as WWF Champ, and Shawn Micheals' ascent to the upper echelon, as well as WCW's acquisitions of Hulkster, Macho Man, et al.  It wasn't until 1999 when I separated from my ex-wife (not the same chick from college, actually a different chick from college) that I rediscovered my love of Professional Wrestling, aka, Sports Entertainment.    I was channel hopping one Monday night and landed on USA.  Stone Cold Steve Austin was cutting a promo on Vince McMahon, and the "Corporation", and I got hooked from there on in.  Or re-hooked, as it were.  Since that week in '99, I haven't missed a week of wrestling.  Even if I missed a Raw or SmackDown! or Nitro (at the time) I was blessed with the internet to catch me up on things.   There was a point to all of this, right?  Oh yeah.  Bret Hart vs. Ric Flair?    I've already documented my Ric Flair experiences.  During Bret Hart's time at the top, I was more or less away from my TV.  I won't say either amn was a better technical wrestler than the other.  Maybe Ric Flair had a better ring psychology than Hart.  I can't honestly say.  My main experience with Bret Hart's Championship runs are from renting tapes at Blockbuster. (And yes, I did rent Survivor Series, aka Montreal Screwjob).  To be fair, Ric Flair drew more of my money than Bret Hart, but I'm sure Bret Hart drew more money from people elsewhere.  Sadly, Bret had a stroke a couple years ago, and most likely will never get in the ring again (not as a full-time wrestler, anyway).  Ric and Bret will never have it out in the ring to determine "who's the best" (although, Ric did slam Mick Foley in his book as well, and I can't wait for that to materialize).  But for my money?  Who's the greatest?  It's easy.  Stone Cold Steve Austin.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, I'd like to say that Smackdown! has gotten interesting again.  For a while there, the brand was in the doldrums, post Wrestlemania, due in part to Brock's departure, Angle's injury, and too green an undercard.  Then of course came JBL's push/title win...  Anyway, Smackdown seems like it's coming back into its own as of recent events.  JBL, oddly enough, is managing to pull off the heel Champion a bit.  He's not "there" yet, but he's getting closer.  It looks like he'll have a decent buildup going into SummerSlam against the Undertaker.  One of the reasons I'm starting to buy into the JBL character as a credible heel has a lot to do with my burning desire to see Bush/Cheney go in November.  Bradshaw makes it a point to come across as the neo-conservative, racist, money-bagged asshole that embodies the current administration.  (A case could also be made that Bradshaw's title win was fishy at best, just like Dubya/Cheney's "victory" in 2000.)  But that's another Blog (I just started a new one dedicated to this years elections, http://www.usorthem.blogspot.com )  Anyway, I got to thinking tonight about some fueds of the future. The beauty of the brand extension (which many wrestling pundits hate, I personally love), is that you can hold off certain money feuds until both wrestlers are big enough money draws to pull it off.  Therefore, I'd like to see in the next year or two:   John Cena vs. Randy Orton  These two are the future of the WWE.  The next Shawn Micheals & Bret Hart.  One day down the road, they'll find themselves on the same roster and headline a Wrestlemania together.  Not to mention that they both debuted around the same time, and my wrestling-fan-ex-girlfriend's nipples would pop out any time one of those guys came to the ring.    Hurricane vs. Rey Mysterio  Mild-mannered reporter Gregory Helms' alter-ego The Hurricane has been horribly under-utilized on RAW.  During the post WrestleMania Fantasy Draft, I was rooting for Sugar Shane to go to SmackDown! to finally be able to compete for the Cruiserweight belt.  He's the second best cruiserweight on both rosters.  Sadly, 'Cane got left behind on the RAW roster only to be a constant jobber to Kane, et al. I say let the Hurricane compete for the Cruiserweight title.  The matchup has so much drawing potential that the writers wouldn't even have to turn one of them heel.  Just give the match a proper PPV push and let them go nuts for 20 minutes in the ring.  This matchup would also help WWE's ailing house show attendance.  No one is lining up to see Rey Rey vs. Chavo jr. for the umpteenth time.     Batista vs. Brock Lesnar  By all press reports, it appears Brock Lesnar's chances of signing with an NFL franchise is slim (although, I do have him as a linebacker on my Chargers team on Madden '04).  Brock pissed a lot of people off by quitting like he did a few weeks before WrestleMania.  He decided he wanted to persue his dream of being an NFL player, despite the fact that he hadn't played football since High School.  (To be fair, he was an All-State HS football player during his Senior year.)  Barring some desparate team like the Lions looking for a quick ticket draw (ala aged Joe Montana going to the Cheifs in '94), it looks like Brock will have to return to the business that he had already earned 10 Million dollars from.  Would WWE be willing to welcome him back?  Of course!  Would Brock get the same "Superman push" he got the first time around?  Hell no!  Vince would gladly take Brock back, but Brock might have to do some jobs to the likes of Jamie Noble and Tyson Tomko.  The way they're pushing Batista these days, like the behemoth that he is, he'd be a natural opponent for Brock, once he comes back and gets back in good graces.  Who comes out on top of that feud is anyone's guess, though.  (Side note:  Brock Lesnar may actually become the very first member of the OFFSCREEN Vince McMahon Kiss-My-Ass-Club.)   Ric Flair vs. Bret Hart  Actually, I'm going to make a separate blog entry on this whole ruckus.  Apparently, The Nature Boy badmouthed the HitMan in his book (which I haven't read yet), and now the whole IWC (Internet Wrestling Community) is abuzz with debate on the topic of who was better.  And lastly, the Ultimate feud I'd like to see in the ring:   Pedro "Admiral" Stockdale vs. The Almighty Drewcifer  That's right, WeeWee, I'm calling you out!  Not that you'll get in the ring with me, cuz you aint got the nards!  You heard me! You call me an old thirty-something, and you may be right, but I can still take your pubescant ass to that mat and make you tap, just like I tapped your mama the other night!  What?  Yeah, you heard me, little man!  C'mon! Your sister tapped, too!  Whoo!  I'm so filled with hellfire, you'll get burned just by laying a finger on me!  I'm like the Sun...the World revolves around me, and I'm way too hot to touch!  Yeah, C'mon!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You should just think of it this way Drew. I aquired this shirt today from  urlLink Chad .    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and I apologize to each and every one of my dozens of readers.    I'm sorry.  I was mistaken.  I wrote on 7/22/04:  "By all press reports, it appears Brock Lesnar's chances of signing with an NFL franchise is slim...[much snippage]....) Barring some desparate team like the Lions looking for a quick ticket draw (ala aged Joe Montana going to the Cheifs in '94), it looks like Brock will have to return to the business that he had already earned 10 Million dollars from."  Whodathunk?  Brock got himself a contract with the team he wanted to play for in the first place:  The Minnesota Vikings.    Granted, he still has to make it through Training Camp and the pre-season before he "makes the team."  But by all media accounts, Brock just might have what it takes to be a bonafide NFL defensive tackle.  I'm rooting for him.  
     
    
</post>


<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Wrestling Blog   Hey I have a wrestling blog. And I hope all of the people that visit this one (like all zero of you!) will check it out  urlLink http://wrestlingroundtable.blogspot.com . I am not the only person on it. "The Guru" Drewcifer would probably be the main read here. He knows what needs knowing. His posts will be better to read...but read mine too. I'm not that boring.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Renaissance/No Posts   Sorry for not posting lately...I have been slacking with football, homework and the Minnesota Renaissance Festival. I will blog about it later. Like tomorrow perhaps. Or maybe later tonight if I have the time and gumption.  Thanks for being patient with me...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Funnier than crap!   Hey everyone go to  urlLink Rachel's Blog  and check out some funny entry that she has!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Fort Dodge   Fort Dodge is a relatively big town that has a mall and a Target and all that stuff in it (which Humboldt does not). So Travis just turned 16 and we (Travis, Mitchell, Justin, and I) were going to take "Ed" (this big huge boat of a Mercury Marquis that he has) and take it for a spin to Fort Dodge to a pizzeria there and tool around town. Somehow though we got it decided that we would take my car instead (more on that later). So we go for pizza and stuff, and it was good. We then went to Target and looked around for stuff with "no dice". Justin bought two movies. I cant remember which ones.  Then we decided to go over to Wal-Mart. There we walked all over the place and were trying to find some cheap and really really obnoxious things to buy. We ended up looking for fish with Justin. He decided that he was going to buy about 20 goldfish, a small bowl, some fish food, and some little rocks for the bottom of the bowl. We were waiting and waiting for service for about 10 minutes. Then someone finally came and talked to us. But then they left to "go get water". They never returned. We ended up waiting another 25-30 minutes for the stupid lady...but no luck with that. I then whipped over to the camera section and bought a disposable camera for no apparent reason. Then Travis decided to get a pack of some cheep genaric brand...uh...nevermind.  We get to my house at 8:08 and then we switch cars (I said I'd be back by 8). We get into Ed. And me, Taz (Travis), and Mitchell, decide to cruise the town for a few minutes. I get home at 8:45ish and my mom goes nuts on me. She wants to know why we took my car and not Ed. And then she wants to know why my car was here but I wasn't. Then she also wants to know why I wasn't home by 8. COME ON I WAS EIGHT MINUTES LATE!!! But whatever. It was a day well spent! I had a blast!!!  (There are many things that I did not mention due to the fact that if anyone that really cared about my safety read they would probably tell my mom, or some other authority figure in any young teens' life)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Early Practice   Dang man! I get out of practice today at about 8:30, I have homework! Chemistry, US History, Current Events and all that jazz. Then on top of it all I have an early practice tomorrow!!! Since Wednesday is the "Church Night" I have to be there. But then if we dont get out of school early for heat, I still have practice after school! That is stupid. Really really STUPID! AND THATS THE BOTTOM LINE!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Yet Another Early out   Today we got out early again. So I had Jadie come over and we watched the movie  Undisputed . The movie was okay, but who am I to judge...im not Ebert or Roper or whoever they are. As I was taking Jadie home just about 10 minutes ago, some frickin moron just about ran into us. Some lady was turning right, off the highway, and into the  urlLink Hy-Vee  parking lot. But she was stupid and wasn't paying attention and about hit me while I was waiting to turn out of the parking lot! I bit my tongue so as to not unleash my fury of big words and swearing onto her and just let it go. No biggie right?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Early out   We had yet another early out for school. Due to a nice and toasty 98 with a heat index of 107...I think that they had reason. That meant that footbal would be late (6:00 to 8:00 or whenever). After school I went to Justin's to pay some money that I owed him (I always owe him money). Then I picked up Jadie and we finally got around to watching  1 Hour Photo . As we were about 20 minutes into it Travis, who had just gotten his liscence, decided to drop by. So he decided to come over and eat one of my pizzas, drink one of my  urlLink Gatorades , and watch the movie with us. I didn't mind. Travis is cool!    Football   Football wasn't that bad. Bruce kinda got after me when I was pussy-footin' around a little, and he seemed quite mad. Then he made me do the drill again. And I got pissed and did it really good. And he said good. I felt really good. About an hour into our practice it started to lightning. So we moved the practice into the brand new multi-purpose room. It was quite easy. We couldn't really do a whole lot in there so we just ran plays and that sorta jazz. Practice got out nice and early 8:10. I then got outside to see that it was lightning like a butt-monkey! I came home and saw that my town was in a severe lightning storm warning of some sort, it said to stay away from electrical appliances. But I dont care I'm on the computer anyways. :D Somebody sue me!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Yesterday Afternoon   Ok yesterday afternoon Joel came over and we decided to try out my dad's new  urlLink Henry Rifles . They are pretty nice. We used a  urlLink .22 Lever Action  and a  urlLink .22 Pump Action . We also bought a  urlLink .22 US Survival Rifle , but my dad didn't like the color (silver) so we decided to return it. Me, Joel, and my dad shot off 200 bullets at popcans, pennies, pop boxes, and birds. Then Brian (my sisters boyfriend) decided to join in on the fun and we shot about another 100 bullets with my dads Browning .22 semi-automatic. It was fun shooting that gun. You could just go rapid-fire and hit the pop cans and blow them to pieces!    Yesterday Night   Joel had gone home, we had polished up the guns all nice and neat, and then I was bored once again. So I went out to Joel's and helped him clean up their horse, Ernie. (Ernie is owned by Sue Skow, she ownes  urlLink Sue's Arabs and Pintos . If you want a horse check this out!) Ashley was there and she got all wet and was mad. She pouted until Joel and I decided to cheer her up. Joel and I got this funny-as-heck idea to have a pushup contest. Joel won (cuz his dog was chewing me apart when I did mine). Then we dicided to do some chin-ups. I won, no contest. After that Joel, Ashley, and I decided to play some frisbee. Joel is pretty good. After that we all went out to eat at  urlLink Pizza Hut . I called Jadie and she went with too. After all of that I got home at 9:00 and had Chemistry to do. :( NOT COOL!!! I was up til about 10:30 doing homework (Chemistry, US History, Cellular Biology [incomplete], and a little math) Speaking of math I have some to do...I had better jet!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        No Post   I didn't get to post last night. I will post this afternoon.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        New stuff   I think that I am going to try something a little different with my blog. Like have a new heading on it or something. Look for posts later about it...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just invited into another blog by Gideon from the wheresgeorge channel on IRC.  check it out  urlLink http://georgers.blogspot.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Man today Jadie has been doing crap with her family so I have been on the computer all day. I am really really bored, and I am also tired of workin on my website. I was hoping to have a pictures page up and running today. But instead I got side-tracked with making a page for all of my CD's and everything. Then I decided to open my big mouth about making a database on my  urlLink Where's George  stuff. So now I have someone talking to me about php, asp, and all this other jazz so that I can make a database. But I dont even know any php (or any of that other crap) (I barely know HTML). So I am in a mess.  Jadie is going to Kennedy park with her family for something today.  That is where I went and looked for the  urlLink Geocache  yesterday. Ya never know. Maybe Jadie will find it and put something inside. But I wouldn't bet on it. She probably wouldn't want to walk to the opposite side of the lake for that.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up the morning and began my day with my mom yelling at me, as usual. Church was going to start in about 15 minutes whether I was ready or not. So I flew downstairs and hopped into the shower quick. Got out, went upstiars and quickly dressed. I had 5 minutes to spare. I grabbed a banana and headed out the door. When I got to my car I noticed that there were no scratches at all on from the night before. Church begins as every church service does, announcements, singing, a little more singing. The service wasn't that bad. You can tell when I think it's a dull service because I will nearly fall asleep. But this one I was wide awake and listening. Maybe it was the  urlLink Power Point  (by stupid and worthless  urlLink MS ) Presentation that made me want to pay attention. But I dont know.  On my way home from church I spotted Joel at J.I.T. (a company that manufactures metal parts for machines, and other objects.) He was using the power-washer in the shop to clean his truck for a horse show that he was going to do later in the week. I gladly stopped and began to chat. Yesterday I had gotten a new set of BIG Fuzzy Dice to replace my small ones. So I gave Joel the small dice to contrast to his MAMMOUTH V8 Beast of a  urlLink Ford Truck . He enjoyed them I guess. I dont know if he will keep them. But then I decided to go and get some doughnuts at  urlLink Hy-Vee  (which I still haven't done). So now I think I am leaving to get some doughnuts and visit my granparents for a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It is about 10:00 and I just got a call from Joel and he said that he wanted to come out. Last night he came out and he had about 3 or 4 beers, and chatted with me, my sister, brian, and my mom. But for about 20 min he talk to me about his new job, and how my resume that I helped him with had gotten him hired, and how he couldn't wait to get on a normal schedule for once!  Tonight however he was a little quieter. He just called and said, "hey bring out a couple of beers. I'll be over in about 10 minutes." So I did as I was told and met him outside with a couple of beers. Only tonight he must have been really tired. He just guzzled his first beer, then belched a few belches that would almost rate on the richter scale. And had asked for his second beer to-go. Then he was off.  I then realized that I had to park my car in the garage still. So I wheeled it around a little and pulled it into the garage. Except it looked as crooked as a politician. So I decided to back it out and re-do it. But you see if you can wheel a car into a garage crooked...you have little luck getting it out safe! So I just about run over the cats, and mow over the garage trying to get my car out. I pull my car into the garage (straight this time). And as I sit here now eating  urlLink Chick-O-Sticks  I wonder if I damaged my car; I wasn't really paying any attention if I hit anything  inside  the frickin garage!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got done cashing in cans. I got $7.50. Of course I got my cash in all one dollar bills, so that I could enter them all at  urlLink http://www.WheresGeorge.com . This site is pretty cool! You enter your money and see where it goes. That simple. I also rented 3 movies. Vanilla Sky [w/ Tom Cruise], Undisputed [w/ Wesley Snipes], and One Hour Photo [with Robin Willians]. I have not seen any of these movies, but  urlLink Chad  told me that 'One Hour Photo' was pretty good. So I will see!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I went looking for a Geocache this afternoon ( urlLink www.geocache.com ) I went with my lovely girlfriend Jadie, and we walked all over the trails of JFK park with no GPS system to help us out. (it is nearly impossible to find a geocache with no GPS) We found the relative area that the geocache was located, but we didn't want to rummage around in the weeds too much. With a nice 45 min. walk out of the way we headed home a defeated couple...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      After staying up a little later than I was hoping to last night (12:30) I woke up this morning to a nice sensation of something that smelled good, but then again something that smelled like it was horribly burned. I decided to investigate and see who the frick was trying to burn down my house. I come downstairs and see my mom, my sister, and Brian (my sisters boyfriend) all eating pancakes. Brian was cooking. They were pretty good I thought. But apparently he must have gotten bored, for when I came downstairs, there was a pancake with my initials in it. Then I proceeded with my odd ritual of toppings. First the butter, then the Peanut Butter, then the syrup (we had no powdered sugar out). I ate the pancakes and thanked Brian while my sister insulted me by calling me names like stupid, moron, weirdo, etc. (keep in mind that my sister is 17)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      JV Football reigns supreme!!! After a ruthless 50-0 mercy rule over prairie Valley, Humboldt's Junior Varsity Team moves to 3-1. Not a whole lot to say about this game. It was an all out bull-rush victory. Adam Moritz came back after a pretty nasty  urlLink hip pointer . Preston Peterson was a little hurt so he couldn't kick. Up steps...  ....  .... ME!!!! I got to kick JV. I kicked off 4 times, the first being a pretty good kick, the second being down-right sucky. The third being decent, and the fourth being a really great boot! Nothing too much else to say.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This last Saturday I went with Justin, Jordan (Justin's little brother), and Jeffy (Justins Dad) to an Iowa State University Hockey Game. They are so much fun! We live about an hour and a half from the ice arena and it was a nice car ride up there. We listened to some of the Bob and Tom show Justin had on a CD and whatnot. We get to Ames and eat at Hickory Park. It is an awesome restaurant. The food is great, the service is great, etc. etc. I dont think that there was anything wrong with this restaurant at all. It was all pretty affordable too!!! I had a chicken sandwich, with a chocoate shake for dessert.  After that we went into a Wal-Mart in Ames just to waste a little bit of time. I was walking around looking at something to buy to bide my time at home on the weekend. I was really leaning towards getting another pro wrestling figure like I had begun to collect in the late 90's but opted not to due to the cost, $7.50 (up over $2 from 2 years ago). Just as I was leaving Justin said, "LOOK!" And he pointed right at a replica modle of the  urlLink WWE Cruiserweight Title Belt . I started to drool as I awed at it. "I must have that!" I declared.  So I decided to buy the belt (for a little too much if you ask me). But the whole rest of the night (except at the hockey game) I was screaming "I AM THE CHAMPION!!!"  The hockey game was everything that I dreamed of, from the goalie heckling, to the chants, to the cheap food/drinks, to the awesome atmosphere. Despite the loss (8-3) I still had a great time. I also plan to go back some time soon!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't posted in ages. I have 3 blogs to keep up with and I just made a MONSTER BLOG on my  urlLink Wrestling Blog .  Homecoming is this week. Perhaps that is the reason that I am not getting a whole lot of posting done. This week we have these little dress-up days where we can show our "school spirit".    Monday)  - Occupation Day - This was quite funny to see what people dressed up like. Drew, and Shamus dressed up in blow up costumes. Drew was a body builder and Shamus was a Sumo Wrestler.  Tuesday)  - Pajama Day - This has got to be every girls dream. They all wore pajamas and were all giddy the entire day. I still dont see why girls are girls...But what the frick...eh? Why should I know. They are confusing.  Wednesday)  - Retro Day - Quite a few nice costumes today. Nothing too special or anything. I liked Drew P. and Jacob H.'s the best.  Thursday)  - Idol Day - Much...almost exactly...like Occupation Day. Most people who went as someone in particular on Occupation Day, came as something to the same genre on Idol Day. We had Kiss in the house though! And Elmer even dressed like a chick! BRA AND ALL!!! Oh yeah, Shamus came as 2 Pac and painted the black skin tone on with some shoe polish. He will be brown for a while.  Friday)  - Blue and Gold Day - Woo...whooptie doo! Blue and gold (note that I said that in a sarcastic tone)  I didn't dress up one single day. Im not really that much into homecoming because it has the whole king and queen thing which is just one big popularity contest. Which just makes me re-organize my prejudices. I think how the popular people all act exactly the same, and yet they still manage to pick the stupidest people out of the bunch to be the king and queen. This year wasn't quite as bad as earlier years. We had Joe Gruhn and Amanda Ropte be our king and queen. But still its not like I care. I still hate "popular" people.  Usually you pick a really easy team to play on Homecoming right? Wrong! This year we chose Esterville. And normally they aren't too good. But this particular year, they are 3-0 coming into the game, and they even had votes to be in the top 10 for prep schools in Iowa. I hope we live to see another day.  It is also butt cold outside and I am going to be on the sidelines the entire time. I am already cold just sitting here, how will I possibly survive standing in 40 degree temp on the sidelines? I liked our last JV game. It was a little chilly, but I played the entire game, therefore I kept pretty warm.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday night we played Saint Edmonds in Junior Varsity action. Saint Edmonds is an over cocky catholic school in Fort Dodge. They all think that they are pretty bad news bears, but in all actuality they SUCK! At the end of the half its like 14-0 and we are behind and getting our butts chewed out. Late in the game we made a surge to tie it at 20 points all, with about 1:30 to go, but our plans backfired as an interception spelled definate doom.  Me personally, I didn't do too bad. But there is always room for improvement. My blocking could have been quite a bit better, I probably should have had about 3 or 4 missed tackles, etc. etc. There are also some people on my team that I dont think are giving it their 100%. And one is probably...no no no...the one person that I am aiming at is BRYAN GOTTULA...but what do I know...I only play football with all of my heart and all of my soul trying to do my personal best on every down of every game...I mean its not like I can slack off or anything....like some people...  Chew on that for a while!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This last Sunday I worked with my girlfriends dad at Humboldt Sausage. He needed a little help, I guess, on this particular day so he asked me. I didn't know what we were going to do but it turnes out that we were going to install a super huge-o-fricking-mondo refrigerater door. It pry weighed 1000 lbs...maybe more maybe less. We tore down a bunch of stuff and I got to sweep up after Jim (Jadie's dad) and "O-D" (Jim O'Donnald...who oddly enough was my bus driver from about 1st grade til about 5th grade). Then I got really excited when he said help me with this heavy stuff...so we moved it and he said..."Use this chisle to scrape off all the extra caulk off of this metal..." I was crushed...but I did as I was told.  More pointless work...and a few mini throw ups (from the stench of over-salted meats) later, I finally got a good job. This piece of heavy thing (the sliding hinge for the top of the door) had to be moved onto the wall. So me and Jim were to walk up a ladder with it....and to make a long story short...THE DOOR LIVES. Then I cleaned up one last time and went home a little more "Beef'd up" with pride.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you mean like this???   LinktoComments(' ')   urlLink  ">Comment  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot my keys in the high school so I had to go back in. Jadie has a volleyball game tonight too. I would go but I have to go to hunter's ed. again. I looked into the gym where they were warming up and saw Jadie. She looked so pretty, so athletic, so so...GREAT! I couldn't believe how great she looked. She looked so pretty. Now I dont throw words like this around very much but it is the truth. Jadie almost looked completely different. And no that does not mean that I think she isn't athletic or that she isn't pretty/good looking, etc. etc. She looked great.  Jadie I love you!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had a nice hour long football practice in the rain. It wasn't that bad but it was pretty dang cold. I didn't know that it was going to be so cold today so I wore a sleeve-less shirt to school. But it wasn't too bad. I lived
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today there was no school. I woke up after no sleep the previous night and went to go shower. I get into the shower room and our shower (being in the basement of an older type house) is infested with a TON of crickets. I managed to mangle, poison, and beat most of them to death with either my bare hands, some cleaner that shouldn't touch bare skin (it has a skull and crossbones on it) and/or a broom. I finally get showered and call Jadie.  I spent most of my day loafing around at Jadie's house. We went out to eat at Lomita's Mexican Restaurant, then bought some paint for our model car. We get back to Jadie's just in time for her to say..."I'm Hungry." So we go to Casey's Gas Station where we get ripped off. (bought something and they lady rang it up about 80 cents too much) No Biggie. Then I dropped her off at volleyball and I went to football.  Tonight I went to some Hunter's Safety Course. It was from 7-10 and I would consider myself lucky that I grew up around guns, because if I had not I wouldn't understand a thing the moron's that are running the course are talking about. But we learn safety, laws etc., different types of guns, and more. Its nothing too big. And its a little boring. But I will live.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      On Monday we had a Junior Varsity Football game, at home, against Pocahontas. Our first half was a little slow with only one score. Not to brag or anything, but I played awesome. They started the game running the ball to my side. But I made every tackle for less than 3 yards. The rest of the game they ran the ball away from me. Never once (except on a play where they screwed up) did they run the ball to my side again. I also made 3 kickoff and 1 punt tackle. The second half we were really pumped up. We won the game with a score of (I think) 20-6. Also with time dwindling down we attempted a field goal (something the varsity cant even do) but missed barely to the left.  Our JV is 2-0 while our Varsity is 0-2...am I missing something here???  Last night the Des Moines North volleyball squad was in Fort Dodge yesterday night. Larissa (one of my friends from summer camp) goes to Des Moines North. Now instead of being 110 miles away she was a stones throw (20 miles) away. I took Jadie with me and we went up to Fort Dodge and I let Jadie and Larry (Larissa's nickname) meet. Larissa is a cool girl. I watched one of the most boring volleyball games ever. North lost in 3 games. I hope Jadie's volleyball games aren't this boring because if they are I dont know how I will ever live through going to them :S  Last night after I got home my mom came downstairs and said that the Cross Country boys were TPing (Toilet Paper-ing) our house. She told me to go yell at them. Instead I went outside and joined them.   Why would you do such a thing!!!   Well for one I only threw one roll and only one time. I let them do all the heavy damage. Plus my sister has to pick it up. HA HA HA. So I guess that is too bad for her.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I woke up at about 10 o'clock and my mom told me to get ready for the day. So I dragged my sorry self out of bed and showered, etc. Then my mom tells me that there are some cans to cash in! Hooray!!! I gathered up all of the cans in my car and headed to  urlLink Hy-Vee  to cash in the cans.  Dang it! It was full of about 8 Mexicans (no I do not me Mexicans to be racist) with garbage bags full of cans. So I decided to go to Jadie's house and chill out. While I was there we weighed our deciscions on what we could do for the day. We decided to just sit on her nice couch and watch some TV. We watched some college football. Iowa vs. Iowa State. Iowa won, but I dont care cuz that game means nothing to me.  After that we went down and cashed in the cans. I got $7 and some odd change with it I think. I of course got all of my money in ones so that I could enter it at  urlLink Where's George . So we get back to Jadie's and pick up her niece Kayden and babysit for her til Jadie's mom came home. By now it is about 4:00 in the afternoon.  We decided on homemade pizza for dinner, but Jadie's mom needed some pepperoni. So I took Jadie and Kayden to my house and got some really good, all beef, pepperoni. While I was there I also picked up my modle car that I had been putting off working on for a little over a year. It was a  urlLink 1960 Chevy Custom Fleetside Pickup Truck. Really really nice looking truck !  We painted most of it without any assembly for simplicity sake. I need a blue color for the engine though. Or maybe I will modify it and make the engine a different color like red or something. After about an hour and a half of painting we got tired and decided to go watch the Nebraska game. Nebraska won. Then I went home.  I had a GREAT day yesterday!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had one of those easy practices scheduled because we have a game tomorrow. We all get out to the field and it starts to rain. Not too heavy at first but suddenly it is pouring. We added about 10 lbs. of water that got absorbed in our clothes. In about 5 or 10 minutes there were 2" and 3" puddles forming under our feet. Everyone was sloshing around and doing "razorbacks" (you run at a full sprint and do a Pete Rose type, head first, dive into the wet ground). I did about 3 or 4 razorbacks, including one through a  HUGE  mud puddle. I was covered from head to toe in mud. Then it began to lightning, so we had to head inside for safety reasons.  We get inside and our coach says get clean clothes on and go to Mr. Van Pelt's room. I do as I am told peeling off layer after layer of wet soaking clothes...then it hits me...I had no clean underwear. I had to go "commando" for the time being. I put on my mesh shorts and shirt after I had cleaned the mud off of my body. While in Van Pelt's room we watched game-tape and a nice little highlight reel.  After all that, I got home and realized that Jadie had a volleyball game. But I more than likely could not attend, due to some internal family problems. But hopefully she will forgive me for not going. And by the way Jadie if you read this...thanks again for all you have done in my life! I really appreciate it even if I dont show it
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't think that the September eleventh "trageties" were that big of a deal. I mean don't get me wrong. I do hate Osama Bin Laden all the more. And its not like I don't have a soul. But seriously. If every other country had a nice little memorial day for each and every terrorist attack that had come into their nation, they would have memorials every other day. What makes the USA any better than any other country? Honestly???
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Just in case anyone was wondering. Jadie and I went for a little drive on Saturday and talked things out. A few tears were shed by both parties, and now I hope everything is hunkey-dory. I just thought that I would mention that here quick. I have a lot of messages to get out :D
     
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had a chemistry lab that we were to work on the entire period. I showed up wearing my farely new pair of blue nike nylon shorts. My Chemistry teacher gives me one look and says nope sorry you cant do the lab. I'm like why not, but then it hit me. For safety reasons (which our school has a lot of) you have to wear long pants on days you have a lab. Just in case you spill an acid on yourself or something to that nature. But I dont mind a whole lont. I will have to start doing my homework tonight and get to bed earlier than usual (maybe 10:30 after  urlLink That 70's Show  is over. I love that show. It is so funny.  Footnote: Check out my blogs to the right and read them. Like  urlLink Chad's Blog  or  urlLink Rachel's Blog  perhaps. Both are good reads. Click around on my options. See what blogs you like the best!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a nice Junior Varsity Football game yesterday night. It was in Estherville (spelling check :S) Iowa. A good hour and a half drive at least. We got there and were ready to play and the game before us hadn't even ended with the 3rd quarter.  I started at quick tackle (left side...two away from the center). I played the whole game there except about 4 minutes of the 4th quarter. I also started at right defensive tackle. I was also relieved of my duties there with about 4 minutes to go. By that time we had scored 4 touchdowns and 3 extra points. Combine that with our solid defense and we were ahead 27-0 late in the game. We held onto our lead and won the game by that same score.  The game ended at about 9:00 so our whole team went to  urlLink Mc Donalds  and ate like pigs to celebrate. I had two chicken sandwiches (which I forgot to order plain so I had to clean them off with a french fry) a large drink and a large fry. It was pretty good. I ate until I just about exploded. Travis made a little mess on the floor of the  urlLink Mc Donalds  by spilling a little pop. And "Elmer" tried to get into the playplace with no luck either.  The ride back was interesting with Travis and me talking about everything from cars to other ppl's sex stories (since our sex lives dont really exist quite yet) and multiple other things. Preston (our kicker/substitute D-end) slept on the floor underneath me. We got back at about 11:15 and all headed home. I was so tired. I just crashed at home.  It was not until I woke up that I realized that I had a few minor bumps and bruises. Nothing too big but it was fun to show them off to Jadie and watch her ooh and ahh at them :D
     
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Thinking   Man...I have a lot of thinking to do going into tonight. Megan (a girl that is near perfect in the eyes of many...but I am always mean to her) has brought up some very good points. I need to have a serious talk with Jadie. I dont konw what is going to happen between us...but it might be something that she will finally get,  that love is a two way street . And that one persons values (like a simple thank you) are important.  Too much shi....crap on my mind today.  Once again thank you Megan!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Stupid mess   Okay so Jadie went to this polka fest a couple of months ago and met this guy named Chad Boyce. I didn't like this idea from the start. First of all I am a little jealous of everything around me. If its mine I will let people know. And that includes girlfriends.  At this particular time Jadie and I had been going out for about 6 months. She comes back from a polka fest raving about her new friend Chad. I was like oh jeez. She gets his email address and begins to email him. In a short 2 or 3 weeks she had accumulated nearly 35-40 emails from Chad. I had concurred that she was telling him more than she was telling me so I felt shunned out of her life. I told her I didn't like Chad and that I didn't want them talking anymore. So after a little fight that a few tears were shed in she agreed to do so. About 3 days later she came to me and said that she had told him off, completely yelled at him, and blocked his emials and instant messenger.  It was only until today that I had lied about having key logs on my computer and all that stuff when actually Jadie was the last one to sign onto my AIM and I could see who all was online and who she had added to her AIM. To my surprise Chad's address was there. I questioned her about it and she said that she had blocked him. It is about 1 month and a half since this "blocking" that never took place. And in fact she owned up to talking to him over this whole time. In that month me and Jadie have become less and less involved with one another. Less romance, less hand holding, and all that gooey jazz.   I really really want to dump her, but I know better. I know Jadie. She would go nuts and so would I if that happened. So I wont think irrationally about that one. No dumping will be involved. But I am also tired of the lies. I tell Jadie everything. I am so sweet to her and I get what in return? Chad Boyce? No thank you! I am tired of playing the proverbial "Atlas" in this relationship. I have 2 options, make Jadie shoulder a load for a while while I collect myself...or just pass that heavy ball I call a responsability....onto Chad
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        First Football Game: results   We lost 26-27 and I dont want to talk about it really...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        First Football Game   Today is the first high school football game for my school. Also this will be my very first varsity football game that I will have been involved in. I am just suiting Varsity, whether or not I will play that Is another story. I dont think that I will play a whole lot this year (unless of course we are way ahead...or way way  way  behind) I hope that I letter this year. But that would involve playing in more than half the games...and I dont think that that will come true. Today we play Eagle Grove. And last time we played here (at Humboldt (my school)) they ended up beating us 49-0 or something like that :S...I hope either they are worse or that we are better.  Our intensity level is  WAY  higher this year than last year. Everyone that is out there wants to play. Except for a few other sophomores in my class that are just a bunch of whiners and puss'. I hate those guys...but whatever. Not quite my call on that...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Saturday/Renaissance, shoe shopping   Saturday I went to the  urlLink Renaissance Festival in Minnesota . It was pretty good. I hear the festival is pretty popular. But I didn't know. I went up there thinking that it would be really stupid. I got there and it was pretty neat. It wasn't as good as the  urlLink  Medieval Times   in New York City. I went there on a school music trip. But this fest was still pretty neat. It was over a 22 acre area and they had different stages where they had different plays of sorts. I liked the Puke & Snot comedy act! It was so funny. You had to be on your toes in order to understand them. They had some jousting, and some cool stands there where I bought some stuff. They had some people dressed up as hobos on the street and they would make fun of people. I would reccommend you going yourself.  Okay...onto shoe shopping. This didn't go quite as well as I had hoped it would. We are at the Nike Outlet in Minnesota. I was looking for shoes...and about 2 minutes after I get in there I say, "These shoes are cool!" And of course my mom says, "No those are UGLY!" Anyways...my sister looks at those same shoes about 20 minutes later and my mom is like, "Those are cool...do you want them???" I about crapped myself! But whatever...a few racist comments later by my dad and we are on the road again with everyone pissed off...end of story
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Saturday/Renaissance, shoe shopping   Saturday I went to the Renaissance Festival. It was pretty good. It was up in Minnesota. I hear the festival is pretty popular. But I didn't know. I went up there thinking that it would be really stupid. I got there and it was pretty neat. It wasn't as good as the  urlLink  Medieval Times   in New York City.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        No Posts   Sorry all...I have a lot of stuff to blog about....I just dont have time...Tomorrow maybe I will write...I have a lot of crap to do :(
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm...where should I begin...where can I remember?  First off our Varsity won against Algona last friday. Go them...  JV had a game tonight, and I got my bell rung. Everything before this in the game I forgot. I think we punted...or maybe we kicked off, but anyways...Im the lone guy going down to smoke this little shrimp with the ball. I go 100 mph as hard as I can because not only do I want to tackle, I want to  punish!  I dove...(ummm like jumped...is that the word dove?...spelling maybe...) and smoked the dude...and next thing I know im being asked by the ref what day it is...I replied 'Monday' (but I was later informed by a few guys that instead of saying Monday i said Mo o nday.) I guess I was sluring my words.  Final analysis...very bad stinger...maybe a mild concussion. I dont quite know...but if I know my way home...can get onto my computer which is password locked...etc. etc. I guess I'm doing okay...Just a small memory loss...  We were behind anyways. And we tied it up.  THEN  with about 40 sec. left Preston (a.k.a. toe) picks off a pass and runs it back for a TD and we win. everyone goes nuts. But except for the pounding headache, very soar back, neck, and torso (like stomach muscles...), and the spacing off...Im fine =S
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Man...in just a short day and a half Jadie will be home...hopefully. Its almost like she dumped me...cuz I have never been so miserable in my life since the day I asked Jadie out and she said "sure". Im going completely nuts without her. There is nobody to walk to class with. Nobody's house to go to after football. Nobody to make me do my math homework. Nobody to annoy with stupid jokes. Man...am I a sad-sack or what???
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate alcoholic beverages. They are SOOOO stupid. My dad is a growing alcoholic. He frequents liquer stores, and always has a beer in his hands. I am to the point where I want to just dump all of his frickin beer down the drain. Nothing good can come from beer! It is an evil invention. It ruins lives, and ruins your body too!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I forgot to let my dog out of the house before I went to school. Not only was she inside for the entire day...but she ate a pound of raw hamburger and also a few more things....that isn't that good for me however because I got yelled at. Oh well...no biggie :P
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got done posting in every blog that I have...I have a few more things to enter into this one...but that will be in the next post...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Somebody knows something. I dont know what. Its probably nothing. But they wont tell me what it is...and I want to know really bad. It has something to do with school though. And they say if I know my life will change...which might not be so good...whatever it is...I dont know if I want to know anymore
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Last Thursday Jadie left to go visit her sister in Boston. Not only that...but she was going to be gone until a week from the next saturday!!! That is roughly 10 days without Jadie. I miss her so much and cant wait for her to be back. Its not like I am really obsessed with Jadie, but without her here my life seems kind of boring. I have nobody's house to practically live at anymore. No person to beat-up ;) . Man...now I'm sad...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember how I ran into someone with my nice  urlLink blue car ? Well my dad found some parts for it and fixed it. It then had a red bumper, and then my dad found some touch up car ready spray paint stuff so now the bumper looks newer than the car. But it all works out.  My dad took  urlLink his truck  in today to get fixed so I had to drive  urlLink my Sundance  to school. Wiht 185,000 miles of stop and go driving...the tranny on this car was pretty banged up. So sadly enough it couldn't even get me to school. I had to call my grandpa today to get a ride to school.  Lucky for my my dad gets his truck back tonight so I can drive my car around...yay!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      On Saterday  urlLink Chad , Justin,  urlLink Zach , and  urlLink I  had a Quiz Bowl Competition in Bishop Garrigan. Humboldt brought 3 teams other than ours. There was a team of seniors that think they are the shiznet...and then two teams comprised mostly of newbies.  A quizbowl has:    -20 questions where you just slap in and answer. (10 pts each)    -10 "bonus" questions where if you answer right you get a bonus question (10 pts & 25 pts for bonus)    -Lightning round where you have a minute to answer 10 questions on a set topic. (100 pts total (10 pts each)  Our team chose  urlLink Chad  as the captain since he knows the most about everything and anything and then a little bit more. He is the man when it comes to this kind of stuff. We ended up winning all 4 of our morning rounds.  After a breif lunch we went back to the High School to see what we were seeded, if we were seeded, for the final tournament. We were seeded 5th and our Senoir team was seeded 12th...Since there were only 16 teams in a bracket...do the math...we had to play our super cocky, super brainy, senior team.    AHHH! How did you guys do!?!?!   Well to cut right to the chase we got to the lightning round and we got to go last. We were down by 20 pts...so we only had to answer 3 questions right to win. Our topic...**queues funky music** duh duh duh 70s MUSIC!!! Not to fear... urlLink Chad  and Justin know their 70s music and we won.   Our final positioning....4th out of 67 teams   To see the final results of the Preliminary rounds:                 urlLink http://garrigan.unlimitedweb.net/qb/prelim.html  To see the final results of the Play offs:                 urlLink http://garrigan.unlimitedweb.net/qb/playoff.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      On Friday Night our team got beat once again in football. Not only that but the homo's in band began to play 'Taps' (the popular military song to honor dead peoples that gave their services). Our coach went nuts and was about ready to go ape on someone. I didn't care too much. I was standing on the sidelines just minding my own business when coach said JV offense was gonna go in. I was quite happy. But not only did I go in...but my friend Travis went in on Defense. Travis is short and a little husky...but not fat...if thats possible. Me and a few other guys on the sidelines got a 'RUUUUU-DY...RUUUUU-DY' chant going. I had a great time. Although we lost...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad got some parts to fix my car. Well...my dad did I guess, but it is getting fixed none the less. I wonder when it will get done. My Plymouth Sundance just doesn't quite cut it anymore. I am not a huge fan of that car. It is an awesome car in general...just not mine. It has a very bad transmission.  Tammen said that he could have gotten the parts for me dirt cheap, but I guess my dad took time over cost. But whatever...its not quite my call. But I think that I still have to pay for it :S. That makes me a little mad. But once again its not like I am in control of my life...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is Jadie's Birthday.   WHAT DID YOU GET HER!!!   I got her a ring made out of solid brass that was a replica of some sort of midieval times ring called a "love knot". I thought that it was pretty cool. But not as cool as her gift to me on my birthday a few months ago. She got me an awesome book.   Well it sounds like her gift to you was cool...and your gift to her just plain SUCKS!   I also baked her something to take along with her to Boston. She is going to Boston on Thursday, so I will only get to see her for tonight (which she has gay band...which I like...but she is in too many things. But I wont control her life too much....:S). I also get to see her tomorrow...but not at school. She is job shadowing. Tomorrow night will be the last night. She will be gone for about 2 weeks...I think. But Im not quite sure. I miss her so much...and she hasn't even left yet!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well tonight we were supposed to go to Clarion and face the Clarion Cowgirls...er...Cowboys, but there was just a  little bit of a mixup. We got there and there was no team. I thought that I saw the Clarion bus heading for Humboldt...but chose not to say anything. It turns out that Clarion had packed up, and headed to Humboldt thinking that our game was there. Unfortunately  IT WASN'T ! We didn't have any ref's to ref our game when Clarion finally got back...so we just headed home. What a load of crap if you ask me...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I actually got to play Friday night against Spencer. I only played a short amount of time, but still. It was late in the fourth quarter and we were trailing quite a bit. Coach looked around and said...JV "O" you're going in!  I was kinda excited, and kinda not. Ya see they still had their Varsity Defense in. I went in for 3 plays and got pummeled. I have a new found respect for our varsity team...we may not win many games...but we are still pretty tough.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Last Friday I got into a little bit of a fender bender. I was going down a hill that eventually turns into main street, while going down the hill, I noticed that my breaks were acting just a little bit funny. As I turned the corner I saw a car and slammed on my breaks. Nothing happened. I now have a bent up car, with no damage to the opposing vehicle. My whole front bumper is nearly trash. But I dunno yet if it can be fixed or whether or not it has to be replaced. We will see later...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know what the FUCK has gotten into everyone, but lately everyone has been a HUGE dick to me!!!  Sorry....I just had to get that out....  I dont know what the heck everyone thinks, but they think that they can just take me and push me around and whatever. I feel as though I went from being at my most liked state, at the pinnacle of my social ladder (so to speak), and I guess that I just fell off the ladder.... I dont know how to explain it....  Everyone just decided to hate me, I have no classes with any of my friends, so I pretty much keep to myself. The only class that I have with any of my "friends" is band. And I dont even like band anymore. Playing the trumpet is gettin really really REALLY old! Hence me taking upt he guitar. I am also in a few classes that I could probably do without. Like US History with Milewski; why in the blue heck do we have to do a current event every friday? and compare it? EVERY FRIDAY!  My second trimester schedule: 1. Mythology (I sit by pot smokers and drinkers) 2. Math (farely good to me....nobody I really hate) 3. Language 10 B (I sit next to a kid who failed last year, and by about 3 ppl I really hate) (Lunch) 4. Spanish 2 (nobody I hate....Cassie is nice to me at least) 5. Band (already talked about it) 6. U.S. History (I dont like this class....too many pot smokers) 7. Chemistry (pretty good class...makes me think and I like the class I guess)  There you have it. My very boring month in a nutshell....  P.S. -- My depression is going away too...for a while
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well remember how I was complaining about how everything that I do, someone is better than me or someone has already done it? Well here is the jig. I felt pretty cool seeing how I was just starting to learn the guitar, but someone already knows how. Dan, but oh well...no biggie. I'm not going to quit.  But the bad things are the set backs that I have to face: 1. Nobody to teach me 2. The difficulty of learning to play correctly 3. Time 4. Pressure 5. (last but not least) the fact that Im a frickin complainer...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The opitamy of my hate....PuNkS...Too Bad. I think that in the next year I will be making a slow transformation into a pUnK!  I dont know why, but in the last couple of days I have been listening to a ton of PuNk music. Especially NFG (New Found Glory). Ya never know. Maybe pUnK wont be so bad.  Ya never know. I will be a HUGE rock star, it will be there....give me a year. It will be there...you just wait and see
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so I have been practicing my guitar for about 3 or 4 days now...I'm not terrible, but I'm definately not good. In those four days I have put about 8 hours of work, and I now know almost all of the notes on the entire guitar. Now I have been practicing pretty hard from what it seems like to me, and today I went over to Jadie's house. She picks up the guitar and my lesson book and learns everything that I know in about 15 minutes!  I was soooooooo pissed off! I couldn't believe it. I put in so much work into everything that I do, and no matter what it is, Jadie is better. I think the only that I can do better than Jadie is...I dont know...honestly. She is better than me at everything. This past year she got better grades than me! I couldn't believe it! I felt like the arm-pit of the world. I felt like everyone was looking at me thinking:   What a retard! He couldn't even get better grades than his girlfriend...AND HE WAS IN TAG HIS WHOLE LIFE!!!   I work hard, and get crap; story of my life. I hate it! I hate every second of it! I tell you if I was good at something I would probably keep it a secret. That way someone wouldn't find out and then become better than me.  I seriously think that something is wrong with me. Perhaps I have social anxiety disorder, mixed in with a little depression, and a lot of stress...hmmm...Maybe I'm just not fit for the outside world....maybe...  I hate my life!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today has sucked from the beginning. I dont quite know what it was, but it just wasn't good.  I woke up at 7:50 and showered then went to school as usual. Today we had ITEDs (Iowa Tests of Educational Development). I did those with no real troubles. After that I went to Chemistry and did some of that stuff....nothing fun. Then Cellular Biology. Oh maybe that is where it all began.  This class was one of my favorites at the beginning of the year, I mean I had and A (and roughly still do). But I had to job shadow and I guess we have a test on something like Cellular Respiratory summin er another.... But I wasn't there for the notes and I dont have barely any of them. It kinda makes me mad...but nothing too bad. It wasn't until about 2 days ago that I realized that I didn't know anything. Some of the pot-heads in my class know more about this shit than I do. We played Jeopardy, and I didnt know anything. After answering 2 questions incorrectly everyone looked at me and said you are so stupid and all this stuff....so I just blurted out "I DONT GIVE A SHIT....JUST SHUT UP!!!"  Then everyone was like...JEEZ SPAZ! And thats about it...I got pissed off and just left the class for a while. Then there was lunch and I went and sat with Jadie, and all her whiney friends (especially Emilee) were complaining as usual. I just said, "WHY DO YOU COMPLAIN SO MUCH!!! ITS SO ANNOYING!!!"  Then in STAG (student teacher advisory group) I was reading the Bible and I had on some reading glasses. First I got asked about my glasses....and then someone asked me why I would read the Bible...I about went nuts again...(and yes it was Emilee once again that pissed me off)  Band was no fun cuz I'm so bad at the trumpet....and I dont really want to keep playing...cuz well...I'm bad. And then when my All-Pro gaywad sister sits behind me its not that great!   Footnote : I have lived in my sister's shadow all my life. Every class I have my teachers are all like...'Oh I hope you are just like your sister!!!' I just do my own thing (I'm averaged...unlike my know-it-all sister). Teachers act all disappointed with me like...oh...thats too bad...you could do so much better...I'm just like...nope. I even had one teacher tell me...'Its too bad that you aren't anything like your sister....she is so great!'  After school I had a basketball and a football meeting. Our Varsity coach said that the freshmen would be getting upgraded to Varsity...and I think that is so stupid...but Im not the coach so whatever. Then After all that mumbo-jumbo I went to Jadie's and had a great time watching her do homework....then I got bored so I went at watched TV....Nothing good on...so Jadie comes in and is trying to cheer me up or summin and like rough-hosue with me...needless to say the day I had made me pretty pissed off...there fore rough-housing = NO! And I left later in a nice display of asshole-ness...not a good day....not only did I practically go nuts in a few of my classes...but Jadie probably is beginnning to realize that I am not that great of a boyfriend...I think I am having another phase of depression...not cool.  Oh yeah...when I got home my mom yelled at me for getting a D in school. She expects me to be just like my sister...but I told her the more she rags on me and tries to force me to be like Anne (my sister) the more I am going to be NOT like her. Which means that I am gonna just pretty much just gonna....grrr....  Who the hell do you all think you are anyways!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I decided to check out a Bible from my school library. Not like I didn't have one...its just that I like to read different versions of the Bible to get the whole story....so...you do the math  Anyways, our creepy media center lady person, Mrs. "K" showed me where I could get one....then I asked, "Can I check one out?" Then she replied with the most degrating remark ever to come out of someone mouth intended to hurt me... she said, "Well of course...with as much as you need it, how could I say no?"  I about went nuts... I was going to make some reference to the amount of drug dealer dirt balls in my school....but didn't want any of them to over hear, then shoot me in the parkin lot after school...  Story of my life...never getting respect....
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Stacy, can i come over after school? We can hang around by the pool Did your mom get back from her business trip? Is she there, or is she trying to give me the slip?   Man I wanted  urlLink that CD  soooo bad, but that wasn't to be tonight...   urlLink Chad  and I went to Fort Dodge tonight and drove around. We hit up  urlLink Target , then  urlLink Wal-Mart , looking for my CD. Realizing that neither of them had it, we decided to go to the dreaded prices of  urlLink FYE ! I found the CD for a treturous price of $18.99. I wasn't about to pay no frickin 19 bucks for a CD. Thats just insane. Instead I went to  urlLink GNC  and got some  urlLink YJ Stinger . I have now had  urlLink Pounding Punch  and  urlLink Sinful Citrus .  So instead of that, Chad and I went out to eat at  urlLink KFC . Needless to say I ate WAY TOO MUCH. But thats just me :P After taht we went to  urlLink Hy-Vee  and Chad bought a papaya, a mango, some apple juice, and some odd vegan chocolate chunk baker's cookie. Quite a combo. I ended up buying a chick-o-stick and some dried bananas.  We went back and went to  urlLink Rachel's  house. While there we shared the mango, papaya, and banana thingers. I didnt like the banana things that much, the papaya wasn't that good either. The mango was pretty dang good...but it wasnt ripe.  Nothing else too great tonight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN!   Quite simple really...nowhere. Nothing good to blog about. But I guess I can blog. Job shadowed Wednesday. Great fun. I think my job shadow was one of the the best! I played some fooz-ball, ping pong, and even had time to go out to eat!  Friday we won our last game of the season. I dunno why we did so bad at the beginning of the year...we lost a lot of our games by just a couple of points.  Hmmm....what else?   What about your guitar???   Oh yeah! I am just starting to learn the acoustic guitar. And hopefully by the time I am a senoir I will be good enough to form a band. I dont know if I will be any good...or if I will be ready by then. Heck I dont even know if I am any good at the thing...I'm doing some very basic things. Dont know any chords really yet. Just dinkin around. Yeah...if I get good, I have a band in mind....  **smirks**  Only time will tell
     
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry everyone to make a holiday mess, but my IP address has changed today....BAH HUMBUG!!!!  now its  urlLink http://64.71.88.201 . once again sorry for the troubles....  Happy holidays everyone!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently purchased the first  urlLink Lord of the Rings  movie:  urlLink The Lord of the Rings - The Fellowship of the Ring . I didn't think I would like it, but I bought it anyways. I loved it so much that a little over a week later I went out and bought the second Lord of the Rings movie:  urlLink The Lord of the Rings - The Two Towers (Special Extended Edition) . And now I sit here waiting for 8 days until the third Lord of the Rings movie:  urlLink The Lord of the Rings - The Return of the King  comes out! I hope it wins some Oscars :) and I hope it puts a GOOD end to the trilogy!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey its been a long time since I have posted in any of my 3 blogs, however I have been entertained by some of  urlLink Chad's Latest Blogs . Quite comical what the genius can find on the internet....Chad seriously is a freak show....  Nothing much to talk about. I am borrowing Brian Gorman's (my sister's boyfriend) electric guitar now. My band, well...not  MY BAND  but the band that I am in, is comprised of Jake Short, Tom Hanrahan, Dan Blair, and I. I dont know if we will be any good, but we are all pretty good players by ourselves :) so you never know....  No name yet for the band by the way....  Nice bloggin fer ya....adios!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With the astonishing and amazing 1 year anniversary with Jadie knocking on my back door, I have had a lot of time to think of how lucky I am. Also I have had a lot of time to think of what to get Jadie...   What have you decided to get her?   Well nothing too great. I dont have a dang thing picked out for her that I know she will like. That is the bad thing about having our anniversary so close to Christmas, that I run out of ideas on crap to get her. I could go for the normal (stuffed animals, chocolate, flowers) but where would that leave Valentines day?  Ya know what material objects are no where near as good as memories. I will give Jadie the best thing that anyone could ever get. A night to remember forever.  And if you are using your perverted mind...then SHAME ON YOU!!! I wouldn't do that.... :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am now a novice in SQL!  urlLink Chad  was nice enough to teach me some :-). I cant wait til I get good enough at it to quit looking at the commands every 10 seconds. Now to finish learning php, and start learning CSS. Boy coding is fun. Even though I am nothing great.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now I see why this movie was not rated a 4 star classic. It was lacking something. I just cant quite tell what it is...I cant put my finger on it.  Ironically I saw  urlLink Chad  at the movie too. He was waiting for Ben, and couldn't find him so he sat by us (Jadie and I) to waste time.  Then Ben came, so they sat a row behind us.  What would have made this movie awesome would be if our movie theater had lazyboys in it :-) But on the plus side I did have my  urlLink Junior Mints  with me. I love  urlLink Junior Mints .
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today at 2 I will be traveling to the Humota Theatre to view the final installment of the Lord of the Rings Trilogy. I heard mixed reviews. Some people said that the movie was nothing compared to the book, and some said vise versa. I think....no....I know I will LOVE it!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is the scoop. I have been looking at many and many different websites around. I have realized that my website doesn't have jack crap on it! Also I have realized that my site looks like crap. I is way too bland, So look for a site remodeling here pretty soon. I will be trying to study some basic commands in something other than html (something easy too probably CSS if  urlLink Chad  will teach me).  If I do get around to editing my website it will probably be the same until about spring or later febuaryish. I dont know quite yet. Maybe I wont change it... I need to change some things on it a little first. The directory is terrible on it.  We will see...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Justin,  urlLink Zach ,  urlLink Chad , and I went to a quiz bowl today and ended up getting 4th out of about 25 teams or so. Once again we defeated our Senior rivals from Humboldt...except this time it was more indirect than direct. They didn't even place. But who is to complain.  Today I also saw American Wedding. Nothing too great, but it was a nice way to pass the time with  urlLink Chad  and  urlLink Rachel . Sorry for not posting.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay...I experimented with my own blog a few times...and it sucked MAJORLY! So I'm back once again to good old  urlLink Blogger.com . I actually miss this. My other blog was SOOO dull. All black and white...But I just came back to say I will be here. And I'm here to stay (unless I make a fantasitc blog with the help of  urlLink Chad .)  I love this site :)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My blog has moved to my ip site.  if you wold like to view it go to  urlLink http://www.geocities.com/pedrofromhum   click on the link there to my IP site  then go to my blog
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No its not about my blog. Its about  urlLink Chad's  Blog named  urlLink Waffles of Thought . It is a must see. He has beefed up his blogging experience with a barrage of pictures. Very nice going Chad!  Before you leave. Dont forget to SAY IT and comment on the blog entries!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight Tom, Jake, and I played our church songs with Steve our youth pastor. It was so awesome. Steve leads the way with a pretty loud and awesome acoustic guitar. I come in with an electric kinda just for background and to jazz it up a little. Tom keeps the beat with the bass. Then Shorty (Jake's nickname is Shorty) Pounds away SUPER LOUD with the drums.  After we were done liberating people with our rock, we went trough our wednesday night Crossfire sermon and etc. Then when that was all done Dan joined us and we practiced some more church songs. And dont get me wrong...most of your normal church songs are dull, but these ROCK! They are so up tempo, and I'm not that good when it comes to F and B chords...but its awesome!  After we were done with that, Jake and Tom and Dan and I (our band called Active Input) practiced our song called "In this Diary" by  urlLink The Ataris . Tom kinda likes it...but he thinks the bass part is too dull. So he wants to put his own bass part into it. I think he should do it!  Now Tom and I rock out major. I think we are the hardest rockers of our band. And now we have bloody fingers. Maybe Jake is though too...he broke his 2 brand new drumsticks today :) It was AWESOME. We were playing and then all the sudden no drums. Jakes stick busted into 4 pieces....so he used it anyways...and then he broke his other stick. So we stopped. About 3 and a half hours of pure playing!  Im pooped and I have a major headache. I cant wait til this summer. Active Input will rock the town of Humboldt with a passion!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After nearly getting dumped 234523049560239470592349520927530937 times this weekend...I am finally cool with my girlfriend (for the most part). I am very very very happy and I hope that she will love me once again. But anyways...  After a breif talk to her I realized that what I am most like in life is a love-sick puppy :)  Is there anything wrong with that....NO!  =D
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went to Fort Dodge with Hannah. We dropped off some of her film then drove to random places...then I locked my keys in my car in the Hy-Vee parking lot :)  It was quite funny. So we went back to Wal-Mart to pick up her film...then went to see if my mom was in Fort Dodge with my spare key yet. She wasn't so we waited for a while on my car and then my mom came. After that we went to Wendy's and had an awesome talk.  I know now that no matter what happens, Hannah will be a GREAT friend. She will always be there for me. She will never betray me. I talked to her for an hour or so (from Wendy's all the way home, then in my driveway) about my dwindling relationship. She helped me out a lot. She made me feel really good despite knowing that my girlfriend doesn't love me as much as she loves another guy. She confirmed many things that I was scared about...but she also made me feel good because I knew she had been through this before as well.  She is so awesome. I love everything about Hannah. She is a great friend :)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Trey's SUV died, so I had to help jumper cable it. Travis and Mitchell came up in Mitchell's truck so I hooked my jumper cables up to Mitchell's truck and onto Trey's SUV. Easy as pie. After about 1 or 2 min of charging...VROOM! We were good to go.   I like how  urlLink Chad  watched. It was funny. It looked like he thought we were gonna blow something up or summin like that...Oh well :)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I came home sick. I woke up and didn't feel good. I really did not want to get out of bed. It is the very first day of the 3rd and final trimester so I figured I should go. So I did. I took a shower but threw up while in it, but I still felt like I should go. So I did.  I felt pretty good for the most of the day. I even had enough energy to play a little bit of basketball, although I really messed up my back while simply bending over to pick up a ball. My back still kills and I need to go lay down.  While at lunch I felt really tired, almost like dizzy. I thought I was going to pass out, and now I am here. At my home. Hooray for me...NOT! Well anyways. Thats the story morning glory.  Peace!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here. I entered these in my other data base on my website...but now it is now more!   Hairy Situation 2004-02-04, 06:03:34 PM  Today while eating a salad from the salad bar, I found a nasty, 10" long hair in my salad. First, I about puked. Then I decided, this is stupid...this is at least the third hair I have found in my food here. So I went to the lunch ladies and started to complain. They didn't care. So I yelled to everyone sitting near me to boycott the salad bar.  How fricking nasty!     New Where's George Link 2004-02-02, 10:32:46 PM  I just made a new Where's George link on my site. It will show all of the neat bills I have found. It can catergorize them by denomination, serial number, or federal reserve bank. It will show a picture of the front and back of the bill. Please go back to my homepage and check it out. It took me over 2 hours to do!     Snow Day 2004-02-02, 07:11:56 PM  Today at about 6 A.M. my dad came into my room with my dog and siad, "School is going to be two hours late." I smiled and went back to sleep...but not before I yelled at my stupid dog for chewing up something in my room. (I still dont know what she was chewing on)  Then I woke up at 11 o'clock and thought to myself, uh oh! I missed school! Then I heard my sister downstairs so I just figured what the heck, maybe there is no school today. Low and behold...no school. I went out to eat with my aunt from Kansas, my grandparents, my dad, and my sister. After that I attempted to go to Jadie's. Well, I got stuck in the 2' of snow in my driveway. I had to shovel my way out. Not cool.  I watched some movies at Jadie's then came home. And now that it is still snowing, I would probably bet on a two hour late start tomorrow. Or at least I hope so. I really dont want school, but I will take whatever I can get!     Snow 2004-02-01, 11:08:54 PM  Today it started to snow at about 3:00 P.M. It has been a slow sustained downpour of snow for around 5 horus or so...I hope that school is canceled tomorrow. Or at least I hope that it is delayed. Fort Dodge has already delayed their school 2 horus. I bet, if anything, we will get a two hour late start. Jadie really doesn't want to cancel school, she doesn't like to make up days, but I really dont care. I hope school is cancelled. I can go rent or buy a movie and watch it at Jadie's house.  Just in case you are new to my blog, Jadie is my girlfriend.     Patriots Win 2004-02-01, 10:14:55 PM  Once again my ritual has not failed me. I played guitar most of the time tonight, I even watched a little of the game...but most of the time I was playing guitar. After a while I got bored and played some basketball with Jordan, Sam B., and Tom B. We played 2 on 2 at first but then switched to the game of 21. I won of course.  But Peter, what about the commercials!?!  I did see a few commercials. Not too many. My favorite ones were the AOL 9.0 Optimized commercials. They hooked up the modem thing and their car/motorcycle took off like a bat out of...yeah. My other favorite commercial was the Pepsi commercial with Jimi Hendrix. Jimi was walking down the street. To his left was a a href="http://www.pepsi.com/home.php">Pepsi machine. To his right was a Coca-Cola machine. He chose the Pepsi and when he looked up, behind the Pepsi machine was a guitar shop. Then he looked across the street and behind the Coca-Cola machine there was an accordian shop.  Pretty good ending to a pretty good game. I really wanted the Panthers to win, but I figured that the Patriots would win. And the Patriots, of course, did win the Super Bowl in case you have your head in the sand. Congratulations to all of the Patriots, even though I dont like half of you guys. :P     Super Bowl Party 2004-02-01, 05:05:10 PM  There is a Super Bowl Party at my church. It is going to be awesome. Jadie is coming with me. Shorty, Tom and I are all going to rock out big time and learn to play some songs hopefully today.  As for the Super Bowl end of the party...I dont care a whole lot. I will probably just watch the last couple minutes of the game. Not like the game is going to be anything great. Its just the Patriots and the Panthers. Nothing too cool. If I had to bet money on the game, I would say the Patriots would win by 10 points. But I dont know, sometimes the NFC teams can be tough. Oh who am I kidding this game is going to SUCK!     Doing Just Fine 2004-02-01, 04:42:46 PM  After a very very scary moment in our relationship, Jadie and I are alright :) At least I think that we are all right.  Yesterday I bought Jadie some roses at Floral Creations in downtown Humboldt. They weren't exactly cheap...but I thought they were worth it. Especially since they were for Jadie :)  Today I went to the Country Club with her and sat there patiently while she ate. Then we came home and I ate some breakfast. I hope that we are fine. I dont see any signs of hostility anymore.  One more thing. Chad Boyce...Im very sorry for everything.     My New Blog 2004-01-26, 09:41:20 PM  Hello everyone and welcome to my brand new blog. I have been taught by Chad how to use my SQL with my PHP and when you throw them all into a can this is what you get. A very novice version of a blog. Made completely by me! I wonder if this will even work. Technically this is my test entry, but I will use it as my other entry too :) Thank heavens for Chad because even though I konw what I am doing, I still ask him a ton of questions every night. Thanks, Chad.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I am going to have Andrew P.,  Zach L., and Russ B. over. Russ and I are stupid...put simply :)  Andrew and Zach are nerds. Put bluntly and kinda mean ;)  The whole point of this is to pretty much discuss how badly I am going to fail the upcoming chemistry test...but oh well. Im over it. Only about 20 more days of school left. That equals out to ALMOST a month  Not too shabby whe you think of it.  P.S. If anyone else wants to come out...just call here first... I think we are starting at about 7:00-7:30...Russ said he might bring some pizza...and if he doesn't...I have frozen pizza :)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going to be open here and hopefully my inbox isn't filled with ppl say BLAH BLAH BLAH....but  WHAT SONG SHOULD OUR BAND SING!?!?  restrictions: -no country -no rap -no preppy boy/girl bands -probably gotta be punk somewhat -something kinda popular -nothing explicit about drugs sex etc  email me at  --   urlLink peter.stockdale@gmail.com  title the subject  song suggestion  please. and dont write me a novel.  give me band name, song, album (not necessary), and a couple notes about the song if you want....thanks a TON for your help! :)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is an awesome website (made the easy way [by templates]) about our crossfire group its at:   urlLink http://www.icrossfire.com   Steve (my youth pastor) is making it. Way to go Steve-o!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cant believe it. It seems like my life has been consumed by track. 3 track meets this week, and 2 every other week. Its terrible, I only have 2 days to myself it seems like, monday and thursday. Wednesday is band practice. Active Input and I jam out and stuff at the church. Its quite awesome :)  Just frusterated..thats all!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The pre-prom gig was pretty cool. At least we got our name known a little bit. Every thing went great, but the song we sang was a little hard for Dan to pull of...so that was tretcherous...  I nailed my solo, I couldn't hear anything wrong except the singing a little bit...  All in all good deal :)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      8:30 ... tomorrow ... R.W. Carleson Auditorium ... be there or be square!!! Yeah thats right. Our very first gig is tomorrow !!!! Isnt that awesome? We are the opening act for preprom!!! I hope we rock the joint. I know of a lot of people that want me to fail terribly...but there are even more that want me to do great. I dunno some people are just bitter. But thats their problem. When I bust out my solo on our song, yeah you aren't going to want to even talk to me. Ill be too cool for you!!!  *LOL*  Not quite, but whatever. Our band kicks butt. I hope that somebody that matters hears us kick some major butt!!! Then we can get another gig to practice for :)  Also, thanks to Kyle S. and Brian G. for helping us in the sound area! :)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow Active input is gonna rock the house :)  At about 7:15 we are going to play and do that sorta stuff. Kinda like a rehersal to make sure our content isn't explicit and all that jazz. Hopefully we wont get ripped too much by Cindy and Abi :S....we will see  Only time will tell
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I went to soundsations. Usually it is a great time where some bands get together and play some music...but NOOOOOOOOOOOO...there are no bands in our high school anymore. Before this year, there were 3. Now all are defunct. Our band wasn't ready when auditions came so we scrapped that idea.  I would have to say...overall. A waste of a perfectly good dollar.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't want to have track today. Luckily it rained and poured all day until about 230-3 or so...So there was no track meet in Webster City.  ARG!!! Now the Bad News Bears....we had to run hills. We ran the hill out by sumner ave. It was deadly. For someone like me..who is only in tip top physical condition during late summer into the winter months (football :) :P ) it was hell....pardon the french. We ran the hill 12 times...not much? Well you go out and run it without getting winded...then we will throw a parade for you...  word life...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night Active Input practiced...minus Dan. What a bum...his parents are very strict. Jake, Tom and I got up there at about 8:40ish or so...Then we played for an hour or so. Jake has his part down simple. Tom just looked at the music for the first time Sunday, but he is a fantastic bassist (bass guitar player-ist). He has his part almost to perfection. I know my part great with all the little lead parts trown in there and everything. I got the solo down pat.  All I need now, is to find something to wear. I think that I will ask Gorman (my sisters boy toy) to wear. He is a fashon guru...but not one of them feminine ones. Anywho... I need something to wear...then I need to sound check the auditorium. Need to get Dan to learn his part, and TUNE SHORTY'S DRUMS!!! That bothers me...his drums are awesome...just out of tune.  We need Dan there today though. We are practicing again, and he was sick from school...He is our lead vocals...he also plays a pretty impoortant part after the solo...  We will see what happens...  P.S. Adam Moritz said he might come out tonight and play a little with us. He is just starting to play guitar! That will be cool!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today sucked track wise. Cody and I both pretty much sucked... I threw a 40' then after that a 34' ... my best for the meet... 40' 1.25" Cody threw maybe a 42' 6" or summin...but It wasn't that good  Our team got 4th overall. Not too shabby since we got last every meet last year... :) Thats about it...  Oh yeah, I lost my Humboldt Volleyball T-shirt today... I must have left it out in the locker room when we left for the meet...so phooey...that was one of my favorite shirts too :(
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went golfing with Jadie at the Humboldt Country Club. I only hit a few balls. I really really suck...its not even funny. Jadie isn't half bad ... actually she is pretty good for only golfing a little.  After golfing for a couple hours we went back to her house and ate a little...then went back to my house and hit golf balls into the field. It was great. I am an animal :)....I love to hit balls into fields when nobody is looking and all that jazz...then I can swing as hard as I want :)  As for a title now...I dont know if we have one...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Jadie and I got into another arguement on msn...go figure...  We founght about everything but religion this time...and the worst part she said she really didn't want to go out with me...but didn't want to dump me cuz she just couldn't. She did say that she knew we had to break up...and I didn't want these stupid games anymore.  They had been going on for 3 months or more, and I hated it. Its been tearing me apart horribly...and frankly, mentally I feel drained. I need to go on a long overdue vacation away from everyone I know. Maybe I will go to Wyoming with my father this weekend...  Anyways...I decided to break up with Jadie. I said I was tired of the games and hated her for playing them on me constantly so I said I would see her later...much later. She didn't get it. So I said we were done...and she got offline. So I called her. She just cried the whole time...So I hung up. Then my dad came in (Mr. Sensative and buzzed on beer) tried to cheer me up only the way a half drunk father can. So I got pissed off and went to Jadies going almost 90 mph on the gravel road...  I sat outside her house for 40 minutes before she noticed my car. She sat inside for a while then decided to come out and talk. She rested her head on my shoulder. And I kissed her forehead. I tried to find the words...but none came...I couldn't believe that I had just dumped Jadie. She is the light of my life...and I dont think that I could be in a right and proper state of mind without her...  I think we are starting to be okay...kinda...I dunno. Im terribly confused. I think she doesn't want me to go...because she knows if we are totally done....then Im not going to have anything to do with her...simply because she has hurt me really bad. But she says she is living a lie by going out with me...  I love her terribly. And I really want her to be happy... I dont know what to do. We seemed okay when we were watching Patriot with her parents...but as I left I sensed some hostility...I dont quite know...  I have had many people ask me if I loved her...are they stupid? Of course I love her! If I didnt' it wouldn't be this hard to let her go...think if you hadn't eatin in days....you have a glass of milk and a slice of pizza...now throw that away...thats like me...okay...and if you dont like my analogy then F*CK OFF!!!  All I have left to say is:  Se amo Jadie siempre....   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most of my pictures are up on  urlLink my website .  Click to go to my IP site....then follow the links til you get  to my pictures ...  enjoy!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I knew a girl once from Texas named Hannah. I didn't know her that well. I stumbled across her one day while in a chatroom I think...then suddenly she disappeared...and today she re-appeared after almost 1 year...  I was pretty psyched :)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im going to  try  to paraphrase this...but it probably wont happen.Oddly enough this is the second bomb threat in the last 2-3 years... :) anyways...on we go!!  Also note these blogs that have stuff about the bomb threat: Chad Brandos >  urlLink Waffles of Thought  Zach Loder >  urlLink Trekkies Have No Sanctuary  Sarah Freund >  urlLink crayZchicken2003    1:14 P.M. 5th Period: Band room --   Im sitting there trying to keep my sanity with some lame excuse for music... wait...dont you think that is a little harsh??? ... FINE! The music is okay, just we play it over and over again. Point being...Im ready to leave. Im jonesing to get out of the dang school. Im dreading to take a test 7th period in Spanish II because I already failed the chemistry test a couple days ago with a cool 59%...anyways...Im sidebarring. Then over the intercom, the coolest of the secretaries, Billie, says, "Teachers please evacuate your students to the softball or baseball diamonds immediately!" I think Ms. Feekes thought it was a joke...but did as she was instructed.   1:30 P.M. 6th Period: New softball diamond --  Maybe getting out of school was kind of cool, but why the heck were we outside!!! I was snooping around listening to the teachers talk and Mr. Johnson (who is very non-chalant) says, "Hey hey hey...bomb threat!" So the word spread quicker than a hookers....nevermind....anyways   1:45 P.M. 6th Period: New softball diamond --  Once again Im in the same spot. I look out into the parking lot. I think there were 3 or 4 cop cars. Oh our donut patrol members are so smart...NOT! The one guy (not gonna say a name) looked like he was half drunk....stuttering to someone on a cell phone he borrowed, "Uh...yeah...we got them out of the school...and...uhhmmm...there...uh...so far its good...nothing big...there was a bomb threat...uh..." I was just like WHAT THE HECK! This is STUPID...so I went and sat by some of my friends, Tom, Shorty, Beth, Megan, and some other people that are just too numerous to mention. Bored our of our minds Dan and I tried to color my hair with a window marker (ya know...the ones they use for homecoming on everyones windows)  Did it work???  Sure I guess...   2:00 P.M. 6th Period: Walking from place to place --  I got bored, so I decided to walk to the football field. None of us were allowed to leave...and my keys, billfold, books were in the school...so I took a little walk. I talked to cooper and her gang of friends. Then went and talk to Fischer and his friends. Then went and talked to Lexi and her friends (kinda talked...more like felt out of place...didn't say anything so I left) I went over to the baseball field next and there were all the juniors that are funny as crap. They somehow got ahold of a permanent marker and wrote "Survivor of the Bomb Threat '04" etc. etc.  Then Randy Krecklow whistles and tries to get our attention...I thought we were going back into the school...which I didn't want to do. Some people heard him some didn't. So all the teachers are whistling loudly to get everyones attention. Mr. Orr (one of the funniest teachers) whistles rather softly, because he cant whistle that loud, and says, "come on folks" Mr. Orr...quite entertaining :)   2:10 P.M. 6th Period: Walking to the Church --  It just so happened that we weren't going to the school again...we were going across the highway (that the police had blocked off) to Our Saviors Lutheran Church. There we would be a safe distance from the stupid high school. We sat inside until a table got broke, then we went outside. Todd (our stupid and slightly bald Vice Principal) Havel was trying to announce that there was going to be a bomb dog on its way from over 2 hours away. **GROAN!!** So that meant that our car keys were in the school, our car keys were going to stay in the school and there was no way were were going to get them out of the school. Oh well..,  My sister showed up at about 2:50 and took me home. She was on a school art show (just like  urlLink Chad ) and just showed up with everything being new to her. The stupid dog hadn't come yet...so we went home. Then my mom gave me some spare keys and took me to get my car. I went up to the church after that at about 5:30 P.M. and saw that the school was open. the bomb threat was over!!!  BIG FRICKING DEAL!!   Now I look back the waste of a day and wonder how classes are going to go over tomorrow...or who the dillhole was that called in the stupid threat. I highly suggest you read these blogs to get other peoples points of view on the topic...  Chad Brandos >  urlLink Waffles of Thought  Zach Loder >  urlLink Trekkies Have No Sanctuary  Sarah Freund >  urlLink crayZchicken2003 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zach you smoke the cheeba....Chem test wasn't hard.....  BUT IT SURE WASN'T EASY!!!   Im the pot smoker who thought molarity = grams / Liters  where as the way the got of chemistly (aka Holste) teaches it that molarity = mol / L  who is right???  NEVER CHALLENGE THE GOD OF CHEMISTRY ...  There is another C test grade in the bank... I also saw my Chemistry test grade go from an A- 2 weeks ago to a hearty B- today.... :( Chem is poopy  ( urlLink to read Zach's Post go here )
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad is going on another stupid power trip. He wants to get rid of everything made of metal that he doesnt want. And his delegated assistant??? ME! Woot, woot....  Today I hauled a coal auger up from our basement.  Hard?  Not really... It is just long...laboreous work. Takes time...i guess you could call it  urlLink Tedious  work...but whatever...ya know???  anyways.. Enough bickering. I gotta go practice guitar!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uhmmmm...I dont really want to say it all. Simply put,  urlLink Chad  and I almost got kicked out of Younkers for taking pictures!  For full details go to  urlLink Chad's  site:  urlLink http://blog.chadbrandos.com/archives/2004/04/04/younkers-sucks/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good news to all of those who read this daily...I DIDN'T GET FOOLED!  Thats all for this post
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many sites are sporting April fools day jokes. Here are a few of them (notice you wont be able to see them unless its April 1st)   urlLink Where's George  - Has George Bush instead of George Washington in the header   urlLink Slashdot  - (Chad told me about this one) All Fake Posts   urlLink Think Geek  - (Chad told me about this one) All fake items for sale on the frontpage
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So far this day hasn't been that bad. Nothing has gone bad and nobody has tried to pull one on me. Maybe later (if someone pulls a fast one on me) I will re-blog tonight and report about it...  Until then...Shalom
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Much like  urlLink Zach , I have new aquierd photoblogging! It is quite simple...NOT. I have had to try to figure it out for about 20 min and I think I might have it now. Here is my test   urlLink    This is one of the many guitars that I want!  However...after further testing, I think that the pictures that you want to put online have to be in the jpg format... That kinda sucks.  urlLink Zach  if you find out if they dont have to be in this form, please contact me.  And one more thing, how can I view all of the pictures in my database that I upload? This is actually kind of confusing. I'd almost rather use  urlLink PhotoBucket.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got the new  urlLink New Found Glory   CD , "Catalyst". I was a little disappointed, but alas its  urlLink New Found Glory  and they can do NO WRONG!  I highly recommend this CD just because it is way different than all of their previous ones!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a new computer chair. Granted, I stole it from  urlLink Chad , and its a little broken, but still. I like it a lot :)  Its comfortable and I bet my parents make me get rid of it in like 2 days tops :(  They are so mean to me!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know how many of the readers (yes both of you ;) ) are familiar with the  urlLink Foo Fighters ...but if you are you should listen to the song Everlong. It is quite great. Then when you are done with that...you can DL or find a copy of the the video somewhere or another. It is an absolutely great music video. Tom (my bass player) showed me today. It is awesome!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, not  urlLink the singer ! Me!! Tonight I got bored, so I told Jadie to dye my hair. I didn't know how I wanted to dye it; all over color, tips, highlites. Whatever...I still couldn't decide.  Crunch time...I decided to dye it... ... ... ALL OVER COLOR! BLEACHED WHITE!!!!  However the stuff I used to dye my hair was super super potent. I almost passed out. Just before dying my hair...I hit my head too. So there was a small cut on my head, that felt good with the bleach on it :P  After that I played some game with  urlLink Zach  back to his house to play some video game that I can never remember the name to.  That was the excitement of my night. If my mom doesn't like my hair Im gonna dye it black like  urlLink my idol's  hair!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Chad  is a great guy. Tomorrow is the last day of school and he decided to make cookies for everyone that sits at his lunch table.  urlLink Zach  and I were bored so after playing some video games we went to  urlLink Hy-Vee  to talk to Sam Bendixen...for no aparent reason. After buying some  urlLink Mt. Dew , it was off to  urlLink Chad 's house!! As we went into the parking lot... urlLink Chad  was just walking into  urlLink Hy-Vee . That was when we figured out he was making cookies.  I would compare him to  urlLink Emeril Lagasse   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HELLO EVERYONE!!!!  My latest addition to my guitar learning sequence of the summer has come in the mail. After waiting 14 longs days (even though the suggested shipping was 5-10 days) I have finally recieved my tablature book:   urlLink The Offspring  - " urlLink Americana "  I cant wait to try this out. I have it sitting in my lap...but have yet to try to attempt any of the songs. After I have perfected this I might get a  urlLink New Found Glory  tablature book (if I can find one)   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just thought I would make a post for those of you (probably not many) that like speed motorcycle racing (whatever its called) and also read my blog.  urlLink Chad 's super cool brother-in-law has a website about speed racing and stuff.   urlLink Chad 's brother-in-law,  urlLink Craig , recently got into an accident on his cycle too. The site has mainly just forums...but if that floats your boat then go ahead and check it out!   urlLink Craig 's little group of racers are named IFM - " Iowa Farm Mafia "
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that  urlLink Chad  has become quite a trend setter. I have fonud myself going to more of the same sites he does, and also trying to do some more of the same stuff he does.  It was  urlLink Chad  that told me I should get  urlLink Mozilla Firefox , as opposed to the crappy  urlLink Internet Explorer . (also he told me to experiment with  urlLink Opera  for a while too.  urlLink Opera  is quite nice as well)  But it's not just the software that interests me; the websites he visits are quite cool too. For example:  urlLink Wikipedia . This site uses  urlLink wiki  (which I was not too familiar with until tonight when  urlLink Chad  explained it to me). He was also the very first person to get me involved in  urlLink Where's George . You can use  urlLink Where's George  to track all of your american currency, free of charge.   urlLink Chad  also told me I should start my very own  urlLink blog . He has his  urlLink very own blog  and he uses  urlLink  Home">WordPress  However I use  urlLink Blogger .  Why?  Because Im not spiffy like  urlLink Chad  and I dont have my  urlLink very own domain . I am stuck using an  IP  Address website. But since my  IP  Address changes every now and then, I have to host a site that will link to it at  urlLink Geocities .  urlLink Chad  also showed me this site in 7th grade when I made my very first website (which is not up anymore, but it was terrible!!).  But as you can see,  urlLink Chad  has done quite a bit to influence the lives of millions...or maybe just one... :)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There was a tornado last night in Bradgate, Iowa. Bradgate is north of my house by about 5 miles then west by about 5 more miles. The tornado moved south-southeast and just missed Humboldt by about 2.5 miles. I live on the north edge of town, so I stood outside a little while trying to see it...(the rest of the time I was inside with my radio listening)  I never caught any glimpses of it. I did see a very very dark set of clouds move just north of us. I can almost guarantee the tornado was in it. For about 5 minutes the sky got a puke kinda greenish color, and the storm stopped. I thought the tornado was going to hit...but it never did.  This morning my youth pastor called and a bunch of us went out and helped in Bradgate. You had to park almost 2 miles out of town because of the peope helping. Then the cops shuttled us in on busses. When we went in the town was pretty decent on the east side...but as you moved west, the houses were completely hammered. There were ambulances everywhere, fire trucks from everywhere too. It was amazing how many people where there to help. They even had a correctional facility there from Rockwell City.  As we were shuttled through the town I also happened to notice the Humboldt sherriff's car. This particular car is always parked outside of a house by Jadie's (my girlfriend's) house. The guy is her neighbor. His windows were all busted in and the car had debris all over on the inside of it. The first one to report the tornado was our sherrif. He went to Bradgate in the Sherrif marked SUV. Then the tornado hit and he went into the ditch. A 2x4 hit him in the leg and he called for help. I saw the SUV later that night as I was driving around town. The SUV had no windows, and was terribly crunched up.  Luckily for everyone...not too many injuries. A couple people had stepped on nails and they went through their feet. As a matter of fact; more people have been physically injured while cleaning up the debris than got hurt in the actual tornado itself. However, the emotional hurt must be great...  My church group and I ended up helping out a farm just outside of town a couple miles. After moving trees for a couple hours we left. Our work was done. But on our way home we noticed that there was debris from the houses in Bradgate almost 2-3 miles outside of town...quite amazing!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today while I was carting Zach and Chad around to try to cash in some cans Chad found, I was driving down a through street. That means that all other crossroads have to yield. Somebody (who could kick my ass) didn't quite yield and we almost hit each other...so I honked just in case he didn't see me...  He must not have liked it. He slammed on his breaks and made a HUGE screeching noise. I kept driving (faster of course). His backup lights turned on and he started to go in reverse. I kept speeding up, knowing I was no match for the smoking, beer drinking, bad ass of a man that was pursueing me.  He put it back in drive and tore around the block trying to find us. I freaked out and drove to the local Fareway and walked inside so he couldn't really beat me up without causing a  HUGE  scene. I didn't see or hear from him the rest of the night.  Now for the real test. I see him in the halls tomorrow once or twice by just casual walking by...I dont know if he knew it was me, but we will see. If he does then there is going to be a rumble tomorrow. And I dont fight much and dont like to fight too much...so Im either gonna get laid out or summin.  We will see if maybe he killed enough brain cells last night smoking dope or not to remember the confrontation that we had. I will blog later about this (maybe saturday).  I have a track meet tomorrow, its gonna be a BIG ONE. Conference meet!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cant believe how dull today was. Actually, it wasn't dull at all... I was quite pissed off most of the day. First, my dad came in and said there was a 2 hour delay for school due to bad weather (fog). That was the one good thing about today. P.E. always makes me mad just cuz its unfair. Coach Ras is a moron and I greatly dislike her. She is biased towards her volleyball players and the people who kiss her butt 24/7 ( a.k.a.  people who drink everyweekend)  Fifth period, I go in to realize I had left my trumpet out the day before. Could people leave my stuff alone...OF COURSE NOT. WHY THE FUCK SHOULD THEY!!! Jeez my stuff was all over the place. All my music had been stolen. My valve oil was stolen, and even my mute had its last cork busted a little. People just tend to piss me off. That means that at the pep assembly I didn't play. I was too pissed about my trumpet. Instead I shouted insults at everyone (cheerleaders who are mostly kinda skaggy, and then a few teachers here or there). I was pretty much asking for it the whole day.  Today I just wanted to go on a rampage and beat everyone up. It wasn't a good day...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Natalie. Long time reader...birth giver to my friend  urlLink Zachary . I hope you enjoy reading about my life :)   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My sister had her graduation party today. I showed up dressed in navy blue dress pants, black socks and shoes, a button up shirt, AND EVEN GOT MY HAIR CUT!!!  Phooey; there es one thing that every hippie wanna-be fears: THE DREADED SHEARS OF A BARBER!  Actually it wasn't that bad. I usually go to  The Regal Barber Shop  on main street, but I decided that they cant cut hair worth a crap. So I decided to venture up the main street hill to Dakota City and try out  Roffler Family Hair Center . That is a hair cut.  I think the difference between the two is  Regal  cuts your hair more or less with pretty much simplicity. Straight edges all the way around. It kinda makes you look like  urlLink Captain Spock .  However, At  Rofflers  they actually "texturized" my hair. And the guy that cut my hair actually told me what he was doing to it. Showed me all this neato stuff that he could do and all this other jazz. I felt more like he knew what the "F" he was doing.  I think that I wil be going to  Roffler Family Hair Center  more often in the future
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our district had its track meet today. I decided that Dan should throw other than me because he is a senior. He did farely good.  The purpose of a district meet is that people in a certain district have a HUGE co-ed meet. In the mens it is the top three compeditors in every event goes on to the state track meet at Drake Stadium. With girls its a little different. They send the top two, then the third place people are all thrown into a group and they find the fastest one in the whole state of the third place finishers. That person also goes to state.  We had many people going to state:  Tyler Vermeer  -  Long Jump, High Jump, Medley Relay (400 m leg)   Tyler Dodd  -  High Jump, 110 m High Hurdles   Nick Harklau  -  110 m High Hurdles, Medley Relay (200 m leg)   Thomas George  -  Medley Relay (800 m leg)   Chris Lee  -  Discus   Alex  -  Medley Relay (200 m leg)   Congrats to everyone that is going to state boys and girls, you have worked hard.  P.S. My sister is going to state. Congrats Anne
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that Kevin (a huge huge HUGE HUGE  urlLink Kiss  fan) is in our band, I think that it is only fair that I try to learn some  urlLink Kiss  songs to play with him. I figured why not choose one of the best, "Detroit Rock City". Brian (my sister's boyfriend and guitar freak whom also likes  urlLink Kiss ) played Detroit Rock City with his band at a concert. They used face paint and all! It was so awesome.  Anyways, right now I am reading up a little on  urlLink Kiss . There is only so much a 3 A.M.  urlLink MTV  special can teach a person...  Also check out this article about Gene Simmons:  urlLink Gene Simmons Offends Muslims in Australia   urlLink Gene Simmons Offends Muslims in Australia   (if one doesn't work...try the other one)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight we are going to try to change our practice session a little bit. Kevin will be joining our band for tonight ot see how well we can function. We hace decided that we should have Dan either play guitar and not sing, or sing and not play guitar. And wherever he chooses thats where Kevin comes in. He is going to probably play a little guitar and/or sing for us.  I guess we will just have to see how this goes at first
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight we had our local meet. Cut to the chase...we lost by 2 points to St. Edmonds. They are a catholic school about 20 miles away or so. But whatever, I really dont care too much.  However, achieving personal greatness...that is a good thing. I opted to throw crappy Monday in the throw off so Dan could throw varsity instead of me. However, he only threw 35' and some odd inches. I threw JV shot put and ended up with 39' 5.5" and won the whole shindig!!!  Anyways...go me. The official champion of the 2004 Humboldt Invitational Relays Junior Varsity Shot Put!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The seniors have their last day of school this wednesday.   Will you miss many of them???   Nah...not really. There are a few that I will miss. There are also a few that I am glad to see go. But there some people I want to stay. Some that I think that I have built up a relationship with just a tiny bit. I will let those people know who they are before they have a chance to go.  My sister is also a senior this year. She is going to go to ISU (Iowa State University) and become an engineer of some sort. Then I will have the computer all to myself!!!  One more thing before I go...I wonder if there will be any "super seniors" coming back for next year!!!  *Congratulations senior class of 2004*
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got the old  urlLink New Found Glory  CD -  urlLink Sticks And Stones . Its actually a very good CD. I think when their  urlLink new CD  gets cheaper I will buy that as well.  At the same time I got  urlLink Sticks And Stones , Chad got the  urlLink Kinky  CD...a mexican band.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to my neighbors with my dad today because my old babysitter was back. She was in high school when I was just a little toddler. Now she is all grown up and she is very pretty. Okay...pretty sounds lame, but she isn't hott, and she isn't not hott...so pretty she shall remain.  Anyways, I just thought I would share that with the world
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my new blog template. Thanks to some new additions to  urlLink Blogger.com  I am able to do some cool things that I was not able to previously.  This is the new look for my blog. Email me if you like it, dont like it, or are just bored:  peter.stockdale@gmail.com
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight the Humboldt High School 9-10 and 11-12 bands had to go to Forest City to compete in a state band competition. It wasn't head to head or anything...you went and got a rating. The ratings were 1 to 5 and 5 is a DQ...they tell you pretty much you suck and you dont get squat. 1 is awesome and you can have a cookie. The judges never seem to give out 4's and guess what...we got a 3.  Not good..not bad...but we could have done better. Oh well...there is next year. Then we arent with the crappy freshmen!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I have made up my mind on what guitar accessories I am going to buy when the summer becomes a little closer and I realize that rocking out with a tiny amp and a guitar isn't going to be good enough.  First I think I will start with a  urlLink Boss Distortion Pedal . That is something that is pretty simplistic. It isn't  needed  but is great to have if it is convenient.  Next, I absolutely  NEED  a new guitar strap. The one that came with my strat just isn't cutting it anymore. It is leather and crappy leather at that. I think that I am going to get a new  urlLink Kepur Strap  with an  urlLink aum  on it.  And lastly, this is not a necessity, and I dont even really have to buy it, but I want one. So depending on when/if I get a job this summer, and I hope I get a job....any job.... I wil get a  urlLink Crate FXT 120 . It is a 120 watt guitar amp and it has the option of hooking up additional speakers to it as well. Also a nice little toy that could go along with that is a  urlLink wireless guitar amp cable . Nady Blem makes this one.  My mom said she would go halves on some things... like a new amp and/or a new guitar. So I figure only $200 for the amp, $20 for the strap, the full $40 for the distortion pedal, and maybe if I feel like it, $85 for the wireless cable...that comes up to eh...just about too much. I think that I will rethink this before I go and make any rash decisions...  Only think I absolutely need is a new strap...we will build on that later....
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lately I have been listening to two bands:  urlLink New Found Glory  and  urlLink The Offspring .  I play a few songs by  urlLink New Found Glory ; Hit or Miss, My Friends Over You (the first guitars moving part played at the intro is a little tough for me), and last but not least Head On Collision (still working on the solo a little). I can play those songs almost fluently so go me.  A couple songs I play by  urlLink The Offspring  are; Gotta Get Away (this song sounds tough but is very easy), and The Kids Aren't Alright ( urlLink Noodles  is a stud and I have no clue how to play the solo...but Im working on that one too)  The songs our band knows fluently is still low. We can play Swing Swing by  urlLink The All American Rejects  and if we had the solos we could pull off Kids Aren't Alright by  urlLink The Offspring . Other than that...we aren't too good. We dont have a very good vocalist. Dan wants to try to play all the leads but I think he rushes everything and kinda goes all  ADHD  on us. He also doesn't take it as seriously as most of us do...but oh well.  Not like it matters too much....
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay...I know not everybody that reads this knows my house inside and out. But you go in my back door. You can go up or down. Up 5 uncovered cement steps, or downstairs to the basement...about 15 uncovered cement steps.  That being said. Im upstairs, going out to my car... ready for a band concert. I fell down the first 5 and jumped up...hmm Im okay. Turned around and fell down about half of the other 15. That time I wasnt okay. My elbow got really messed up. I bruised the bone terribly. It is swollen on the joint where it hit the cement a couple times.  I had to throw varsity shot today at Algona. I threw about 38' something...I was pissed off. I probably should have said something to the other people about my elbow...but I thought it looked pretty good. Then I threw terrible and got mad. It is radiant with heat constantly. I cant do more than 3 pushups without nearly crying. I had to hold the shot with 2 hands so I wouldn't drop it and look like a fool. But then I threw terribly and looked like a fool anyways. (for those of you wondering our shot is 12 lbs)  I think I will let Dan throw the rest of the meets on varsity...we will see. Depends on how fast my arm recovers.  By the way, we won our second meet of the year. Humboldt High School are the 2004 Hackbarth relays champions!!!! I think we can do farely good in the conference. Wonder how that will go...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dan D. started us off neck and neck with everyone...then I got the baton and blew everyone away (okay so maybe it wasn't so much of a blowing away...but I did get a 20 meter or so lead) Then Ben T. got the handoff...I ran into him and then tripped and ate dirt... but Im over it. Ben handed off to Chris L. and Chris solidified a victory for the 4 by fat... :)  Does that mean anything that we beat up on a bunch of overwieght people...not really...but still, it was fun :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My uncle from Des Moines came to Humboldt today. He had a CD that he wanted to show me. He put it in my grandpa's computer. And be played...  "EARACHE MY EYE" by Cheech and Chong...  It was probably the funniest thing I had heard since I had seen Blue Collar Comedy Tour a couple days prior.  Also I have taken a liking to reading people's web blogs and/or web diaries.  LOOK HERE FOR SOME BLOGS AND DIARIES   -------------------->
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been playing guitar almost non stop in the past couple days. Every free chance I get, I play. Even when Im at the computer... like now... I have my guitar in my lap and I am pausing to play every now and then.  My fingers are getting really callused over big time and they hurt really bad... ISN'T IT GREAT!!!  The other day I was at the local coffee shop getting a mocha and  urlLink Jody Hawkins  came in and played guitar...I was amazed. He can play it all. Ive heard him play rock and roll, but he was playing classical and jazz that day. He is a stud and a half...  It would be awesome to be just like him :)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I have just realized that my summer sucks. I go to bed late, wake up at noon (or maybe later), then loaf around on the computer the rest of the time. I dislike doing work and waking up early...but with what I am doing now, It jsut seems like a wasted summer thus-far.   urlLink Hy-Vee  is taking up quite a bit of my time as well. Tomorrow I work 10-2 then 3-7. A cool 8 hours. Im getting about 25-30 hours a week. Im happy that I have money...but mad that I have to work. All-in-all...its a fair trade :)  This summer sucks...put simply
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a new perloid pickguard on my guitar... It didn't quite fit...but with some bruit strength and one stripped screw hole, its in there :)  I also bought some new knobs for it. I replaced my volume and both tone knobs with 3 neato looking chrome telecaster knobs. My guitar almost looks like  urlLink Steve Klein's    urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  Gothador  - Devilishly Good Fun! Play online now for free!   Gothador is free and awesome. It takes a little getting used to...and you might have to leave...  Nevermind go find out for yousrself. My name is PedroV1 so if you see me say summin :)
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think its funny how  urlLink Gmail  is all the rage. Its actually quite awesome too. I have invites...and people constantly email me asking for an invite.  I dont want to just waste my invites, but all the people I ask if they want to try it, or even use it, dont use it once they have it...aka Jadie and  urlLink Chad ...  I dunno I feel cool...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other day I went to Jody Hawkins house with Tom. I played on an amp that is almost $5000 for just the head! I also played on an awesome Ibanez guitar that is just under $2000. I was scared to touch it. There are pictures of both below!   urlLink      urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate sleeping, its true. The only times I can ever seem to get any sleep is if I am dead tired, then I get about 12 hours of sleep. This summer I have went a few days of just running off of 4 or 5 hours of sleep, but in the last week I have been sleeping over 12 hours a night...  What does that say? Well if you think...I go to bed at 12 A.M. (midnight) on a good night...and about 2 A.M. on an even better night ;)... I sleep until my parents come home from work basically (about 1 P.M. or so). I have been running those sleeping patterns for about a week or so; today I had to get up at 7.  I dont know about you, but I went to bed at 10 thinking oh crap Im gonna be late to work, better go to bed early. However, as some may know, you cant change your sleeping patterns that ealisy...I tossed and turned all night long. Finally getting some shut eye around 2 A.M. (right on schedule for a normal day). Then my alarm went off at 6:15...  Time for  urlLink work !!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have become an employee at  urlLink Hy-Vee . I bet  urlLink Chad , and  urlLink Zach  are happy :)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have had a slight obsession with the  urlLink New Found Glory  Guitarist, Steve Klein. He is a stud...plain and simple!!!   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to go get a new set of guitar strings. I was playing guitar today with Dan and Tom (after Jake left early) and I busted a string. That almost ended my playing for the night. I tried to play a few songs...but its almost impossible, as I broke one of the strings that is most played...  Prior to that; today  urlLink Ashley  brought out a couple of real Oklahoma girls! Their names were Pepper (16 yrs) and Holly (15 yrs). They were pretty cute...hope Jadie doesn't kill me! ;)  We went bowling, Jadie, Ashley, Holly, Pepper, and Ashley's sister Cathy. I won the second game, and Jadie won the first. Pepper and Holly had never bowled in their lives!  All in all I think Oklahoma girls are all right...and they even said ya'all a few times. Here are some pictures of us, Holly is in the brown, and Pepper is in the red. Ashley is in the yellow, and Cathy is in the light brown. My dad is also in the last picture.    urlLink      urlLink      urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah...I said  hay  not hey...  Yesterday I had to bail hay. Then I had to help my dad plant corn at Randy's (our neighbor's). That was decent. Not too terrible. Today I had to tear down a tree, then mow lawn. I got the tree down easy...it wasn't too big. Then Jadie and I started to mow lawn. We got one part done when I decided, hey lets go inside, so we did.  We made a very drawn out attempt to put an air conditioner into a window (since we dont have central air). That went great. It should have taken about 20 minutes tops...it took almost an hour. Then I had to fix the squirrel cage fan, that went great. I couldn't find the stupid right size socket. Then I got it done...after getting mad over stupid things.  THEN, I had to go with my dad to change a tire on a hay rack (with the hay still on it). He was taking it somewhere and the tire ran out of air (just sorta deflated). We had to jack it up and put a new tire on. That took a few "hail Mary's" but we got it done. I let down the jack and saw the tire was low...but didn't say anything. We got it to its destination...then it exploded...so my dad got very pissed...  We got home and had to go bail some more hay, about a mile and half away...so I drove the tractor with the hay bailer along the high way. Some asshole (pardon the language) thought it would be funny to SPIT ON ME! So that made me happy...not.  I tell you...people suck!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes if you want comedy that speaks the truth and does it with political incorrectness, a little potty mouth, and some neat flash, this is the place for you   urlLink http://www.ebaumsworld.com/endofworld.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know if htis has become more of a blog, or a "lets post as much guitar crap with pictures as we can"...  Anyway, this is Rich Ward. He is an awesome guitarist! I want to have tattoos all over just like him...and play guitar like him too. He is the lead guitarist for  urlLink Fozzy , and former guitarist for the band  urlLink Stuck Mojo . I have been very obsessed with  urlLink Fozzy  in the past couple days more than anything. I want to see one of their concerts so bad. I want their merchandise, I want their  CD  that I dont have...anyways, here is Rich Ward!   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder just how many of yo have heard of the greatest metal band on the face of the earth,  urlLink FOZZY . I have just read about 40 things on  urlLink MTV .  urlLink Quite interesing...   If you haven't yet heard of  urlLink FOZZY , check them out! This is Mongoose McQueen, who also looks a little like Chris Jericho!   urlLink    urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thats what Kevin J. told me when I said my right rear window of my car wouldn't go up anymore...he said - 'A French Fry Is Wedged In It'.  I think the wiring is just faulty. I dont know...but I think I am going to end up being just like my sister with her stupid window...Her's wouldn't go up...and she didnt want to buy a new motor, so she cardboarded and packaging taped it up :) Very very  urlLink red-neckish . quite amusing though :)  I dont know what to do though. My dad doesn't really seem to care...ever. My mom is doing nothing but softball with Anne. I hate that. When its softball season nobody pays attention to me. Maybe thats good. I like to be left alone...just because I cooperate with myself :)  I might have to take it in to fix it myself...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been wowed once again by yet another amazing guitarist.  urlLink Yngwie Malmsteen  is perhaps one of the most skilled guitarists in the world. He has fantastic covers of many great songs including 'Carry on My Wayward Son' - by  urlLink Kansas , and some of  urlLink Beethovens 's pieces as well.   urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who knew that finding a song on an illegal peer to peer downloading network could be so hard ;)  Im trying to find the song: Stereomud - "Anything But Jesus"  and lets just say its not going to well. I have only found one file, but they got offline from the network thingy so I couldn't download it from them...  I wish people would let me screw over our music industry.  urlLink The  RIAA   can eat my poo.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I seem to have  urlLink misplaced my sunglasses 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Enough said 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of yesterday I became an employee of the city of Livermore. Every off day that I have (other than weekends, because then I will work at  urlLink Hy-Vee ) I will go to the huge town of Livermore and do odd jobs (mow lawn, haul crap around, clean up peoples compost, etc.)    Right now we are seal coating about 15 blocks of city street. Joe (my boss) and I drive the tar machine to Algona, get tar and come back. Because the tar machine is a trailer type thing, we can only go about 35  m.p.h. . So the whole trip takes about 1.5 hours to 2 hours. It is a long journey, but I get payed for it. Then I stand behind a rock laying machine while other guys lay down the tar. I make sure the machile has rocks spread evenly, it sucks.    But thats all I have done. Get up and be in Livermore at 6 A.M. That sucks. But I get about $50-$60 a day (I make $6.50 / hour I think) Its not too terrible of work, pretty easy money, since nobody gets hours at  urlLink Hy-Vee  anymore. (yes even I have been set back)  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so terribly sad. For multiple reasons. The first reason is pretty stupid. Actually...its really stupid.  urlLink Blogger  and  urlLink Mozilla  dont seem to like each other on my computer. That is why I haven't posted in a while. The other reason is a little more practical.    Jadie went to Orlando on a youth gathering trip of sorts for her church. I miss her so much. I cant wait for her to get back. She said she will get back wednesday night out of the Des Moines airport...but knowing her mom I probably wont get to see her. Just because they have been gone and they need their "family time" or summin....    Oh well. I cant wait until Jadie gets back. I miss her so much.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went jet skiing today with Jordan. It was pretty sweet actually. There weren't many boats out there so we didn't have to look out a whole lot. But there were 2 boats out there giving off waves that were almost 6' tall from crest to trough. We would go flying off them and about poop ourselves afterwards. It was so sweet.  Then when we were almost out of gas I got a brilliant idea: Have Jordan go 50 mph by our docks, I would jump off into the water and swim to the dock. Yeah that was awesome. HUGE adrenaline rush. My pants about flew completely off my legs in the water...It was so awesome.  I had a great day :)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Long rant stick with me...   Working Last night was interesting. Im sure if you take the variables I have here and think about it...you will get this easily, here we go.  I am at work with Person "A", and Person "B". "B" brings 2 of his friends (we'll call them "C"). One of them just so happened to be "A"'s little brother. "A" knew the 2 friends wanted beer, so he took it inside with me. While we put it away the group of 3 outside lit stuff on fire with the lighters, quite mature.  Then "B" and "C" went to put crap in the truck. Some other people pulled out behind the store. "A" got in his vehicle and I knew he was gonna kick some butt if the people didn't leave, so I went with. After "A" threatened to kick some butt, the people left. "A" called some authoratative people and got "C" (the friends) to leave. Then we finally got to doing some real work... at about 1 A.M. ... oh yeah, did I mention that one of the two "C"s also work at the store.  We hauled crap all over in the store. We have too many  urlLink Cheerios . I dont know why they ordered so much. We also have a lot of old orchard juice crap. I got the privelage of climbing all over on top of the coolers and freezers to stack crap on top of them...that wasn't too bad. Kinda entertaining at about 5 AM.  After we were done with the majority of what we could have gotten done, I took a pallet jack around back (it had lots of boxes on it). As I was walking in the side door (that needs to be propped open or you get locked out) the  urlLink Hy-Vee  truck driver asks to get through. I move my pallet jack out from the door way to the outside. The F'ing arse kicks my door prop off the door and slams it shut. I was pissed. I had to wait for someone to come open the door. Then it took us almost 20 min to crush all the boxes we had...  I have a new respect/hate for  urlLink Hy-Vee ...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cant believe I did one of these things...but hey...gotta have some "fun" sometime. I got this from  urlLink Hannah's Blog . I could see some of this crap happening...like me killing "G" Dub :)        Who will you be stuck with at end of time? by  urlLink  chi_a_baidh        Your name is           Your sex is      Male Female Undecided       Your favorite color is      Red Orange Yellow Green Blue Purple Black White Other       You are stuck there because    you were dead, but then you weren't.. Look at that...      For _____  years    21      With     urlLink  George Bush. Click for pic.       He/She will think you are    horny      You will    kill him/her             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah that was what I did as soon as I got home from visiting zach at the tent sale. I bought a 27 cent lighter at the sale and some cereal, then went home and started to burn stuff. I burned a coffe can lid (we stuck all the stuff in the coffee can itself), some plastic forks, and some straws.  I tried to burn a golf ball with not much success. I did get it to light for a minute or two. I like to burn stuff. I would love to make cool melted crap art :)...I would call it modern art and sell it to people for $500 and make a 1234507503071% profit :)...  Maybe not, but at least Im optimistic
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like the 4th of July. I enjoy fireworks, the parade, and ... thats about it. However... the older I get the more it sucks. I think the firework display gets worse and worse every year. This year there were pry about 50% green tinted fireworks...  I dont know. Call me a fun-hater..but thats how I am.  Rating this 4th of July on a scale from 1-10 (10 being highest):   3 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This makes me mad. I got HALF of what I ordered. I got the cabnent but not the amplifier. Arg!!!  That makes me mad. Now I have to wait until next tuesday or so in order to get my full purchase. Until then, my cab is virtually worthless... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been going paranoid waiting for my  urlLink Marshall  guitar amplifier to come. There is supposed to be a 2-5 day shipping on standard shipping items. Its been 4 days. I looked on the  urlLink UPS  website and this is what it says...     It is currently August 12th at 11:51 AM and I WANT MY AMP!!! Every truck that drives by I jump up, look out the window, run to the back door, look for the big brown truck...but its not to be :( 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a fantastic  urlLink Where's George  hit today. You will never belive this -   urlLink http://www.wheresgeorge.com/report.php?key=3a44ccb2ffcfa51a0d0af6f5402e2cae  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, my job in Livermore didn't last long. 9 days to be exact. However, it did allow me to get almost $450 working at just $6.50 / hour. I will be doing it next year and maybe the year after that...   What did you do with the money?? Save it for college?   HECK NO!!! I got this!!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is my birthday today! Hoorah...actually...this very minute it is my birthday :)  Wahoo!!     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>