<Blog>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, today is my birthday.  I am 36.  I have now reached an oddly symbolic age since this is the end of a second set of 18 years.  I remember not being able to wait until I was 18 years old; now I have lived that age twice!  The nice thing about getting older for me is that I actually LIKE getting older.  I am fascinated by it.  The world's changes, my body's changes, my emotional experiences, my perspectives,... it is fascinating to me to see the patterns of Time.    I have never really feared getting older or even dying.  To me, these are two things that are as natural as gravity and green.  The only time I have ever had any strange feelings about getting older/dying was just recently, and only briefly.  It was after accidentally stumbling across a web cam for Time's Square here in NYC.  I launched the cam and watched the streets.  It was around 5am so the streets were fairly quiet, but they were also amazingly alive.  I saw the buses pulling through the intersection, sporadic images of people walking down the street, the lights from the giant signs all blazing in the dark grey winter light of such earliness.  I don't know why this is so beautiful to me, but it is.  (Oh, the irony of being in awe of the patterns of Time, while being so moved by the patterns of Time's Square!)   And that's when I felt it...  For the first time in my entire life I had a feeling similar to claustrophobia sweep over me and I thought:  "I am really going to miss this."  I felt jealousy and panic and claustrophobia and a deep, deep, grief.  It wasn't about dying or getting older, but more about feeling this rich and powerful Love for this life and NYC and Earth and the beauty of animals and insects and plants and people.  I just thought how perfectly and profoundly fantastic it all is.    I have always felt like an alien in this life, not so much because I am inherently different from a lot of people, but because I have never been able to take this planet for granted.  Whether I am in Nature or in Time's Square, I marvel at it all and I can't help but think, "What a fucking great idea this was!!"  I mean, seriously, if some "higher power" did conceive this, It was brilliant.  And if this is all some cosmic accident??  All the more reason for me to be in awe!    Yeah, I know there is pain and suffering, but if you actually look at everything as a whole, pain and suffering are proportionally a very small part of the picture.  And then at least half of all of that pain and suffering isn't because of something "real", but because of the way we choose to interpret events.   99% of the time, the world we experience can change into something more awesome and beautiful with just a slight change in attitude/perception/interpretation.  Anyway, so I had that slightly suffocating feeling of realizing one day I would not be here, at least in this body in this form I call "troy", seeing the world in my own unique way.  I will miss "me", too, I am sure.  I know it sounds slightly morbid to be talking about these things in this way, but that kind of thinking is another of the things that makes me, "me", and it helps me to appreciate every single day.  They say that one of the last "lessons" of a Soul is to "learn to love the schoolroom", which means loving this world and your life in it.  I absolutely love this place.  I hope it isn't my last lesson here.    (more details later about my surprise tiny love birthday party from Nick and Cyprus!  what sweetnesses...)   urlLink TIME'S SQUARE CAM   Choose CAM 1 for the most fun....  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I have finally uploaded the photos from our New Year's and Christmas gatherings!  YAY!   urlLink  PHOTOS    We had such a great time over the holidays.  Since my digital camera was part of my Christmas gifts from Cyprus, you can see that I had no clue how to adjust any settings for good photos, but I just consider them "artful".  I'm learning...  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh my GOD it is cold!  My fingers were burning and itching within minutes this morning while walking Spyder.  That might be because I was excited to be out in the powdery snow of the pre-6 a.m. street traffic, so took my camera and was trying to snap photos through the wind and sharp snow flakes.  I LOVE that:  the quiet blanket of snow over the beautiful streets of my neighborhood.  Spyder danced and played in the drifts while I tried to take pictures of her.  She is quite a bit retarded, so a photo shoot of her was not easy, but she was adorable with her wide eyes, darting, and snorting of the snow.  Today the chill is going to get even worse, with winds up to 45 miles per hour and the chill being between -35 and -50 at some points!    Now this is winter!  I love it!  I've decided to use ofoto as my image storing source, so you will most likely be asked to register and sign in to see any pix I post.  I've been signed up with this service for a long time and I have never received obnoxious promotions or ads from them, so you should be fine.  Besides, if you register, you can comment on the photos, save the albums, create your own, etc.  It's a way cool service!    See pix of my morning,  urlLink here!   STAY WARM! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What does it mean to someone when one says something is "blessed"?  I understand it in terms of religious mythology, of course, but when one has a more inclusive and broader spirituality, how does "blessing" become interpreted and applied?    Does "blessing" become a metaphorical term to indicate that one has simply become more Aware or Conscious of an exchange?    Does "blessing" mean more about expressing/acknowledging gratitude?  Does "blessing" mean more about a sense that you are infusing a thing or Being with a finer energy conducted through you?  What exactly does it mean to you?    What is the purpose, and how does this improve things for all parts involved?  I ask this because there are many practices that are just blindly applied, such as saying "bless you" when someone sneezes.  Why do we do that beside to satisfy a social pressure?  Does anyone really mean it?  Does something occur that is beneficial for anyone?    Why don't we bless a person who has burped or farted? 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last night we celebrated Don's birthday by hanging out at Pieces and listening to/participating in AWFUL Karaoke hell.  I will be posting pics tonight.  Taren, Richie, Alex, Jeffrey, Don, Josh, and I had a great time, despite the crescendo of "singing" voices emitting painful sound at the end of SUMMER LOVIN'.  I have always held a soft spot for Don's friends whom I had met only briefly in the past, but with time spent with them recently because of the holidays, I can conclusively say I REALLY like them!  They are very sweet, thoughtful, and mature guys, despite the lascivious slurping over my boyfriend.  Nick sang last night and when he sings the room changes from being a corn-ball, off-key, homo frenzy to seeming ALMOST like a serious venue for talent!  It is amazing to watch him.  He commands the floor, captures the attentions of all the boys, and silkens the room with sound.    Of course, this makes the already-lascivious boys of Don almost pee themselves with desire for Nick.  Although I am MOSTLY fine with this harmless expression of attraction for Nick, I have to say that a teensy part of me was/is jealous and annoyed.  Ironically, as I stood processing some of the more annoying and jealous feelings, (you know, not taking it too seriously and keeping things in perspective) suddenly this guy who was probably one of the prettiest guys I have ever seen (and everyone had been commenting on how amazingly attractive he was) came over to me, leaned across a table, took my hand, and just started talking, saying he was compelled to talk to me,... he asked my name, what I did for New Years, etc.  It was VERY awkward and I was completely taken aback.  All of my friends just stared and Nick stood there tolerating the entire scene.  And then it was over.  He just smiled, relaxed his grip on my hands, slid them away, and said we would talk more, later.  That was just the strangest thing!  So in the middle of this processing and letting go of the annoying feelings about feeling so unattractive, feeling jealous of Nick's attention from these guys, I suddenly became the center of attention from the cutest guy in the place (besides my burn-your-hands-and-heart hot boyfriend)!  It was very exciting and confusing and embarrassing and satisfying at the same time.    Why do I have to be so hard on myself...?!!  Maybe I'm not the doughy, boring, John Goodman-lookalike I see in my head? 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      See, this is what I hate about the holidays.     As much as I LOVE the holidays because of the glee, the snow, the cheer, the presents, the giving, the gatherings,...  I always forget that I and my friends are such a minority.  It seems so foreign and barbaric to me to actually go and cut down a tree, or to pick through a virtual graveyard of dying trees, decorate its dead body in your living room, and then, while it is bleeding saps and losing strength of needles, you laugh with families and friends and celebrate the season, and THEN you toss this dying thing because its life has been taken for a couple of weeks of your stupidity.     I don't know why this surprises me and makes me sad.  I saw these trees tonight as I was walking  urlLink  Spyder  .  I took a few moments to thank and mourn all of the trees who died so that people could have a wire-and-light-bound beauty to stick boxes under.    And what about our lovely  urlLink  Rockefeller Center Tree  ?  It's all going to be mulch soon.  It reminds me of that movie, BABE, wherein the little piggies were forced to make the damn movie and then killed afterwards.  I think a unique and brilliant idea is to have Rockefeller Center host an artistic rendition of a Tree each year.  One could sculpt, build, create a tree each year!  I don't know... it's a suggestion.  Now why can't people enjoy a kick-ass tree like ours!!?  urlLink  FiberOptic Fantasy!    Now isn't that nice...?  Here's our other fancy ass tree:  urlLink  SilverSensations!    God knows what kind of hell came from creating these artificial trees, too...    Oh!  And speaking of Body Bags...   PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE let me know if you are interested in accompanying me and my gang to see this world premiere to help all of the amazing animals on this planet who suffer every day.  Here are details:   WORLD PREMIERE! Manhattan PEACEABLE KINGDOM  Saturday, February 28 Lincoln Center - Alice Tully Hall 6 pm Reception / 7 pm Screening Please join us as we debut Peaceable Kingdom at one of the nation's most respected arts venues, Lincoln Center! The filmmakers and many of the documentary's subjects will be attending and will answer audience questions after the screening.  General Admission: $25 Multiple Tickets (min. 5): $15 Premium Seating: $100 Lincoln Center's Alice Tully Hall is located on Broadway at 65th St. in Manhattan for more information:       urlLink TRIBE OF HEART  TRAILER:   urlLink PEACEABLE KINGDOM   I really love this world we live in, and I think we are doing ok, if you ask me, but what an amazing planet of people we could be when our compassion extends beyond our own species.  I imagine this kind of compassion couldn't help but extend deeply into our own species, as well.  Ahhh, to dream....  G'nite. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      God, I am struggling to get my ass back into the routine of work.  I never thought I would become such a drone, and I don't know how long I can continue in such a state.  I am an extremely adaptable person, but because of the way things are run and how people are treated at my job, it makes this one of the least appealing positions ever.  It's so frustrating, because it would take only a slight change to make this one of the best jobs ever, but because the place is run by socially-crippled, ignorant fucks, it makes everyone involved lose all interest in team work and loyalty.  UGGGHHH!  Things are a-gonna haffta change....
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, here it is.... my potential template!  This is just another test as I seek for one to which to commit!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, here it is!  The new home for my Personal Blog!  I never could get used to using that damn MoveableType.  Besides, using MoveableType meant using valuable space on my own server and Blogger graciously hosts us without question!  I am about to launch my revamped web site and cannot wait to personalize/customize this Blogger template to match my little 7Paths world!  So this is my testing, testing, one, two, three post!  YAY!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, my blog is turning into a full-blown Dream Journal, but I swear I will balance it with the realities of my days!  I think the dream state has become emphasized as a result of the processing of my break up.   DREAM:   Okay, first, in waking state, I got this "wink" from somebody who saw my personal ad.  Yes, I did it.  I put out a personal ad shortly after being dumped.  Partly because I was like, fuck it, whatever, I gotta move on, and partly because, fuck it, I AM ready to move on!  Heh heh... So I have my ad in several places looking for friends and dates.  Well, I got this "wink" from a boy and I thought he was cute.  I get tons of "winks" because they are safe for people to send and they don't cost anything, but I rarely find them interesting enough to respond to.  This guy was cute and interesting, though.  So when I went to bed, I dreamt about him, but not REALLY him... I dreamt that I got an email from him and he said he really looked forward to going out with me before he had to leave the country.  I noticed that he signed his email with a name that looked Icelandic, but I don't know how I thought/knew that.  Then I noticed a link in his signature that was for the  urlLink Sigur Ros  web site!  I followed it and realized this guy was the lead singer for Sigur Ros!!  I could not believe the guy from Sigur Ros was asking me out!!  I was so excited in my dream!  I love Sigur Ros because their music is so mournful and emotional and the crescendos are intoxicating.  Add to that the reviews that call the lead singer " urlLink Elizabeth Fraser  in a gay man's body", (my all-time, most-influential, inspirational person to me on the planet!) well, how freaked out excited could you possibly get me?!  If you have not seen or heard Sigur Ros, try starting with this video.  Watch closely, all the way through to the end.  It is the most beautiful and sad thing EVER.  Follow this link and watch the second video down, called:   urlLink "viðrar vel til loftárása"           Of course, it was all just a dream.   WAKING STATE:  Okay, so in "reality", I am healing, moving on...  I can't believe how fast I am processing this!  I am actually kind of excited.   When I was in my worst state of anger about Nick dumping me, I decided to do this meditation called "decording".  It's a way of separating your energy from another person, or group of people.  I wanted to do it as a way to kind of punish Nick, actually.  I thought, fine, if you can so easily dump me, I am severing all ties with you and you will be left with a husk of a relationship with now hope for a future with me!  Within hours of doing the meditation, freeing the energy between us, I started feeling AMAZING!  I started seeing him in a very compassionate light, full of love and acceptance for the bravery of his choice (he really did not hurt me or intend to hurt me), and I saw that my worth was not tied to his interpretation of me or our relationship!  The freeing feeling was AWESOME!  Suddenly I was very excited about just being the best of friends and my moving on to find a more appropriate boyfriend who really shared in the same interests and hopes, which Nick and I did not.  I could easily take Nick back in a heartbeat.  I think I would love him as completely with or without the label of "Boyfriend", but I realize it is a nice thing for me NOT to be with someone who doesn't want me like that.  Interestingly, since the meditation, I have been reunited with two guys from a time when I first met Nick.  They are guys I would have gone out with, but I had already started dating Nick!  So now I can go out with them if I want!  I know for a fact that one of them is interested, already telling me that he has waited for years to hear that I wasn't with Nick anymore, so we could "snuggle and kiss and date"!  He said he always knew Nick never wanted me as much as other guys seemed to want me.  Whatever.  Everyone wants what they don't have.  The true test is wanting it after it is yours, and nurturing it for the years to come.  Sigh...  I don't know if I am really ready for seriously dating, but it's nice to know that I might be able to do so when I am ready.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I dreamt last night that I had discovered a new love for someplace in Europe, but I am not sure where I was.  I have never been to Europe in my waking life.  I was much younger in my dream, which has never happened before.  I always dream of me as either non-age specific or my current age, but in this dream I was just about 20 years old.  Apparently, I had gone to this place in Europe and had left to go back to the States.  I guess I had just returned and had worked really hard to be able to come back.  I vaguely think there was someone there whom I had fallen in love with and had vowed to return to him, but now I couldn't find him.  I remember walking down this lovely, quiet street and feeling so alone, but so happy to be back at the same time.    At one point I was standing in front of this house that sat on this street nearly by itself.  I knew my mom lived there, but I never did see her in the dream.  I just knew she was there.  I was standing around outside this house when a car pulled up about a half-block away.  It pulled up onto the sidewalk and parked.  All of its doors opened, and I was already half-running to the car.  It was the women from the  urlLink STARTING OVER  house!  What the..??!!  They all got out of the car as if they had expected to see me, and though I appeared to have expected to see them, I was also SO happy to see these familiar faces!  I hugged  urlLink Hannah  and discovered since I had seen her last, she had damaged/injured her neck and back and was in minor pain.    urlLink Karen  is the one who appeared to be happiest to see me, with a huge, tight hug!  We were all walking back down the street toward the house where my mom lived.  I woke up.  NOTES:  I do love that STARTING OVER reality show!  I think it is one of my all-time favorites of the reality tv phenomenon.  I wonder if I dreamt this because of my recent breakup with Nick. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Nick informed me tonight that he made yet another confusing choice in asking me to be his boyfriend again... he dumped me AGAIN tonight.  My heart really hurts now, after working so hard to open back up over the beginning of the week when he told me he had made a mistake and wanted me back.    I wonder how many people can say they have been dumped by a boyfriend twice within two weekends.  Everything seems so flattened right now, but I know I will be ok.  Someone will really care about me someday, want me, and keep me.  For now, that person will have to remain just me,... and, of course, Cyprus... my best friend.  God, I can't believe this happened to me!  I feel so stupid.  Good Night, Nick.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, another great dream!  I am back on track in recalling!  YAY!   DREAM:   For some reason, I have rarely if ever dreamt about  Nick .      Maybe it's because he is on my mind and in my life so much anyway that my night time is for other adventures?  Anyway, I had a dream with him, finally!  Now that I am writing this, I am unclear as to the details, dammit, but Nick and I were out and about, but for some reason got on a wrong train or something.  We ended up somewhere that was confusing, but still kind of familiar.  I don't know how this merged together, but somehow we found some tickets to a show of some sort.  The tickets were for only part of an event that had varying levels of possible participation.  Our tickets were ONLY for the show, so we could not stay for any receptions or discussions, or whatever.  I don't even remember seeing the show, but I know we went.    After the show, we were laughing and trying to figure out where/what to do next, so we started working our way through this place.  It seemed we were in a mall of some sort, but it was long, the way outdoor plazas are designed.  We worked our way through and by many, many stores, and we began to wonder how we were to get out of this place.    Finally, we found a fast food restaurant that was interesting enough to eat the food, so we were standing in line.  As Nick got the food, I was called over by someone at a table who informed me that we had to pay for the tickets we had found earlier.  I tried to explain that we had found them, but that didn't matter since we had used them.  He said we would be billed on our Credit Card for $14.95 each.  This upset me because we had only seen the show, but participated in nothing else, and he was charging us for the entire event.  We should have been paying only $6.  We were both annoyed, but just resigned to paying the price.  Suddenly I saw a door that appeared to lead outside!  I rushed over and stepped through to see where we were.  I couldn't figure out anything except that there was a restaurant across the street called SWOOP, which was a Soup and Sandwich shop!  I looked up at the lettering above the doorway I had stepped through and it read:  SWOOP & PASTA.  I guess it was because it sold soup, sandwiches, and pastas/salads.  That's all I remember, EXCEPT that at some point amid all of this, I was flirting with Nick, then lifted him onto my shoulders with his legs over them, FACING ME, so my face was in his crotch!  We were getting all bizarrely sexual, but someone walked in on us and we stopped, though we weren't that embarrassed.    What the hell is going on in my lil head!!??  heh heh  PS:  Nick and I are officially dating again...  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't recalled a dream very clearly in a long time, which is very odd for me.  I usually have very bizarre, detailed, intense dreams that can become epic, lasting over several nights of sleep.  I love it!  Lately, however, I have not recalled much at all.  Last night, the clarity and recall returned.  I always post my dreams in my journal for future reference because the insights gained from watching your dream patterns can be profound and even prophetic.   DREAM  I dreamt I was in a "duplex".  Not the two-story version of a duplex, but the kind that refers to a two homes, separate, but completely connected.  I was in one side with Cyprus and some other people, I am not sure.  I do know that  Taren  was with me.        At some point I realized that Taren had wandered off and had entered the other home/apartment that was part of the duplex.  I knew that the previous tenants had only recently moved, and when I entered into the apartment where Taren already was, I was very uneasy about being in there.    Taren was rummaging through all of the stuff that the tenants had left behind, unconcerned about whether we should be in there, or not.  Though the apartment was bleak, dirty, messy, and poorly lit, she expressed how much she would love to move into it so she could live next door.  For some reason, I knew this was not an easy option, so I expressed support that we would have to check out how she could go about doing it.  Suddenly, through the window, I could see that the manager of the grounds for the duplexes was coming toward us.  Taren had turned on some lights, so it was obvious we were in there.  I thought fast and told Taren to just play along.  She went to a rickety kitchen table and sat as I answered the door when the manager knocked.  He knew I was from the other part of the duplex and asked how I was settling in.  He asked if Cyprus was around so he could finalize the lease with us.  Then he asked Taren if she was ready to sign HER lease!    I have no idea how I thought this would fly, but I guess I assumed that the manager was just making rounds to finalize leases for all new move-ins (I remembered that he was coming to see us in our own apartment), and that he MIGHT just assume Taren was a new move-in!  He sat down with her, went over the lease, she signed it, and they shook hands!  She was so happy!!  I couldn't believe what had just happened, but I was so happy for her and happy that she would be our neighbor.  Any interpretations?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After a weekend of tears, kindness, understanding, and patience, Nick has now decided that staying with me is the right choice.  He proposed this to me today.  No matter what would happen, I had decided I would never have hard feelings about a break up, and that I would make the best in whatever position I created or found myself.  It never crossed my mind that Nick would ever dump me, and it didn't cross my mind that he would have such a swift realization as to what he truly wanted since the breakup.  Now I am in a weird state of mind and heart.  Do just let myself be whipped around by Nick's indecision and confusion?  Do I just admit that I do understand his position and just relax back into the relationship with a continued passion?  On the one hand, I am in love with Nick and can easily accept a life with him indefinitely.  On the other hand, considering his inability to accept the reality of responsibility to nurture an indefinite commitment, I might need to be more focused on my career and casual dating?  I don't know...  I do know that my relationship with Nick would never "end" or "die", but it would always find a means to grow to accommodate our growth as friends first.  Any advice or comments?  Use the link below!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
        After nearly 4 years, it is over...         But is it the end...?   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Since my and Nick's Birthdays are so close together (20th & 29th), we not only celebrate them separately, but we gather a gang and celebrate together.    This past Saturday we went to one of our top favorite restaurants in Manhattan,  urlLink  CARAVAN OF DREAMS  :  An amazing, vegan, totally organic heaven of foods.  They have an extensive Raw (aka "Live") menu (meaning that the foods are either literally uncooked, or they have not been cooked above a certain, low temperature) that is incredibly delicious enough to convince me that I can move beyond my Veganism some day!  For now, I will just settle with being Vegan.  I'm at about 90% dairy-free!  YAY!  It's not been difficult at all.  I used to read Tarot Cards at Caravan of Dreams a long time ago, so it has a special little place in my heart...  After our wonderful dinner, which was given to Nick and me from Thzaira (Thanks, Thzaira!!), we went to  urlLink  THE SLIPPER ROOM   in the Lower East Side for a raunchy, playful, overcrowded burlesque show!  An asian girl go-go danced for about 30 minutes while the room continued to fill up, and she was so boring.  It was like watching a 9-year old boy caught in a spider's web.    Finally, a giant, blue, high-heeled-glass-slippered, glittery, camouflaged, homo bunny took over the room as MC.  He was hilarious.  At one point some girl was pushing and shoving and screaming out, "hey, mister bunny!"  She got on my nerves so much that I "corrected" her and told her it wasn't a bunny, but "the tick" (from the cartoon series)   So she started yelling out, "Hey, TICK!!"  The homo bunny whipped his head around and put his hand on his hip and laid into her!!  He lisped out, "Listen, you waspy bitch!  I am a homosexual and I don't have no problem hittin' a girl!  Take your New Jersey Bridal Party and go to the back of the room!!"  HA HA HA!!!  Of course, he was trying to be caustic and funny, but she did shut up and stop pushing.  Hee hee...  Cyprus and Taren were finally able to get seats, and so did Nick and I, but Josh, Jennifer and Jeannie were stuck in the crowd, so they left fairly quickly.  After the first set of strippers, which were really hilarious skits and just plain fun, Nick started getting whiny and wanting to leave, so I obligated myself to escort him out and home.  I was actually glad to be home fairly early, but I was really enjoying the show.  Cyprus and Taren stayed and I hear the second part of the show was over-the-top hilarity.  At one point, Taren had smacked the homo bunny's ass, so he grabbed her by the hair, dragged her onto the stage, whipped her around, pulled her pants down, and started spanking her bare ass in front of the entire venue!!  HA HA HA!!  We will be going back, more than likely, for our Valentine's Night Out together!  Ahhhh... New York.  I love our home...   urlLink  PHOTOS from BIRTHDAY WEEKEND   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've been quietly (and not so quietly) having a really hard time with my breakup.  It's such a stupid looking thing from the outside, but when you are inside that kind of rejection, god, the things that run through your heart and mind...  For me it's like every hateful, angry, "told-you-so" inner criticism of myself and my life comes out in crescendo.  I've been finding myself hating Nick and mustering the strength to completely remove him from my life.  I know this is not what I want, but there is a sort of satisfying sense of punishment found in that possibility; "if i can't have you, then you can't have me AT ALL!"  That kind of thing...   Anyway, I know this stage is as normal as any other and I will heal and it will pass.    Last night I obligated myself to some cocktails with Nick and Don because of it being Nick's ex-coworker-slash-obnoxious-acquaintance's birthday.  ( NOTE :  Nick would rarely, if ever, go out on a weeknight just for drinks and socializing, but oh, have some obnoxious, ex-coworker off-handedly invite and he is there!  )  We went to  urlLink XL  in Chelsea and actually had a good time, punctuated by my occasional badgering of Nick as to WHY WHY WHY did he dump me.  I am sure he just loves that.  Otherwise we had to listen to his obnoxious, car-salesman, loud-mouthed acquaintance scream out faux-jock "woo hoo's" peppered with "oh I LOVE HERRRRRRR!" when someone like Britney or Christina came whoring onto a video monitor.  Interestingly as the night wore on, Nick and I discovered that most of us there were only remotely connected to this guy, all of us being mere acquaintances, which was at once a bonding factor and also just sad.  I did end up with two guy's numbers by the end of the night.  I may be in mourning, but I have been dumped and my ass isn't going to be moping around shunning men.  Speaking of... I have YET to follow through with actually going on a date with any guy who has asked me out.  I just keep making excuses and delaying it.  Dating seems so tiresome right now, even though I actually have some really cool guys to go out with and just have fun.  Luckily, they all seem to be just nice guys with very embracing and earthy attitudes (except a couple of them).  I will take the plunge soon enough.  No rush.  On the artistic front:  a long time ago I was browsing through  urlLink STRAND BOOKSTORE  in the village just trying to find something fictional to read.  I read so much non-fiction that sometimes I just want a really great fiction book to get into.  I found this gay-themed, sort-of-adventure-coming-of-age, book called IN AWE.  I was less impressed by the actual story than by the author,  urlLink SCOTT HEIM .  For some reason he struck me.  As I went to read the book later, I saw in his "gratitude" notes that he thanked  urlLink Elizabeth ,  urlLink Robin , and  urlLink Simon  for "constant inspiration".  I could not believe I was reading that!!  A random author I had just found was thanking Cocteau Twins!!???  Cut to years later now, I am updating my own web site and entering a link to  urlLink Cocteau Twins'  web site... I happen to check in on the site and read the latest news... Robin, of the now-defunct Cocteau Twins, along with  urlLink Harold Budd  (who worked with Cocteau Twins on a project called  urlLink MOON AND THE MELODIES ) will be scoring the soundtrack to  urlLink one of Scott's novels  being made into a movie!!  Congratulations, Scott!  Your life is my fantasy!!  Troy   [to leave a comment, or read comments, use the comments link below]    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First off, I think I have injured myself when working out.  I don't think I should still be this sore in such a specific area.  The muscle/tendon right above my elbow is actually kind of bulging and I can barely lift my hands to my face.  Hmmm, I will have to see.   DREAMS:   I dreamt that I was with someone and I am not sure how we heard or knew this, but we knew a friend/acquaintance of ours was in a bizarre predicament in his apartment.  It almost feels like I and that person with me were detectives investigating a report, but I am not sure.  Anyway, when we entered into the apartment of the friend (or person having been reported), we found him with his face/head smashed into a high part of a wall, with his head completely pushed into the wall to his neck.  His neck had been broken and he was hanging all limp about 3 feet off the ground.  You couldn't even see his head, it was pushed in so completely.  It was particularly startling because the space that his head was pushed into seemed too small, like his head must have had to have been crushed to get it through.  I went over to lift his body up, to take pressure off of the neck, and that's when the guy spoke!!  I could see his lips and eyes moving as he spoke from his mangled head.  I cannot remember what he said to me now, but it was a message.  Next I dreamt that I was pressing on my right chest muscle and massaging it because a sharp pain was shooting through.  Somehow there was a discussion about the fact that my heart was actually scarred.    [note:  yesterday in Waking Life, I really did have a sharp pain in my chest that caused me to massage my chest]  [leave your comments by using the comments link below!] 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Bruises, Bruises...   So last night was my first night doing my weight lifting routine.  One of the very fit men from the gym showed me around the machines I was scheduled to do, being very patient and very instructive.  I have a workout plan (generated from www.workoutplan.com) that is designed for weight loss and lean muscle building and scheduled for five days a week.  Monday, Wednesday, and Friday are Cardio workouts (running, biking, rowing, stepping), and Tuesday and Thursdays are weights, focused on lean muscle development.  The very fit man from the gym commented that I had a "great workout plan", so I guess that site knows what it is doing.    Okay, first of all, I just realized it is freaking me out that I am talking about a GYM or WORKING OUT.  Well, as with my breakup, new dating life, and working out,... it is all just another adventure in the end.   I can't believe how enthused and committed I am to getting in shape, but I'm going to do this... for me.  One of the things you may not realize is how HARD it is for me to type this morning!!  My arms are killing me, but not where you would think they would be (like the bi- or triceps).  No, they are aching and difficult right around the ELBOW!  Now... what the hell??!!  I think I did the "Lat-Pulldown" exercise incorrectly or something, because I just can't imagine why someone would need to work out an ELBOW muscle?  I'm trying to remember if I have ever commented to myself about how fit someone's elbow area is?  I just don't think so.  So this is either a stupid pain in my elbow from a misused weight machine, or I am just not educated enough yet about this working out stuff.   DREAM   I dreamt about "C" last night.  I haven't even met the guy yet, but we have a strong online interaction going, so I am looking forward to our date Thursday night.  He is a temperamental, fucking brat, who throws tantrums and expresses severe cynicism on a regular basis, so it is clear why I am attracted (god help me).  In my dream last night we had just met and I was surprised by how big he is, as in tall and big-boy-ish.  I do know he is over 6 feet tall in Waking Life.  When we met, we were all giddy and silly and joked about how scared we were that we would reject each other in 3D.  There were other people with us, but I am not sure who they were.  Oddly, he made me stand up in front of him and he laughed happily as he made me do a turn around in front of him.  He helped turn me by putting his hands on my waist and moving me in a slow spin.  He was so excited and laughing, commenting on how he could not understand why I would ever have been concerned.  So then I affectionately made HIM get up and do a turn around for me.  I was very surprised by how "hard" his body felt in my dream, but at the same time it was so soft, through his clothes.  One of the mystery people with us asked him to show his tummy, so he begrudgingly leaned back on this stool and pulled up his shirt.  He was very fit, but that was the least attractive thing about him in my dream.  Instead, I was totally attracted to his playfulness and ability to poke fun at our fears.  Making us do a spin in front of each other like some kind of cattle auction seemed to put things into perspective and make us laugh and get that whole stupid distraction out of the way.  Cut to us walking around someplace I didn't recognize, but it seemed "small town", like a semi-residential neighborhood.  We were walking Spyder and talking and laughing.  Somehow Spyder got loose and took off running, and though she had a long delay in responding to my calling her back, she did eventually come back and I was so relieved.  Hmmmm....   [comments can be made by clicking on the "comments" link at the end of any post] 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After a long, long day of work, and despite the tempation to skip it, I made my first step into the gym!  I barely made it before it closed, giving me about 30 minutes to do exactly what I had gone to do:  walk fastly for 30 minutes on a treadmill.  To help me with my newfound enthusiasm for fitness, I bought some simple, but cozy and cool sweats and a couple of cheap t-shirts and a good ole hat to throw on before and after.  I walked at 3.5 mph at a 6.0 grade for 30 minutes and then a cool down.  My damn legs were burning and I felt like I was walking on rubber when I stepped off of the treadmill.  I wondered if I would feel self-conscious in the gym and for the most part, I didn't feel anything except my focus.  My music helped, though I swear, just one teensy step with the wrong angle or timing and I would have flown off the belt.  I had to really focus and just keep walking, walking, walking...  Luckily, there were very few people there that late at night.  And even luckier that no one saw the large, long strip of tape running up the side of my new sweats reading  [size:  L L L L L L L L L L] .  I found it as I bent to breathe after my long, intense walk...  Tomorrow is my first weights work out!  WOO HOO!  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Euthanasia of the Heart  It is at once exciting and very sad that I am single again.  I had that few days where everything seemed perfectly alright and then I was hit for about 3 weeks of grieving and sadness; nothing debilitating or too difficult, but just surprising.  I know Nick didn't intend to hurt me, so I don't take it as a hurtful choice of his to move in a different direction than we thought (for nearly four years!)  Still, I miss everything about our relationship; and because that is the only way I have ever known Nick, he now seems like a stranger to me.  I think that makes me the saddest of all.  I'm trying very hard to be his friend, but for now I can't seem to reconcile the momentum of our routines, concerns, plans, and affections as boyfriends and these new, muted behaviors that would support only friendship.  It's just awful to have to make a profound effort to let someone go, but even worse to actively have to kill a happy, loving, affectionate part of your Being so that it can accommodate a new version of a relationship.  But I am trying.   Dating Delirium  In an effort to "move on" and harness the tiny part of me that might be excited by being single again, I have actively announced my single-hood and posted/updated my Personals Ads everywhere.  I've received numerous friendly, complimentary responses, which is nice, but 99% are, of course, not compatible with me (based on reading their ads).  I am not opposed to going out with someone who appears incompatible with me, but there must be SOMETHING intriguing about that person.  Sometimes that intrigue is in their look, sometimes it is in their interests, sometimes it is just intuition.  So today, or sometime this week, I am going on my first date with one of about 4 possibilities I have decided are of interest, with one particular guy in the lead.  Ironically, this one is the most interesting, intriguing, and challenging of all of them, with very little in common!    In my fantasies, I always want to date someone "just like me".  I have this general idea about what I am attracted to, and lo and behold, I never EVER end up with that kind of person.  NEVER.  I have NEVER dated someone like me.  I can only conclude that there is some freakish part of me that loves the learning more than the idea of comfortable love.  I think I have this idea that love must be challenging and stretching of my capabilities.  The first guy (I will call him "C") I am going out with is an adorable, gorgeous, impatient, restless, calloused, homo-hoodlum with a caustic sense of humor and a secretly-huge heart.  I think I am attracted to the contradiction within him.  He is pierced, defensive, cynical, and arrogant, yet this seems to cloak a creative, gentle, yearning, devoted heart.  We have spoken on the phone, exchanged emails constantly, chatted for hours and hours, and developed that strange, deep affection across the internet.  I really can't wait to meet him.  I am sure that even if we aren't attracted to each other in 3D, we would be very interesting friends to each other.  There are other guys I want to plan to meet and go out with, but I am terrible at that part.  I have a hard time "dating around".  Once I have met one, I feel like I can't meet any others until I determine what's going on with one.  I am weird.  Another guy I am seriously interested in meeting is "M":  a very cool, ex-club kid poster boy from the 90s with a genius streak and an over-the-top, semi-famous presence in the NYC underground and across the web.  He wrote me in response to my blog when I announced I had been dumped (hi "m"!)  I guess he has been a fan of my website and varying incarnations of my blog for about year!    Who knows what will come of the New Year...  I have been dumped and I am on the rebound and I am working harder than ever, even joining a gym!  It seems so ironic that now that my life is so much more stable, defined, and happy, that my boyfriend would find it important to dump me.  Ahhhh, the irony.   DREAMS:   I have been having massively-packed dreams lately, but I couldn't remember them.  I remember Friday's and Saturday's, though.   Friday:   I dreamt I was walking around Brooklyn Heights with Don and I kind of wanted to go home.  It was chilly, grwasn'tand damp out.  Don wasn't ready to stop hanging out, I could tell, so I suggested walking across the Brooklyn Bridge.  I suggested this, but I remember thinking that surely he would dismiss that option because it was so cold, windy, and late.  Instead, he blindly said, "oh!  Ok!"  I was annoyed, but couldn't back out, so I started making comments as we climbed to the bridge, pointing out how long it was and how it was farther across than it appeared.  Don continued oblivious to my disinterest in doing this.  As we walked onto the walkway of the bridge, instead of it going straight across, it severely curved upwards like a giant skate ramp.  We pushed forward, climbing the ever-steeper incline until the incline literally became vertical enough that you had to climb by hanging onto something.  Toward the top, we were actually climbing by sticking our feet and hands into grooves worn into dirt, as if the material of the bridge had now become the side of a very steep hill.  We reached the top and found a room.  Gently, I began to remember that I had been there before.  There were people there, milling about and having cocktails.  Some people said hello to me as if they remembered me.  I was fascinated by how high we were and wondered how everyone got there.  It seemed at this point Don went wandering off.  I went to a doorway that led to one of the huge cables that hold the bridge together.  I remembered it used to be okay for us to scoot out onto the cables, but people had fallen and died, so it was discouraged.  I still found myself hanging onto the thinner cables and standing on the giant barrel cable, working my way out about 10 feet.  I suddenly had a flash of a couple of people falling, watching them seem to go in slow motion, and then seeing one of them hit a part of the bridge and slice himself in two.  Suddenly I got really nervous and wanted to get back inside, but I also made a note to myself in the dream that the memory of others falling was from a previous lifetime and that I had been one of the people who had worked on building the Brooklyn Bridge!   Saturday:   I dreamt I was on the set of part of the filming of the remaking of DAWN OF THE DEAD.  Now I can't remember much, but it was scary.  I also dreamt that  urlLink Michael Myers  (of Austin Powers fame) had responded to my personals ad!  What up wit dat!?   MOVIES:   2 rather disappointing movies seen recently:  THE  urlLink SECRET WINDOW  and  urlLink DAWN OF THE DEAD .  Both were very well-done movies overall, but there was nothing of substance to them.  I mean, I was not on the edge of my seat, the plots were predictable, and I left feeling nothing.  They looked good and should have been exciting, but they were not.  I was disappointed in both, even though they were worth seeing.  Dawn of the Dead I would see again if in the mood, but Secret Window, I would not.   urlLink 28 Days Later  was much more genius and scary compared to this Dawn of the Dead remake (and I actually liked  urlLink the original  much more).  Secret Window was good ONLY because it is such a treat to look at Johnny Depp and watch him act.  He is oddly mesmerizing and so likeable.  Secret Window, however, is a Stephen King story and is a recycled story of The Dark Half (quote: "Novelist (Tim Hutton) is shocked to discover the alias he uses for some of his books, has manifested itself and is acting on the violent urges and thoughts the author has.")  Hello, that's the same story as Secret Window.  And I don't know if it is supposed to be tongue-in-cheek, but Timothy Hutton was in this film, too.  This film would have done better as an Outer Limits episode.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well it has finally happened (again)... Cyprus and I are moving!  We continue to work hard and do our best to create a stable adult life, which is harder than you may think for two overgrown, big kids at heart.  The apartment is not far from where we currently live, but the DRASTIC nature of the neighborhood is amazing.  But that's the way New York is anyway.  One side of our current block is swarming with the stink of fast food, street noise from hell, screaming 'hood people, sometimes fighting, and just horrible, scraping trucks that idle for hours...  then on the other side of our block, it is serene, gorgeous brownstones and playful dogs walked with pleasant people, trees, history, peace...  Well, Cyprus and I are now moving into that kind of space,... but even BETTER!  The neighborhood is embracing, warm, friendly, civil, and beautiful.  I don't want to post too many details, since this is public, but some pics are below.  For the most part, I wanted to document the transition from the BEFORE and AFTER.  We are renting an apartment that is not even finished being renovated.  Thankfully, I have seen the renovations of this landlord in other apartments, so I trust it will be excellent.  All new appliances, an elevator in the building, and laundry in the building.  I cannot wait to move now!!!  YAY!!  We will be living near the water, along the promenade, with tons of neighborhood amenities!    Check out the BEFORE pix below.  Our new apartment is currently gutted and in the process of being completely revitalized.      The entrance to our home!  YAY!    The gutted kitchen!    First Bedroom w/Bathroom    First Bedroom w/Bath (note how HUGE it is with the person in the photo!)    Second Bedroom w/o bath    Second Bedroom w/o bath    Gutted bathroom outside of second bedroom!    A portion of the Living Room (it was filled with debris and too big for one photo)    So watch for your HOUSEWARMING PARTY invites in JULY!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How hilarious... I am barely a month into my online dating scene and I find I have been targeted with a scam.  Thank god I am internet-savvy and very research-oriented, because in all seriousness, I might not have figured this out for a long time.  Why wouldn't I have figured it out?  Because as much of a researcher and an internet-savvy person I may be, I am also a sucker for kindness and giving the benefit of the doubt far too long.  I had received an email from a guy in Russia, flattering me and asking if he could basically be my pen pal and just have a gay friend with whom to share.  I thought this was cool, kind of reminiscent of high school when I did have literal "pen" pals.  I even affectionately thought about it today while at work, thinking this was a nice treat, no pressure, because I have been avoiding actually going on any dates.  A pen pal might be a nice, non-threatening way to just have fun.  So I go to write him back tonight, re-reading his broken English email, and I decide to search on his country so I can speak intelligently with him, ask him questions, etc.  About 6 entries into the search results, I see the words "INTERNET SCAMMER".  Some part of me must have known, because for some reason it totally made sense to me within seconds despite my original affection for the idea of a pen pal.  Sure enough, the alert from  urlLink  ANTISCAM   not only included the guy's picture, but his email to me nearly EXACTLY as I had received it.  The letter continue on, eventually leading to a request for money, presumably once the victim is hooked with prospects of a foreign love affair coming to fruition through a few cash advances and a ticket out of Russia.  WOW! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I love the cold, the cool, the chill of Fall, Winter, and Spring, and I   HATE   the heat, humidity, the stink of Summer. I have never been able to understand why some people prefer to sweat, give off odors, and generally appear greasy. The dry heat of the southwest is better, I admit, but that's like choosing between the lesser of two evils, like choosing between being trapped inside the thighs of an angry whore after three days of street-walkin' or being trapped inside the doors of an oven. Oddly, I do think we had quite a long Winter of cold, so I was actually happy to see the sun coming out in such glory recently within the chill.     &nbsp;    Then, all of a sudden, it's an 80+ degree day!!! Where the fuck did Spring go?? Supposedly it will cool again and I hope that is our Spring, but if it just jumps right into humidity and heat, I am going to be in for a long, miserable Spring/Summer. Uggh. Still, for some reason, any weather in NYC is glorious in some way.  And that glorious day prompted all of us to go out and have a great time!  First, we all went to  DOJO's  on  St. Mark's Place  in the  East Village   for a nice brunch, then walked around for treats, and finally went to see  KILL BILL Volume 2   (which was just brilliant!)&nbsp;     &lt;see pix below of the sunny fun day&gt;      DON      JOSHUA      THZAIRA      Cyprus     [through Tibetan store window]        Nick   [with lover]      Troy   [in my new Gay Pimp glasses]      Cyprus   [with lover]    SO much to write about, so little time!!  [ excerpts of a life synopsis of a week:    a.   cyprus and i are moving again!   b.   have had tons of dreams to upate here   c.  had another funtastic night out with Hedda and the Classics, so funny my face was still hurting the next day!] 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "....and most poor suckers are starving to death!"   My god, this past week was SO full!!  First of all, it was a very busy week at   urlLink work...          This is a pic of my little cubicle that encapsulates my Being far more than any other location on Earth.  As Wednesday came around I was getting serious cabin fever, so when   urlLink Leela   spontaneously invited me to some friend's   urlLink Comic Book   release hosted in   urlLink The Coral Room  , I was ready to go.  Who doesn't love a huge wall of LIVE Mermen and Mermaids!?       I called my pal Paul who was also synchronistically, spontaneously available, and we headed out after work to meet Leela.  That night turned out to be surprisingly profound as Paul and I talked about Loss, Grief, Consciousness, Transformation, and Love.  Although I have had a great support group around me throughout my oddly-quiet breakup with Nick, I have to give Paul the trophy for  "Greatest Breakthrough from Grief while in a Synchronistic, Spontaneous Environment among Swimming Mermaids and Too-Loud 80s Punk Rock" !    Most people who are close to me tend to step back when I am grieving, angry, or lost and confused, because I am such a control-freak that I have convinced everyone I can do everything better by myself.  That's a reality I prefer most of the time, but one that can bite me on the ass when I am really lonely or in need of a profound breakthrough.  I think the resonance of what Paul had to say was amplified by the innocence through which it was delivered, because it was less advice and more of a personal story.    Paul was sharing his perception of a friendship in his own life that had caused him a great deal of grief, depression, and anxiety.  This friendship was one in which Paul would have preferred more, and one in which the friend was allowing a blur to occur between that "friendship" and "more".  This had become frustrating and painful for quite a while, but over time Paul realized that most of the pain had come from his own EXPECTATIONS of the friend, and not from the friend.  Paul finally allowed himself to see just how much the friend did Love Paul, how much the friend gave to his fullest capacity in his own way, and just because it was not in the way that Paul expected or wanted, it was still a depth of giving from the friend that had to be recognized.  So when Paul basically let go of the inner demand for the friend to fit that expectation, Paul was able to finally Love and Be Loved in a more intimate and meaningful way.  It is all bittersweet, but it struck a very powerful chord in me about Nick.  Nick has always given me every ounce of Love he can manage.  I know that.  The fact that he will not love me in the way I want him to love me does not negate the reality of his important love for me in his way.  As Paul spoke to me about his friend, a forgiveness toward myself and for Nick swept over me to the point of tears.  I kept myself composed, of course, but I was feeling a relief from the anger and resentment toward Nick that I hadn't felt before.  It was like I finally "got it".    You know, on the surface it can easily look like Paul or I have "made excuses" for the behavior of the other person we wanted so much to be with, but that's not the case.  The reason I am secure in my genuine realization is because Nick has never intentionally hurt me, as Paul can say about his friend, too.  It would be one thing if these guys had been mean or insulting and then I accepted these lame philosophies just to make myself feel better, but in both relationships, Paul and I agree that our guys were 100% giving of 100% of what they could.  It actually put into perspective how,  ironically, Paul and I were the ones lacking in our efforts to "love".  It put into perspective how conditional we had become.  I can't say the grieving is over, but I can say that my night with Paul probably removed weeks, if not months, of time from the process.  Thank you, Paul.  And thanks to all of my friends for any part of support you have given me across my life!  We said goodnight to Leela (who was just the cutest social butterfly of the night), and eventually Paul and I ended up at   urlLink Barracuda.    Paul and I continued some great conversation, but we quickly had to succumb to the tiny stage show that we had not realized would be ensuing.    A 7-foot tall drag queen who could have easily passed as   urlLink Kathy Griffin   came onto the stage with a bored demeanor and a deep voice only to lip-synch to awful songs and pass around a spitoon for money.  Despite my lack of interest in the show, the night wore on, and Paul left, and I stayed, and eventually I heard a lip-synched song by PEACHES.  I know my friend   urlLink MYKEY   loves her, but I hate that raunchy, rap-like, rough shit.  But that night/morning was the first time I actually found myself liking her, too!  The atmosphere, the liquor, the people, the overall great night,... all contributed to my finally saying "YES!" to   urlLink Peaches!    Now I LOVE that song, "fuck the pain away"!  It was deliciously obnoxious and perfect for the night.  I didn't get home until around 5am.  I won't say why.  I stayed home from work on Thursday to recuperate...  Thursday night had been a plan for going to   urlLink Chelsea's Clearview Classics Night   at the theater.  It was the first time we had heard about these great classics being played on the big screen every week!  We were so excited because they were playing   urlLink AUNTIE MAME!    I almost bailed on going out for the movie, but I had a feeling it was going to be so worth it.  Nick, Don, and Taren had never seen the movie, so to watch something so inspiring and funny with people who had never seen it, and on the big screen at that, I knew I had to go!  What I experienced was nothing short of one of the best times I have ever had in NYC!  The night was hosted by   urlLink HEDDA LETTUCE  , one of the most genuinely witty, talented, and funny Drag Queens in NYC.  She was actually in character as her Jewish Aunt, "NETTA ICEBURG", as she hosted AUNTIE MAME.  She was so hilarious.  As she asked the audience to raise hands if you haven't seen the movie, she insisted no one be shy about it, "no judgments here, no judgments here...", she said in her strong Jewish Aunt accent.  Once the room was about 1/3 full of raised hands, she spittled out, "YER ALL STUPID!  HOW COULD HAVE NEVER SEEN THIS MOVIE!!???"  That was particularly funny because Cyprus and I had that similar response to everyone who had told us he or she hadn't seen it!  The movie generated smart laughs, inspiration, and reminder that life is really so grand if we make it that way.  After the movie, Hedda was in her "Hedda" character at the   urlLink EAST OF EIGHTH   lounge performing her weekly show.  She had invited all of us during her hosting of the movie and I am glad we went.  She is SO FUNNY!  She sings these hilarious parodies of classic and pop songs, mixed with commentary and interaction with the intimate crowd.  It's just so New York City and I love that whole lounge scene with the martinis and laughs and good people.  A special bonus for the night was in meeting the hotties from the new movie   urlLink SHOWBOY  .  I love NY for the fact that famous, semi-famous, and infamous people are just a part of the pedestrian world like everyone else.  Hedda, Christian, and Adrian were kind enough to let Don take a picture with Taren and me.        Normally, I do not take photos, but these days I am seeming to be visually document everything!  I don't know if I would have been interested in this movie on its own, but in meeting the boys, I now feel I should see it as a form of support.  The writer and star, Christian, used to write for Six Feet Under, so he has a HUGE amount of admiration from me just for that!  God, I swear I look like Rosie O'Donnel in the photo above!  Speaking of infamous...  I also had the sweet experience of recognizing a worker at East of Eighth as being a former member of the staff from the reality series   urlLink THE RESTAURANT  .  He was the little flaming gay boy waiter/host who quit because of Rocco's abusive, neglectful, and arrogant effects on the work environment.  He was so friendly and sweet!  Again, I ended up at Barracuda for the night.  Taren and Don accompanied me.  We were just being ridiculously silly!     DON, TAREN, ME    A PENI-TINI    A TAREN-TINI    Don and Taren left, but I stayed for the "Star Search" show, hosted by   urlLink Candis Cayne  , a very beautiful transexual who is one of the many famous Drag/Trannie hosts in the NY underworld.  The   urlLink CHEER NEW YORK   gay cheerleader boys were spontaneously called to the stage, which was a lot of fun.         I got home around 4am and still got to work by 8:30am on Friday.  The rest of the weekend was pretty calm and uneventful, thank god, so I could work on my stuff with   urlLink Michael   and the web site.  I am nowhere near being caught up with that.   DREAMS UPDATE:   I dreamt I was chatting with some guy who suddenly acted like he was surprised and appalled at my being gay.  He still insisted on meeting me.  I dreamt I killed someone, which I have never dreamed in my life!  I can't remember what led to my killing him, but it had something to do with his constant threats against my life.  I remember the killing wasn't planned, but I broke his neck while trying to make him shut up.  I remember knowing it was only a matter of time before someone found the body, but I acted like nothing had happened and went about my days in quiet panic, wondering what I would do.   [comments can be read or posted using the comments link below]  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been having dreams that I have not recorded, which include:  Cyprus and I decided to move to Australia.  I remember it being a bittersweet decision that was full of hope and yet deeply saddening.  The view of the house was very similar to what one might see in the Tucson, Phoenix, Tempe area of Arizona.  Now I can't remember who won, but someone in my dream won a substantial lottery jackpot.  I don't think it was me, but I knew it would be shared with me.  And last night I dreamt about a disturbing sexual competition that involved keeping an erection and rotating partners and doing all kinds of weird things.  I remember that I felt like I was winning, but some kind of interruption was happening that was making the competition break up.  I think I was very disappointed that I would not be able to win.  [note:  as with all of my sex dreams, the actual sexual part is always implied rather than actually experienced.  I don't think I have ever actually dreamt of an actual sex act... hmmmm]   [comments can be made by using the COMMENTS link below] 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I hope I look back on this day and see that I made the best of it... I was told today that I no longer have a job.  Saks let me go.  Several people were let go.  I don't know the extent of the changes, but that's all moot.  I now have no income.  Oh, and we signed our lease to our new apartment today...  Sigh...  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am finally getting these images posted from our amazing time with  urlLink METRIC  last week!  I could not believe how much energy and charisma this band has.  They have been on tour forever, and they still manage to seem as if every single night is the best night they have ever had performing!  It feels so good!  If you have not checked out METRIC, you really should.  The music is deceptive at first, but after about 3 listens to one or two songs, you are hooked by the smart lyrics, catchy choruses, and impressive/expressive energy that is infectious.  Emily was in her trademark charismatic spastic weirdness that drives everyone into a happy worship, even leaping into the crowd to body surf briefly.  She is so thin and tiny, it is not much a deal that 20+ hands can pass her around easily.  I love seeing people do what they love to do.  It is so inspiring.  I grabbed a few snapshots as best I could...  click on an image for a larger version.   urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink     [leave your comments by clicking on the comments link below]
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Elizabeth Fraser in Shhh... @  urlLink Victoria and Albert Museum  in London  My god... the glorious sound of Elizabeth Fraser has graced me today in the throes of my illness.  I am so happy.  It is at once heaven and hell to hear her, because the clip is just too small and it just taunts me.   urlLink  Elizabeth Fraser   (formerly of  urlLink  Cocteau Twins  ) was asked to do a piece for an auditory museum theme in London, along with a number of other worshipped, unconventional true artists such as  urlLink  David Byrne  ,  urlLink  Leila  ,  urlLink  Faultline  , and others.   urlLink  Shhh... Sounds in Space    urlLink   go direct to Elizabeth's feature      [hear Elizabeth below]    urlLink QuickTime Clip  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I dreamt I was in Taren's apartment (in which I have never been in waking life).  We were all getting ready to go out or something.  I had to go to the bathroom really bad, so everyone was waiting for me to piss.  I stepped into the bathroom and was immediately disgusted.  I started getting that tickle in my throat like I was going to vomit.  There was a bare bulb hanging from the ceiling, mold everywhere, and the tiles/walls were this seafoam-greenish-nauseous color.  I don't remember any smells, ironically.  The room was very tiny so that my ass was actually touching the tiny sink as I angled to pee into the toilet, which was turning into its own disaster.  The toilet was covered in piles of clothes, a basket, and various other things.  I wanted to put the stuff on the floor, but I couldn't because the floor was wet and muddy with stones, dirt, gravel.  So I lifted the seat to try to pee while holding it up, which of course left my pants to become too loose and they fell around my ankles.  Because I was freaked out about my pants getting dirty, I flinched and started pissing onto the floor, but I quickly realized I not only pissed on the floor, but all over my own messenger bag that was dangling near my feet, and I had pissed on my jeans, too.  I was getting really grossed out, but felt obligated to act like it wasn't offensive to use her bathroom.  Meanwhile, the floor had become softened by the liquid and my own piss, and my shoe got sucked off.  For some reason there was no solid floor anymore, just piss, mud, gravel, and disgust.  I can't remember what led to my losing both of my shoes and my socks, but at some point before I awakened, I was standing with the piss and gravel squeezing up between my toes and the smell of urine was getting stronger (AND I hadn't even finished peeing!)   I woke up and had to pee.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Uuugghh...  I am sick.    I have some kind of flu or severe   SEVERE   cold.  The coughing I have endured has caused my ribs around the back of my body to ache beyond belief.  Today I decided to check and I can't tell if it is my imagination, but I can swear that my skin is showing bruising along the sides of my torso.  The pain is excruciating.  I am taking 4 different drugs to help reduce the symptoms and aching.  I have  never  taken drugs like this before.  I am in a rare state, that is for sure.  I finally went on my first date since my breakup.  I went out with the cutie who everybody refers to as my "wigger".   urlLink    "wigger boy" (posted with permission)  The interesting thing is that we have absolutely nothing in common, he is antisocial, he hates my music, my tastes, my lifestyle, is impatient, distracted, comparatively superficial, very emotionally young, cynical, defensive, he eats animals,... basically he is the very antithesis of me.  Somehow, though, we actually had a very sweet time.  We walked all over Brooklyn Heights, along the promenade, to the pier, back through the heights, down Smith Street, all over.  He peppered the evening with surprise gestures of affection and overall, we both had a great time.    Unfortunately, because of his distractions and our lack of common ground, I doubt much will happen beyond this one meeting.  He seems to think the differences make no difference, and as friends, maybe they won't, but as far as dating, that gap would be a big problem.  Also, I am a very indulgant boyfriend, so I love to indulge in the other person and expect as much enthusiasm from my boyfriend to indulge in me.  That includes healthy compromises, passionate open-mindedness, patience, and a deep, deep trust.  I don't think I would find that in "wigger".  But who knows... he may prove me wrong across time.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just thought I would share some of these gothic photos I took while exploring our potential new neighborhood.  I'm beginning to think I should take up photography as a serious hobby.  I really love it.   urlLink    Gothic Neighborhood   urlLink    Gothic Neighborhood   urlLink    Gothic Neighborhood   urlLink    Gothic Neighborhood   urlLink    Gothic Neighborhood  I say our new neighborhood is "potential" because now the new landlord has said that the gutted apartment he showed us may have to be "given" to a relative of his!  I cannot believe it.  He tells us this AFTER we have committed to a move out date with our current landlord, so now Cyprus and I really are in a state of limbo.  The new landlord says he will confirm with us on Monday with a yes or a no to the apartment we were promised.  He is trying to redirect us to an apartment that is half the size in a far less desirable location.    Needless to say, Cyprus and I are not amused.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We are finally done with our big move to our new apartment, settling in, and making the space liveable.  I have not been this happy with an apartment and neighborhood in such a long time!    The neighborhood is full of gorgeous brownstones, very friendly services, conveniences, etc.  It is the perfect balance of City vs Nature.    The people around here leave a little bit to be desired so far.  The area is populated by what appear to be a mix of midwestern suburbia transplants who still do not know how to smile or be friendly to a stranger (true NYers are very friendly), and transplanted hipster cuties who generate a posture that was obviously learned from bad TV shows about NYC.  It is really odd.  When you say hello to most people around here you may as well have just spit a hocker on their faces.  They react like you have just committed an atrocity!  Very weird.    Despite the lack of friendly pedestrians, I still LOVE the apartment and the neighborhood.   Here are a few pictures of the day we moved in, along with one picture of how we have managed to make the best with what we have.  We won't be able to paint for at least a couple of more weeks, but that will make a huge difference.    urlLink    Living Room view from Dining/Foyer area (before)   urlLink    Living Room area (after)   urlLink    Looking toward Dining Area/Foyer from Living Room    urlLink    Looking from my room across Living Room to Cyprus' room    urlLink    Kitchen and Bathroom off of Dining/Foyer area    urlLink    Cute Little Kitchen    urlLink    Cute Little Kitchen (view 2)    urlLink    Partial view of Cyprus' teeny Bedroom    urlLink    Partial view of Cyprus' teeny Bedroom    urlLink    Partial View of Cyprus' teeny Bedroom (looking out toward living room)    urlLink    Partial view of Troy's Bedroom    urlLink    Another partial view of Troy's Bedroom  I am so happy with how much light, air, and coziness there is in our new home!  I think I could live here for the rest of my life!  I will post more updates as we make the place into more of a home!  As you can see, the landlord did NOT paint or complete repairs... sigh...   WORK:   I am adjusting to my lack of steady work now... unemployment sure helps!  I have been busting my booty to get my web site functional, revitalized, and made into a wonderful community again, so I hope that pays off on many levels!  So far, so good.   urlLink  7 Paths     DREAMS:     1:  I dreamt that Nick asked me to get back together with him.  How sad is that.    2.  I dreamt that I was part of a secret society that had learned how to extract a liquid from a person that carried a quantifiable life force measured in years.  So you could basically extract 5 years from someone and give that 5 years of life to someone who had been seriously injured or was terminal.  Once that liquid 5 years was used, then 5 years was immediately removed from the donor's lifespan.  You could actually see within minutes the aging of the 5 years!  Anyway, this was a totally philanthropic organization who also had metaphysical knowledge as to who were the most powerful and positive and pivotal people on the planet.  If any of those key people were harmed or became sick, we would track them down and give them the viles of liquid to extend their life until their pivotal task was done!  I remember looking at my hands as I climbed a ladder and they aged before my eyes; I knew a vile of my years had been used successfully to help someone.    3.  I dreamt about a bizarre display room in the basement of a mall where these unusual watches were being sold.  I tried on this cool watch that looked like a smoothed, oddly-shaped stone.  The stone was hollowed out and opened to reveal a glowing light of either blue or green along with its hollow filled with 3 differently sized stones.  There were like 3 of one size, 6 of another, and 12 of another, all resting in this wet muddy moss.  I was very confused as to how this was a watch and as I stared at the moss and mud, the stones started moving and shaping themselves into an order.  The moss and the mud began dividing, too.  I don't know how I knew it, but I figured out that the arrangement of the moss, mud, and stones, along with the color of glowing light, indicated exactly what time it was!  I was thrilled with the concept!    4.  Finally, I dreamt that I was invited to a TV cult classic movie showing.  I was invited because people couldn't believe that I had created a movie, but it wasn't me.  The name was very similar, but it was a couple of letters off.  The movie was titled, "The Strange".    I dream the strangest dreams... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Progress is coming along on the apartment.&nbsp; This is the longest amount of time I have ever had to spend on painting, but I have so many conflicting priorities that I just have to squeeze the paint into my schedule whenever I can.&nbsp; I still have both bedrooms and the kitchen left to do, but, my god, it's almost all done...&nbsp;&nbsp; When I am completely done, I will put all the pix together in one post.&nbsp; The Living Room post is a few entries back...  &nbsp;   urlLink    urlLink   
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       On a more serious note:&nbsp;   Please help the animals...  &nbsp; I don't care what you might think about different organizations designed to help the non-human animals suffering in this world, just help the animals, if you can.    urlLink       Help Them    I got an update today from   urlLink  PETA2    alerting us to the atrocities being imposed on these amazing creatures at Columbia University in NYC.&nbsp; PETA and many other supporters of animal rights are such important pioneers in the movement toward ultimate peace.&nbsp; They may seem weird or overly-passionate, but that's because they have to make up for a world of apathy among most human beings.     Here is a copy of the letter.&nbsp; Please pass it on:       A PETA investigation has revealed the grotesque abuse of animals in laboratories at Columbia University, including baboons who are subjected to invasive surgeries and left to suffer and die in their cages without painkillers. This horrific story came to our attention because a courageous whistleblower who was a veterinarian in Columbia's laboratories stepped forward to tell us what she had witnessed. Thank goodness for good people!  Now, PETA is calling on Columbia to end three crude and cruel experiments, one of which involves artificially inducing strokes in baboons by cutting out their left eyeballs so that a critical blood vessel to their brains can be clamped. These experiments have no practical value. Animal records reveal that baboons have been left without veterinary care while they hunched over in their cages, unable to drink, chew, or even lift their heads. This is the sort of thing that you expect from a horror movie, not a prestigious university!  This abuse must stop! Please e-mail the president of Columbia University, Lee Bollinger, at bollinger@columbia.edu, asking him to put and end to all three experiments now.  To earn 500 Street Team points, BCC your e-mail message to StreetTeam@peta.org before noon on Tuesday, July 27. Be sure to use BCC so that Lee Bollinger can't see that you're also sending a copy to us. If you don't know how to do that, just send us a second copy of your message. And as a thank you for helping animals, we want to send you a pack of our brand-spanking-new Columbia Cruelty stickers. We'll e-mail you the link to the sticker order form after we receive a copy of your e-mail message.  Please forward this message to your friends and family.  For more information about Columbia's cruel tests and to watch our undercover video, visit   urlLink  http://www.ColumbiaCruelty.com    and   urlLink  http://www.peta2.com   .  Thank you for speaking up for those who cannot speak for themselves.  Sincerely, Noah Cooper Street Team Coordinator People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) 501 Front St. Norfolk, VA 23510 PETA2@peta.org   urlLink  http://www.peta2.com    
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The gang and I&nbsp;went to see Josh's latest play:&nbsp;   urlLink  HOPSCOTCH "the new york sex comedy"   .&nbsp;      &nbsp;   What started off as a disorienting, sort of startling and&nbsp;disturbing display of half-naked glittery homos and a couple of Paris Hilton/Britney Spears knock-offs eventually turned into this really endearing, totally hilarious jaunt into the world of NYC created by the expectations of mid-westerner transplants.&nbsp; The play began as if it was taking itself seriously, and then suddenly you totally get it that it is not only making fun of the corny version of NYC that is portrayed by TV shows like Sex in the City, but they were making fun of the people who move here thinking that is really what it's like!&nbsp; And even better was that the play makes fun of itself, sex, relationships,... I really loved it.  &nbsp;  Once you started to "get it" what was going on, you started seeing that each character/actor was playing their parts perfectly.&nbsp; Josh was excellent as usual, but his role as the dead, fat, horny&nbsp;Elvis in a dream sequence with a fetish for thong panties was at once creepy and brilliant.&nbsp; Brianna Leigh Hansen played the naive yet snotty, secretly-from-Oklahoma girl trying to make it big in NYC, apparently by only using her ability to put on airs.&nbsp; She played it up EXCELLENTLY.&nbsp; So much so I wanted to smack her silly.&nbsp; And oh my god, particularly striking and achingly funny was Diedre Kilgore playing the multiple facets of a sexed up psychic dominatrix hiring a detective to look for her long lost love (read: one-night stand), whom she can only describe in terms of how he approached her at the bar one night to offer a drink and how he fucked her with his maybe-10-inch dick.  &nbsp;  The whole play didn't really seem to go anywhere, but for some reason when it was all over, you really liked all the corny, sexy characters a LOT!  &nbsp;  We all wanted to go home after the play, but the cast convinced a few of us to go out for drinks for a bit, and even Cyprus went!&nbsp; And this was a Wednesday night!&nbsp; GO GRANNY!  &nbsp;  PICS of part of the cast having food and drinks after:&nbsp; 
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It is taking me forever to paint and clean and settle into our new home.  I just thought I would send up a quick  BEFORE/AFTER image of our Living Room.    We love happy colors!!   urlLink    BEFORE & AFTER
     
    
</post>


</Blog>