<Blog>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The 17th of every month is brings something intense to me.  This morning before I woke up I had a crazy dream.  For some reason it was St. Patrick's Day (the worst holiday ever) and I was in church.  The first Presbyterian Church in downtown Portland, to be exact.  Now this particular church is pretty formal -big stained glass windows, velvet pews, gigantic organ up in a loft (not a drum-set or electric guitar to be found), preachers who wear doctoral robes and bifocals and lecture from the podium.     So, in my dream, I was in this church, but instead of being in my regular place -- house right balcony -- I was in a little room behind the Chancel -- not a Sacristy, but like a focus group observation booth.  I could see the backs of the preacher's chairs.  A bunch of Irish guys came into this room to sit with me and lit up a joint.  They started smoking up and I was really appalled.  "This is CHURCH - maaaaaan.  -- not too cool"  "Chill out."  one of them said with a devil-like smile.  So I waited.    Instead of the organ prelude, a little man in a suit came out and started playing some kind of a jig on a calliope.  I thought this was weird and decided to try to sneak out of church.  The bells rang, and the acolyte came in to light the candles followed by the preachers who took their places on the chancel.  Instead of doing the call to worship, however,  Dr. Tom chucked an M80 or something into the nave.  Suddenly the congregation all had sparklers and fireworks -- and holy hell was breaking out in the sanctuary.    I tried to sneak out -- through the frenzy -- and found my self in the church basement.  A typical sterile place with a kitchen and a bunch of church ladies with pies and cakes and urns of coffee.  And Bo was there.          I knew I had to get him back to Boston.  Away from Portland -- so I told him to get in the baby backpack carrier so I could carry him out and somehow get to the airport.  He argued with me about that, but I forced him in to the carrier and hoisted him up on my back.  When I got outside, the entire downtown had changed.  The Church was on an island, surrounded by deep cracks in the earth that revealed molten lava.  There was no way to get out and get to the airport.  I kept looking at my watch -- worried about missing my flight, and frantically calling people on my cel trying to reach someone who would get us out of this mess.   Bo was getting so heavy that I could barely lift my legs from the ground.     So I went back in the chruch and tried to find some church lady that I could pay to take me to the airport.  None of them wanted to help.  Frustrated, I sat down and began to cry in the basement of this church.  That's when I woke up.           Bo has been dead for 10 months today
      
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bo's room was hellacious.             I mean it really drove me nuts how crappy he kept it.  Periodically, I'd bust in there and scream and yell about the mess -- and tell him to clean it up for Chrissake!!!     He was pretty stubborn about that.  He meant to keep a certain ambiance that I never understood.  When I look at Ed's garage, it reminds me of this room.  Bo created a sanctuary -- a place where no mother would ever want to go.  In fact,  when my sister Jana cleaned it and found a bunch of women's undergarments (presumably from women who had been in there) she wrinkled her nose and remarked that she could not imagine EVER getting naked in that room.       urlLink staticpoetboy 
      
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was an interesting day. I had coffee with my friend Jim and we talked about how I thought God put me and Ed in a cloud of oblivion while Bo was dying.  The last thing Bo said to me the night before he died was "take some really good pictures of you and Ed in Hawaii.  Get a lot of pictures of you guys.  Don't let Ed take those stupid scenery shots. I love you Mom."    So Ed and I took pictures of each other the whole day -- wanting to bring them back to show Bo. Every time we took a picture I thought about how Bo would like to see us here in this place.       The strange thing is that Ed and I both look really contemplative in all of our photos even though we were having a totally relaxing time not arguing -- nor worried about anything.  You can see even see a hint of the famous "Booth smirk" in this picture of me.        Ed is contemplating the universe here.  We found a fantastic feather for his hat on one of the beaches where we stopped off.     
      
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is Bo in the last picture I took of him a few weeks before he died.  He was posing for a headshot so he could be an extra in Gus VanSant's Elephant.     Ultimately, Bo was cremated in this very outfit.       He used to smile so much as a baby and little kid.  When he hit 14 though, he decided that smiling was not cool.... so he perfected this esoteric -- bored gaze that used to drive us crazy.  You can see the tiniest hint of the famous "Booth smirk" on his lips in this shot.    When we shopped for the the red shirt in the picture, Bo dragged Abra and me all over downtown to find the perfect THING to wear for his MLC prom.  He wanted it to EXACTLY match his hair.  What a pain-in-the-butt afternoon.  We looked everywhere and FINALLY found it at Magpie on 9th and Washington.  I was pissed off, but would do it again a million times to have him back.  
      
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Bo was so cool in this shirt. This is one of my favorite pictures.  Ed took it in our garage.  The image is the "BlueMeanies" from Yellow Submarine.  Ed and I  picked it up at the Experience Music Project during a trip to Seattle.  Bo loved the Beatles.  It totally cracked me up when he "discovered" The White Album.  We'd sit in his room and listen -- and he'd interpret the lyrics.    I'll never forget how excited and thrilled he was -- not that you could see it in this shot -- to get this shirt.    
      
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been thinking a lot about shoes.  I love them.  (Proof of that love on the Nordstrom bill).  In 1991, I was fortunate to see the six-hour production of Robert LePage's "The Dragon's Trilogy".  There was a scene that I will never forget because I was literally blinded with tears -- unable to speak or move during the intermission.  (Larry K. Ash you totally remember this).   At the end of the second hour, shoes of all sizes - babies' booties -- ladies' sandals -- gentlemen's tie-ups line the stage to conjure up a 1940s shoestore. Earlier, the shoeboxes have been a girl's toy village and Quebec City's Chinatown, and the booties were all the audience saw of a baby being born to a shoe salesman's wife.   A loving couple - a girl and her soldier boyfriend - skate around the stage to the sound of the "Skaters' Waltz."  As the music grows, the soldier, now joined by other uniformed men, marches across the sand in ice skates, --  cutting through the sand and trampling the shoes.  The salesman rushes about, vainly trying to rearrange them into pairs, but the soldiers kick them back into the sand. The salesmen gives up: the destruction is complete. The happy image of a shoestore has become as shocking as the photograph of children's shoes piled outside the Auschwitz ovens.  The shoes are a symbol of identity, the biological becoming of age. (The dictionary of symbols, under: shoes, 1986: D. Kuper, shoes).   I've read that the symbolism of the shoes which is related to the world of the dead, as well as the symbol of a passenger, is a Western one.  Take, for example,  the custom where shoes or boots (or socks) are put near the fire place the night before Christmas.  Since the main idea of all passage rites is visiting the world of the dead and being born again is maybe the reason why passage rites connected to the life cycle include a great role of the shoes, like saving baby shoes and bronzing them.  Smashing a wine glass with your shoe at a Jewish wedding. Dying with your boots on.    I did a Bible search on shoes and found an interesting thing:  When Moses blessed the tribes of Israel before his death, he mentioned something about shoes.   In Deuteronomy 33:25 he said, "Thy shoes shall be iron and brass". Both of these metals can withstand a lot of heat. But, those shoes might totally suck to wear.  They would, however, stand up very well as protection against the various "enemies" of our walk which lie in the pathway of LIFE.   God also told Moses to take off his shoes because he was standing on holy ground. Does this mean that God was demonstrating that "holy ground" does not require shoes in order to "walk" comfortably?      Remember the end of Snow White when they found the evil witch "Then a pair of red-hot iron shoes was brought into the room with tongs and set before her, and these she was forced to put on and to dance in them until she could dance no longer, but fell down dead . . ."  Think of all the fairy tales about shoes.    	The Red Shoes 	Cinderella 	The Twelve Dancing Princesses 	The Shoes of Fortune 	   I think that shoes symbolize a person's character and that shoes  have a special place in everybody's life.    I've had Bo's first pair of Reeboks hanging from my rear-view mirrors for 15 years now.  I still wear his Doc Martins from time to time.    Bo died with his shoes off -- But his earthly remains went to the Great Beyond wearing these:       Here's to Shoes -- And everyone who loves them.
      
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      StaticPoetBo     I love this picture because Bo is relaxed and smiling.  He and Izabel took pictures one afternoon.   Here is a picture of lovely Iz.       I wish she's still come around.  Hey Iz!!  If you are out there ... call me.  We miss you.  
      
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Pretty Mom" said Bo when he took this picture outside last spring.      
      
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      THE HARLICKIN EXCENTRIX  spider bites are painful they burn and itch and swell i get bittin everytime  well she bothers me  im always teased i dont know how to feel she kissed me and she held my hand but her feelings are not real she became an addiction i carefully got hooked it seemed she liked me to  but thats just how things looked  life is boring and im to preditable its all the same, teenage angst our glass is never full our little group grows tired from the little games we play i care too much, it hurts inside i dont know why i stay  run away leave this place sumwhere warm and dark sleeping on the ground blind to life destroy yourself but never look around  i always feel attracted to the hurtful painful ones with my self destructive nature im glad i dont like guns to die would be a petty thing i care to much to try its so hard to be different when everybody tries i try real hard to live this life but everybody dies  run away leave this place sumwhere warm and dark sleeping on the ground blind to life destroy yourself but never look around  Bo Booth 2001     
      
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Random Wishes     I wish Bo hadn’t died. I wish I had him back.  I wish you wouldn’t be afraid to speak his name.  Bo lived and was very important to me. I need to hear that he was important to you also.  When I cry and get emotional when you talk about Bo I wish you knew that it isn’t because you have hurt me.   I wish you wouldn’t "kill" Bo again by removing his pictures from your home.  I might be sad and I might cry, but I wish you would let me talk about Bo.  I wish you wouldn’t expect my grief to be over in six months. I wish you could understand that my grief will never be over. I will suffer the death of Bo until the day I die.  I wish you wouldn’t expect me "not to think about it" or to "be happy."   When I say "I’m doing okay," I wish you could understand that I don’t "feel" okay and that I struggle daily.  I wish you understood that when Bo died, a big part of me died with him. I am not the same person I was before Bo died, and I will never be that person again.  I wish very much that you could understand — understand my loss and my grief, my silence and my tears, my void and my pain. AND I pray daily that you will never understand.  
      
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HOWL  of Pain.  That's what I'm drunk and doing when I look at these pictures.   HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!     HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!      HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!      HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!      HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!      HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!      HOOOOOOWL!!!!!!!!!!    I almost can't stand how beautiful he was.   Damn it.
      
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really didn't think Bo did any drugs except for smoking pot, drinking coffee, cigarettes, and the an occasional beer. In retrospect, I should have looked closer. Closer into his world -- listened just a little bit longer to him when he talked. Paid attention.........  Because hindsight being 20/20 and all -- Bo gave me a lot of clues. He talked about opiates. He knew about Methadone....even to the extent of lecturing me on the evils of treating Heroin addiction with the stuff. "It hangs out in your body for a long time", he said - this expert son of mine. "That's why withdrawl from methadone is so much harder than heroin."  Please Bo. Dont ever take heroin. It's so dangerous. I don't want you to die.  "I wont Mom." "I swear."   How many moms have heard those words from their children as they wiggle out of babyhood?  "I swear Mom -- really, I'm not stupid."  I can't recall how many times I've said that to my Mom -- except that I'm a girl so it went something like:  ***exasperated sigh ***** eye-roll ****** "duh mom. I'm not stupid... I swear to god . (turning to dad) Pleeeeeeese let me go out tonight...."   And how many times I turned around and did that exact stupid thing I said I wouldn't do.    Cut out of school with Debbie Schlissel   Smoked joints before school with Marybeth  Got drunk and screwed a marine superbowl sunday 1986 and got knocked up    There's a big list.    But that's about me. Not Bo. I'm 40. I've got some wear and tear to show for all of the stupid things I've done. I'm alive. Bo isn't.       Life is a risky business. 
      
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      FANTASTICO!!!!           
      
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Amnesty        "Please."  (that's all he needs) "what!?" (you wanted to say something)...  "SO SAY IT!" she said with anger in her voice  The angrier she got the more trapped he felt.....  "Well, um-m-m-m-m..." he mumbled. "Whatever!" she groaned in frustration.  and then she was gone.  and he was alone.  bundled up in his blanket of cold feelings.  Alone.  She was finished with him. He was finished with himself.   
      
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      have I told y'all I miss being a MoM??  I really do.   The sweet sweet feeling of having your child think you are so cool.  Loving you -- YO!! hang out with my friends.        Yeah,  that lasted awhile.  Until Bo was maybe 12 or so.  But even as an adolescent, he brought his peeps around all the time.  I rememember most days after he was done with school, he'd stop by my office...and wrangle 20 bucks out of me -- which he mostly spent at the Roxy.  Coffee and cigarettes.  Fries.....intense conversation.    I miss having his friends over -- I loved cooking for them.  The tuna melts for Tony and Robbie,  the veggie pizzas for Abra .. the half and half veggie / meat pizzas for me and Iz the veggie melts the tofu pad thai for Bo and Ana.   The contraband cigarettes and beers in the back yard with everyone....  thinking I was connecting....but obviously being so fucking far away that I didn't even know that my own kid was taking drugs that would kill him.  Damnit all to hell.  If I could lay my head down and sleep forever -- just to see and talk to Bo one more time I'd do it.   I miss him so much.  Stabs in my heart all the time. 
      
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Clouds  As I was flying out of Chicago on Sunday I had a waking dream where I saw Bo.  As is my custom, I settled in to my seat, pulled out the pillow, and promptly fell asleep before take-off. It's really the best way to fly.  Get in.  Sleep as much as possible.  I like the window seat because i can scrunch up next to the glass and lay my head on the tiny airplane pillow and go oblivious for the first hour and a half of the flight.  We must have been making our ascent when we encountered turbulence. The dark western Illinois sky bounced us around -- up and down, back and forth, side to side ...  half aware of my seat mate digging her nails into her palms and gasping, I remember reaching over and patting her knee.  "don't worry.  it's cool.  tornados never happen this time of day."    As I was drifting off again to the up and down jerking of the plane, i remember thinking "gosh.  it sure wouldn't suck to die this way.  it would be quick.  i'd see Bo again."    and then he appeared to me.  in red.  a red jumpsuit.  all polyester.  all super-fly.  and his hair was brown.  he was floating in the clouds.  smiling at me.  peaceful.  smug.  vague.  very.... Bo-like.  i felt very comfortable -- peaceful even...like i could sleep right through a plane crash and maybe see him again.    it wouldn't be my fault.  just an accident.  and then, i could be with Bo.  and then i was conscious.  my face pressed onto the window glass -- i blinked my reluctant eyes open to the blinding white light.  in front of me was the most brilliant beautiful blue sky.  way up above the storm we had flown. and the new grownd below was a snowy landscape of cumulus clouds streaked with gold and pink.  it looked like Heaven.  and for a second i thought i was there.  in beautiful heaven -- looking for Bo.
      
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      About Me: i am bo. i am a pacifist, i am an idealist. i am 16 i am cynical. i am blue eyed. my hair is dyed red. i wear grungy thrift store clothes. i live in portland. i love music. i hate violence. i like thinking. i like writing. im that boy with the porceline eyes im that boy who never trys im that boy whos never rite im that boy with the wasted life        Turn Ons: intelligent cynical beutific open minded idealistic girl with a sense of irony. drugs and self destruction are very sexy but i try to avoid them. Poet boy meets dreamer girl they trip to melt in bubble world immersed in life philosphy they speak in quit poetry Static boy dynamic girl they live fast young and bored feel now dark pain afliction they take love drug no addiction        Turn Offs: violence closed mindedness those women at concerts that stand up on sumones shoulders and take there shirts of then scream "WOOOO!!" basicly, aply that mentality to any situation   
      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was cleaning out some boxes of stuff this weekend and I came across this picture.   Danika, Bo, and Brittany in 1987. We all lived in a small house in Asheville, NC -- out BeaverDam Road.          When I moved to Interlochen I lost touch with Brittany and Danika and their Mom.  A few years ago we re-connected.   Nilda and her kids live in Beaverton.   Funny.  I called Nilda when Bo was born.  She called me when he died.
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I left my heart in San Francisco      Ed and I went to SFO on June 17 for the 1 year anniversary of Bo's death. We sprinked some of his ashes off of this bridge into the bay.       Fly away Bo.&nbsp;  
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Psalm for the Lament of Bo   OH God. Hear my wails. Hear my screams.   Hear my damage.  Bo is dead.  My son, my progeny. Oh my adored. Oh. Oh. Oh.  I am dark and restless.   Stabbing at your angels as they try to comfort me.  I suppose I should thank You for the other times when you have come in the machine.  But now, I can only shake my head and ask you why have you done this terrible thing.  God.   Wash away my anger.  Take my cries and wring them like a sponge upon my head bowed down  So that my tears   Bloom in me the shriveled flower left so much to die.  Amen.    
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mugging      &nbsp;  Can you believe how young we were once?  And how 'bout those ugly glasses?  We were clowns, the two of us....These were Bo's favorite pictures of me.  He kept them on the wall next to his bed.  You can even see the tack marks.  It's funny how little things like a $1 strip of mall-booth photos can last longer than a person.&nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bo always preached tolerance.&nbsp; He believed that people should not be judgemental.&nbsp; Bo pushed the envelope a bunch.&nbsp; One day, while he was in summer school he wore a dress to school to mess with the "homophobes" in class.&nbsp; I never got to see him in this dress.&nbsp; My friends from Japan did -- and took these pictures .        Last night I was touched by memories of Bo and his tolerance.&nbsp; Here is an excerpt from a note I sent a friend last night after doing outreach:   "So, before I go to sleep tonight, I wanted to recount this small little sliver of grace and peace I felt doing outreach this evening. &nbsp;Remember that the last thing I mentioned to you was that woman I was volunteering with -- and how I just didn't like her and was not looking forward to working with her again? &nbsp;And, &nbsp;how it was my hang-up and I was so judgmental (just like Bo always said)?   I got to YBR early, &nbsp;and after reading the log and stuffing my bag with condoms and foot powder, &nbsp;I sat alone on the couch and asked god to grant me the patience to&nbsp;just be with this woman tonight and accept her for who she is without personalizing her experience. &nbsp;I wanted to get into a good place- BEFORE getting all preoccupied and agro -- so that I would not have a shitty time doing outreach -- just being pissed at her the entire time. &nbsp;   When she showed up -- bummed out and complaining and not motivated to go -- I took a deep breath and I started asking her about her day and her life. &nbsp;As we walked -- I discovered why she is so sad and so miserable -- and why she does some of the things she does that never made sense to me before. &nbsp;She is young, &nbsp;the same age I was when I had Bo and on the street. &nbsp;Only she had her baby and gave him away so that he would have a better life. &nbsp;And now she is off the streets and doing outreach and really missing her baby. &nbsp;Whoa.......humbling huh?   I had the best night in outreach -- ever. &nbsp;I was relaxed and open to the kids. &nbsp;I didn't have the usual flashes of annoyance when someone reached into my box and grabbed a handful of condoms -- or bitched because I was out of socks -- I just accepted that things were the way they are just because. &nbsp;I sat with these children and looked at their tats and drawings, and one even showed me the sonogram of her six month pregnancy. &nbsp;And I kept seeing Bo in their eyes, and smiles, and shrugs, and shy shuffling feet. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;In the three hours of walking and talking -- in the 120 kids I saw last night -- I got the gift of seeing Bo alive again -- through them -- because I stopped jumping to conclusions and passing judgment before I saw what was really there."&nbsp;    So thank you Bo -- for helping us all to see what is really there.    
      
</post>


</Blog>