<Blog>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finished my move-out ... finally. I'm tired now. I guess I can always sleep on the bus. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hate moving. Why does it seem like I have so much crap?   It'll be a relief when I'm done. Though, I probably won't get much rest afterward.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally back in Arcata. More delays at the airports in Los Angeles and San Francisco. But I made it back. Now to finish up moving out of my apartment. I hate moving.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm down visiting my parents this week, since I'm "going off to war" on Saturday. I'll tell you, yesterday must not have been a good day for United Airlines. I got to the airport in Arcata and my flight was delayed an hour. Then they announced the flight was cancelled and everyone on that flight was being sent through Sacramento. They couldn't even get me all the way to Ontario, I had to go through L.A. My flight wasn't the only one. I saw a few more flights from Sacramento and San Francisco get cancelled as well. And after all my trouble, they couldn't even give me something as small as a meal voucher.   Here's hoping the trip back to Arcata goes a little more smoothly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Changes are afoot. I was going to completely redesign my site, but decided to wait till I learn CSS and come up with some good ideas. I did manage to figure out how to make blogger match the rest of my site though (I bet you noticed that already.)    I'm leaving on Saturday for Ft. Lewis, Wash. I've been activated with my National Guard unit and we're going to Ft. Lewis to prepare for our overseas deployment. I think we all know what "overseas" means. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today is the day. Going to Ft. Lewis.  Put some new pics up in the gallery last night. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Been down in Petaluma the last few days getting ready to deploy with A Co. of the 579th Engineer Battalion. Tomorrow we're leaving for Ft. Lewis, Washington to in-process (BS, BS, and more BS ... oh, and some shots) and begin training for our deployment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Busy, busy, busy up here at Ft Lewis. Update more when I get the chance. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally, a little time off. But not much. Gonna put some new pics up. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Still up at Ft. Lewis.Still going through a lot of BS. Supposed to get the old wisdom teeth out soon ... Oh joy!  . Will it ever stop raining in this stupid state?   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Still around. Going to Ft. Irwin very soon to finish our training before heading overseas. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We're down at Ft Irwin now. We're in Circus tents, but I'm not dressing like a clown. Nice to finally see the sun again.   I feel like I'm in prison being surrounded by a fence and guard posts.    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Still at Ft. Irwin. I've been learning how to drive the 2.5-ton truck. It's big and slow, that's all there is to it. The sun finally came out for more than a few hours.   I've also been learning the Javelin anti-tank weapon. It's pretty cool, but heavy. We finally get some time off next week. Shortly after that we'll be off to Kuwait, then to Iraq. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Saying "goodbye" sucks.   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Back at Ft. Irwin now. That time off wasn't long enough.   I bought a new laptop this week. Let me tell you ... Never buy a computer from Best Buy! The computer I bought had a virus on it. I formatted and reinstalled Windows and the virus was back! It was on one of the installation CD's. Of course, their checks came up with no problems when I returned it, so I had to pay a 15% restocking fee. They will rip you off.   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally! We have our time off. But not without the usual complications and hoops to jump through.   Nothing like having all your stuff being searched 5 or 6 times before you can leave.   Oh well, that's in the past. Time to relax.   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi again from Iraq. It's starting to warm up.   This body armor doesn't help keep the heat out, but if it keeps me safe I'm ok with it. More to come later ... 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, we're finally here in Iraq. Less sand and more grass where we are. Not too much excitement here, the occasional emergency siren, but nothing ever comes of it. I guess they want us to run for PT anyway. Still working on getting pictures up from here. Till next time ... 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi there. It's really hot here.   I finally got some pictures up from the Kuwait and Iraq. Not much else to report. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nothing like 3 hours of sleep to make your day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Still here in Iraq. The Easter Bunny didn't come.   Pretty much just sat around all day. How exciting. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Too many chiefs and not enough indians.   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Five missions in three days. What are they thinking?! At least that is over now. Time to sleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We did good this week. We caught two bad guys and blew up a cache of explosives. Here's hoping we do a lot more good in the future. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I put some more pictures up in the gallery. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Put up some new pictures. More are on the way soon. We went and did some night firing last night at the range at LSA Vanguard. Range control had to come out and shut us down because we were scaring the ICDC (Iraqi Civil Defense Corps) with our tracers.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Been a while, so I figure I'd write something here.  What's up with the mail here? At first I was getting lots and lots of mail, now I'm hardly getting any?   Maybe someone is changing the name and giving it to someone else. GIVE ME MAIL!!!    Someone get those kids away from the Humvee!    Haven't had anything get stuck lately. I guess they're watching for the water now. The guys at the gate have also learned how to move the spike strips when vehicles are going through.    I put some new pictures up in the gallery. Hope they're interesting for you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What happens when you try to drive a 10,000 pound M1114 Humvee over soggy marshland? A sticky situation.   Luckily, I was able to pull it out with my Humvee and manage to keep myself from getting stuck too. Who told them to go that way anyway?   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Put up more pictures. Happy Mothers Day, mom.    It's hot! We had Quick Reaction Force duty yesterday and we ended up spending about 9 hours sitting in the sun providing security for about 5 tanks because one of them became stuck in a ditch. What were we needed for? I don't know. M1 tanks have a 120-mm main gun, a .50-caliber machine gun and an M240C 7.62-mm machine gun. All we had was a couple Humvees and some M16s.  In other news. Did I mention it's hot? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Time off? Yes, it's true! I had a day off today. I spent it hiding from the company, so I could enjoy it in peace. Who would have thought that driving around in circles could be so tiring?  Would somebody turn off the heater please?! And while you're at it, sweep up all this dirt and dust.  Again, I ask: Please get the kids away from the @#$% truck!    No, you can't have my sunglasses.    Do we really need permission to do something that we know is the right thing to do? Isn't free will what makes us what we are?  What would happen if everyone listened to the suggestions of everyone else and took them into consideration? If nobody went on a power trip, or tried to quell somebody's opinion just because they are lower on the ladder. What if people treated each other with respect and didn't demean others just because they do not agree? What if those higher on the ladder actually did something for themselves once in a while instead of making the unwilling do it. What would happen if people could simply take a joke?   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I said turn the heater down! And why hasn't anyone swept up this dust?   When did one job with specific duties turn into the "same" job with different duties?  What will happen when all our vehicles are broken? Will we walk for everything? I'd like to see that. By they way, how long till mine is fixed?  No, your tank can't fit there. And no, the road will not hold it, so stop trying.  Is it time to go home yet? I can be ready to go in five minutes.  "We, the unwilling, led by the unknowing, are doing the impossible for the ungrateful. We have done so much, for so long, with so little, we are now qualified to do anything with nothing." - Anonymous 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Argh!!!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's still hot. And our non-working generator and air conditioners aren't doing anything to help. You know it's bad when it's hotter in the tent, than outside (and it's 107 outside!) Still waiting on the trailers. Some day.  I finally did some exciting work over here (because staring at empty fields is akin to watching grass grow, literally). We had a demolitions mission with Explosive Ordinance Disposal the other day. We got to dispose of some old Soviet-made missles with RB8 submunitions inside. All in all, we picked up 560+ submunitions and 5 missles. Then we BLEW THEM UP!   Now that's some real engineer work.  I put a few more pictures up in the gallery. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Make it stop! Make it stop! Make it stop! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Only the dead have seen the end of war." -- Plato  We lost two great soldiers on Tuesday. Cpl. Patrick McCaffrey Sr. and Lt. Andre Tyson. McCaffrey was my bunkmate and one of my best friends. Lt. Tyson was my platoon leader. It still a bit of a shock to think that they're both gone. I keep hoping that I'm going to wake up and it will all have been a dream. I wish it was. They're in a better place now. A place away from all this madness.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, I never mentioned we finally got our trailers. It's nice to be able to come "home" to an air-conditioned, private place to sleep. It only took "4-6 weeks." Not really.  I put some more pics up in the  urlLink Gallery , as well as some videos.  Back to work tomorrow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finally got a picture gallery again. Just click  urlLink here  to go to it, or you can click on the link in the corner.  Today was the memorial for Sgt. McCaffrey and Lt. Tyson. It was very emotional. Everyone had wonderful words to say about them. They were honored with a bagpiper playing "Amazing Grace" and a horn playing "Taps," as well as a rifle salute. We'll all miss both of them. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Heat + humidity = Miserable day.  I put a few more pics up and a video.  I had duty at the ING camp yesterday. Me and another soldier taught them how to throw a baseball at water bottles. It was a good time waster. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Put up some new pictures.  No big news to report. Just the same old stuff. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Back to the grindstone.    We have Combat Camera coming out with us today. Though, I don't know why anyone would want to watch what we do out there. Watching us watch the fields has got to be about exciting as watching paint dry.    Put some new pics up.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Things are the same as they've ever been. It's still really hot. In the 120's and 130's.  Anyone know when we're supposed to get out of here?  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Are things ever going to change? It seems no matter what we say or try to do to bring about change, it doesn't seem to work.     Why do people try to stifle others' opinions, yet get mad if someone disagrees with their own? Everyone is entitled to their own opinion, so don't belittle them because you don't agree.    Everyone is not perfect. So why try to act like you are?    Quit flip flopping. You aren't impressing anyone by taking both sides of the fence when your opinion of the minute helps make you look good at the expense of others.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>