<Blog>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      A terribly amusing way to spend some quality time with your computer.  Build your own hell!      Bill Gates  Circle I Limbo   Riceboys, General asshats  Circle II Whirling in a Dark & Stormy Wind   Slow drivers in the left lane  Circle III Mud, Rain, Cold, Hail & Snow   Scientologists  Circle IV Rolling Weights   DMV Employees  Circle V Stuck in Mud, Mangled  River Styx   Parents who bring squalling brats to R-rated movies  Circle VI Buried for Eternity  River Phlegyas   Osama bin Laden  Circle VII Burning Sands   Saddam Hussein  Circle IIX Immersed in Excrement   NAMBLA Members  Circle IX Frozen in Ice   urlLink Design your own hell  
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Our story begins as our heroes return from their latest foray into the depths of a nearby dungeon.  Weighed down with loot and carrying their sorely wounded companions, the adventurers trudge happily towards town.  Suddenly, disaster strikes.  The skies go from clear blue to pitch black, wind whips around the travellers, and rain drenches them to the skin.  It's an unpleasant day.  Groaning, the companions quickly set up tarps and attempt to light a fire, but have no success.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And we're live!  Is there a point?  Is there any reason to create such a beast?  No!  Outstanding.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw a couple of neat things on the roads in the last couple days.  The first was a store that I can only assume did car "tricking out."  The name of the store was "Carsmetics."  Heh.  I like that one.  The second was a road sign that used to say something that has now slipped my mind, but now, thanks to some sort of (probably illegal) modifications, says "try."  I just thought that was cool.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a blog; it's rarely used; is there a purpose?  Not likely.  I guess my real difficulty is that I have no idea who or what my audience will (could) be.  When I send an email I know who's going to get it.  Write a paper, draw a picture, build something: the recipient is always pre-defined.  But this...well, thanks to the Internet I don't have a clue who'd ever see it.  That's both exhilerating and frightening at one and the same time.  Hmm.  It's freeing as well.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's no excuse for it, but I'm sitting home alone and doing nothing but watching TV and surfing the web. How bad is that? I know I should just get up and go out, but I just don't  want to bother with it.  I'm sure I'll come up with something, but the wait until then is annoying.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Psychology Of Torture   I'm still trying to work my mind around the idea of the morality of torture.  I don't have much of a problem seeing it (sometimes) as justified, but moral?  That's another question entirely.  This article has another few points to contemplate.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's about the only reason I can come up with for my feelings of general malaise.  The reason I'm wondering if it has something to do with rhythyms is that this tends to happen every once in a while, and to go away just as quickly.  There's nothing that sparks it, but neither is there anything that ends it.  Now it's just a matter of time before it goes away.  The worst part is that there's so much good in my life right now, that there really is no reason for any kind of depression.  Ah well, time heals all.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.geocities.com/preciousgurl147  What is this girl thinking?  How much can I believe such a page?  She puts up an attractive picture and declares, "All I want is sex."  It seems too easy, and way too perfect.  I dunno.  Too good to be true usually is, right?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What are the right words to Robert Frost's poem, Fire and Ice?  Specifically, I'm looking for the right word in the following lines.  "I think I know enough of hate, To [blank] that for destruction, ice"  I've seen it both as "know," and "say."  The Internet, formerly infallible, comes up with both versions at about a 50-50 ratio.  So, which is right?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You all know the rule: "I before E, except after C, unless sounding like A, as in neighbor and weigh, unless it's weird."  Well, I've found a weird one, but in the other direction.  "Deficient" breaks the rule, sort of, so what I figured was to tack on a phrase to the end.  "...it's weird, or deficient."  Yeah, it sounds odd, but it's grammatically correct, and that's about the best I can do.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was totally astounded earlier today.  A blogger I've been reading for a couple months,  urlLink No Loyal Knight , put up a link to an article he'd written years ago.  I was flabbergasted to discover that this article was part of the infamous "Dirty GM Tricks" series run in  urlLink Pyramid , a gaming e-zine.  I loved those articles.  The best part is that I was introduced to  urlLink No Loyal Knight  by a friend who cannot stand to be in a room with anyone even discussing RPGs.  Heh.  It seems it IS a small world after all.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've recently realized that the term "aether" really should be involved in some sort of accepted scientific doctrine.  It's just too darn good a word to be relegated to the backwaters of the late 19th and early 20th centuries' random scientifically experimental attempts.  I mean, just look at it...aether.  How cool is that.  Speak it aloud, let the syllables roll off your tongue.  I'm not even sure how many syllables it has.  Doesn't that just rock?  I guess I should now toss out some conventional scientific theory that could be enhanced by the addition of our "word of the day," but I'm not going to.  I'm just going to let all of you nonexistent readers out there come up with your own theories as to how best we could serve "aether."  Sweet.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>