<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So late, so tired, must post   I've been trying to keep up with a daily post routine, and so far so good. But tonight there isn't anything interesting going on. Well I did make the mistake of engaging my very passionately political sister in a debate about the current presidential administration and I was so not prepared. That'll teach me!  In case you're wondering, I don't have much of a I-hate-Bush or I-love-Bush position. It's really a case by case issue. So in  case  you were wondering, here's my political opinion run down:  1. Bush and the FMA= I hate Bush 2. Bush and the global gag rule = I hate Bush 3. Bush and current committment to environmental standards= Ehh. Bush could do better. 4. Bush and his Evangelical Christian bedfellows= Ehh. He should pick better friends. 5. Bush and the Iraqi conflict= Conflicted (so conflicted that I usually choose to answer any question regarding that issue with "No comment.") 6. Bush and his primary control and residence no longer being Texas= I love Bush.  Of course all of this is subject to change (though I doubt it.) And as I've stated before, I only really know  two  things:  1. Blockbuster charges way to much frigging money for DVD rentals. 2. Life is just better after a Raspberry Blue Otterpop. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     JDate may be worth it after all.   I haven't logged into my account on JDate in ages!  So, because my boss is gone for the day and I'm so tired of looking at specs for digital cameras, I thought I'd sign on and see what's happening.  By the way, not much is.   I noticed that I had quite a few messages waiting for me but being notoriously cheap (please! I'm not spending $49.95 to read "Hey, I liked your profile. Wanna chat?"), and JDate being so enterprising, one has to be a paying member to acutally read those messages. So I'll probably never know what they say. Of course a fun little thing JDate has are records of who has looked at  your  profile.  It turns out Mr. FlyReeves has (please turn your attention above to the elegant profile of the brooding "filmmaker/teacher/student".) And I just might reconsider paying that $49.95.   (Sorry Mr. FlyReeves. I just thought you would be a good addition to my daydreams.)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sprechen Sie Deutsches?   My friend J. just got back on Sunday from Germany and France. I knew at some point he was going (I rarely remember anything if I don't write it down) but I'd forgotten when (see previous parenthetical remark).    Last night I stayed at the office until late, and was goofing around with AIM, when he signed on.  I hadn't talked to him in several weeks but I assumed it was because he was traveling for his job. But nope, he was galavanting across Germany. The Germany he had cryptically invited  me  to visit with him last fall.   At least I think he invited me. He mentioned it in passing once or twice to the effect of "Hey, I might be going to Germany with my friends B. and S. You wanna go?"  Now my ears translated that to: "I might be going to Germany with my friends. Do you want to go?"   Doesn't seem too far off from what he really said, now does it? Of course I replied with an enthusiastic "Hell yeah I do!" And then not so much talk about it after that.  My assumption was that as we got closer to the actualy date of departure, he'd let me know when to buy my ticket, what to pack, how much money, etc. But I never heard anything. That was okay really, because I'm almost 100% sure I forgot about it anyhow.    Imagine my shock when last night after I had wished him a belated birthday and commented that trying to track him down was like trying to track a member of the CIA down (it looks so easy on TV!) he said "you should have tried looking in Germany."   And then the conversation went something like this:  E.:  "Hey cool! But wait...isn't that the same Germany that you had invited  me  to visit with you?"    J.:  "Yep. Sorry, but I was on a mission. And I don't think it would have been as well carried out if you were there."  E.:  "You know, communism fell in '89. What mission could you possibly have to carry out?"  J.:  "Mission Hot German Chicks. I couldn't have Cute & Funny Texas Chick trailing me.  That would have just made it messy."  E.:  "Cute & Funny Texas Chick? Ok, I forgive you."
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Service ain't what it used to be   I had dinner tonight at an old childhood favorite. I probably haven't eaten there since I was ten or so, and thus my memories of the food are well...that of a ten year old.    So the food sucked. I can handle that. It was noisy and crowded. No problem.  But service ain't what it used to be. Or is it? At one point during dinner, I asked the waitress where the restroom was.  You'd have thought I asked her if she knew what the word for  chalupa  was in Japanese. Then with all the charm and grace of a drug dealer, she said "Follow me. I'll take you to it." I politely declined.  The last time anyone  took  me to the restroom, I was still in diapers (at least I'm assuming that's the last time because frankly I've been doing it pretty well on my own for the last twenty years or so.)  The whole incident made me laugh so hard, I tipped her a $5.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dorkus malorcus    I'm wearing my cool red  urlLink Reef  flip flops at the office today, but they pretty much pick up a ton of static electricity when I walk on the carpet. As a result I keep shocking the hell out of myself when I open a door (metal door handle + build up of static electricity = discharge of static electricity, resulting in sharp pain and profanities.)  So I finally got wise and started using my car key to discharge the static before I open the door, thus preventing pain and profanities.  The result? A really cool blue-white electrical arc! Wanting to impress my co-workers (and myself; don't ask why), I spent five minutes scooting across the carpet to bulid up static, looking like an ass and providing cause for lots of laughter, but to no avail.  I couldn't reproduce that cool phenomenon of electricity.  Hi. My name is E. I'm a  Dorkus malorcus .
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "You lost your girl. You lost your job. And now you lost your cool."   Last night I rented  urlLink Love the Hard Way  from Blockbuster.    First, let me tell you about the interesting exchange I had with the clerk at Blockbuster.    But before that, here's what I know. 1. Blockbuster likes to charge the hell out of its customers for DVD rentals.  That's just a given, and I've learned to live with it.   2. I rent from Blockbuster more than I like to admit, so I live happily in denial that I  do  have a life and I'm not just trying to make myself feel better by repeating that to myself over any over.  So since I'm already bitter that Blockbuster = way too much money, I'm not very keen on buying into their specials (i.e. seven free rentals plus DVD of "Lord of the Rings 3" [aka longest movie EVER] for $29.99). But like all good store clerks, this one was compelled to try to sell me the special anyway. I stood firm. I resisted. In the end, I prevailed.  But it didn't take long before he sucker-punched me with...  unlimited rentals . For a "small fee" of $35.00 a month, I could rent as many movies as I wanted with no late fees (and some other perks I don't remember.) As I stood there, my resolve beginning to weaken, I thought "I can't sign up for that!  That's just over the top loser-ville. Besides, I don't come in here  that  much. I'll just tell him I don't rent enough to really use a service like that.  Yeah! That's what I'll tell him."  Ready with my strong-as-steel comeback, the clerk politely says "I see on your Blockbuster account that you are quite a frequent renter. This would really save you money over the long run."  Doh! Damn the Blockbuster network! Damn computers! I was caught. I couldn't escape.  I just gave him my check for $12.96 (there were some late fees) and meekly took my movie.  Ahh..sweet humility.  So with that being said, I proceeded to watch a very sexy, not terrifically outstanding, but yielding-some-good lines flick. And Adrien Brody is still my #1.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [clever title here...later]   Besides not feeling particularly clever at this moment, I'm also not sure what the hell I want to post here.  I'm beginning to understand that the only one who is reading this blog with any regularity is...me.  And that's okay.  So now, having finally identified my faithful audience, let me say Welcome! This post is for you:  *Thanks for stopping by and enjoying "Everyday Baby." This blog was started as an expression of a follower who felt the need to hitch her wagon to the Blogging Bullet Train.  This is literally the seventh attempt at making her blog "stick." So far, it's stuck.  *E., author of this blog, is 26 and lives in a small apartment in the very northside of her home city with her few but valued possessions and two rescued cats, who she reminds frequently that they were "free and can be sent to the pound at any moment" if they don't "stop _________, right now!" (add "Scratching furniture", "jumping in the shower while I'm in it!", "Playing Indy 500 over the couch!", or any combination thereof to that blank.) But knowing that she would probably just be heartbroken if she ever gave them away, they stay.  *E. graduated from college two and a half years ago with a degree in both marketing and management and aspired to working for a strategic marketing firm in urban development. Currently, E. is working for a small, non-profit public health organization and those dreams have changed: marry rich! (kidding...sort of)  *Between taking frequent breaks to read her own blog and the blogs of other very entertaining people, E. enjoys listening to the great mixed CDs made by her  urlLink sister , ironing everythinig in sight with her brand new iron (if you'd only seen the ruin of her favorite skirt by the  urlLink POS iron  she bought last Sunday, you'd understand), learning how to cook Indian and Middle Eastern Vegetarian food, and getting acquainted with  urlLink Carrie, Samantha, Charlotte, & Miranda  (some people are late bloomers.)  *E. is particularly found of the color pink (shoes, purses, skirts, flowers, etc.), bands she never would have listened to if her sister hadn't made her the mixed CD (The Darkness, Franz Ferdinand), movies with subtitles, berries of any kind, and naps.  She also enjoys reading books by Armistead Maupin and expressing her opinion about anything to anyone.  I hope you've enjoyed this little "About the Author" segment.  Sure it's gratuitous and a little (okay a lot) self-serving, but it is my blog. See you soon! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Grease, Salt, Sugar, Alcohol: America's 4 Food Groups   On Monday night my friends and I saw "Super Size Me." It was a strange and sad look at the fast food industry (specifically McDonald's).  The amount of garbage that people (myself included) will eat is amazing! Thousands of pounds of sugar, fat, and salt every year course through the bodies of millions and millions of Americans (no doubt, it tastes so good!)  Of course after watching this film and seeing this guy eating fast food three times a day, my friends and I were ready to call it quits on grease, salt, and sugar for good.   So this morning on the way to work, having already forgotten my pledge against the Four Food groups, I stopped at Chik Fil'A for a sausage biscuit, mini, greasy hash browns and and Diet Coke.  And frankly, it wasn't worth it.  Every image from the movie keeps playing over in my head!  Blech!  Even now as I'm writing this, I have the slight apprehension that I might be revisited by that breakfast any minute.    This isn't the first time that after being exposed to the "real truth" did I have a change of heart.  I included some links to other people who've changed the way I see the meat industry, tobacco, and firearms.  The only impact however is that I still don't own a gun.  But interesting nonetheless.  Interesting Links: 1.  urlLink SuperSize Me!  2. Howard Lyman,  urlLink Mad Cowboy  3.  urlLink Jeffrey Wigand  4. Michael Moore's  urlLink Bowling for Columbine 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mazal tov!   In my opinion a marriage is something to celebrate no matter the genders of the couple to be wed.   To all of the men and women who married the loves of their lives in San Francisco, New York, and now Massachusetts (as protected under state law), I wish you a long and happy marriage, blessed with love, joy, and peace!  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Un Jour de Merde   I'm beginning to think that some days you get it and some days you just don't. Today would be one of those days I'm not getting it. To make life even more irritating, I had blood drawn this morning and that never fails to make me cranky (one would think that as much as I have it done I'd get used to it.)  One consolation is in the FANTABULOUS mixed CD my sister made for me this weekend.   "Rock-a-Licious" featuring The Darkness, Sweet, Franz Ferdinand, the Hives, and a little old school GNR.   Thanks baby!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       8 Things I Learned Today   1. Tangerine flavored popsicles are good, but they'll never top Blue Raspberry OtterPops. 2. People who wait until the very last second to plan a HUGE task that inevitably I have to execute and/or clean up really, really irritate me. 3. Said people in #2 can make it up to me with a box of tangerine flavored popsicles (I never said I wasn't easy). 4. I don't like being unprepared for social situations by either a) not being properly attired (i.e. scrubby jeans, a faded tee, and flip-slops vs. a cute flirty skirt, soft slinky top, and sandals) or b) not knowing when to be there. 5. I don't think I've ever not had a stuffy nose at any point in my life while being in  urlLink this  city. Today is no exception. 6. My new red Reefs are just cool! 7. People who send e-greetings instead of real, through-the-mail birthday cards baffle me.  It's only 37 cents! 8. Betta fish   will   jump out of their bowls.  Trust me!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Diamonds are a Girls Best Friend"   I am so excited about  urlLink this!   Last night's "60 Minutes II" had a story about Apollo Diamond and Gemesis (in Florida), but I had originally heard about them in a small article published by  WIRED  last summer.    Okay, maybe my #1 interest is really in a low cost per karat gem quality diamond (unlike Holly Golightly, I see nothing tacky about wearing diamonds before you're 40). But don't think I'm not aware of the political implications of what lab created, flawless, near colorless gem quality diamonds will do to a small little cartel named De Beers.    The current mark up of natural diamonds is in the thousands percent and De Beers has spent hundreds of millions of dollars convincing women and would-be grooms that diamonds are rare and forever.  Ironically they're only rare because De Beers made them that way (geologically, diamonds are quite plentiful. There may not be as many  gem  quality diamonds, but the commercial never really tells you that, does it?)  Having taken control of nearly 70% of the current diamond market, De Beers is a formidable opponent, not above benefiting from civil war, apartheid, and organized crime.  I'm sure Bob Linares of Apollo is aware of De Beers' power, but if the company is willing to go ahead in perfecting the technology to create these stones (the first and foremost reason for the techonology is for use in optoelectronics and nanotechnology, which will no doubt create a revolution in computer chip manufacturing on its own) then they have my support 100%
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Going Postal   Have you ever been in the post office when suddenly they run out of those numbered tickets?  It's not pretty!  Otherwise mature, well-educated adults regress into five year olds.  "Hey! I was here first!" followed by "Nuh uh! You were not!" "I didn't  see  you standing in line, did I?" "Hey buddy! There's a line here! Can't you see it?"  Luckily I left before the crying and hair pulling began (though it would have been fun to see the president of the local bank branch throw a tantrum.)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BFFs   So tonight, P. who is a guy I used to date but then we broke up for a long time and then out of the blue we get reaquainted and things are different and better but the vibe isn't there, you know, is coming over to stay the night (whew! that was all in one breath too!)    Anyway, let me explain. He has this thing he goes to on Wednesdays that's close to my house.  He's  living  on the otherside of town, so crashing at my place makes more sense then driving an hour home.  The thing is that the last time he came over we had been "officially" an item. Then he freaked out about something and wanted to take it slower.  I said that was fine with me (and girls, it really  was  fine.) So when he said "let's be friends," I thought that meant "we're not dating, but we're only friends." But I think he may be under the impression that we  are  dating just in more Victorian terms.  (I have a feeling this is going to be a long, complicated story made even longer and more complicated. I'll try to cut it down.)  So to recap: We went out. We broke up for several years. We got reaquainted recently. We went out. He freaked out. He wanted to be "friends." I said "No problem." He wants to take it back. I said "Let's slow down." I think he still thinks we're dating but it's just without the sex or anything that looks like two people dating. Whew! I need a nap.  Don't be surprised if this gets edited later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Turning Japanese   My dad works for a company whose international home office is in Japan.  After working for this company and resisting for as long as possible to have to do any kind of overseas travel, he finally had to make the trip.  So last night (or actually tonight at 10:00pm in Japan...the whole date line yada, yada) he made it safe and sound to Kumamoto.  My mom forwarded the e-mail he wrote to her to me this morning but reading it I felt suddenly embarrassed.  Who knew that my father was such a romantic lover?  "Father" and "lover" in the same sentence does make me mentally say "eeewww!", but I'm pleased.  I had no idea that in this sensible engineer of a man lived the heart of a poet.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Look Ma, new blog!   Wow!  New look, new skins, new everything.  Not bad, Blogger!  Thanks for setting it up so that the website-challenged don't have to whimper and rock in the corner when we can't get our sites to load correctly.  Love ya, baby!  Don't ever change!  Speaking of change, my little sister graduated on Saturday...from COLLEGE!  I'm not ready for that!  It seems like just yesterday she was a freshman in high school, awkward and quiet, and I was so afraid she'd get eaten alive by the social hyenas.  Little did I know then that she can pretty much take care of herself and anyone else who comes along.     She's off in August to the  urlLink coolest  gig in D.C.  Yay!    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Help us Van Morrison   In the 1920s, when my grandmother was born, her name ranked #36 over all for that decade according to the  urlLink Social Security Administration of the U.S.   My name (not coincedentally the same as my grandma's) has not managed to break the Top 100 in the last ten years.  But we're hoping for a come back!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Diane, this is my 7th and final phone call..."   I've done this about a hundred times before.  The blog thing, I mean.  I wonder if this time it'll stick.  In the mean time, check out  urlLink this girl .  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Would you like fries with that?   Hello everybody! It's been a couple of weeks since my last post. I've been trapped under an avalanche of paper for the past several days and I think I can finally see daylight. Things have been uber-hectic and with budget cuts all around, it looks like I might be taking my mug and my stapler and heading out onto the open road. No, I'm not doing stand-up or starting a very weird office-supply/S&M show. I'm talking about old-fashioned job huntin'.  I'm thinking of a career change-of-direction. Any ideas?  If you can help me pronounce the name of this company,  urlLink Tocquigny , I might be trying my luck there (I figured knowing how to pronounce a company's name during an interview was pretty much half the battle.)  I'm out of here.  10-4 Good buddy! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Bad Blog Writer! Bad, bad!   I'm sitting alone (managed to ditch my colleague, thank god. More on her later)at this little, tiny place on Connectticut (is that spelled right?) Ave. just south of Dupont Circle writing this to you. I just realized there hasn't been a new post in forever!  Well my time has been spent preparing for this trip (STD conference and all) and now that we're here I just want to go home.  Here's what's happened so far:   1. Chicago's O'Hare airport fucked up everything (all flights delayed by two hours). 2. Some brilliant meeting planner on our staff thought that  we  should pick up a car and DRIVE in DC to our hotel (bad bad idea). 3. I can't navigate for shit and got us stuck in a fantastically dodgy part of town. 4. Exactly 12 hours and 17 minutes from the time I left my house for the airport, I made it to the Omni Shoreham Hotel (a whopping 3 hours and 14 minutes  behind  schedule). 5. They didn't have our room ready at the hotel. So they gave us a tiny one w/ a roll-away bed.  6. The roll-away wouldn't fit in that shoebox-room so they "found" a double queen room, non-smoking that had its carpets recently shampooed (and was still soggy). 7. On the drive to Kinko's we discovered why America has every right to hate the French (stupid French city planners.) 8. A 20 minute trip turned into 2 hours. 9. It takes exactly 7 seconds to go from cool and comfortable to sweaty, soggy, and sticky in this city. 10. But...about 9 minutes ago I just met super super hot Alejandro who speaks English "poquito" to which I replied "Hablo espanol poquito, poquito tambien. Quiere ir a tomar algo?" (I don't know if that makes sense or not, but he smiled and said "Sure!")  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       High School Reunions & Other Such Nuisances   What is the appeal to going to one's high school reunion? I'm sure it's so you can catch up with old friends. See what everyone's doing these days. Who got married. Who's making a million. Who dropped those twenty pounds or who turned out to be really good-looking.   Today an "old friend" contacted me through MSN Messenger and it dawned on my that the only people I'd love to reconnect with from high school, I still manage to see on a weekly or bi-weekly basis. We're still good friends.  This isn't to say that this "old friend" isn't someone I wouldn't want to get to know a little better, but I feel as if those days have passed. She was pretty helpful though. Apparently, a very industrious alum of my high school created  urlLink this website  to keep us connected. It's nice to know that someone cares about keeping in touch.  Oh! And I finally learned what the  real  words to our fight song were:  Beer beer for old Austin High  Bring out the whiskey, bring out the rye  Send those freshmen out for gin, and don't let a sober SENIOR in  We never stagger, we never fall  We sober up on wood alcohol  All ye saints of Austin High are out on the drunk again! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A Ferrari is Forever   I've been wondering why men give diamond rings to their would-be brides when they propose. It seems like an arbitrary custom. Essentially, it's an act of giving the woman a symbol that says "Hey other-guys-who-aren't-my-fiance, back off! I'm taken." So if that's the case, I suppose any sort of a gift that symbolizes such a promise would suffice, right? I mean there's nothing by law that says that such a symbol  has  to be a ring. It could be a bracelet. Or a necklace. Maybe a nose ring (if she had her nose pierced) or a tattoo ( that's  one hell of a symbol). Maybe he buys her 100 acres in Napa Valley or an engagement cottage in Tuscany. Those all seem like worthy gifts for one's intended.  So after giving the whole issue some thought, I've decided that once I'm proposed to, I would like an engagement  urlLink Ferrari.    I mean  any  woman can have a diamond (you see it all the time.) But how many women can say her engagement ring tops out at 218 mph. Or can go from 0 - 60 in 3.65 seconds. Besides, when was that last time you saw a woman's engagement ring with 12 cylinders? Or the last time you saw her driving  anything  with 12 cylinders?   Diamond engagement ring: $10,000 Honeymoon tour to the Mediterrenean: $15,000 House in La Jolla: $10 Million Only bride with an engagement Ferrari: Priceless!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Work is a jealous mistress.   I never quite understood the appeal of working after your scheduled work hours. In fact, I usually don't stay late at the office unless specifically asked to by my supervisor and during the two+ years that I've worked with my current employer, I've been asked to to stay late a total of 0 times. But this week (and last week too) I've consistently stayed about an hour and a half later than my normal work time.  I figured out why.  It's quiet!   There are no phones calls from unorganized, frustrating, and ill-prepared clients. No co-workers to come by for a chat. No crises that need immediate attention (and always interrupt the flow of the day.)  Just peace and quiet. Productive momentum at its best.   As an added bonus, once I head home, there is usually no traffic. I can certainly appreciate the workaholics addiction. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     My New Toy   Last night I bought my first digital camera...ever! It is so much fun! I had done way too much research on one for my office (which is the Kodak EasyShare CX6330) and really wanted them to get this Canon, but apparently it was "too much camera" for the people who would be using it (go ahead...laugh. I was too.)  So I've taken dozens of photos of just about everything around the apartment (piles of dirty laundry, the computer, the TV, my shoes all marching from the front door to my bedroom, etc.)  I'll have to post some on here when I get the chance.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As the Water Cooler Turns    &nbsp; Sorry, y'all for not providing a timelier update! Thanks Paul for reminding me.&nbsp; The business of business can get kind of hairy. I think in my last post, I mentioned that the real fire fight was between  who  exactly would manage my new position, Sara or Jane.   Day 22: Sara takes me to lunch. We talk. We gossip. We get down to business. From  her  vantage point, it looks like Jane is just wanting to have her cake and eat it too (who can blame her, really.) Sara tells me the story of Drs. Prim and Proper. They are the trainers for my company's community coalition-building seminars (the same seminars, if I got the position, I would be contracting) and "high maintenence" is the understatement of the year. It turns out the Drs. Prim and Proper are unhappy with the current state of affairs at my company (again, who can blame them, really). They sold their program to my company seven years ago and now want it back (No takes-ies, backs-ies). Because the Higher-ups won't allow the good Doctors to reneg on the contract, they tend to go to whoever will be sympathetic to their plight.&nbsp; Enter Sara. Sara is the most sympathetic person I know. Not to mention slightly passive-aggressive. At lunch she sells me on the idea of why she should manage the new position:  1. It's a "sales"&nbsp;position and sales goes under marketing (I beg to differ, but that's a different story.) 2. She has a better relationship with Prim and Proper, while Jane does not.  3. Prim and Proper really want  her  to be involved 100% with the whole conference thing (Hmm...seems they only want her because they know she'll do whatever they want.)  I choose not to say much at this lunch with her, but remind her that we all need to sit down and have it out...me, her, Jane, Bald-headed Manager, and Jane's Cheerleaders (let's call them Muffy and Buffy. If you can't remember that, don't worry. They're pretty interchangeable).  Day 23:&nbsp; Preparation for Battle  Day 24: Battle begins 2pm. Place: Large Conference Room Players: Jane, Muffy, Buffy, Sara, me, and Bald-Headed Manager (via teleconference).  The conference starts out very genial. Jane presents her side and what she needs. Sara rebuts, but agrees with some things Jane says (i.e. need for sales person to work closely with Jane; Sara to help orchestrate marketing plan for position, even though Jane disagrees with this.) Muffy pipes in with budget numbers (this is critical. Our company is in a bad state financially, and it would help very much if we could bring in revenue via conferences. But in order to do that, we have to take a financial risk on the sales person. See the viscious cycle). The new position can practically pay for itself...in 6 to 8 months.&nbsp; Bald-headed manager who is usually quite chatty, remains mum.   Sara jumps in with her reasons as to why the new position should be managed by her ("It's a sales position and sales belongs under the oppressive control of the marketing regime, dammit!"&nbsp; Okay, she didn't really say it  that  way, but you get where I'm going.)&nbsp; This vollying between Jane and Sara goes on for a good 20, 30 minutes. I'm doodling on my scratch pad, wondering if the job market is really as bad as all my unemployed friends are really telling me.   Bald-headed Manager stops to conversation a moment and asks to here from me.  So I say, "Well, these are all very interesting points made by Jane and Sara. I don't disagree with them entirely. But I would like to add that I see three things going on here. One, the discussion with regards to Drs. Prim and Proper is probably best saved for another time. Two, Muffy's numbers state quite clearly that this position is self-payed if management is willing to take the risk on the 6 to 8 months needed to get a few conferences contracted and booked.&nbsp; And three, I am in an unenviable position in many ways right now.&nbsp; I'm asking for some committment from you, sir. I need the management question to be solved by the time I sign on to this new position. My preference is to work exclusively under Jane because of the specific nature of the conferences, but also to work very closely with Sara on marketing issues as they relate to conferences. On the subjects of Drs. Prim and Proper, I'm quite aware of their past behavior, but as I understand it, they are contract trainers, not staff. If The Company is unhappy with their service, let them be reminded they are replaceable [ I have NO idea where those  cojones  came from!!! ] Boundaries will have to be established with regards to just how many perks the trainers will receive and I refuse to work directly with them on any issue other than scheduling between the hosts, the meeting planners, and the good Drs. Finally, I need a date as to when this new position will go into effect. As you know, I am young in my professional career and advancement is very important to me. I have enjoyed working in my current position for the past two and a half years, but I feel its time for me to look for other ways and even companies to enhance my professional development. I know that there are many unknowns in the financial state of The Company, so please understand that I know what I'm asking when I say that I will need a decision with regards to rolling out this new position by September 30th. If a decision can not be reached, I will need to seriously turn my attention to finding a position that better suits my abilities, talents, and professional needs."  So, um, guys...do y'all know of any positions open with your company come October 1? Things will probably be slow around here. And as you know I'm already lazy on the updates, but I'll do my best. Who knows? We could  all  be out of a job by September 30 with the way things look around here.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Maybe It Would Just Be More Fun to Get Fired   Did I tell you exactly  why  I'm thinking about quitting my job?  I'm not sure it's important, but it's the most drama I've had happen in a long time.  I might have told you, but I post so infrequently now, and stopped reading my own blog every hour, that I don't really remember. I'm going to quit because the heads of two departments can't decide whose team I should play on.  It kind of goes something like this:  Team A is run by "Jane". Team B is run by "Sara." The one who pulls their strings is called Bald-headed Manager.   Day 1: Jane offers me a new and potentially lucrative position in her department. Meetings included compensation discussions, outlined projects, a little gossip, and some well enjoyed ego stroking. I like Jane and Team A. I tell her "Ok. I'm in if all goes well with Financial Committee and Bald-headed Manager."  I tell Sara, leader of Team B (where I currently play), that I'm interested in working with Team A. Sara seems very positive about the change over.    Day 2: Jane calls me into her office and says "Sorry. Finance Committee nixed the deal."  I'm a little disappointed, but no worse off then when I started. I go on my merry way, looking at other ops elsewhere.  Day 3: Jane calls me into her office and says, "Sorry. Finance Committee and Bald-headed Manager say it's a go. When can you start?"  I said "ASAP. I'm ready!"  Sara pulls Jane into a meeting and said "Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! You can't take E. I need her here. And besides, that new position should be managed by me."  Jane disagrees and consults Bald-headed Manager. He says, "Yankees in Tara!?  Well I just won't think about it now.  I'll think about it tomorrow."  So far he hasn't thought about it at all.  Days 4-14: No one says anything. It's eerily quiet and we all tip toe around pretending there's nothing wrong.   Sidenote: Sara is my supervisor. All updates I've heard regarding this new position have been through Jane. Weird, neh?  Day 15: Sara, Jane, Bald-headed Manager, and four other people are behind closed doors for negotiations about where I'll go. I'm not there. I wasn't invited. Jane provides an update. "You potentially have three options. #1 Stay where you are (or quit.) #2 Come play for my team, or #3 Stay on your team but split your projects between Team A and Team B and be managed half by me and half by Sara. This will include no raise, no commission, no assistant, and you'll probably develop a nervous condition."  I tell her I'll think about it.  Day 16-20: Very quiet. Jane is out of town. I am editing my resume, pulling old favors, and getting ready to make my escape.  Sara is still mum on the whole thing.  Today is Day 21 and still no real update about what will happen. Stay tuned!     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This Blog thing is HARD!   Okay, it's really not; I'm just supremely lazy. Hey fellow bloggers, what do you do when you've posted on your blog about someone you used to date and they find out about it? That happened to me recently and it was very awkward!  Of course, I didn't say anything offensive or snarky about this person, but it was hard to hear him repeat my own words. Is there a blogger tip on how to play that off?   These posts seem to be getting further and further apart. A simple recap on life from the last eight days (in no particular order):  1. Mentally committed to finding another job. Yay me!  2. Have not revamped resume or seriously been looking for a new job. 3. Committed in writing to vacate my apartment at end of lease in 30 days. 4. Do not have another place lined up. Looking at houses to rent with best friend and nice, new girl.  5. Found GORGEOUS, HUGE house in favorite part of city; 4 bedrooms, 3000 sqft., pool, $1600 a month. Catch: Need 4th roomie; house is directly across the street from my parents. 6. Discovered it costs a lot of money to rent when you own pets.  7. Spent 4th of July with fun friends P and D.  8. Came back to work from 3-day weekend so unmotivated that I spent Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday looking for jobs, houses, and things to buy on eBay. 9. Saw Spider Man 2 (fun, enjoyed it alot). Rented Cold Mountain (thought it was wonderful and now want to take fiddle lessons). 10. Went to party for very young, newly enlisted neo-conservative. Almost had to break-up girl fight between 26 year old friend (sister of said new recruit) and 19 year old drunk child. I don't miss high school, thank you.  How was your last week? 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>