<Blog>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I finally saw mah grrrl on TV today!  My friend Matthew told me last week that there were new commercials featuring Claudia Schiffer, but I assumed they were L'Oreal ads.  They're for the Gap!  Personally, I am not a fan of the Gap, and I do not purchase their products, but I've  always  adored their ad campaigns!  The music and visuals are always appealing.    So, the new TV spot has her walking blissfully down the street in her Gap Stretch pants as autumn leaves breeze by and she twirls with a smile as the wind sweeps over her blonde locks and the 70s song "September" by  Earth, Wind, and Fire  grooves on.  After seeing it, I went to Gap.com and watched the commercial over and over.  She's just gorgeous and I am so glad to see her on TV again, since she mostly does television work in Europe.  She probably received a nice payday for the Gap commercial too.  She has been indicated in the  Guinness Book of World Records  as the highest paid model, and (as I mentioned before) having the  most  magazine covers, in addition to landing the biggest cosmetics contract.  Back in the early to mid 90s when she was the face of  Revlon , Claudia was reportedly earning $6,000,000 a year!  She's the epitome of blonde beauty and her name will go down as one of the greatest fashion models ever.  Go Claudia--luv ya!  I woke up today feeling good. Refreshed.  I did have a difficult time getting to sleep at first because I'm used to staying up late. I think I finally achieved unconsciousness after 3 a.m. I'm gradually trying to break that habit.  Sleep is more important than most people realize.  It allows your body to cleanse, rejuvinate, and repair itself.  A consistent lack of it may lead to illness, a dull complexion, and a grumpy attitude.  On the whole, I get enough sleep because I usually feel and look good.  But tonight I may be out late since I'm going out dancing with friends.  I am excited since I haven't been dancing in a while and I have never been to Luxx.  I'm sure it will be fun.  I'm off tomorrow so I can sleep in if I need to.    I made plans to see my friend Marcia tomorrow.  She'll be in my neighborhood so we talked about her dropping by for a bit.  But it is tentative, because Marcia changes her plans abruptly from time to time.  She hasn't been to my house in a long while and hasn't seen my garden yet.  It is not looking all that great since I have a little weeding to do and the rosebush could use some pruning, but it could be worse...  My aunt Cathie's birthday is tomorrow.  I sent a card but I think it won't arrive until Monday.  I don't know how she's taking the whole liver cancer thing.  Maybe she'll be in good spirits.  I'll find out when I speak to her.  I still have to see about getting a plane ticket out there to visit.  Ok, that's all for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ah, things are back to normal for the most part.  Wednesday, my friends returned from their trip abroad and I went back home.  My home.  It feels good to be back, but I have a lot of work to do.  I have to get new bookshelves to keep all the new books and magazines I have acquired over the months.  I have so much stacked on my dining room table.  I don't like clutter.  Clutter creates stress.  I want clean smooth clutter-free surfaces in my home.   I need to get some shelves too and mount them on the walls.   Last night, I went to my friend Beacon's birthday gathering at Caravan of Dreams.  It was nice to meet some of her family and friends that I did not already know.    I am at work now.  There is not a lot going on presently and I have not written in a few days.  I would write daily, but I do not have a personal computer.  I am looking into getting one.  I have so many things I feel that I need to buy.  Like everything else, it takes time.  Time, time, time.  (Sigh), I just have to be patient and keep my ambitions.   I am determined to create the life I want and enjoy it.   Earlier, I took a break and went to the new Wai? Cafe on Sixth Avenue.  I ate there for the first time with my friend Enrico Wednesday night.  I had the Wai? Salad.  Delicious.  Justice, the waiter there is really nice and has a healthy complexion--I automatically love people with good skin.   He's very sociable and mild-mannered.  We chatted a bit again today.  He recommended a book called  Dance, Dance, Dance  by a Japanese author, his name escapes me at the moment, but I'll check it out.  After I left the cafe, I felt energized walking down the avenue.  I felt strong, confident, sexy and at a good point in my life.   Well, it is getting close to the time for me to go home.  So, I'm going to finish up here.  Bye-bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I met with my financial advisor today.  He's pretty cool and very helpful.  We went over some things with my mutual fund.  It has performed well over the past few years and I saw the percentages to prove it! We also discussed my money market account, it has been inactive since I stopped contributing to it regularly so, I restarted monthly deductions from my checking account.    Then I walked around town a bit and went to Urban Outfitters on 14th street and Sixth Avenue to look for some new jeans.  They had nothing in my size!  Hardly anyone ever does.  I am tall and thin with long legs.  I tend to favor 31" 34" or 32" 34".  The ones that  were  in my size had that faded washed out look on the thigh and rump-side of the jeans.  I cannot stand that.  I do not want that faded look on my new jeans.  I'll just wear them until they fade on their own--thank you!  I wish that trend, fad, or whatever you want to call it would just go away.  Every time I turn around someone is sporting these tired played-out jeans.   Granted, some people look pretty darn hot in them, but the style is just not for me.    Then I went to Mavi this new Turkish jeans store on Broadway.  It is their first store in the U.S.  They didn't have what I wanted either, but the guy who helped me look was nice and really cute.  He agreed with me about that trendy-faded-washed-out-look on jeans.  He wishes it would end too.  Anyway, it was his first day working there and I thought he was wonderful (personally and professionally).  I thought he said his name was Kyle at first, but he said Kai (rhymes with tie).  I told him he's doing a great job on his first day.  This Mavi store also has an art gallery downstairs.  How nifty is that?  Shop for jeans and see some art.  Splendid.  Then I go off to the Virgin Megastore and look at CDs and mags.  I love magazines.  The glossy pages, the text, designs, layouts, models... I would love to work at a magazine, especially the ones at Conde Nast.  Here's a fun fact for you.  Which model has graced the cover of more magazines than  any  other in history?  No, not Cindy Crawford.  Kate Moss--nope.  Not Linda Evangelista either, or Naomi Campbell, Chirsty Turlington, or Nikki Taylor.   The Guinness Book of World Records  states that supermodel Claudia Schiffer has been on more magazine covers than any other model (I don't know the exact number, but it is certainly over 800).  Pretty amazing, huh?  She has some other record-breakers too, but I can cover that later.  Sadly, Claudia wasn't on any of the covers I saw today.  She's not working as much, being a new mother and all.  And she's pursuing other ventures, but maintains her lucrative contract with cosmetics giant L'Oreal (because she's worth it).   After looking around the megastore, I head over to Chop't--this salad eatery that I adore, to meet my friend Michael.  I get my two salads and we go next door to this other place and he gets falafel.  Sitting in lovely Union Square park on a bench, he and I catch up.   Then we go shopping.  I bought my first pair of Diesel jeans!  I have never paid that much for jeans, but I do look good in them.  I am so not into designer labels usually, but this time was different.  Then we went to this other store on Eighth Avenue called Bang Bang.  They had some cool stuff in there and it was much more affordable than Diesel.  I bought some jeans there too.   Then Michael had to get going to an appointment.  So, we left and took a taxi over to the east side.  It was fun shopping with him.  After that, I went home checked my mail and phone messages and did some laundry.  Went go get some groceries and came back to the house I am watching over while my friends are away.  I fed the cats and baked some tofu broccoli and cauliflower with Thai peanut sauce and herbs for myself.  I put it over Thai basil rice noodles.  I'm going to have the leftovers for lunch at work tomorrow. YUM!  My friends return Wednesday and I get to go back to my own house.  It has been fun though--like a little vacation--but local. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My aunt April just called me at work from San Francisco.  Aunt Cathie has liver cancer.  She had breast cancer a few years ago and recovered, but this is more serious, I'm afraid.  April told me doctors estimate three to five years.  Naturally, I am shocked and devastated.  I did not speak to Cathie because she is still processing it since she found out Wednesday.  Her birthday is a week from today...  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      "Money, success, fame, glamour! Money, success, fame, glamour!..."  That's what crazy club kids, Michael Alig and James St. James chanted in the movie "Party Monster".  That struck a chord in me, because those are in fact the things I want for myself and those within my inner circle...    MONEY:  And I am not being shallow; just think of all the people I could help with all my money!  Of course I would support animal rights groups, and other organizations that work for protecting the planet, its people, and its creatures.  I would do so many wonderful and exciting things in that regard.  I'd promote veganism in a positive non-confrontational way that engages curiosity and interest.    I, without question or hesitation, will have to buy a house.  I want a house so bad I often think of my apartment as if I own it--which I shouldn't because it is not mine.  I have to own a home, I feel compelled to do so.  I want to do all the organizing, painting, decorating, gardening, coordinating, ALL that stuff.  I just love it.  I want go all Martha Stewart and Bob Vila on a house of my own.  I'll get one for mom and dad too.  After getting the house(s) and contributing to my Roth IRA and other investments.  I will simply have to travel to delicious places all over the world and purchase more property because real estate is superfun!  SUCCESS:  I think as long as you're happy with who and what you are, and you keep challenging yourself to be better, you're successful.  Presently, I feel moderately successful, but I wan t more--and I will have it.  It is a matter of time, really.    FAME: Well, I have had many brushes with it, and achieved modest levels of it myself over the years, but that is the beginning.  This phase of my plan will evolve, but I will not go out of m y way pursuing it.  It will be spontaneous and somewhat unexpected.  GLAMOUR:  This is something we all have to a certain degree.  It is what one does with it that makes a difference.  The way one smiles, the twinkle in the eyes, the walk, the talk, the a ttitude... I just love glamourous people!  In my Natal Chart I have Venus in Aquarius.  In 'Parker's Astrology' they wrote that this placement contributes "more film star glamour than any other".  Love that!  Glamour is fun, it is alluring, attractive and always sexy.  These things are a must have when combined with the other three elements mentioned above.  As days go by and I develop my plan of action, I look forward to seeing how these things come to be.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, yesterday was a great day!  I had such a wonderful time.  So, I get plenty of rest and feel good.  I get up feed the cats blah, blah and go to my house to drop of some things.  I am still house sitting for my friends so I have to go home and check my mail and water the plants etc.  While I am watering the plants, my friend Robert calls.  We make plans to hang out a bit, because he wasn't able to join the group to see "Party Monster" that evening.  We met in Union Square at the Virgin Megastore cafe, then we walked to 'Lifethyme' a health food store.  Then I run into one of my best friends, Marcia!  I hardly ever just run into her, so that was a surprise.  Then as Robert and I are walking down Sixth Avenue, I see my friend Enrico.  I haven't seen him in months!  Then Robert has to go to his friend's birthday party and I head over to the movie theater to get my ticket and wait for the others to join me.    Well, while I was in line, I had yet another brush with fame.  I notice that someone 'special' is standing behind me (I have celebdar like you wouldn't believe).  Since I couldn't just turn around and blatantly look at him, I checked out the reflection in the glass at the box office.  It was just as I suspected--Ethan Hawke was standind right behind ME!  He bought a ticket for "Lost in Translation" and I watched him go inside to get snacks and then off he went.  It was nifty.  So, when my friends, Eitan, Mani, and Haq (pronounced "huck") arrived I told them the exciting story.  After "Party Monster" (which I thought was entertaining and somewhat comical, but not stellar. Macaulay Culkin has nice legs and Seth Green's character James St. James has great lines) Eitan, Haq and myself went to Big Cup cafe.  On the way there, I saw Dave Chapelle pass us.  I am pretty sure it was him.   I saw him once before a few years ago when he came to do stand-up at my university.  He's a funny fellow.  At Big Cup, I'm sitting with my mint tea and listening to Haq and Eitan discuss jobs and career when I catch a glimpse of someone I think I know.  It was Ed, one of my newest friends on Friendster!  Through reading his blog, I was inspired to create my own, but I had never met him in person until yesterday.  So I got his attention and he came over and joined us.   I introduced him to my friends and he introduced us to his pal Gennadi.  Later, Gennadi, Ed, and I went uptown to the Barnes & Noble at Lincoln Center and chatted while looking over magazines.  We laughed and told stories, it was fun.  We then went downtown and back to Big Cup.  Then Ed and I went to some clubs to see who we could see and then later I went home.  It was a very fun-filled social-celebrity-enhanced-Saturday.  Much different from my boring Friday.    I just love making new friends.  It is such a delight.  New people, new perspectives, new ideas, new attitudes--those are things that help create a sweet happy life.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thursday, I went to a party at the International House with my friend Emily.  It was so much fun.  It was a going away party for Michael and his friend.  They're German.  I speak German so it was fun to converse with them in another language besides English. The I-House is very large and has all sorts of rooms and reception halls and a pub and all this space for people to socialize and study of course.  There were all sorts of interesting and attractive people throughout the house too.  I think the international aspect adds to its appeal.  I found myself doing a double-take from time to time as Michael gave Emily and I a tour of the place.  Some of the rooms smelled old and weird, but I'm sure a couple of sandalwood incense would have helped that a bit.  I met some very pleasant people.  Some of them are only here for a couple of months on internships etc.  But we danced the night away to hits from the 80s and 90s and some music from Germany and Italy too.  Yesterday, I did not do much at all.  It was a low-key day I suppose.  I was off from work so I lounged around the house.  I am currently house-sitting for friends, and taking care of their cats.  Their apartment is nice, but it needed some plants so I brought two peace lilies I had at work and later bought three palms.  I had to elevate them because the cats eat the leaves.    Anyway, so I didn't do much.  I watched bits and pieces of the "Today" show, "The Ellen Degeneres Show", "The Wayne Brady Show" and "Dawson's Creek." I read a little, made some steamed broccoli and tofu with olive oil and herbs for brunch, then watched "The Young and the Restless".   After that I got dressed, fed the cats, changed their litter box and went downtown to see Emily at her office at the UN Plaza.  Later that night, I came back to feed the cats and watch "The Tonight Show with Jay Leno" and "Late Night with Conan O' Brien".  As I write this, I realize that I am watching more TV than I used to.  Well, the reason for that is simple really, I am not in my house and I do not watch TV in my home.  I also read some, then I went to bed.  I slept well so I feel better now, but I have to do laundry today and that does not make me smile.    Sometimes this city gets on my nerves, something that I am sure happens to everyone who dwells here from time to time.  All these people, millions of them, are so close together yet somewhat morbidly distant at the same time.  But it has to be that way I suppose.  Mother told me you can't be everybody's friend and not everyone is going to like you no matter what you do.    I guess that's all I have to say for now.  In time things are bound to get more interesting.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It is cloudy today.  There was some sunshine this morning, but because of Hurricane Isabel, there is residual cloud and wind in the New York City area.  I am at work now in midtown Manhattan.  Not much is going on and I just had to write something today.    I'll tell you, I am a PSA for SPF.  Even when it is cloudy outside, I still wear sunscreen.  We all need protection from those UV rays, and dermatologists have been telling us for years the effects those rays have over time.  Wear it daily.  And for th ose concerned that sunscreen will make you look shiny and oily, do some research.  There are some that are non-greasy and unscented.  You will really see the difference when you are middle aged with relatively smooth and healthy skin while your colleagues look older than they are.    But really, sunscreen is only the beginning.  My philosophy is to drink a lot of water, stay active, and eat moisture-rich foods like fruits and vegetables on a daily basis.  Most people do not eat enough of these anyway, so it will do everyone some good to put more plants in their diet.  It keeps you slim and full of energy.  You feel good too!  Seriously, a diet consisting of animal products, sweets, and processed foods is NOT the way to go.  To make a difference you really have to change long-term behaviors and eating habits.  Yes, I know, "easier said than done," but it can be done.  I myself have been vegan since 1999 and I have no regrets and I do not miss the way I used to live.  It was the single most powerful choice I have made in my life thus far.  My sense of well-being, the way I see the world, my connection to the Earth and its many creatures, the way I interact with others, everything changed for the better and I am still thrilled about it!  It is also important to think positively.  When you feel good you look good and the other way around.  Be good to yourself, and your Self will be good to you.        
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, here I am.  My first 'blog'.  After thinking about writing and having some type of journal or collection of thoughts on the Internet for some time now, I finally got around to doing it.  Thanks Blogger!  This is exciting, inspiring, even groovy.  I feel all this potential rising up within me.  New thoughts and ideas are forming so quickly!  I also feel a sense of contentment.  This is the birth of a new era for me.  I can sense it.  My perceptions are acute--insightful even.  Also, I have learned from my studies of Astrology that writing is prominent in my Natal Chart.  I have Mercury in Capricorn in the tenth house and Jupiter in Gemini in the third house.  More on that later.  I feel good.  I hope you do too.  Ciao for now.  Jason
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      These past few days have been highly active.  Sunday morning, I received a surprise call from my friend   Arthur !  He was my first friend after moving to New York City. He is from Brazil and moved back there two years ago.   It was so nice to catch up with him.    In the afternoon, I had brunch with the  20Something  group.  It is a social organization that offers an opportunity to socialize beyond the city's bar/club scene.  The people I dined with were nice, but there was little for me as far as food goes.  The brunch menu only had one veg option--a grilled vegetable sandwich on Tuscan bread.  After attempting to eat it I realized that I do not like grilled vegetables.  I'd much rather have them raw, lightly steamed, or stir-fried.  After brunch I made a mad dash back to my palace (by NYC standards it is because most apartments are small) to whip up an apple pie for  VegOut .  It is a group that meets for monthly potlucks and I hadn't been to one in months.  During all this I packed some clothes because I had to house sit for  Carl .    The potluck was nice and my apple pie was a hit.  I arrived late so I all had was dessert--a delectable chocolate-peanut butter-tofu pie, vegan cheesecake that was unbelievably delicious, and my pie, then some Rosemary Olive Oil Chips.   My only problem with  VegOut  is that there is hardly anyone my age that attends!  I am all for having friends of varying ages, but most of the group is over 35.  Where are the veg youth? (*sigh*)   After that, I hopped on the train to Brooklyn.  I arrived at Carl's at 8 p.m.  I watched  The Sopranos  for the first time.  I don't like it.  I never liked mafia hit-man type shows or movies--my mom does though.  It was good to see Carl.  We haven't seen each other in person since July.  Later, Carl's friend  Wayne  dropped by.  He slept over too partly because his roommate is not a pleasant lady and he's preparing to move into a new condo he bought in Park Slope--nice.  So, it was like a slumber party sort of.  We talked, laughed, and ate.  They both liked the vegan cheesecake I brought from the potluck and my apple pie.  Carl told me all the things I need to do for his dog etc. while he's away in Florida.  He left for the airport around 5 a.m. Monday.  Around 9 a.m., I got a surprise call from  Roland  on my cell phone!  He's my friend from Germany.  It was great to talk to him.  I plan to visit him next year.   Monday was also my dear friend,  Delyn 's birthday.  She invited me to see a musical show with her called  The Cure  (has nothing to do with the band--which she initially thought).  I was half an hour late because of constant train delays from Brooklyn into Manhattan.  I called and warned Delyn, plus, the show was free so it was OK.  It was about some guy that was dying and he somehow got involved with this vampire coven through this vamp girl called "Unique".  The "cure" would have been immortality, but the guy didn't accept it.  All but one of the vampires died in the end. He goes off to start a new life.    After the show, I headed home, picked up some more apples on the way and made another apple pie for Delyn's birthday.  I met her and her friends at a cafe in the East Village and chatted away.  I would have stayed later, but I had to get back to Carl's and check on the dog.     I have a lot to do today as well...  Ciao now!     
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I woke up feeling so tired this morning.  What the hell was that about?  I didn't stay up that late.  I think was the junk I ate yesterday.  Yes, I am a health-conscious person, but I am not immune to indulgence from time to time.  Yesterday, I had these two heavy vegan cookies--heavy in content not weight.  They may have taxed my system with excess sugar.  Or it could be that combined with staying out dancing and getting home at 4:30 a.m. on Friday.  Well, I am not staying out late tonight.  After work I am going home and resting.    Before going to work today, I went to  Marcia 's house.  I helped her clean and declutter her apartment.  I love that grrrl, but she is a piece of work!  Seriously, it was fun hanging out at her house and helping her take control of things again.  Her friend,  Mike  arrived later.  He loves Marcia, but she's not havin' it.    When I took a break from work to go to  Wai? Cafe  for my usual salad, guess who I saw on the downtown F train?  Marcia!  Well, she saw me before I saw her.  She joined me, and had a Wai? Salad too!  It was fun.  I was so hungry I had two salads.    There's this guy that works at the cafe behind the counter.  I think he's a superhunk with mystery--a powerful combination in my book, and I like the sound of his voice.  He wears glasses too, so he looks very intellectual.  My guess is he's in his late 20s early 30s.  I told Marcia how smitten I am with him and she said I should talk to him.  Well, it just so happened that I needed change to leave a tip for our waitress, so I strolled on over to him at the cash register.  He said that  Justice  (the waiter I know from when I first started going there) said to tell me hello.  That was nice, because I haven't seen Justice in a while.  So, I asked for his name.  It is  Jeff .  I introduced myself and shook his hand, with a smile.  Hopefully, something may develop...but I'm not 100% sure he's in the "boys club" yet.   Tomorrow, I have a brunch in the afternoon and potluck to attend in the evening.  It is good to be more social again.  I do enjoy interacting with new people.  It makes me grow as an individual, and helps me learn more about my Self.    After all that I will be going over to  Carl 's to house sit for a few days.  He's going to Florida.  I sure have a lot to do tomorrow.    Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      During my lunch break, I went to  Saks Fifth Avenue  for the first time today.  It has a nice layout.  I never went before because I thought you had to be rich to shop there.  Well, that is still sort of true, but it is not completely out of my league.    On the first floor near the perfumes and stuff, I walked by the  Louis Vuitton  area (of course I would never shop there--leather!) and as I watched male models on the runway on this large screen, I bumped into this old chap and was embarassed for not watching where I was going (damn those models!).  Thankfully, he didn't seem to be upset.    There was an air of snobbery around, but overall I found it to be a nice place.  I went to the men's floor and saw all these nice suits.  I could use some new suits.  I saw the old fellow that I bumped into earlier on the first floor and made sure I didn't pull a repeat.  He didn't even notice I was there.    There were some lovely displays and plush decor for the eye to savor.  Nice plants too.  I could feel the luxury as I strolled around like I owned the place.  I may go back someday....  After work, I am going to a taping of  Marcia 's show  Making the Scene .  I haven't been to a taping of hers in a while so it will be a treat.  Originally, I was going to hang out with my devilishly dashing Danish friend,  Martin  from Copenhagen, but his father just popped into town on business, so we postponed our plans and that freed me up to accept Marcia's invitation to see her show.  For the past few days, I have been using this new product I bought at  Whole Foods Market  in Chelsea called  Ultimate Meal --the name says it all.  I don't have the ingredient list on hand, but it is packed with antioxidants and all the great nutrients one needs--and it's totally VEGAN!  No genetically modified ingredients, no soy or artificial anything.  It is comprised of freeze dried sprouts from various plants packed with nutritional power.  All you do is blend 1/3 cup with 10 oz. of purified water, half an apple, and a large banana.  The color is greenish with a mildly gritty texture (maybe I should blend it longer), but it does not taste bad--doesn't taste supergood either, but you can't win them all...  It fills me up and I feel good.  I think I'll buy more when my 10 day supply runs out.  Ok, I'm off....Ciao now!  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sunday was an active day.  My landlord,  Rose , and her husband  Carlos  came by around 1 p.m. to look at my door locks.  One needed tightening so after they painted the vacant apartment upstairs for awhile, Carlos came and adjusted the lock.  It is much better now--the key doesn't get stuck like it used to.  Then we went to  Home Depot --FUN!  I browsed and looked at paints to get some ideas for my place.  I purchased four different varieties of ivy in hanging baskets, some plastic pots, and ceiling hooks.  Next week, Carlos will help me with some shelving I want to put up in the kitchen.  That evening I met up with my friend  Martin .  He's a writer from Copenhagen and an intelligent fellow with a good sense of humor and good looks to match.  I met him last summer through my old college gal pal  Claire  when she visited.  She'll be here again next month.    So, I met Martin in Brooklyn.  He was attending exhibits at D.U.M.B.O (an art community under the Manhattan Bridge).  It was so exciting to see him again.  He gave me a real firm solid hug.  It was really great to catch up and laugh with him and I met some of his old friends from London who just randomly happened to be there at the same time.   How nifty is that?  Reunited with old friends times two!  We went to hear a discussion about art communities, and movements in the art world from a panel of critics.  It was an open discussion and I found it very interesting.  We were surrounded by paintings and some type of blue sculpture thing on the ceiling.  Martin's friends from London stayed for a little while, but later bailed.  Martin is in town promoting his web site www.wooloo.org, so after the discussion, (in which he made some relevant comments and observations I might add) he went up to briefly talk with the panel members and gave them his card.    One of the panel members, his name escapes me, approached me as I was leaving.  He said he noticed that I was really listening and expressed genuine interest in the discussion--which was true.  He appreciated that.   It was nice to know that he noticed.  I shook his hand and thanked him briefly but did not get the chance to introduce myself or stay to chat because I was walking out the door with Martin and was in the middle of a cell phone call with  Carl , (we used to date, but are now friends) who I haven't talked to in a while.  It happened so fast.   In retrospect, I should have told Carl I would call him back and asked Martin to wait a moment so I could have spoken to the art critic that came up to speak with  me .  It is so rare that people just come up to talk to me.  Partly because of living in New York City, but I find that usually I have to initiate conversation with others because I am generally extroverted.  Friends have told me that there is a cool detachment in my demeanor that can be intimidating.  I don't really see it, but one thing I know for sure is that other people always see you somewhat differently than you see yourself.  Anyway, Martin and I took the F train back to Manhattan's East Village and I visited the apartment he is subletting with his associates.  I met one of them, but I am not sure how to spell his name.  He came out of the bathroom attractive and blonde adorned with  nothing --but a towel.   I was a bit uncomfortable at first.   I mean really, how often do you meet someone for the first time and he's only wearing a towel (looking good in it too)?   Of course, I managed to appear unaffected (cool detachment I suppose).  He had a pleasant accent too.  So, Martin and I go to  7A  a 24-hour restaurant on 7th Street and Avenue A--hence the name.  At first we were seated in the back, but Martin wanted to be near the front window, so we moved.  As I walked toward the front, guess who I passed dining with her son?  She has appeared in two successful films with  Tom Hanks  and was once married to  Dennis Quaid  YES!  We were sitting a few feet away from  Meg Ryan !  Later as she departed, the restaurant took note of course.  It even got a little quiet--too quiet really.  Anyway, we saw her driver open the door for her and off they went in her large black SUV something or other (I am so not into cars) with tinted windows.  I am glad Martin was there because I usually see celebs when I am alone so it was nice to share the moment.  Later, when I arrived home, I repotted some more plants and did some other house chores.  I am always going to be doing something around that place.  My home is a major part of my life.   Speaking of which, Monday I weeded in the garden, pruned the rose bush, trained the ivy along the fence and cleaned up the area.  I was supposed to do laundry.  I have put it off for over two weeks!      Monday evening I saw  Marcia .  I love that grrrl.  We went to  Gobo , a wonderful vegetarian restaurant on Sixth Avenue in the Village.  It was her first time there.  She loved the place and the food.   Later, I met up with my new friend  Carlos  and I ate again at  Cilantro  on the Upper East Side.  I was so full after doing so much eating!  Carlos took me to his building on 90something Street and Second Avenue.   The Waterford , I believe it is called.  We went to the roof and the view was gorgeous!  I saw the Empire State building lit up and all the glowing activity of this mega-city I call home.  Afterwards we met up with Carlos’ cousin  Juanita .  She was so sweet.  Upon our introduction she said, “You’re very handsome, Jason.  Where’re you from?”  What a gal…   Ciao now!    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a good day.  At first I woke up not wanting to do anything but lay in bed and lounge.  Then, I decided to get up and be productive.  I cleaned up some more.  I have so much to sort through with various papers and magazines I have collected.  I  finally  repotted my two large citrus trees.  Their roots were ultra-compacted in the pots they've been in for the past two years.  I know they will appreciate the larger pots and fresher soil.  I grew these trees from seed during the summer of 2001 and they are so tall now.  One is at least 6'3", two inches taller than me.  I met my friend  Kasheik  for brunch at  Wai? Cafe , and had my usual  Wai? Salad .  I had two.  Kasheik thought our waiter was cute so he left a note and his phone number with the tip.  I admire his boldness in that regard.   However, it will be a bit awkward the next time he and I have brunch there and he's our waiter again.  I am off Sunday and Monday so I will be able to get more done around the house.  It really is a job of work keeping that place tidy.  I have a large apartment.  Well, that's about it.  I doubt I will be around a computer during my days off so, it will be sometime next week when I add a new entry.    Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Not much happened today.  I slept late and read in bed for a while.  Then I popped in my  Perfectly Fit: Arms  videotape.  As I began my workout with  Claudia , I received a phone call from my grrrl  Ginger .  She and I haven't talked in a while so we chatted a bit and she invited me over for some of the raw cake she won from  The Raw Bakery .  So, I showered and dressed--then  Megan  called.  What a riot that grrrl is!  We always laugh when we talk.  Megan invited me to lunch but I had to take a raincheck since I already made plans with Ginger (who introduced me to Megan earlier this year).  After catching up with her, I headed downtown to visit Ginger.  She is such a gem and I always enjoy time spent with her.  I am contemplating what to do this weekend.  Besides, my house work like laundry and cleaning, I want to do something fun.  Maybe invite some people over and bake apple pie....  Ciao for now!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Uhhhh, I have got to get a computer.  I would write much more often if I had my own, and I could better document what I do from day to day.  Sometimes, so much time goes by between entries that I forget what the  hell  I did during that time.  Well, the party I went to on Saturday night was fun.  Most of the people I invited to join me either did not return my call about the invitation (RUDE!), or called to say they could no longer go.  Two pals did accompany me to the Billburg (a.k.a. Williamsburg) pad where the party took place.  To the event, I brought red grapes, one friend brought some little coffee cake thing, and the other brought beer--I always bring something with me to parties, and ecourage those who come with me to bring something too.  I must say that our host, who is an old college friend of mine, was looking fit and trim thanks to his new running routine, and he is such a pleasant fellow.  It was good to see him.  The music was appropriate, and the guests were an interesting mix of the host's law student associates, mutual friends, acquaintances, and Europeans.  One of which caught my eye immediately upon entering the scene.  I'll get to him in a moment.  I chatted with these two girls, one from Stuttgart (here on an internship or something) and one from Austria (an actress having moved to NYC a mere month ago).  I think they were amused by my genuine enthusiasm for speaking German.  They said I speak it well so that was nice to hear.  On the roof of the building, I later spoke with that eye-catching chap and discovered he too was German--how nice.  But there was nothing of note after that since he was only visiting NYC from North Carolina on fall break and I didn't sense much interest in me on his behalf.  Well, after a while, things slowed down.  The party was nice, but I wanted to  dance .  So, my pals and I went to  Luxx .  This place was all the rage last year.  Well, that is not the case now.  The place has rarely been packed since I started going a few weeks ago, but I don't care.  It gives me room to shake my a$$!  After about an hour or so of dancing we decided to call it a night.  Sunday, a friend and I went to  IKEA  in New Jersey.  That was fun.  I bought a few things to add to the decor of my kitchen, two candles, and a nice picture frame.  Back in Manhattan, we ate at  Veg-City Diner  and my friend went home.  I met up with my gal-pal, Marcia and we went to  The Collective Unconsious  for open mic night.  It was fun, we got some laughs.  Then we went to  The Sidewalk Cafe  and saw Marcia's friend Mike taping a performance by Helen (I forgot her last name).  Later, Marcia and I went to a pizza place and had garlic pesto foccacia.  We talked for a long time.  It is always good to catch up with her.  She is a dear friend.  After that we went home.  Monday, I stayed home most of the day and cleaned up the apartment.  I mopped the kitchen floor and moved the refrigerator etc.  That evening, I met up with Matthew at  Whole Foods  and bought some groceries.  I took the groceries home and rushed back downtown to  K-Mart  on 34th Street to buy some ivy for my kitchen.  Their plant selection  sucked !  Most were DEAD or bone dry.  I was outraged to see so many plants in a deplorable condition.  I almost complained but I was in a rush so I scurried over to the Astor Place  K-Mart  and got in just before closing--literally.  I bought five cute little ivy plants and headed home.  I'd better get back to work.  Ciao for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       All you have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to you... -- Gandalf  to Frodo in  The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring   I went furniture shopping today with my friend Eitan.  He had already eaten so he went with me to  Wai? Cafe  and had ginger tea while I had my delicious Wai? Salad.  Afterwards, we walked down 14th street and popped in a futon furniture store, then  Seaman's  furniture, then another store on Third Avenue, and then I had to go to work.  We didn't buy anything, but it was so much fun to browse and look around in the stores.  I saw some things I may go back and consider buying.   I'm going to a party tonight at my friend Keenan's house.  He lives in Williamsburg.  I really like it there because everyone is youthful, trendy, and sexy--nothing like my neighborhood.  But it should be fun.  I invited a lot of people to join me too.  I'll write about it later.    Although I am feeling glamourous today, I'm tired of being single.  I want a boyfriend.  Today is  National Coming Out Day .  Who knew there was a day devoted to it?  I found out about it this past Tuesday.  I wish the whole issue was not as complex as our society makes it.  Whatever.  There are people that I am sure suspect that I am interested in the men of the world, and there are some who I have not talked to about it yet.  People are people no matter how they are wired biologically.  I used to be so concerned about what people thought about me, not just regarding my sexuality but general things about me.  It does not matter as much to me now, because I am more secure with my  Self .  I am what I am, just as you are what you are.      The other day I was at my bank getting money from the ATM.  These two teenaged boys were sitting by the window.  After I got my money and turned to walk out I overheard one of them say to the other, "he's gay".  A few years ago, something like that would have me flee in shame and embarassment,  but this time I retorted, "YEP!" in agreement with his observation as I walked on my way with a smile.  I mean, really, the foolish child merely stated something I have known myself for over twenty years.   Anyway, things are much better now.  Living in New York City will do that to you.  It will make you stronger, more ambitious and more powerful if you know how to take care of yourself.  There are those who, for whatever reason, cannot endure the burdens of this metropolis.  Sometimes, people really are victims of circumstance, but I am a firm believer in willpower.  No matter what life hands to you--or  throws  at you, it is up to the individual to do what must be done in order to achieve one's goals and move to the next level.  People constantly rely on things that they do not need to get by.  Cigarettes, coffee, pills, blah, blah, blah...  Personally, I view these vices as weakness--and weakness is disgusting!  Vulnerability is appealing--and altogether different, but weakness is unacceptable.  I know people who just have to have their cancer-sticks--knowing full well it is not good for them or the others they smoke around, but their weakness allows them to submit to their addiction.  Simply put, smokers are people that have made a stupid decision in life.  I used to think that smokers were just plain  stupid  but that is too brash and brazen of a judgement to make, and has implications I would rather avoid.  The same with coffee.  It is so silly to rely on some beverage in order to "wake up" and start the day.  If you take good care of yourself, you will wake up and not need anything to get going.  Just be good to yourself.  Listen to your body and it will take care of you.  (Sigh) I make it sound so simple don't I?  Well, it isn't that difficult if you are dedicated to bettering yourself.  Anyway, I have said enough for now.  I am going to go drink some spring water...  Ciao for now! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       It's not about how much you can do, and it's not about keeping up.  It's about doing what's right for you.  Looking great.  Feeling great.  Taking yourself where you can . --Claudia Schiffer    Perfectly Fit  Series  I think that is great overall philosophy.  Sometimes, it is good to be competitive and challenge yourself to keep up or excell beyond your limits, and not just when it comes to fitness.  But other times it is good just to do what is best for you as an individual and keep things simple.  Yesterday was a good day.  After work, I went to visit my friends at  Lantern Books  to say hello and drop off some books from work I thought they might enjoy, as well as get Martin to sign my copy of his first book  Nicaea .  It was good to see Martin, Anne, Jason, Erin, Sarah, and Gene, and to meet Olivia, a recent addition to their team.  Unfortunately, Laura was not present due to her class schedule.  It was convenient that I visited when I did, because there was an impromptu birthday celebration for Gene whose birthday was October 4.  So, I signed his surprise card and we all had tea when he returned to the office.  We laughed a bit and caught up with each other.  Sarah recently returned from her visit to Italy and Jason advised me on how to start composting for my garden.     Once again, Martin and Jason really inspired me.  Martin thinks I should send out 100 word compositions on things I like to write about until I get a response.  He says he could see me as a columnist (I could see myself as one too since I've thought about it often).  Jason suggested I start a review section on my blog to supplement the work I send out as a potential freelance writer. What a GREAT idea!  Maybe those of you reading this will become inspired too!    I still would like to work for Conde' Nast.  But it would be better if I could have my own column.  Even better than that would be to have my own magazine.  It would take some work, I know and I shouldn't get too far ahead of myself.  But that would be a dream come true.  I have an idea about what it would be about, but I'd better keep it quiet for now since I don't want to see  my  ideas on the newsstand next to  Martha Stewart Living !    So, there will be a review section coming soon.   Ciao for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It has been a while since my last entry.  I would like to write more regularly, but I do not yet own a personal computer.  Things are all right.  I have been eating light for the past few days.  My body is detoxing, I can feel the changes.  It is a little uncomfortable, but the experience is not new to me.  I am avoiding processed foods as much as possible.  So, it has been mostly salads, water, and fruit.  As my body purges itself, I get mild headaches, a little tired, and the worst part is stronger than usual body ordor.  It is  not  from a lack of personal care--I am a clean and fresh fellow! But when you allow your body to elmiminate excess by-products it tends to affect one's scent.  It only lasts a few days and then it passes.    On the plus side, when you cleanse your system, it really improves your skin.  If you think you have good skin--wait until you change your diet and lifestyle habits.  You will glow with a new healthful radiance! You look and feel gorgeous inside and out.  You sleep so well too.  Your energy levels reach a new peak and your mind is much more active and creative.  It is just delicious.  Wednesday, I met my friend Matthew to view an art gallery in the Bronx.  His friend Derrick was a participant.  It was nice.  Then at my house Matthew and I discussed what colors I could use to paint my home.  He used to work for Martha and he's a graphic and web designer so I trust his color judgement.  I am watching John Carpenter's  The Thing  on TV.  That movie is just so gross.  I saw it when I was young and it scared the hell out of me.  Even now it still gives me the wiggins.   I am hungry so I think I'll go get a salad soon.  Tonight should be fun.  I plan to go out dancing with friends.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am off to California for a vacation (I sure need it).  So, it will be a while before I write again.  I'll be back in a few days.  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have  so  much to write about, but not enough time to write about it.  Things are well in my life to say the least and I will elaborate soon.    Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I saw the Lunar Eclipse!  It was pretty.  I saw it on the way to  Wai? Cafe .  Remember  Jeff  the guy that works there whom I thought was a "superhunk"?  He's sweet and has initiated a few conversations with me.  Cute as he may be, he's not for me.  First and foremost, I have  Kris , second, Jeff smokes!  Yes, as I was eating my  cold soba noodles (made of buckwheat), I saw him outside puffin' away!  Nooooo!  Oh, well it matters not.  Kris and I have eaten there before when Jeff was working so whatever the deal is with him, he's seen me with my pleasing-premium-Polish-prize.    At my house this afternoon, Kris and I watched,  View From the Top .   Gwyneth Paltrow  stars in the airline-based comedy with  Mike Myers ,  Christina Applegate  and  Candice Bergen .  Ms. Paltrow is so gorgeous.  Those lovely blonde locks, sweetly luminous eyes, glowing smooth skin.  Gwyneth...  She's a wonderful example of Libran beauty.  I love Libra's.  Being an Aquarius we have a natural affinity because we're both air signs.  Aquarians are known to be fair and pleasing to the eye also, but in a more striking or unusual way with magnetic appeal.  Libra's have the market cornered on "classic beauty".  I was just watching a show on  VH1  called  Super Secret TV Formulas  where they decode classic themes and characters used all throughout TV shows and cartoons.  One topic was the "Untouchable Hottie"--female characters that no one   ever   gets to sleep with.  Like  Ginger  on  Gilligan's Isle  or  Jennifer  from  WKRP In Cincinnati  and  Chrissy Snow  from  Three's Company .  The show also mentioned "The Very Special Episode"--like when a sitcom covers a controversial topic relating to sex, drugs or something.  The example they used for that one was an episode of  Diff'rent Strokes  where some bicycle shop owner was a pedophile!  I don't remember  that  episode.     One segment was about the fatter a character is, the more sassy they are.  Like  Nell  from  Gimmie A Break  and that grrrl from  What's Happening  (I forgot her name I think it was  Sherley ).  That was the segment where I saw  Dion Flynn  appear and offer commentary (you know how they always have an actor or comedian say something witty while they show a clip from a show).  I know him!  He's an acquaintance.  My long-time-gal-pal,  Marcia  has known him for years.  How did he get on  VH1 ?  I'll have to find out!  I think I may already know, but I'll have to confirm it.  Ahhh, time for me to close.  Until then...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm baaaaaack.  Sorry, I have not written in a while.  I was feeling a bit lazy and when I did feel like writing, the urge went away when I started to articulate my thoughts into words.  Well, enough of that.     Kris  and I are so happy together.  It really is a lot of fun being in a relationship again.  For those that don't know, I was going through a dry spell for a while (*sigh*).  I don't date very much at all and I'm not into bars and clubs or any of the usual stuff.  I go out clubbing to dance with friends sometimes, but when I do, I'm not looking to meet someone  special .  Really, darlings, how many of you met a  quality  guy or gal in a bar or nightclub?  Yes, yes, I know it is possible and it does happen for people once in a while.  But I'm all about wholesome healthy relationships where the people involved grow together and learn more about themselves as well as the other person.  I know it sounds like something  John Gray  would say (that guy that writes about men being from Mars and women from Venus--whatever) but that is really how I feel.  Sure, I could be a bootylicious-cleavagey-slut-bomb walking around saying, "look at me, I'm wicked cool. I'm five-by-five," but that is  SO  NOT what I am about.    If you must know, (and I think you do) Kris and I met through online personals.  I've tried them before, had some nice dates and then stopped for a while--not a big fan of looking online, but it serves a purpose, and I like how you can meet people you normally would not encounter in your daily life.  I gave it another go, used a different web site and Kris found me.  The funny thing is I didn't get his message until two weeks after he sent it because I forgot I had the ad online.  So, when I saw his message I e-mailed him back apologizing for the delayed response.  He was happy to hear from me--because after two weeks he thought I wasn't interested.  But I was.  He wrote back saying, "I hope to charm you with my unique personality."  Well, hot damn--that's one  hell  of a way to start!   He's a 26 year old Leo from Poland standing at 6'1" tall (how I love Europe, I couldn't count all the ways).  I like his accent and I'm learning some Polish words too.  Some of them sound really funny to me.  Anyway, I won't detain you with more details or TMI ( T oo  M uch  I nformation) about my new beau.  Although you must be aware that his name will reappear from time to time...   Martha Stewart  (love her!) is of Polish origin, but she doesn't talk about it much.  I watched her interview with  Barbara Walters  last night on  20/20 .  It was good.  I think Martha will walk away from this scandal.  I love her!  I do.  I don't care what naysayers say or think.  Whatever your opinion of her, she's come a long way on her road to self-made-super-success.  This woman created an empire all around things in and relating to the home.  That really is, "a good thing."  Last week, Kris (told you that name would reappear) and I saw  Kill Bill Vol. 1 .  It was entertaining and amusing but hardly what I call great cinema.  It was Kris' second time seeing it--and he has the movie soundtrack!  We're going to see  Matrix Revolutions  next week.  He loves science fiction and has a DVD collection to prove it.  You will not believe what I saw in Penn Station a few nights ago.  Well, come to think of it, you just may believe it.  I was on the platform waiting for the 2 train and I saw this lady--and I'm using the term loosely--a more accurate description would fall along the lines of an underworld (or underground) ghetto goddess.  This woman was out in public view smokin' up with a joint in her left hand and a cigarette in her right hand.  It was after midnight or close to it in case you're wondering why the hell she wasn't busted.  I hate the way reefer smells.  Her total disregard for everyone around her was so blatant I found it almost comical.  Yes, I think I did giggle a bit as I walked in the opposite direction.   It feels good to be writing again.  And believe me, I have more to tell you.  But I'll save it for later.  Until then...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Many thanks to all that have been reading my blog.  I haven't forgotten about you.  I have more to share and will post it soon, but this computer is being a pest today, so it will have wait for now.  Ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I received some lovely gifts from  Kris  today.  The fourth season of  Buffy  on DVD,  Andre Agassi 's new cologne,  Aramis Life , a  Kenneth Cole  shirt,  Diesel  underwear, a cordless phone, and money from mom.  I also received a winter jacket, but I am going to exchange it for another one or something of equal value.  I got Kris a stress relief gift set of aromatherapy bathing products from  Ben and Oliver , a small wall mountable organizer made of cherry wood, a quality bath robe, a yoga mat, and a nice fleece scarf.  I have more gifts for him on the way, but I didn't order them soon enough online so they will arrive early next month.  Later, we met up with  Marcia ,  Carl , and his friend,  Nelson  at Wai? Cafe for brunch.  It was a lot of fun to see them and we took pictures.  After brunch, Kris came with me to work and not much has been going on since.   I called my family to wish them a Merry Christmas.   It has been a good day.  Ciao now!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It is the day before Christmas.  I have to work tomorrow, just like I am today.   I just got back to my desk from taking a break.  I went to Wai? Cafe again for my usual Wai? Salad.  I was looking through my January issue of  Martha Stewart Living  and on page 88 I saw my friend  Zofia  in an ad for  Chico's .  I know she is a model, but this the first time I have actually seen her in an advertisement.  I did see her in an issue of  Gotham  magazine a year or so ago at an event.  She is really an exotic beauty with finely sculpted features and great skin.  I haven't seen her since earlier this year at yoga class she invited me to for her birthday.  Things have been all right this year.  I am looking forward to 2004.  I will be 26 in January, and I do not feel old.  People worry too much about age anyway.  I take good care of myself and my health so I don't get too concerned with how old I am.  Drinking water and wearing sunscreen daily, avoiding alcohol, and eating organic fruits and vegetables keeps me young and my mind clear.  Having a positive attitude always helps too.  I have not been writing a regularly as I would like.  I have cable again.  Naturally, things have changed since  Kris  moved in.  I stopped watching TV at home years ago, but Kris really wanted to watch TV so he got cable.  I find myself watching it more often now instead of doing more productive things (like writing this blog).    I get up at 9 a.m. to watch  Charmed  on  TNT , then I turn to  E!  to catch  Video Fashion  at 10 a.m. and  Fashion File  (great show) at 10:30.  At 11, I snuggle up to an old fave--the denizens of  Melrose Place   (Heather Locklear rules as Amanda Woodward!).  I don't really watch much at noon.  It depends on my mood.  Either  E! News Live  or local news or I'll do something around the house.  Then when 12:30 p.m. rolls around, it's time for  The Young and the Restless .   After that, I usually get dressed and ready for the day.    Well, that's all for now.  I plan to write more often these days.  I need to.  I sincerely hope everyone everywhere enjoys their holiday season.  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It is good to be back in NYC.  I returned on December 7, just after all that snow.  I had a wonderful time in California.  It was refreshing to be in warmer weather and see my grandparents, aunts, uncles, and cousins.   Most of them were surprised because they did not know I was visiting.  That was the plan.  I really surprised my dad, and aunt Cathie.    On Sunday evening at JFK Airport when I returned, I almost bumped into  Tracy Morgan  of former  Saturday Night Live  fame as he arrived with his son to catch a flight.  He now has a show bearing his name.   Then Monday night as I walked down 6th Avenue after depositing some ca$h in the bank, I passed by CNN superstar  Bill Hemmer .    I am at home as I type this.  Yes, at home!  I finally have a computer in the house, thanks to  Kris .  Things are going well for me.  I am content in my warm spacious apartment, planning out my day before I go to work.    Speaking of work, I have not done any Chirstmas shopping yet!  I have some ideas but I need to start drafting a list...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A week ago today,  Kris ,  Marcia , and I went to a comic convention on 34th Street across from  Madison Square Garden .  I've never been inside "The Garden" before and was disappointed to discover the convention was across the street in the  Pennsylvania Hotel .  Oh well, everyone knows that real estate in this city is a high-riding bitch anyway...  Anyway, it was fun.  Kris had a blast.  We met  David Carradine , from the hit show,  Kung-Fu .  I never watched it, but I know it had a successful run.  Mr. Carradine is also in  Kill Bill  (Kris loves that movie and has the soundtrack).  You'll see him more in the sequel later this year.  I don't want to spoil the plot for those that have not seen the movie.  I took pictures of Kris and Mr. Carradine.  I also took pictures of K with  Rene Auberjonois .  He was the stuffy pretentious guy in the 80s sitcom,  Benson  and more recently "Odo" on  Star Trek: Deep Space Nine .  Special K has all seven seasons on DVD.  His love for those shows rivals my appreciation for  Buffy ,  Angel , and  Charmed .  Well, of course Kris wanted to frame the pictures I took with the ones he bought from Mr. Carradine and Mr. Auberjonois.  So, earlier this week he went to  K-Mart  on Astor Place and bought two frames from   Martha Stewart  Everyday .  He arranged the one of himself and Mr. Auberjonois very nicely.  He has yet to frame the Carradine pictures.  I like how creative he is.  A day or so after the convention, I was watching  Charmed  on TNT and guess who was a guest star?  David Carradine!  So, I taped it for Special K and I to watch later.  The funny thing is that I'd seen the episode before and didn't care much about his appearance, but after having met him, I was excited.  I hope the show goes to DVD soon.  I must admit I liked the show more when  Shannen Doherty  was on.  Nothing against  Rose McGowan , she's great.  But Shannen was the big sister on the first three seasons and since she and  Alyssa Milano  did NOT get along, she flew the coop, just like she did on " 9021 -ho".  That was the nickname my friend  Steve  gave the show back in its heyday.  Ok back to the convention last week.  K and I also saw,  Lou Ferrigno  of TV's  The Hulk  fame.  His arms are HUGE.  They're thick like tree trunks!    Marcia had things to do so she left.  Kris and I walked around more and then went to get something to eat.  We went to  The Sanctuary  a vegetarian restaurant in the East Village that we'd never been to before.  The veggie soup was delicious, but my avocado salad left something more to be desired.  Kris liked his veggie burger and non-chicken nuggets. Our waitress,  Sequoia  was a gem.  What a sweet gal.   Well, later that same day, Special K and I had a dispute.  I will not go into too much detail, but it was not a pretty scene.  Due to previous events, and unsatisfactory answers to my questions, I was provoked, doubted my better judgement and lashed out.  In truth, I overreacted to something and made some hurtful statements.  During the conflict, the phone rang (because my birthday dinner was the same night).  After answering the phone I went back and saw I had devastated K.  I felt awful--I'm talking bottom of the barrel, rotten and putrid awful.  He was weeping on the couch and wouldn't let me see his face wet with tears.  I apologized, but still felt bad.  We made amends and I later discovered I was completely wrong about what triggered my anger.  So, then I felt stupid  and  awful.  I should have known better.  Well, now I do.  Everything is ok.  I feel that we are closer than before.    Just a couple of hours later, we arrived at Wai? Cafe to meet those gathered for my birthday dinner.   Phil ,  Carl , and  Megan  were already there.  Later,  Gail ,  Marcia , Megan's beau,  Bobby , my  Friendster  friend,  Roger , and my old pal  Dan  arrived.    Kris' friend,  Randy  came late.  So late that everyone but Dan was gone.  But we waited for Randy since he came down from Westchester.  He was under the impression it was a party that would run late into the night.  It was merely a dinner that lasted for a couple of hours.  More were invited, but they were not in attendance.  I received word from some about their inability to attend (thank you), but a few others never sent word or called or anything.  Not even to say "happy birthday".  Sigh...  Oh, well.  You can't expect too much from others or you will be disappointed.  All in all it was a nice evening and I received some nice gifts.  We took pictures too.    I was glad to end the day on a positive note after that negative incident earlier.   Now, it is a week later.  It feels as if more time has passed.  Special K and I are working on the kitchen.  "Lemonade" is a lively color.  It really brings the room to a new level.  It is brighter and more pleasant.  I am looking forward to preparing wholesome meals in there when the new look is complete.  Today, I have to buy groceries, and Marcia may be by later to play Kris'  Risk: The Lord of the Rings Trilogy Edition . Special K has never played Risk before.  I think he'll like it.   In other news, Wednesday, I sent a letter via certified mail with return receipt requested to  Discover  Card.  I cancelled my account.  I have enough debt to repay and having that card around with a $3,000 limit is too tempting.  Besides, hardly anyone accepts  Discover  in New York anyway!!!  For those of you dealing with credit cards, you really only need one.  Here are some tips if you are seeking financial freedom.   1.  Keep rates as low as possible.   After you pay off your balance(s), cancel all but the one with the lowest interest rate, and cancel the newer one(s) first since you have more credit history on the older card(s).  Also remember, just like your credit  limit can be raised--you have every right to call and request it to be lowered too.  The same goes for your interest rates.  Sometimes, if you just ask them to lower it and your account is in good standing, they will accommodate you to some degree.  You may even be surprised by how low they can drop your rate.   2.  Know your financial limits.   It does not make sense to walk around with a credit limit higher than your monthly income.  That is just ridiculous.  When you have more available credit you are likely to charge more than you need.  Do your best to  not  carry a balance month to month.  If you want to buy something knowing you cannot afford to pay it all back a month later, ask yourself if your really need it at the moment.   Those interest rates really add up.  Remember, credit cards are a multi-billion dollar businesses--they know what they're doing when you charge your way to trouble.  You pay more of  your  money for using  their  money!   3.  Always pay on time.   You can be a little late with other bills like the phone, electric, magazine subscriptions etc. But  DO NOT  ever be late in paying your credit card bills!  They will hike up your interest rate and it will blemish your credit report.  This will affect you negatively when you apply for loans, major purchases like buying a house or car, and in some cases even when applying for a job.  If you're really in a bind, call the creditor(s) and talk about it.  They're people too and you may be able to work something out without being penalized.  But don't wait until the day before you payment is due to call and talk about how broke you are.   4.  Write-up and keep records of your cancellations.    Always cancel in writing !  Your consumer rights are not guaranteed over the phone, and send your letter via certified mail, return receipt requested to the billing inquiries address (in fine print at the bottom of your statement) not the payment mailing address.  Keep a copy of your "cancelled by consumer" letter with your records of the card.  Then you have proof that YOU cancelled the card if your credit report has any errors relating to this.    If you want to know more, check out from the library, or buy one of  Suze Orman 's books.  I've met her before--she's truly a brilliant financial guru and a wonderful individual!  My landlady,  Rose  just called.  She was pissed!  I've never heard her this upset before.   Magdelena , the tenant downstairs from me has ticked her off for the last time with her complaints about the heat and various other things.  It is a little cool in my apartment, but it is not freezing.  It costs Rose too much to keep the place constantly warm especially when no one is here.  She just told me that Magdelena has to look for a new place.  Wow...  Mess with Rose and you get a thorn!  Now it is the last day of the first month of the year.  The Sun has been in Aquarius over a week now.  This time of year, my cosmic powers are very potent.  I plan to make the most of it...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Martha ,  Martha ,  Martha ...  I hope things work out for you.  I want this trial to be finished and your name in the clear!  This whole mess has made you lose over $700,000,000 on paper (she owns about 31,000,000 shares of her company--and the stock has dropped super-low since this whole scandal broke).  I am not aware of Ms. Stewart's current liquid assets, but her cash reserves are still in the multi-million dollar tax bracket.  Her legal bills alone were recenty reported at a nasty nine million dollars.    Martha's stock broker,  Peter Bacanovic  (now there's a man that knows how to moisturize) is also in the hot seat.  He's a distinguished and attractive gentleman in his early forties (but doesn't look an hour over 34) and a well-known socialite.  Well, I hope he gets to walk too.   Why?  Because I like them both.  I don't know who did what, but I want it to end and all of us to move on to things that really matter.  This just reminds us all to be careful with our investments, no matter how large or small.  And this goes beyond financial investments--although they are essential to good living--I'm really referring to all investments like time, energy, emotion etc.  Think about how you spend these things.  We call can make better use of our time.  But yes, we all like to lounge and do nothing on occasion too.  Just be aware of how you handle things.  What you decide to do with your time is like an investment.  What you do now, will affect you down the line.  With money, the point of investing is to give up some now to have  more  later.  And let's face it people, money is not like art--less sure as hell is not more by any means.  That is why it is important to foster good habits now.  Invest in yourSELF.  Like I've said before, drink more water on a daily basis--those sugary drinks and processed fruit juices will make you fat over the years.  Nobody needs the 20+ grams of sugar in one 16 oz. bottle of  Snapple  everyday.  Water will give you an enviable complexion, lift your mood, and help with digestion.    Stay active.  Don't get caught on the couch with that bag of chips watching reruns of  Cheers .  Go for a walk!  If you have a sweetie in your life, take him or her with you.  It is more fun to be active if you have someone around.  Eat fresh fruits and vegetables everyday.  And please buy organic as much as possible--no pesticides, no genetic modification, no hormones or whatever else they put in "regular" produce.  For the penny-pinchers, yes, it does cost more. But what did I just tell you about investments?  Salads are always great.  Use olive oil instead of those thick creamy salad dressings full of dairy and other animal ingredients (make me yack).  Or make your own dressings at home with tomatoes, or avocados, or herbs, and of course, olive oil.    I know it's cold outside and you want something hot.  Well, drink tea or warm water with lemon.  Sometimes when we make hot meals in the winter, we can overdo the starches like potatoes, rice, and noodles.  Now, steamed veggies is another rave fave.  You can never go wrong there (don't forget the olive oil and herbs--YUM).  Just be careful not to steam them too long.  The veggies should have some crispness.  Steamed mush is just gross and you lose a lot of the nutritional integrity.    And of course, wear sunscreen daily of at least SPF 30 or more and apply it at least 30 minutes  before  outside sun exposure--even when it is cloudy you are still bombarded by UV rays.  For many of you, this many not be an easy habit to adopt, but it is blissfuly beneficial.  Talk about investing.  You look good in your teens and twenties, right?  Well, taking the time to buy and wear a UVA and UVB blocking sunscreen will help you keep that fresh face  longer .  It has been clinically proven to reduce premature aging!  Then, remember to moisturize before going to bed after you floss and brush your teeth.    It sounds like a lot, but once you make it apart of your routine, it's like falling off a log.  In other news, another favorite media-maven-mogul,  Oprah  is 50 years old today! Congratulations, grrrl!  The first billionairess of her kind had a surprise party today.  Wish I was there...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am 26 today.  I didn't even leave the house.  Just stayed home and watched TV.  I painted some walls in the kitchen and took a nap.  I received many phone calls from family and friends.  For dinner, I made veggie pizza and watched  American Idol  and  America's Next Top Model  with  Kris .  It was a good day.    It is snowing profusely outside.    Well, it is getting late.  I just wanted to write something on my birthday.  I'll have more to say later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bedroom and computer room look great!  "Flower pot" is a rich and smooth color.  The walls have a deep terra cotta look to them that lends an air of a Mediterranean atmosphere.  The kitchen and hallway are next to be painted.  When things warm up, I'll get some new plants and add them to my collection.  I will be really happy when March gets here.  I want to start working in the garden again.  This year, it will be more lush and vibrant than before.    I have a lot of stuff to clean and throw out around the house.   Things are coming along, but the place is still in transitional stages.    Speaking of transitions.  I am going through a few myself.  I am cutting old ties.  Getting rid of things that do not uplift me.     Well, I should get to doing something around the house...  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Happy 2004!   This is my first post of the year.  Yes, it is long overdue since the year is already over two weeks old.  There is always so much going on, I have to start editing what events to cover on this blog and make time to write about it.  Sometimes, things happen that I want to write about, then I either forget about it or I decide that writing about it will take so much time that I don't even bother.  That is not the attitude to have.  I have a lot of things to do and many moons ahead of me, so as long as I continue to focus I will succeed.  I'm workin' on it people!   I am in the process of applying to the  Fashion Institute of Technology  to study interior design.  I went online and ordered my transcipts from  Auburn University .  They arrived yesterday.  I wish I was a more dedicated student in college.  I did not do poorly overall or fail any classes, but I don't have a 4.0 either.  The bottom line is that I remained in good standing during my college career.  Hopefully, some of my credits will carry over when I apply as a transfer student.  I need another degree.  And what I plan to study is something that holds real interest for me.  This will put me on a more level playing field careerwise and it will help me prepare the process of starting my own business in the future.  I purchased two gallons of paint earlier this week.   Kris  started painted the bedroom while I was at work yesterday.  He worked really hard.  The color scheme is all planned out.  The bedroom and computer room will be "flower pot", the kitchen and hallway will be "lemonade", the dining room will be "teasel" with "new bamboo" trim, and the living room will be "new bamboo" with "teasel" trim. The bathroom will also be "new bamboo".  The colors are from  Martha Stewart 's  Everyday Colors  collection.  I am excited.  It is the beginning of a new era for the apartment.  The whole place was just plain white before, but now the colors will change things for the better.    Marcia  came over, helped Kris prepare, and kept him company during the day.  When I got home, I made teriyaki stir-fry over udon noodles and then we played  Lord of the Rings Monopoly .  Marcia won.  This past Wednesday, I received an interesting letter in the mail from my financial adviser.  It was quite a surprise.  I will not go into detail now, but I will elaborate later.  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a great day yesterday except for waking up with a cough and sore throat.  I went to work as usual and on my break I went to visit  Marcia . She lives five blocks away from my building.  She's a dear friend to me.  After work,  Kris  and I went shopping, then ate at  Village Natural . He'd never been there before and I had only been there once so it was a fresh change.  He liked the place.    I was invited to two birthday parties.  First, Kris and I hopped on the Q train to Brooklyn for my vegan-former-coworker-pal  Jason 's shindig.  I attended his birthday party last year too.  He and his grrrl  April  are really wonderful people.  I always have fun catching up with them.  And with them both being vegan, I know whatever we eat there will be good and cruelty-free.  The party started at six and we were the first ones there around 6:20 or so.  I gave Jason a card and a houseplant.  He's an avid gardener too, so I knew he'd appreciate it.  I could never have too many plants.  (When I was a kid I made a Chirstmas wish list of all the plants I wanted--I didn't get any, but it was ok).    I saw some people from Jason's party last year, and some new faces too.  It was a good mix of intelligent, friendly people.  Some of us talked a bout  Buffy  and  Angel --just like last year.  This past Tuesday I found out that  Angel  will be cancelled after its fifth season.  Damn.  April made this yummy navy bean dip with herbs to accompany a lovely platter of red and green peppers, carrots, and celery.  There were also some cute strawberry topped cupcakes, but we didn't have any.  Kris is lowering his sugar intake and I knew sweets wouldn't help my sore throat.  The room was filled with a basil black olive scent as little pizz as were baking in the oven.  I wish we could have stayed long enough to try some of that and April's carrot beet soup.    The party's entertainment theme was boardgames.  There were so many of them! They even had  The Settlers of Cattan !  I played i t college, it is a fun game.  But after a couple of hours we had to get going to the other party.  If we stayed to play boardgames, I know we'd end up not going anywhere.  So we hopped on the 2 train back to Manhattan.  The second party theme was "Aquariu s Birthed".  My friend  Ed  (born Feb. 3), is back in town staying with his friend  Jacob  (born Feb. 16).  Ed spent some time in San Francisco because he was tired of New York.  But things did not work out as he hoped so he returned to New York.  I'm glad he's back.  We became friends through  Friendster   last fall and he had a link to his blog which inspired me to create my own.  Thanks again, Ed!  This party was set to begin at 8:30, at  Artepasta  in the village off of Seventh Ave nue, and again Kris and I were the first ones to arrive around 8:40 or so.  We were greeted by Ed and Jacob, and Ed's buddy  Gennadi  (they hang out all the time so I still say we were first among the invited guests).  I gave Ed a card and a banana b read scented candle since I know how much he loves fragrances.    Ed is a real character.  Very friendly, very witty, very sharp, media savvy and highly original--I would expect nothing less from a fellow Aquarian.  It was good to see him again since we d on't hang out that often.  Jacob is quite funny himself.  He likes to make off-color jokingly bitchy remarks and was a little envious that K and I are a couple and he's single again.  Ed asked what we did for Valentine's Day.  And I was so happy to tell t hem because this year was my first V-Day not being single.    The rest of the invitees arrived later and we had a lo t of laughs (for me my laughter turned into a cough, but I still had fun).  Kris and I had salad, and both tables had bottles of white wine.  I had water.  Special K likes to wine and dine.    After a couple of hours there we headed home since I have to b e at work early.  As we were putting on our coats, Jacob asked if we were going to have sex when we got home.  Ed scoffed at his remark, but I smiled and took it in stride since Jacob is a sassy chap.  Then as we were leaving, Jacob said, "thanks for comi ng," and Kris who didn't say much during the whole party said, "we will".    Both parties were great.  I had a good time.  I only wish I could have spent more time at both of them.       The saga continues with the  Martha Stewart  trial.  I hope she doesn't have to take the stand in her defense.  Oh, and I think her former stockbroker,  Peter Bacanovic , has put on some weight.  I can't say I blame him.  I'd seek out all my comfort foods if I was facing possible jail time too.  He's still kinda cute, but not as good looking as I know he can be.  When I see photos of him walking to court, he looks puffy and tired.  He's under a lot of stress so I understand.  For those trying to get rid of that puffy-faced mug, here are some tips:   Recognize your sleeping style .  Do you sleep on your back, side, or stomach?  Sleeping on your back keeps fluids from collecting in your head and under your eyes.  It also helps prevent wrinkles and creases on your face from your pillow.  It is not easy though.  I cannot fall asleep on my back.  I am generally a side sleeper.  Sleeping on your stomach is the worst position if your face is cons tantly buried in your pillow.    I once read something online about how a person's preferred sleeping position reveals a spects of their personality but I don't remember what it said.  If I find out more about it, I'll be sure to mention it.     Drink plenty of water .  Just get used to this one because I'll    never   shut up about it.  Water has so many benefici al qualities.  Staying hydrated keeps your face clear and reduces puffiness.  Just don't drink a lot before bed.  Nobody likes wakin g up at 4 a.m. to "pour some lemonade".   Exercise regularly .  This is good for you for dozens of reasons.  Keeping your cardiovascular system in good working order provides an ample supply of blood to your face (and other places) which keeps it look ing and feeling fresh.  Staying active also allows your cells to release toxins--a good overall internal cleansing.        Cut the SALT .  Speaking of internal cleansing, salt causes you to retain water.  You cannot cleanse if water is not flowing ou t of you.  People really don't need much salt anyway.  Avoid buying too many processed foods.  Microwave meals and canned soups are loaded with sodium and preservatives-- so NOT good for YOU .  You know damn well fast food is out the question.    There are some vegetables and herbs you can add to meals that have natural sodium and a mildly salty flavor.  Celery is one vegetable that comes to mind.  (On a personal note, whenever I make any kind of soup, it has to have celery in it.  Kris cannot get e nough of it.  Strange, though, that he does not like it raw).  Thankfully, spring is near and the weather is warming up.  Earlier this week, my March issue of  MSL   arrived.  The photos are really very beautiful.  I cannot wait to start working i n t he garden!  I am really excited this year because Kris wants to work in the garden too.  Ciao for now!   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why oh why do I allow so much time to go by?  I'm off work today, thankfully.  Things have been busy lately and as many know I am not happy there.  Sure, I can pay my bills and lead a semi-charmed life (not a reference to my show  Charmed  by any means, but more so that song by  Third Eye Blind ).     I've mentioned here before that I want to do something more creative.  I'd like to work at a magazine.  Something celebrity, entertainment, fashion, art, design, home & garden kind of stuff.  It could be one or multiples of those topics.  That's what I like.  I still plan to attend FIT, but not this year.  I want to be completely debt-free before I return to academics and I am only a few thousand away from that.  I still have so much to do.  I'm not being as goal-driven as I intended to be when I came to New York back in August of 2000.  I dare say I've become complacent.  Going about day-to-day living without much future planning when it comes to career.   I'll keep you posted as new developments arise.  In other matters, let's get you caught up on things... Kris  went to visit family in Chicago on Feb. 4 through the 10.  I missed him a lot, but we spoke on the phone everyday.     Saturday, Feb. 7, I had lunch with my friend,  Anthony  at  Gobo , a zen-like veggie restaurant with a light atmosphere.  Everyone I take there likes the place and the food.    That evening, I met up with my British-bud,  Kashiek .  He returned from his trip to London near the end of last month.  We were joined by  Naoko , a sweet gal from Japan, and  Romulo  a sweet guy that I once had a crush on long before I met Kris.  The four of us had tea at  The Factory Cafe  on Christopher Street.  I had never been there before, and that's where Kashiek invited us to meet him.   It was a cozy little place.  After that we went to  Republic .  A hip-trendy noodle and soup restaurant in Union Square.  I had to be at work early the next morning, but I didn't care.   It was fun to see those three again.  Tuesday, Feb. 10, Kris came home in the morning, and we spent a nice day together.  That evening, we went to see our gal,  Megan  perform in a theater production.  It's a comedy called, brace yourself...  The Coming of Dick: porn... it's as american as apple pie .  It's about this guy Richard (Dick) who wrote his first screenplay--a love story, but everyone seems to think its pornographic.  Reluctantly, Dick goes along with marketing the film as such so he and his buddy Anthony get financial backing by Anthony's uncle, Juiseppi the "Woo Woo Clown".  The play had some good lines and it was fun to see Megan on stage.  She played a dancer, and a guy named Lou.    Megan's man,  Bobby  was there as was Meg's longtime gal-pal  Tanya .  We all sat together.  I was glad Tanya finally got to meet Kris.  I don't see her very often, but she's a fellow vegan so we're like peas in a pod when we get to hang out.  Friday the 13th I worked and then went downtown to Union Square.  I love that area.  I also worked there at one time for a publishing company called Lantern Books.  I mentioned that last year, but it is worth repeating.  Their office is right above the  Diesel  store on 14th street and Union Square West.  Visit their web site at www.lanternbooks.com  Anthony's boy,  Tarik  was in town from Atlanta and we were to meet at  Zen Palate  for dinner.  Of course they were late because of traffic, but I didn't mind since Kris was working late too.   I read the day's edition of  The Daily  (the magazine they hand out to people outside the Fashion Week tents at Bryant Park) to get my fashion fix.    Anthony and Tarik showed up and one of Tarik's friends was supposed to also join us, so they went outside to look for him since he is new in town on some internship.  In the meantime, Kris arrived with a dozen red roses as I was sitting at the table!  To top it off he whips out the second season of  Angel  on DVD!  This guy really does  love  me!  When Anthony and Tarik returned without Tarik's friend, I introduced them to Kris, we talked then ordered.  After our meal, Tarik's friend called--he overslept.  Oh well.  Then we walked around Union Square and went to to  Diesel .  (Last September I bought a pair of slim stretch jeans there for $135 dollars.  They're good jeans, but I doubt I'll be doing that again  this  September.)  After that we went to  Mexx  so Tarik could see the place.  It's a European clothing store like  H&M  but with higher prices.  New York City is their first location in the United States.   After that, Anthony and Tarik were on their way to the show,  Wicked  a production based on witches from  The Wizard of Oz .  Then I saw  Jason  a fellow vegan friend and former co-worker from my days at Lantern Books!  I was really happy to see him and I introduced him to the group and he finally got to meet Kris after reading so much about him here.  I worked on Valentine's Day.  Later, I met  Marcia  at  Entertainment Outlet .  Her friend  Larry  was with her.  I gave Marcia a dozen white roses.  She was thrilled.  I knew she wasn't expecting flowers from anyone so I had to give her some.   The three of us walked to the  Virgin Megastore  in Union Square to meet Kris.    Marcia, Kris and I went to  VP2  (Vegetarian Paradise 2) and I treated them to dinner.  We had a good time.  Sunday,  William  visited for the first time.  It was nice to have him over since I have not seen him in months.  I made veggie pizza with tempeh on a soy-spelt-wheat crust for dinner.  We watched a new episode of  Charmed .  Yesterday, Kris brought me the last two slices of the pizza I made the night before and an organic pear for lunch.  Awwwwww ...    Then he went shopping for things for the house.  I was tired when I got home from work, but delighted by the two new shiny lamps in the living room he bought from  Bed, Bath, and Beyond .     We watched that new show  Airline  on  A&E .  Special K loves anything to do with airplanes.  That's part of the reason he got digital cable for us this past Saturday so he could watch the  Discovery Wings Channel .  I made green split pea soup for dinner, but I didn't want any.  Kris had two heaping bowls.  That boy supersizes everything...  That's about all for now.  I've been in the house all day, so I should get some stuff done.  Ciao now!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On Saturday afternoon after meeting  Special K  at his job, we went to  Marcia 's house then to  Fairway  and I spent almost $100 on groceries.  I made veggie pizza and we watched an episode of  Charmed .  Marcia loved the show and wants to see more.   The rules for  Risk: The Lord of the Rings Trilogy Edition  were too complicated so we ended up playing  Monopoly: The Lord of the Rings Trilogy Edition .  Special K went bankrupt and I got some of his property.  Marcia got the rest.  She was hanging on but had to constantly mortgage property to pay me.  The game dragged on for a while, but I won.  I'm getting a little weary.  I wish some of the clutter in the house would go away.  Not all of it is mine so I have to be patient.  The painting projects have been stalled for now.  Hopefully, things will start moving forward again soon.  Last night at work I saw photos of  Janet Jackson  and she was a little distressed considering the situation.  Of course most everyone knows that her right breast popped out during her half-time Super Bowl performance.  Well, the pictures are all over the world.  How embarrassing is that?  At least her nipple was covered with a shiny piercing that resembled a celestial sun.    Oops!  Don't do it again!    I was going to go out this afternoon, but now I don't feel like doing much of anything so I am going to stay home until I have to leave for work.  I'll tidy up some things around the house as usual...  Ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a very sad day for me and especially  Martha Stewart ,  Peter Bacanovic  and their families and friends.  This is  not  a good thing.  I heard the bad news right after the verdict was released:  Martha was convicted on all four counts, and Peter was convicted on four of the five counts against him.   They will be sentenced to whatever the judge deems appropriate on June 17.  Thursday, I purchased five shares of  Martha Stewart Living Omnimedia  (MSO) to show my support and hope that the verdict would be not guilty.  Early Friday the stock price went up a couple of dollars.  But after the conviction in the afternoon, the stock was halted by the New York Stock Exchange so no one could buy or sell.  Later, the halt was lifted and MSO dropped 20% before the closing bell.    I am not selling my shares.  I will hold on to them for as long as possible.  Regardless of the day's events, I believe in Martha's brand and her products.  I will continue to furnish my garden supplies, maintain my magazine subscription, and purchase various things for my home from  Martha Stewart Living !  I love you Martha!!  After work,  Kris  and I went downtown to  Lifethyme  and bought organic fruit smoothies.  We were waiting to meet  Marcia .  Then the three of us went to  Dojo  for dinner and discussed the events of the day.  Afterwards, Kris and I went home.  Bye for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am full of new ideas.  I keep brainstorming how, what, and when I will get things together.  I just have to get my thoughts in order and then figure out how to implement them.  I am really excited about it.  I like to think BIG, but it is the little things that need attention first.  I will say that it is media related.  There will be some design, merchandising, and publishing involved.  That's all I'll say for now.  All this stuff with  Jayson Williams  and  Michael Jackson  is getting on my nerves.  These court cases with high profile people is just too much.   Martha  (obviously, that was the most difficult one for me),  Rosie ,  Lil' Kim ,  Kobe ... The list goes on.  The case with Jayson Williams does not concern me much since I care so little for athletes (except for their muscle tone).  I guess I notice these cases more since I work within a large news organization, so I am bombarded with news stories and photos related to major events (or what the media considers  "major events")   Friends  is about to end.  Next week is the final episode.  I am not going to get all emotional about it.  It has to end sometime, and I am ready for closure.   Monica  is my favorite and  Courteney Cox  is so beautiful.  The show focused on her in the beginning because she was the only castmember with previous name recognition.  You know, the "Dancing in the Dark" video with  Bruce Springstein , her TV commercials (I think it was stated she was the first person to say 'period' in regard to a feminine hygeine product), her stint on a daytime drama (I forget which one) and her role on  Family Ties .  At first the producers wanted Courteney to be  Rachel , and  Jennifer Aniston  was supposed to be Monica, but Courteney liked Monica so she got it.     Monica is the glue of the gang, because she's the homemaker and so darned disciplined about almost everything.  She's smart too.  I identify with her because I like things to be neat and organized, but not to the outrageous degree she's portrayed on the show.  I laugh a lot at the jokes related to Monica and the witty lines she quips at the others.   Phoebe  also cracks me up.  I like her because she's a vegetarian and says the weirdest things that are so funny.  I like the others too, but Monica and Phoebe are my faves.    Today, I went to New Jersey to help  Anthony  set up his balcony with some plants to make it more appealing to potential buyers.   We went to  Home Depot  for the plants and other supplies and  Bed Bath & Beyond  for some bathroom carpeting.  He's going to sell that place and earn a substantial profit (that's mah boy)!  *Sigh* I cannot wait to get my own home.  Oh how I wish, hope and dream for it.  I am taking steps to make it happen.  It will just take time--just like anything else worthwhile in this life...  I am going to start going to the gym more often.  I have a membership, but hardly use it--and  Kris  is paying for it (at a discounted corporate rate, mind you, but still, I should put it to use).  The same can be said for Kris too.  He also needs to get in gear.    I've always been thin, so it's never a weight thing (and being vegan keeps me eternally lean--you should try it), but I plan to tone up some and get in great physical condition.  I'm on a quest for a beach demigod bod!  And when I am in good shape, I feel so sultry, sensuous, and sexy!  And we all know when you feel good--you look good too.  Ain't nothin' wrong with bein' a head turner--they can look, and that's it.    Not much going on in the garden.  I haven't been back there in a while.  The view from my kitchen window allows me to see a lot of new sprouts on some vines and my little Japanese red maple trees are so striking and strong with their new crimson leaves.  I love springtime...  Ciao now, J
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a socially rich day indeed!  First, as I was exiting the downtown 4 train, I noticed a familiar face.  I said, "Corey?".  It was  Corey Thompson !  We went to school together in England!  It was  so  unreal.  It turns out he's in town promoting is demo CD.  It was just so random that I happened to see him right there as I was getting out of the train.  We spoke for about 10 minutes, exchanged information and he gave me a copy of his demo.  I have not listened to it yet.   Later,  Kris  and I met  Carlos 's friend,  Piotr  at Grand Central.  We didn't see Carlos because he went to a party and Piotr had some free time to meet with us.  Piotr is Polish too, so he and Kris did some talking and I told Piotr what Polish words I knew.  We had a nice discussion and plan to meet up again when he's in town.  He plans to move back to NYC from Chicago.  After that, Kris and I went to  Fairway  on the Upper West Side to get groceries.  While waiting in the checkout line, I spotted my old pal  Bill !  He invited us over for tea to the apartment he and  Liz  were house sitting (with two cats).   It was so good to see Liz and Bill again.  They're known as the "Talk to Me Folks".  For the last two years, they've been going all around the city with a 'Talk to Me' sign and talking to all sorts of people for hours.  There was a great article about them in  The New York Times  a couple of years ago, and they were on  CNN .   After creating a list of e-mails and contact information from many of the people they met along the way, they later had a gathering in Bryant Park and several local news stations, journalists, and reporters were there.  It was such fun and Bill and Liz were thrilled.  Currently, they are working on their book proposal.  I hope it's a best-seller!!  It was a wonderful day to meet old friends, and make a new one.    Whenever I see the L'Oreal commercial for "Wrinkle Decrease with Boswelox" featuring  Claudia Schiffer , I become full of glee.  I've been seeing it more often lately.  She is still so  gorgeous  at 33.   That's mah grrrl.   Ciao now! J
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I met up with  Kashiek  last night at  Starbucks  on Union Square East.  Having never set foot in that particular location before, I was surprised to see how large and full it was.  Then, again, it was a Saturday night.  One thing that really surprised me, was all the teeny-boppers that strutted in!  I do keep in mind that in almost every person's life one reaches a point where one's age is not readily apparent--the late teens to early 20s.  You know, where someone is chronologically 22 but they  look  19.  Well, I don't know the ages of these kids, but most of them could not have been over 22.  So many (mostly young gals) kept filing in Starbucks giddy with giggles and girl power.  Since I don't drink coffee, I had no idea it was such a popular place with all these young folk.    One young fellow across from us, was joking around kind of loudly with his friends (two guys and a grrrl).  He caught Kashiek's eye, but Kashiek wasn't sure how old he was and if he was "family" (my slang word for gay).  This kid seemed all right, blonde hair, short to average height and frame. His only noticeable flaw was moderate acne.  I glanced over a couple of times, heard his voice and choice of words combined with his his gestures and expressions and knew he was a apart of the "family."  As far as his age, I guessed around 20 (maybe a little younger).  Kashiek is around that age, so this guy was fair game.  But I suggested Kashiek not to make a move in front of this guy's friends, because being asked out in front of others is kind of awkward.  I think Kashiek lost interest in him.  Anyway, since I hadn't seen Kashiek in a couple of months, it was good to catch up.   Megan  was on her way to join us.  She had a performance that night and she was meeting me afterwards to take the train to my house.  She was going to sleep over since we also had not seen each other in awhile.  She arrived later and the three of us had some laughs, then said adios to Kashiek.  Meg and I chatted the whole train ride home.  She and I have a really great rapport.  Other people on the train noticed that too.  We weren't loud or obnoxious, but since we both are animated and dynamic, we tend to get attention.    At the house, I cleaned up some a bit and cleared off the dining room table.   Kris  had to work late to assist implementing a new computer system upgrade at work.  I was cutting vegetables for stir-fry when he got home.   It was getting later and I had to be up early, but I didn't care because I was happy to have Megan at the house.  She liked the kitchen's new look with the bright paint and new shelves.    We ate for the first time on the new dining room table since we bought it.  It was nice to dine with our guest too.  The table wasn't really new, but it was new to our home.  I got it from my friend Gabrielle who moved to Amsterdam.  I used to house sit for him and feed his cats when he was out of town.  So, I had seen the table many times before and even dined on it myself.   I jumped at the chance to buy it and got the table and chairs for a reasonable price.    After our veggie stir-fry with rosemary garlic and herb toast, I had to brush my teeth and get to bed.  Kris and Meg watched an episode of  Absolutely Fabulous  on DVD.  I overslept by half an hour, and was late to work this morning, but no harm was done.  Later, Kris and my college gal pal  Alex  are meeting me after work and we're going to a shopping center in Queens.   Ciao for now! J
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On Wednesday, I spent some time with  Carlos .  We had lunch in an Indian restaurant on the Upper East Side.  I met him last fall at a party in the International House near Columbia University.  We've managed to stay in touch and hang out on occasion.    I saw Carlos again on Thursday after I had lunch with  Anthony  (Indian food again--it was a buffet) in midtown.  Later,  Special K  met us at Carlos's building and we went to the 47th floor to view the city.    Friday, after work, Kris and I did some shopping and I finally bought some bookshelves! Then we went to dinner at  Dojo .  Our friend and waitress,  Asia  (pronounced ah-sha) was there and it was good to see her.  After eating we went home.  Well, my two bookshelves were delivered last night later than I expected, but at least they arrived.  It was so long overdue for me to order them.  At work, I get a lot of free books and some at a  super  discount on a near daily basis.  So, at home I had a lot of books stacked up on tables and in bags on the floor in the dining room.  It was really an eyesore.  Now, I have a total of three bookshelves.  What a relief!  I am freeing up so much space and eliminating clutter!  Now, the room feels more open and clear.  I still have to finish things up and sort out what books I still want and which ones are going away.  But it is such a major step in the right direction and I am happy about it.  Last night, in a seed starting kit from  Martha Stewart   Everyday Garden , I sowed some tomato, morning glory, and moonflower seeds (all from Martha) in addition to some orange seeds I had saved as Kris assembled the bookshelves.  All the home and garden projects are really progressing well.    It rained last night.  That was a good thing.  As a gardener, rain is always nice because it is free, natural water.  I don't have to pay a water bill at my house, but I am still very conscious of how much I use when I turn on the hose.  So, when it rains, I know I don't have to use as much to keep my garden soil moist.    Oh, I almost forgot.  Tuesday night as I was going to the train station on East 51st Street, I passed (and almost bumped into)  Don King !  He and his driver were leaving a restaurant heading toward a white SUV parked in front. That hair of his is an unmistakeable feature that you notice immediately.    Well, today's high is expected to reach the mid 60s.  I love springtime...  Ciao!  J
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "The garden is a safe place, a benevolent setting where everyone is welcome.  Plants are non-judgmental, non-threatening and non-discriminating.  They respond to care, not to the strengths and weaknesses of the person providing it.  It does not matter whether one is black or white, has been to kindergarten or college, is poor or wealthy, healthy or ill:  Plants will thrive when given careful attention.  What is important is that they receive the proper sunlight, soil, water, and nutrients.  Thus in a garden, one can take the first steps toward self-confidence ."  From Green Nature/Human Nature, The Meaning of Plants in Our Lives, by Charles C. Lewis  What an astoundingly true and inspirational quote!  Well, I must tell you that I have been in my garden on many occasions this spring.  I have planted so many new things and I am greatly anticipating a healthy and robust season of foliage, flowers, and fun!   Many of the perennials (plants that return every year) from when I first created my garden are budding with new growth.  My hardy Hibiscus shrubs will sprout later in the spring, while my "Duchess of Edinburgh" clematis already has lots of new growth and is preparing to send out its first bright white blooms of the season.  I have been making many additions to the garden space over the past few weeks.  On April 4, I planted clematis and lilly bulbs.  On the 8th I planted more lilies, some peonies (my new favorite!), anemones, bulbs, and cannas.  The next day, I planted even more bulbs, and received an invitation from  Rose  to help her start a flower bed.  We went to a garden shop and then  Home Depot  for supplies to help get started.    On the 10th, I gave the garden a deep watering after sowing free wildflower seeds I received in the mail.    I also put my citrus trees outside to soak in the sun and warmer weather.    This past Sunday, I planted two rose bushes and some elephant ears.  Yesterday, I planted the third rose bush, a peony, and some bulbs.  I then watered the flower beds and Japanese red maple trees.    Springtime is my favorite time of the year.  I get to be outside, the weather is mild and working with the earth and my plants, while adding to the landscape of my garden, is a true blessing.  I have been taking pictures to keep track of the progress I have made.  I still have a lot to do.  Regular pruning, trimming, weeding, warding off pests and cultivating the soil are always apart of garden maintenance.  I enjoy all the work, although it can be tedious at times.  The soil here is so ROCKY that it frustrates me when I am trying to prepare a planting hole and add soil amendments.  I still find pieces of broken glass from time to time since the area was abandoned before I came along and started gardening here in the spring of 2002.  When I figure out how to add photos to this blog (and when I get a scanner), I will display what has been growing in Jason's garden...  Ciao for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Can you believe I forgot to mention earlier that on June 20 I attended my first  Madonna  concert!  It was fun.   Kris  got tickets for the  ReInvention Tour .  We had good seats on the left side of the stage above the ground level.  It was entertaining and exciting.  I only wish it lasted a bit longer, but I suppose an hour and a half or so is OK.  There were some songs I hoped to see her perform, but she didn't.  Overall, it was great, a real good time.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, well, well.  I am back on the scene after another long hiatus.  You knew I'd be back.  I can't stay away.  I owe it to myself and to you readers out there to keep on keepin' on for as long as possible despite these irregular extended lapses...  Here's recap to bring you up to speed:    May was a BIG month.  I went to Ohio to visit my high school buddy,  Steve  and his family.  We made plans to attend the 95th anniversary celebration of  The Progressive Magazine  in Wisconsin.  He rented a car and the next day drove us from Austintown, Ohio to Madison, Wisconsin.  Madison was interesting and the people were generally friendly.  I heard some great speakers and discussions at  The Progressive  event.  AND the next day, I met up with my college super gal-pal,  Sarah !  After having not seen her for four years, it was an overdue and brief reunion, but it was FUN!  I also met her boyfriend,  Dave .  He's a good guy and gets my stamp of approval.  I am glad I got to see them while I was in town.  I knew Sarah didn't live far from Madison, so I HAD to at least call and see if we could arrange a get together.  It was also good that Steve and Sarah got to meet after hearing about each other from me over the years.    May celebrity sightings include:  soap supervixen  Diedre Hall , rapper  Method Man , former 80s hunk turned soap star,  Lorenzo Lamas , and beautiful actress,  Jennifer Connelly   The first week in June,  Special K  and I went on our first vacation together to Miami for a week!  It was a lot of fun.  When I am able to get pictures up here, perhaps I will add some from the trip.  Miami was nice, but I would not want to live there.    Earlier this month, I saw  Tom Brokaw  again at Rockefeller Center.  A few days ago, I saw  Brian Krause  on West 50th Street.  He plays  Leo  on the WB's  Charmed .  He was walking with a woman and a boy.  More recently, I saw  Linda Vester , the host of  Dayside with Linda Vester  on Fox News.  I said, "Hey Linda."  She replied with a smile, "hey."  And a couple of days ago in Times Square, I think I saw  J. August Richards  who played  Gun  on the WB's now cancelled  Angel .  I am not 100% sure it was him, since I didn't get a good look, but it is a possible sighting.  Things in the garden are growing well.  Just about everything I planted in spring has sprouted.  Most of the flowering plants have bloomed.  My new rose bushes were beautiful.  So beautiful that some infidel came and cut two blooms off a bush and took them!  The vines are growing rapidly over the fence, especially the morning glories and the moon flower.  I've removed most of the weeds, and the compost bin is full of organic material to be used in the fall.  I took some pictures of the garden too.  I have two peonies that will arrive in the mail early autumn.  I don't plan to make too many more additions to the garden.  All I really need now is a ground covering plant and some mulch to keep the weeds out.  I got rid of the grass I planted two years ago because I don't have regular access to a lawnmower and unkept grass is unsightly.  Today, I might work out at the gym with K, work in the garden some more (my work is never done there), or hang out around the house for a while and tidy up stuff.  Well, whatever I do, I'll keep you informed...  Ciao for now! J  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not to sound sexist, but generally speaking  power  and  men  are so commonly associated with each other no one bats an eye, because a powerful man in the public eye is not entirely surprising. The methods in which he attains his status however, is often worth investigating...  Powerful women on the other hand are  always  fascinating. Now, more than ever the grrrls are getting in on the action and reaping the benefits of "livin' large and takin' charge!"  Martha ,  Oprah ,  Madonna ,  Mary-Kate  &amp;  Ashley Olsen  are media moguls commanding public attention in television, publishing, merchandising, fashion, and things in between.  Actresses like,  Sarah Michelle Gellar  of  Buffy The Vampire Slayer ,  Lucy Lawless  from  Xena Warrior Princess , even  Lindsay Wagner 's classic portrayal of  The Bionic Woman ,  Wonder Woman 's  Lynda Carter , and  Kate Jackson ,  Farrah Fawcett , and  Jaclyn Smith  as  Charlie's Angels  portrayed characters with a  kick  and are icons in popular culture as a result.  In sports,  Venus  and  Serena Williams ,  Anna Kornikova , and  Gabrielle Reece  are a few among female athletes that market their names and images, endorsing products on a level that rivals their male counterparts.  The most "super" of all the supermodels,  Claudia Schiffer ,  Cindy Crawford ,  Naomi Campbell ,  Linda Evangelista  ,  Christy Turlington  and  Elle MacPherson  used the attention and tremendous wealth they received from the world of fashion and became celebrities in their own right, practically eclipsing the clothes they were modeling and later moved beyond fashion into other venues. In the 90s they were so instantly recognizable they were often referred to by only their first name, a luxury that used to be reserved most notably for Madonna and  Cher .  As you can see, I am constantly attentive to the world of entertainment, which encompasses celebrity, glamour, prestige, money, sex and power. Every now and then, someone or something that is interesting, compelling, or just downright intriguing will get my attention.  Lately, my sights have been set on  Vogue  editor-in-chief,  Anna Wintour . I have read some notes here and there about her, but I intend to find out more. I am well aware of her tempestuous relationship with  PETA  since she refuses to relinquish her hold on fur fashions (as an animal advocate this is something that upsets me on a personal level). Her rise to power and influence is undoubtedly an engaging story.  In the meantime, like all the above mentioned luminaries: stay strong, stay sharp, and look good doing it!  Ciao now, J           
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had stuff to write about earlier in the week, but now that some time has passed, it isn't of any real importance now. Besides, I forgot most of it anyway... Generally speaking, things are going well. I feel good right now. I'm trying to think of any notable events from this past week, but nothing much comes to mind.  Oh, I did apply for another position where I work. It is in the same department, but a different division.  After work, I passed the nearby flower shop, and I could not resist buying this gorgeous  Spathiphyllum wallisii 'Mauna Loa' . It is a sight! I had one in college years ago, and when I saw this one I knew I had to have it. On the train ride home, people commented on how nice it is and a lady asked where I bought it. I still had the card from the store in my wallet from a previous visit. I gave it to her. The plant I looks great on my little antique side table in the dining room.   Kris  is on his model airplane kick again. He  loves  working on them for hours. Yesterday, while I was cleaning up things around the house and repotting houseplants, he was in his own world gluing and painting his newest plane on the dining room table.  Speaking of repotting: Those of you with office plants or houseplants, you should check them every spring/summer to make sure they're not rootbound. If they are, get a pot that is one to two inches larger; don't get all full of gusto and get a pot too much larger than the one you are replacing, and find a good quality potting soil (not that cheap stuff from the .99 cents store). I recommend  Martha Stewart Everyday Garden  potting soil.  For those of you who have not repotted your plants before, keep in mind you cannot expect them to thrive in the same pot with the same soil forever. Read the instructions for repotting on the bag of soil and get to it. Giving your plants new "homes" for their roots with fresh nutrient-rich soil will be appreciated not only by your plants, but you'll appreciate the positive results it delivers.  I found a strange thing on my balcony yesterday. I was checking on my plants when I noticed a dead bird in the pot of my largest citrus tree! I don't know how it got there. Kris and I think it must have just died and it happened to be on the balcony or on the tree. I still find it odd considering earlier this week while in the garden I noticed an almost fully decomposed carcass of a rat or something near a rose bush. I almost didn't even notice it, but the little bones and hair caught my attention. My guess is that the neighborhood alley cat that gets on my nerves dragged it back there and left the remains to rot. Well, it  will  enrich the soil.  Tonight we're going to  Ed 's housewarming party. It should be fun. If you're a long time reader of this blog, you may be aware that Ed is the one that introduced me to blogging. Kris and I also went to his birthday dinner at  Artepasta  back in February. His blog,  urlLink http://www.edshepp.blogspot.com/  is witty, edgy and entertaining.  That's all for now.  Ciao, J 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I want to share with you what has been going on over the last couple of days, but I don't feel like writing much right now.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'll have more to say later.   Ciao,  J   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saturday,  Kris  and I went to  Tanya 's birthday dinner at,  Sanctuary .&nbsp; It is a great vegetarian restaurant in the East Village that I recommended to Tanya.&nbsp;&nbsp; I don't remember everyone's name, but guests included,  Megan ,  Laura ,  Steve ,  Joe  &  Jeffrey ,  Cherish , and  Christine .&nbsp;   After our delicious meal, we headed uptown to  Patrick Conway's , the pub&nbsp;where Tanya's boyfriend,  Kieran  bartends.&nbsp; There I saw  Jean  again and met her boyfriend,  Tony .&nbsp; Laura and I laughed and talked a lot and found out we're both Aquarians.&nbsp; Her birthday is four days before mine.&nbsp;   Later, Kris and I went to the  O.W. Bar  ( O scar  W ilde).&nbsp; Kris knows the owner,  Scott .&nbsp; Over the last couple of years he and his partner&nbsp;remodeled and renovated the place.&nbsp;&nbsp; I&nbsp;never saw it before the change, but&nbsp;I heard it&nbsp;used to be&nbsp;a dive bar.&nbsp; Well, it is a nice place now.&nbsp; There's an outdoor patio, a lounge area, and a small stage for performances etc.&nbsp; On this particular night, there were go-go boys on stage.   Scott&nbsp;usually gives us cranberry juice when we visit.&nbsp; The first one was fine.&nbsp; On the second one, I thought I detected  something  because my throat was warm, but I didn't actually taste alcohol.&nbsp;&nbsp; I asked&nbsp;Kris if&nbsp;anything was in the drink, but he shrugged it off as nothing.&nbsp; When Scott brought us juice the third time, he said that he put a shot of vodka in them.&nbsp; Aha!&nbsp; I&nbsp;was right.&nbsp;&nbsp; I was a bit unsettled because I don't drink, but I decided to make an exception considering the occasion.&nbsp;   After midnight, we wished Kris a happy birthday and Scott brought us champagne.&nbsp;&nbsp; I was hesitant because I thought the cranberry juice was enough, but Kris wanted to toast his birthday with me, so I&nbsp;did.&nbsp; Afterwards, Scott brought&nbsp;more cranberry juice with vodka, I politely told him thank you for the drinks, but no more for us&nbsp;after that.&nbsp;&nbsp; I was already tipsy and had no intention of getting drunk.   We stayed a while longer and talked to a few people.&nbsp; This big guy,  John  came&nbsp;up to us with cards for this new club in Astoria called,  Fashion .&nbsp; He said some of the stuff used for the new bar/lounge was sold to them by  Claudia Schiffer  from her  Fashion Cafe  days.  Well, I intend to see that.&nbsp;   We made our way home before it got too late. Sunday, I woke up early, but Kris was still sleeping so I slept some more too.&nbsp;&nbsp;   Kris was very happy to receive the sweet birthday card I gave him&nbsp;in addition to one&nbsp;of his favorite colognes,  Le Male  by  Jean Paul Gaultier .&nbsp;   We went to eat at&nbsp; Serendipity 3 .&nbsp; The place was packed and there was a line of people outside.&nbsp; The host was&nbsp;telling patrons&nbsp;there was an hour and fifteen minute wait.&nbsp; Wow.&nbsp; Fortunately, we had a 2 o' clock reservation.&nbsp;   Afterwards, we went to Astoria to see  Fashion , the place John told us about the night before.&nbsp; The card said open at 11 a.m.&nbsp; The place was closed.&nbsp;   We went shopping at&nbsp;Target.&nbsp; I bought some stuff for the&nbsp;kitchen and two rabbit's foot ferns that were so large and lush with foliage, I could not pass them up.&nbsp; Upon his request, I also&nbsp;got&nbsp;the action figure  Merry &nbsp;from  The Lord of the Rings: Return of the King  for Kris.&nbsp;   At home, I worked in the garden for a while.&nbsp; Then we ate and watched,  The Time Machine  on DVD.&nbsp; I never saw it before.&nbsp; It was good.&nbsp; Then we watched,  The Ice Storm .&nbsp; I always cry at the end.&nbsp; Kris asked, "What was the point of that movie?"&nbsp;   I have more to write about, but I am at work and should get back to it...   Ciao for now,  J   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;       
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thank you!&nbsp; Thank you to the person that sent&nbsp;a&nbsp;friendly comment to me about this blog.&nbsp; I just noticed it today.&nbsp; It&nbsp;was my first one and I really appreciate it.&nbsp;   I want  everyone  to know that I truly enjoy sharing my ideas, thoughts and&nbsp;daily activities&nbsp;with you.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Like the rest of the world, I have good days and not so good days too.&nbsp; Thank you for&nbsp;hanging in there.&nbsp; Your readership is&nbsp;important to me.&nbsp; &nbsp;    Please note : my blog's&nbsp;web&nbsp;site address&nbsp;has changed to:&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink http://thejway.blogspot.com/ .&nbsp; So, update your bookmarks!&nbsp; If you have thoughts or ideas you want to share with me in regard to things you have read here&nbsp;(or would like to read about in future posts), please click on the "comments" link, or send&nbsp;an e-mail&nbsp;to:&nbsp;  urlLink thejway@gmail.com .   Warm regards,  J   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thursday,  Kris  and I saw  Tyra Banks  at a midtown  Barnes & Noble !&nbsp; YES!&nbsp; It was  TYRA !&nbsp; The supermodel turned actress/executive producer of  America's Next Top Model  was on her cell phone so we didn't speak to her, but she was looking well in a&nbsp;short-sleeved button-down top, jeans and sandals.&nbsp;&nbsp;   As we were leaving, she was walking downstairs toward  Houston's  (some steak house/bar & grill kind of place).&nbsp; I waved and she gave a brief smile.&nbsp;   Other top models I've seen include,  Cindy Crawford  ,  Marcus Schenkenberg  ,  Tyson Beckford  ,  Jason Lewis   (played  Samantha 's beau on  Sex in the City --I saw that show only&nbsp; once  over three years ago at a friend's house because he&nbsp;insisted I sit down and watch it),&nbsp; Jason Shaw  (former  Tommy Hilfiger  poster boy and  Paris Hilton 's&nbsp;ex boyfriend ),  Karolina Kurkova ,  Karen Elson  and I think I saw  Lauren Hutton  once in Greenwich Village in October of 2000.   Yes, I still have yet to see,  Claudia Schiffer .&nbsp; Our paths will cross one day...&nbsp;   I was scheduled to interview with a different department yesterday as a follow-up to the first one I had two weeks ago, but it was postponed.&nbsp; So, I will have the interview Monday at 1 p.m.&nbsp; I'm off that day, so I can sleep and take my time getting ready.   Yesterday, was&nbsp;a cloudy, rainy, wet day.&nbsp; At least the garden received a good soaking.&nbsp; I haven't been back there in over a week.&nbsp; I need to do some weeding, check the compost bin, train the vines along the fence, and clean things up.&nbsp;   Tonight we're going to  Tanya 's birthday dinner.&nbsp; Her birthday was yesterday, but the celebratory dinner is this evening.&nbsp; Tomorrow is Kris' birthday.&nbsp;   Ciao now!  J       
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This week on&nbsp; Martha Stewart Living  is all about entrepreneurs.&nbsp; They're repeat episodes, but&nbsp;regardless of that they're very useful, informative and&nbsp;inspirational.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Martha talks to people about how they started their own business and made it a success.&nbsp;&nbsp; I have to figure out what I&nbsp;need to do to start my own business...  &nbsp;  I had the day off, so I went to the gym today and had a great workout.&nbsp;&nbsp;As I walked at 4.5 mph on the treadmill listening to&nbsp;music, I thought about what I plan to do to improve my situation.&nbsp;&nbsp; I lifted weights,&nbsp;worked my abdominals,&nbsp;and soaked in the steamroom.&nbsp;&nbsp; All that physical activity helped clear my mind and let off some pent up frustration.  &nbsp;  I went home.&nbsp; I ate watermelon, watched some TV and&nbsp;later&nbsp;went downtown to&nbsp;Kmart to&nbsp;shop for things needed around the house in addition to birthday cards for upcoming birthdays this month.&nbsp;  &nbsp;   Kris &nbsp; came to meet me in Union&nbsp;Square Park, I handed him a heavy bag from my shopping excursion and we went home.  &nbsp;&nbsp;   Martha  was on  Larry King Live  tonight.&nbsp;&nbsp;Kris and I watched it.&nbsp; When  Larry  started taking calls,&nbsp;I&nbsp;kept redialing the 1-800 number, but the line was constantly&nbsp;busy of course.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I am tired.&nbsp; I have to be up early for work so I'd best be off.&nbsp; Everyone feels better when they are well rested.&nbsp; Good night.  &nbsp;  J      
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was my first day of work at the new location.&nbsp; I like the  new  space, but I don't like doing the  same  job.&nbsp; I have been in a rut for&nbsp;years now and I am tired of being patient.&nbsp; I need to make something happen.&nbsp; I need to hatch a plan...&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I know what my problem is.&nbsp; I know why things are not working the way I want them to.&nbsp; I am not focused.&nbsp; I have either lost it or didn't have enough to begin with.&nbsp; That has to change.&nbsp; The same situations and the same routine keep cropping up over and over.&nbsp; I need to break the cycle, stop the pattern, delete the file,&nbsp;pull out&nbsp;the weeds, sweep the floor, clear the air, turn over a new leaf--a new  tree  for that matter!&nbsp; Whatever phrase you can think of that applies to getting on with things and starting new.&nbsp; I need to do it.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  But getting started has continued to be a problem for me.&nbsp;&nbsp; Where to begin is another one.&nbsp; I have to think and I have to stay focused.&nbsp; Sometimes things just get so discouraging, and it is too easy to just call it quits and stop trying.&nbsp; Obviously, that won't get me anywhere.  &nbsp;  I dwell in the most famous, most influential city on the planet and I cannot figure out how to get in on the action.&nbsp; It is frustrating and daunting all at the same time.&nbsp;&nbsp; I just need to start making waves, make something happen and stay  focused  on it&nbsp;to see it through.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I know I am intelligent, capable, competent, ambitious, resourceful,&nbsp;reliable and  full  of potential.&nbsp; I need to get others, more importantly others&nbsp;in positions of power, to recognize this.  &nbsp;  I'll figure something out.&nbsp; I have to.&nbsp; I simply have to.&nbsp; This is serious.&nbsp; I need a change.&nbsp; I need a chance.&nbsp;&nbsp;Sure, I've felt this way before.&nbsp; But this time it is different.&nbsp; I&nbsp;am going to do a lot of thinking, (maybe even plotting) to&nbsp;get some results.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  For now, I may be down.&nbsp;&nbsp; But one thing no one should ever do is count me out.&nbsp; I'll find a way to get what I want.&nbsp; I'll be back in action soon enough.&nbsp; As  Heather Locklear 's character on  Melrose Place , supervixen  Amanda Woodward  once said, "I intend to be the last one standing at the end of the game."&nbsp;  &nbsp;  J  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Upon arriving home after work, I decided to stay home.&nbsp; I didn't feel like going back downtown and to Brooklyn today.&nbsp; So, I did things&nbsp;around the house.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I just concluded a wonderful time in the garden.&nbsp; I planted all the goodies I purchased yesterday.&nbsp; Ahhh what a great feeling of accomplishment and pride.&nbsp; It is so satisfying to work with the earth and plants to create a landscape that is lush, colorful and fragrant.&nbsp; As can be expected, the garden now hosts a variety of visitors daily.&nbsp; Birds, bees, and butterflies are the most favored.&nbsp; I'd like to have ladybugs visit, but I have yet to plant something that will attract them.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Unfortunately, the compost bin is&nbsp;a point of interest to slugs.&nbsp; I love nature and I respect the more unsavory aspects of it, but slugs are just so... Gross!&nbsp; Uhhhggh!&nbsp; I don't kill them, I just&nbsp;flick them off the compost bin with a twig or&nbsp;scoop them in a jar and&nbsp;jiggle them out over the fence.&nbsp; The yard next to mine is full of weeds and is completely uncultivated, so&nbsp;putting the slugs&nbsp;over there is&nbsp;of no consequence.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Not much else going on.&nbsp;  Kris  is on his way home from visiting  Asia  in Brooklyn.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I'm in the mood for some juicy, refreshing, cleansing watermelon...  &nbsp;  Ciao,  J  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is my last day at work.&nbsp; No, I didn't quit or get fired.&nbsp; The company offices are relocating and tomorrow I will be working in a new location.&nbsp; So, it is my last day at work  here .&nbsp; Perhaps&nbsp;working in the new office space&nbsp;will give me a sense of renewal and a fresher outlook on things.  &nbsp;  Yesterday, inside the Astor Place Kmart,&nbsp;I&nbsp;was interviewed by a reporter named  Galia &nbsp;from  Newsday .&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;She&nbsp;asked&nbsp;if I was a&nbsp;supporter of&nbsp; Martha Stewart &nbsp;and&nbsp;various other questions related to her sentencing.&nbsp; I showed her the products&nbsp;in my basket from  Martha Stewart Everyday Garden  and the bedding sheets and pillowcases from  Martha Stewart Everyday .&nbsp; I told her that I have a subscription to the&nbsp;magazine&nbsp;until 2009,&nbsp;that I&nbsp;have many of her books, I also mentioned that I am a company shareholder and that the stock rallied up over 30%.&nbsp;&nbsp;   She was a nice reporter and I was excited to know that I had made&nbsp;a positive statement&nbsp;on&nbsp;Martha's behalf.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;We'll see if it gets published...  &nbsp;  After Kmart I went to the Union Square Green Market.&nbsp; I used to go all the time&nbsp;to get good plants for great prices.&nbsp; I&nbsp;visited one of my favorite&nbsp;plant selling booths.&nbsp;&nbsp;I forget the name of the booth, but I'll mention it later.&nbsp; This really nice lady works there named  Maggie .&nbsp; She gave me great advice on my rose bush and how to get rid of slugs.&nbsp;&nbsp;I bought&nbsp;some&nbsp;regular ivy, Astilbe, Ostrich fern, Cinnamon&nbsp;fern, Boston ivy and a plant&nbsp;called "Snow&nbsp;Over the Mountain."&nbsp; It has bright&nbsp;pretty leaves&nbsp;which I know will add&nbsp;new&nbsp;visual interest&nbsp;in the garden's color scheme.&nbsp;&nbsp;From another booth across the way, I bought a little rosemary plant.&nbsp; I used some in a stir-fry I made last night.  &nbsp;  I took all my new purchases home, watched more Martha coverage on TV and later went back down to Union Square to meet  Kris .&nbsp;  &nbsp;  We went to Chinatown so he could get a handbag for his mom and aunt.&nbsp; He managed to get a good deal after walking away from the vendor twice...  &nbsp;  The vendor said he would sell the two for $60.&nbsp;&nbsp;Kris said he wanted the bags for $50.&nbsp; The guy said no and Kris walked&nbsp;away.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Fortunately, I heard him call us back (after being&nbsp;instructed&nbsp;by his boss, a Chinese lady at the cash register).&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The guy said he'll sell the two bags for $55.&nbsp; Kris reminded him that he already said he'll by them for $50.&nbsp; The guy shakes his head and talks to his boss in Chinese again.&nbsp; Kris is making his way down the street on his merry way&nbsp;as I observe to see what the vendor will say this time.&nbsp; "Sir! sir!" he shouts.&nbsp; "Kris!," I called out.&nbsp; He came back and gets the bags for $50.&nbsp; The Chinese lady at the register&nbsp;said, "That's very good deal!"&nbsp;&nbsp;  Darn tootin'!   I love getting bargains in Chinatown!&nbsp; I bought two&nbsp;Jasmine&nbsp;Vines from one shop and two&nbsp;Money Trees from another shop.&nbsp; I got both sets for&nbsp;good prices.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Then we&nbsp;went to&nbsp;Kmart (my second time&nbsp;for the day)&nbsp;and I&nbsp;bought some&nbsp; Martha Stewart Everyday Garden  potting soil and some flower pots to repot&nbsp;my new plants&nbsp;at home.&nbsp; My Jasmine and Money&nbsp;Trees look great in&nbsp;the living room!  &nbsp;  Today, I just want to unwind, work in the garden and plant all the new things I bought yesterday.&nbsp; Kris is in Brooklyn with  Asia  (pronounced Ah-Sha)&nbsp;and they want me to join them after work.&nbsp;&nbsp;I have to take&nbsp;the remaining personal items&nbsp;at my desk&nbsp;back home, and pick up some&nbsp;garden supplies on the way.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'll&nbsp;see then if I feel like going anywhere after that.  &nbsp;  Ciao now!  J&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Understandably, I am very distraught&nbsp;about what happened to  Martha Stewart.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;Her legal team are filing an appeal regarding today's sentencing.&nbsp; "I'll be back," she said&nbsp;during her public statement&nbsp;outside the courthouse after being sentenced to five months in prison, five months of house arrest,&nbsp;two years probation, and a $30,000 fine.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  One the plus&nbsp;side,&nbsp; at least the&nbsp;judge&nbsp;gave her&nbsp;a light sentence as opposed to pressing it to the max:&nbsp;&nbsp;The four charges&nbsp;she was convicted of back on March 5 carried a maximum sentence of five years each.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;She also gave Martha an opportunity to choose which of her six homes (she had seven but recently sold&nbsp;one for $7&nbsp;million) to&nbsp;reside in during her house arrest.  &nbsp;  Regardless of what you may say or think about Ms. Stewart.&nbsp; She is tough.&nbsp; She works hard and gets results.&nbsp;&nbsp;Everyone in the world of business, knows that she is intelligent, resourceful, and determined.&nbsp; At this point in time she may be down, but do not count her out.&nbsp; It is a known fact that this woman has become one of the most prominent, powerful and successful women in American history, and has done&nbsp;countless "good things" for people.  &nbsp;   Kris  called me from work to see how I was&nbsp;coping.&nbsp; I'm ok.&nbsp;&nbsp; I am going to get dressed, take care of things around the house and go to K-Mart and&nbsp;buy some of Martha's products.&nbsp; She has my support no matter what.  &nbsp;  Interestingly,&nbsp;shares of&nbsp; Martha Stewart Living Omnimedia  have rallied up by over 30% today.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I will&nbsp;continue to monitor events relating to all things Martha&nbsp;in the weeks and months to come.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Stay strong, Martha.&nbsp;  It's a good thing ...  &nbsp;  Ciao for now,  J  &nbsp;  &nbsp;        
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I won the lottery yesterday!&nbsp; Can you believe it?&nbsp; I  won  something!&nbsp; I was thrilled!&nbsp; How much did I win?&nbsp; You want to know the amount?&nbsp; Well, it was two dollars.&nbsp; Yeah, so it wasn't the jackpot, but I won something!  &nbsp;  Ciao!  J   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I forgot to mention that this past Sunday,  Kris  and I went to see our friend  Carlos  in a musical called  Another Life?   It was the first time we saw Carlos perform.  He was part of an ensemble cast.  It was a good show.  I'm proud of him.  Yesterday, after work, I met  Kris  downtown near City Hall.  We walked west to the Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) so Kris could get started on his registration process. He's going to take business administration courses this fall.  At the campus entrance is a cute little garden with a variety of plants and a few peonies.  Their flowering season is over, but their foliage is so lush and exotic.  I am looking forward to seeing the peonies in my garden bloom in the coming years.  Since they are new, they need time to mature before they can flower.  Peonies are ancient plants that the Chinese cultivated centuries ago.  It is not uncommon for a peony to outlive the person who planted it.  So, Kris took care of things at BMCC.  We walked around the building a little, and then headed home.  On the way we were delayed for a LONG time on the 2 train.  Then the conductor announced that the train was out of service.  There's public transportation for you.  Another train came not too long afterwards.  We went to dine at  Candle Cafe  for the first time.  I'd never been there before and Kris had never heard of it until I suggested going.   Marcia  had a birthday party there many years ago.  It was smaller than I thought it would be, but the decor and atmosphere were light and pleasant.  The waitstaff were friendly and attentive, especially when it comes to water refills.  That's important to me since I always like to drink water and cannot stand repeatedly asking for a refill.  After dinner we walked uptown to "Best Buy".  From the clearance section, I bought  The Ice Storm  on DVD.  I saw it for the first time in college and I loved it.   Sigourney Weaver  is one of my favorite actresses, and that film is just very moving to me.   Kevin Kline ,  Joan Allen ,  Tobey MaGuire ,  Elijah Wood ,  Katie Holmes  and  Christina Ricci  also star in this actor driven film portraying two dysfunctional families in the 1970s, and how an ice storm changes their lives forever.  I bought it for $5.99.  I bought a dance CD too but I forget the name.  Upon arriving home and relaxing, we talked about events of the day and just enjoyed our time together.  I did some push-ups and leg lifts with ankle weights.  We also watched the day's episode of  Martha .  Her sentencing is this Friday.  I am really concerned.  I don't want her to do jail time.  I just don't.  I won't go on and on to justify it or explain why.  But by now, you all should  know  why...  Ciao now, J  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This past Thursday,  Asia  (pronounced Ah-Sha),  Kris , and I saw  Spiderman 2 . It was a good movie. I liked the love story and I enjoyed the internal and external conflicts of the characters. I recommend it if you have not seen it yet.   Later that night, after I ironed my shirt for my interview in the morning, I acidentally smashed my left pinky toe on the door frame! That  $#~* HURTS ! It still hurts a bit, but at least I can walk without too much discomfort.   Friday morning, (my day off) I went to work for an interview in another department. It went well and lasted longer than I thought (a good sign). There are other candidates of course, but this would be a step in a new direction if I am selected and IF I decide to accept the position. However, I could use some new skills to make myself more marketable.   After that, I limped over to Verizon Wireless to see about my mobile phone. It fell out of my bag the night before at the movie theater and the battery clip would not lock in completely so my phone won't work unless I press the battery down against the phone console. That sux!   The technician told me I have to call the insurance company and order a new battery back and pay a deductible. I have insurance coverage on my phone, so why can't they just GIVE me a new battery?! I have to read my user agreement or something because the situation makes about as much sense as a turd in a punch bowl!   I went home, ate yummy juicy watermelon, and talked on the phone with  Anthony . Then, I watched  The Young and the Restless  (a.k.a. Y&amp;R) After that I went to K-Mart and bought a good-bye card and a "watermelon slice" scented candle from  Martha Stewart Everyday .   I headed uptown back to work AGAIN for a going away party for  Michelle  at 5 p.m. She's moving to Florida. I know her from my days as a temp. I used to temp for the organization I now work for (after becoming a permanent employee I realize I had more fun as a temp), and Michelle was my contact when I arrived for my assignments.   She worked in HR on the seventh floor and I'm on the fourth, but we would meet and greet in the halls or the caf from time to time, or I would go up and see her. She always gave me a smile, good advice and words of encouragement.   At her going away party on the eighth floor, there was music, snacks and drinks. I saw a few faces I knew and I met some people I had seen before but never met. Since most of those present were in HR, I made a point to remember names. Michelle liked the card and the candle. I stayed for about an hour then said good-bye.   Upon leaving the party, I noticed I had a voice message from  Alex . I hadn't spoken to her in weeks. So, I met up with her at the art gallery she works in on West 20th Street. Later, after her lengthy conversation with her mother who phoned from Germany, we went to get something to eat at a restaurant at Chelsea Piers called  CBC Chelsea . I didn't even know the place existed. It was expensive, but I didn't care. I was with Alex and we always have fun.   It was kind of chilly since we were by the water. Actually, I was cold. Alex, decided to run back to the gallery and get a pullover. As she was leaving,  Jennifer  arrived and greeted her friends at the table directly behind me. Jennifer and I had German class together back at Auburn University! I didn't say anything for a while, but I listened to see if and how she changed over the years. She was like I remembered her. Smart, sassy and sweet.   When Alex returned, I brought her up to speed. She didn't know Jennifer, but somehow, I thought they had met before during our days at Auburn. Anyway, as we were leaving, Jennifer was away from her table smoking a cigarette. I greeted her and she was very surprised to see me. We played catch up and made some small talk and I got her number and e-mail address.   I moved to New York not long after Jennifer did. We were in touch for a while, but things faded. Well, now that I've seen her again, I plan to stay in touch! I'll write her after I complete this edition of  The J Way .   Alex and I walked to a little French restaurant she likes on Ninth Avenue. It was cute and there was a May issue of  Amica , a German fashion mag with  Claudia Schiffer  on the cover. We read some of the interview inside. Alex doesn't care much for Claudia. That's ok, because I think she's top shelf!   Alex had a glass of white wine and I had mint herbal tea. We chatted about the guy she likes and various other tidbits and laughed about events from our past. Later, we walked toward the train station on Seventh Avenue. On the way we stopped at a deli on Eighth Avenue.   In the deli, this French guy was giving me the eye. I saw him looking at me out of the corner of my eye while I was talking to Alex. He gave a little smile as I passed him and I said "hello" while following Alex to the cash register as she paid for her  Soy Chips  and candy. As we exited, I didn't turn around, but in the reflection on the glass door, I saw him look over at me.   Isn't it odd how when I was looking to meet someone, I didn't get that much attention? Now that I am in a committed relationship, guys are checking me out. My guess is that I am more confident, comfortable, and vibrant since I have someone steady in my life. Maybe people notice that.   As we approached&nbsp;Seventh Avenue, we passed  Rufus Wainwright  walking with someone.&nbsp; Alex didn't know who he was.  Yesterday, I stayed home. I cleaned the bedroom, watched some taped episodes of  Martha Stewart Living  and relaxed. Kris got home from work around 2 p.m. We saved our important files on disks and rebooted the computer. Kris is elated that the computer is clean and new again. Later, we each ate half a watermelon and he watched more Martha with me.   I was going to go with Kris downtown to meet Asia, but my foot hurt too much to go on an extended walk. So, I worked in the garden and did more cleaning around the house.   The weather is nice. It is not too hot and I like being outside. The garden has stabilized and most of the plants have reached their peak or are approaching it for the season. The weeds are generally under control and the compost is developing very well.   Ciao now!  J   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I feel good physically.  As a result of my fresh fruit and salad eating over the past few days, I feel lighter and cleaner on the inside.  My state of mind is improving.    I miss  Kris .  The house is quiet. It was refreshing at first, but now I'd rather hear him in the kitchen looking in the fridge, working on one of his various  Star Wars  projects, speaking Polish to his mother on the phone, or watching TV.    He'll be back soon and I still have things to do around the house before he returns.    I am going to do a more serious job search when I get home today.   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Right now I hear them They're outside In the air The sounds The noise The FIREWORKS!  As I type this, people are out and about gleefully lighting firecrackers and filling the air with smoke.  This year, I'm  not interested.  I guess partly because  Kris  isn't here, and I am tired from staying up late these past few days.  After work, I didn't go home as planned.   Megan  called and invited me to attend a picnic with her friends in Central Park.  She and  Neil  were getting ready.  I didn't want to miss an opportunity to meet more of Megan's friends, so I agreed to meet up with them.    Megan lives in Brooklyn's Park Slope.  These plans were made around 3:45 and I was set to leave work at 4:00.  We agreed to meet at Broadway and 86th street at 5:00 and walk over to the picnic.  Who's late a$$ walks outta the subway station at around a quarter to six?!  Megan with Neil (her old school chum) in tow.    Thankfully, I had my book,   Martha Inc.   to read while I waited, and it was getting juicy.  I recommend it, even if you don't like Martha Stewart.  You may learn something.  What she managed create on her own is astounding.  What she managed to create in the corporate world is phenomenal.    Megan is notoriously late ALL the time.  I used to not worry about it, but now it gets on my nerves.  Anyway, they picked up some snacks at a nearby Gristedes supermarket and then we took the bus to Central Park West, where we walked for a while and met  Eric  and  Paul , visiting from New Orleans.  They just left the picnic to attend another event in Brooklyn.  I knew that would happen, we'd be SO late that people would be departing by the time we arrived.  We finally found where the others were and I got to meet the other  Megan  (Megan#2 for now) that I had heard so much about, and her husband, as well as some other friends of theirs.  They were a nice little group.  I knew there would not be much for me to eat there so it was a good thing that I still had some snacks from my trip to  Whole Foods Market  during my lunch break at work.  I still had half a bag of raw cashews, two nectarines, and a mango (that I still have yet to eat).    It was great to be in the park, meet new people, and share some laughs.  Later, others made their exit.  And then the final few of us decided to get going too.  We were on our way to Brooklyn Heights to see the fireworks from the Promenade.  As Megan, Megan#2, her husband, Neil, and I made walked out of Central Park with the remaining food and snacks to put in Megan#2's car, I decided to do what I intended all along: go home.    Megan was disappointed.  I was too a little, but I need to be home and alone.  I also need to rest since I have to be at work tomorrow *sigh*.  Ciao for now, J    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am tired now.  I have a lot to do too.  Since my mood has not been at its best lately, I have not felt like doing much around the house.  There is clutter in every room except the bathroom.     Last night, I met up with my friend,  Asia  (pronounced Ah-Sha) and we saw  Dodgeball .   It had some very funny moments with witty dialogue and celebrity cameos.  Then we went to Wai? Cafe to eat salads, of course.  We were the ONLY ones there.  The place was totally empty.    After parting with Asia, I went to see  Megan  and her friends at a pub a block away from Grand Central Terminal called,  Patrick Conway's .  I saw  Tanya  and  Neil , whom I already knew and I met their other friends  Jean ,  Laura  and her husband (I forgot his name).  Later, I met  Jeffrey ,  Joe , and  Cherish .  I've been reading   Martha Inc.  The Incredible Story of Martha Stewart Living Omnimedia , by  Christopher M. Byron .  I bought the book on July 12 last year.  When I buy a book I like I usually write the date I bought it inside.  I like doing that because it reminds me of the time I bought it, where I was, what I was doing, etc.  I read it avidly last summer.  I remember sitting in Central Park, commuting on the train, and relaxing at home, just reading away how Martha created her empire and the experiences that prompted her to do so.    I decided I needed more inspiration, motivation, and determination.  So, a few days ago, I started reading the book again.  I'm on chapter 10 now.    I cannot believe I forgot to mention how happy I am that my gal,  Claudia Schiffer  and her husband  Matthew Vaughn  are expecting their second child later this year.  Congratulations!   I had some really good nectarines yesterday.  They were organic of course and just so refreshing.  I did push-ups before going to bed after 1:30 a.m. this morning.  My chest is developing gradually.  I like what I see so far.  Getting in shape is fun.      I don't really feel like talking to anyone today.  I know it is July 4th and it is supposed to be a festive holiday.  I'd rather be alone today.  I'm not making plans to do anything after work.  I am going home and fixing up one of the few aspects of my life that I actually can control: my home.  So, I think I'm better off alone.  If you can handle it, solitude makes you stronger.  Happy 4th of July to you!  Ciao, J
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After a scuffle with a coworker yesterday, I realized yet again how much I really, truly, wholeheartedly do NOT like my job.  I have complained and ranted about it for a long time now and I simply must do something about it.  I must escape, yes that's what I said--escape, because I feel trapped, caged, confined with no way out.  This is not healthy, this is not good, I cannot not endure this, no one should.  I would like to plot a vicious revenge, but that is not healthy either.  So, I have to embrace the pain and comfort my inner moppet and move on...  I got home and went online to look for jobs.  Then a thunderstorm made itself known.  I pretended I had control over it and said some incantations to vent my rage.  Then the wind knocked over the containter I use to water my plants that was next to the dining room window.  I mopped up the water.  The thunder and lighting was refreshing.  It was nice to see weather conditions that reflected my mood and state of mind at the moment.  The storm became so intense that I had to turn off the computer for fear of it being damaged. Not much progress in my job search.  I called  Megan .  She was, yet again, depressed and conflicted about personal issues.  I can identify with that. We made dinner plans.    I played the lottey yesterday. Obviously, I did not win.  If I had, the tone of this post would be much different indeed.  As I sat in Wai? Cafe.  Megan called to tell me she would be late.  I was not surprised.    While waiting, I read a  New York Press  article about this woman who is a submissive and seeks out abusive men for sex.  She wanted a black eye.  She said it herself in the article.  She was seeing this guy named  George  who hadn't given her a black eye yet, but she knew eventually he would.  She said she needed the fear.  If she wasn't afraid of him she would not meet with him again.  Everyone before George was a one time thing.  She's been meeting with him repeatedly.  She went on to tell her story about why she was into this sort of thing.  It was bizarre.  I don't know what her childhood trauma was, but she stated her parents were good to her.  But she did have an odd relationship with this boy  James  when she was six years old.  Oh, and get this.  Girl is married! But her husband is too nice and safe she said.  Well, to each their own.  I am not passing judgment, but it was one of the most unusual things I have read in a long time.    It reminded me that no matter how twisted or freaky or shocking your thoughts or the thoughts of others may be, (you know how sometimes when thinking you surprise yourself and ask, "where did THAT come from?"), they are only thoughts; but you must realize someone out there is acting them out, living them or dying by them.    Anyway, Megan arrived and we had salads.  Earlier in the day I had raisins and almonds.  Then some peaches.  I've been having more frequent bowel movements.  That's a good thing.  Get that $#!& outta me!    While we were eating, my dad called.  He was about to see  Spiderman 2 .   Then,  Enrico  was outside the restaurant waving at me.  I didn't even notice it was him since I was on the phone.  He said my name and then I realized who it was.    So, the three of us dined together and had a lot of laughs.  We sat there for a while talking and eating.  After leaving we walked down 14th Street to see if  Veg City Diner   was open yet.  After multiple delays and date changes they were set to reopen on July 1 after renovations.  Well, that was another lie, because the place is gone!  Oh well.  Things come and go in a big city all the time.  As we walked to Union Square, I saw  Liz & Bill , the "Talk to Me" people!  If you live in New York City, you may have seen them around or on television over the last two years with their "Talk to Me" sign.  Or perhaps you read about them in  The New York Times .  Anyway, their good friends that I don't see often, but it is great when we get together.  So, Megan and Enrico got to meet them and we had fun.  It was getting late though, so we all had to get going.  It was nice.  I didn't plan on seeing Enrico, or Liz & Bill, but I am glad I did.  When I got home, there was a message from  Kris .  I called him back. Twice.  The second time was because I could not sleep.  I was still upset from what happened at work.  I'm going to get out.  I know I will.    I'm glad to know Kris is enjoying time with his family.  They're having a party for his dad today.   That's all for now. J  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Kris  went to Chicago yesterday.    Well, the first half of the year is officially history.  It is July 1st.  Today, I stayed home for a while, talked on the phone with my good friend,  Gail .  Talked to Kris, of course.  We talk everyday.  Literally. It doesn't matter if he's at work or in another state.  I think it's sweet.  We don't usually have long conversations since it is a daily thing, but we check in with each other and share tidbits of whatever is going on at the time.  He's having fun in Chicago, and I am enjoying some quiet time at home.  I do miss him though...  All I've eaten today is watermelon this afternoon, some raisins and almonds, and some peaches. I'm eating really light and simple so I can cleanse my body and refresh my innards.  I will continue to eat this way for the foreseeable future and I will document my experiences here of course.    I did venture out to the gym this afternoon after watching  The Young and the Restless  (I LOVE that show!).  I had a good workout.  Ok, for me, one of the most attractive, most sensual, most desirable parts of the body on a man or woman (ain't no shame in the cleavage game) is the chest.  So, naturally with it being summer and seeing all these well developed and shapely chests, I decided that I deserve one too.  So, I worked on my chest and then my arms, and legs (I swoon over a good pair of legs too).  Then I did an hour of cardio; 30 min. on the treadmill walking at 4.5 mph and then 30 min on the exercise bike.  After that, I hit the steamroom and took a refreshing shower.  I felt really invigorated.  I am tired now though.   I need to get to bed.  I am supposed to be off tomorrow, but my coworker had a death in the family so he asked me to cover his shift.  I agreed of course, and I'll get paid overtime, but leisure time at home is priceless.  Ciao! J
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hope that people can still find my blog. A few weeks ago, I changed the address from formidablemind.blogspot.com to thejway.blogspot.com. The problem is that I did not announce it until  after  the change was made. That was not how I should have handled things and I do apologize. I want this blog to be easily accessible to you.  I read last week that  Claudia Schiffer  is planning to write a book. That should be interesting (to me anyway). I'd love to see the legendary model's perspective on the world of fashion, business, motherhood, and all the other things she decides to include in her writing.  I feel another cycle of change approaching. I haven't been keeping up with my astrology lately, but there must be some sort of transit on the horizon or perhaps I am in the midst of one now.  Let's see, I have two possible leads at work. One is a transfer and the other is a promotion. Either way, it will be a fresh start. I also have a tentative meeting with an individual who may help me later in yet another department. The benefit of working within a large organization is that there are several opportunities available if you look for them.  I'm letting my hair grow. Usually, I opt for the short-almost-bald look. It is clean, sharp and brings out my eyes. But in summer when hair seems to grow more rapidly, I tend to let it grow out. I associate a lot of hair with youth, energy, vitality, and earthy sex appeal. The only problem with me is that my hair is so tightly curled that even when it is long, it still appears to be short.  I didn't dye my hair this year. Oddly, it appears that my natural color has lightened up a bit. It really is a dark, dark brown, not black as it would seem at first glance. But now it seems to be a mildly lighter shade altogether. I do fancy it and hope it continues. As a youth in my single digits, four or five years old, I did indeed have sandy hair. Yes, sandy, and very much unlike the haircolor I have now.   Kris  and I talked of relaxing my tightly wound curls. I am not for using a lot of chemicals on my hair, but this is something new and I want to give it a go. So, this weekend, I'll have to get a relaxer for my hair. If I don't like it, I'll just cut it all off again. But I've decided not to dye it. My brand of choice is  Herbatint.  You can purchase it in health food stores. It is more natural than the major cosmetic brands. Last year, when I dyed my hair, the texture became a bit coarse and harder to manage (probably because I dyed it  multiple  times within a few weeks of each other-- Linda Evangelista  I am not!) So, I'll stay natural for now.  Kris called me a little while ago. Someone named  Paul  called for me. He didn't leave a number so I told Kris to *69 it and call me back. The number has a 404 area code. That's Atlanta. Anyway, I called the number and it was unavailable because it is from a calling card. No one I know named Paul comes to mind at the moment, so I am perplexed by this. It may be someone from my college days just trying to get in touch. If he calls back, I suppose I will find out.  All right, kids, that's all for now, J 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday,  Kris  and I went to  Asia 's house. I met her dog  Sonya . That dog is a firecracker! Strong and ever playful, she hopped, jumped, and ran all over the place.  We ate, laughed and talked for a couple of hours.  Asia had to go to work so we all rode the train back to Manhattan.  We saw  Open Water  with  Sam ,  Mike ,  Chris , and  Marc.  I don't recommend it. It wasn't really scary, just tense. It was shot with digital video as opposed to film, so it has a home video feel to it. I didn't like it. Kris thought it was, "a waste of money."  Mike and Sam are our new friends. This past Wednesday, we went to their house. We ordered Chinese and watched  Wonder Woman  on DVD. We saw the episode where she goes to Hollywood and her sister played by  Debra Winger  guest stars. Sam has an extensive  Wonder Woman  collection on display. He has stuff from years past and things from the present day.  They painted and decorated their apartment very nicely. Both of them are Libras so it is no surprise that they are intelligent and have good taste. It inspired me to work on the various home improvement projects that I have left unfinished.  Today, is a lazy Sunday. Well, not really. The apartment is a mess again. I have so much junk to rid myself of. So, I am cleaning and organizing. Kris is working on his display shelves with his  Star Wars  and  Lord of the Rings  collections.  I don't plan on going anywhere today. So, not much to write about.  Ciao, Jason 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hope  Martha Stewart  had a happy 63rd birthday yesterday!  You deserve it, Martha!    Also yesterday, after work  Sam  gave  Kris  and me a tour of  Toy Biz . It was a lot of fun, and I'm sure we'll visit again sometime soon. Sam invited us for dinner tonight. We talked about watching a movie too.  Mike  will be there, so the the four of us will get to talk and laugh. I like making new friends.  At home last night, I made delicious fruit smoothies for us with apples, oranges, strawberries, grapes and a peach. It was so yummy and refreshing.  I've been tired lately, and I have so much to do. Well, I'll just have to take one day at a time.     Ciao, J 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Kris  and I met  Asia  in Union Square this afternoon at 3 o' clock. We went to  LifeThyme , a great natural market on 6th Avenue between 8th and 9th streets. We had fruit and vegetable juice and vegan cookies in the seating area upstairs.  We walked to Washington Square Park, and took some pictures when some comedian started talking to us a apart of his routine and got us to join the audience. We didn't stay long because we were over it real quick. Besides that, he sprinkled the F-word in his jokes when there were children present. I noticed people leaving right after he said it.  On the way to Tower Records we passed the NYU library where I saw  Ali  outside. I haven't seen him in a really long time since we don't keep in touch much anymore. We exchanged numbers again so maybe we'll hang out sometime.  Browsing CDs at Tower Records helped pass the time for a while. Then we went to eat at Dojo. During our meal I noticed  Matthew  outside on his mobile phone. I went outside and sneak attacked him. He was surprised to see me, but couldn't talk because apparently it was an important phone call. Minutes later, he came to our table, said hello and told us where he was sitting inside the restaurant.  After we said goodbye to Asia, on the way out of Dojo we went to Matthew's table and met his friend  Liza,  whom he has mentioned to me many times before. I was glad to finally meet her. Matthew laughed at my  Free Martha  T-Shirt. He used to work at  Martha Stewart Living .     We walked around the East Village and went to St. Marks Sounds, Toy Tokyo, and The Forbidden Planet. We contemplated seeing  The Village  but decided to go home.  It was a good day.  Ciao, J   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ed  and  Jacob 's housewarming party last night,  Dirrty Pop Goes the Apartment  was a lot of fun! There was laughter and merriment all around.  Kris  and I met several friendly and creative people.  Ed, greeted us clad in a vintage navy blue blazer, dark blue jeans, a red shirt (in keeping with the 'cherry' theme), a plastic gold crown, and his face dusted with glitter.  I presented him with two freshly repotted Parlor Palms. They're small slow-growing palms. Any type of palm in the home adds touch of elegance. Anyway, I knew the new place would benefit from some greenery and I was right, because they didn't have any plants yet. Kris gave Ed, a bottle of sparkling white wine.  After taking care of the housewarming gifts, it was time for introductions. I was curious to meet Ed's other friends. I spoke to  Brian,  an affable actor that moved to New York about four months ago from Orlando. He knew Ed from their days back in Florida.   Jayson,  is a charming chap with a winning smile and flirtatious undertones. I say this having observed him across the room talking while sprawled out and lounging on the couch with one leg extended onto  Mike  (more on him in a moment) seated in a chair across from him. He and Mike may already be acquainted, but I do not know for certain. Jayson merits attention because he seemed to make himself the  most  comfortable of all the party guests which in turn garnered him some attention from other fellows attending the party. Now, please understand, I find no harm in this whatsoever. In fact, I found the situation rather intriguing... Oh, how I do enjoy observing people's behavior. Jayson mentioned having a party of his own at the end the summer. We shall see.   Kevin  and  Holden,  are a sweet couple that met over a year ago thanks to Ed. Kevin is witty and a pleasant conversationalist, although Holden was more reserved, he was poised, gracious and well mannered. Others noted that he resembles  Ted  from  Queer Eye for the Straight Guy .  I asked  Leo,  if indeed he is one,   but he was actually born a Gemini. We talked a little about astrology.   Sam  is a delight. Full of glee and youthful exuberance wearing a shirt decorated with an iron-on logo of,  The Misfits,  villainous characters from the hit 80s cartoon,  Jem.  He made us laugh with colorful stories and anecdotes. Sam, and the above mentioned Mike have been together for five years and met through Ed. I discovered at this party, that Ed has been an indirect matchmaker of sorts over the years.  Kris and Sam really hit it off. Sam works at,  Toy Biz,  a division of Marvel Enterprises, which makes many of the action figures that Kris collects, such as the  Lord of the Rings  series. Usually taciturn, Kris declared, "I want to work there." I was glad to see Kris engaged in conversation, but mildly concerned about the implications of Kris taking a tour of Sam's office, surrounded by action figures and all things associated with them. What would he bring home next? But collecting them is his hobby so I respect that as long as they do not overcrowd the house.   Sue,  is a DJ that played Ed's radio show a couple of times and her boyfriend,  Alex,  is a hearty chap with a European accent (Russian I think).   Mark Allen  of  urlLink http://www.markallencam.com/  was also in attendance. He is an interesting guy and has had articles appear in  The New York Times,  and been on  NPR  .    Later, I discussed astrology more seriously with  Tony , an insightful and intelligent Libra with Scorpio rising. He knows a lot and I always enjoy talking astrology. I call it 'astro babble.'  We spoke to Ed's coworker,  Melissa,  who was so sweet and congenial. She was very open and warm and asked how Kris and I met, and I told her the story how we met through online personals. She recalled a recent date of hers through  eHarmony.com,  and mentioned the on again/off again status of her relationship with her exboyfriend.  Melissa also said to Kris and me one of the most lovely things I've ever heard. Something along the lines of how she thinks Kris and I are very attractive and that although it is a big  stretch,  if it was possible for us to combine our DNA and have a child, that it would be amazing. I was moved to hear someone I just met share such a beautiful sentiment.  Throughout the evening, Jacob snapped pictures with his digital camera.  Only one thing went wrong. I invited my friend,  Emily  (whom I haven't seen in months) to join us. Originally, we were supposed to meet around 8 p.m. and go to the party together, but as Kris and I were leaving the house she called and said she would arrive later. The plan was for her to call me when she got to 96th Street and Broadway.  I didn't realize that inside Ed and Jacob's apartment that my mobile phone had NO reception. I had to go outside to call her. When I did, she was already home and said she'd waited about 40 minutes!   Ouch!   She didn't sound upset, but I know she was disappointed. So was I. I felt terrible! I still do.  I'm sorry, Emily ! I wanted to make plans for today and make it up to her, but she has an engagement in Greenwich to attend.  Ed gave everyone goody bags upon departure. The contents varied a little with each one but they  all  had a copy of  Another Ed Shepp Magazine-Type Thinglet! #2,  a mixed CD with original recordings by Ed and tracks from  Cibbo Matto, Pizzicato Five, The Gap Model Collective, David Sedaris,  and more.    Other things in my bag was a mini bottle of  Smirnoff  Premium Triple Distilled Vodka (I'm going to give it away), a sample of Eau De Toilette pour homme  Hanae Mori,  and paper/plastic tiara, and one of those party things you blow and it rolls out with a tooting sound. Kris got a toothbrush, scouring sponge and a little Buddah statuette.  Brian, Kris and I walked down to West 96th Street and waited for the crosstown bus. We bid him farewell as we exited on Lexington Avenue to catch the uptown 6 train, and finally arrived home sometime after 2 a.m. We talked for a while and I discussed events from the party. We both had a nice time.  Ciao now! J 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>