<Blog>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Assumption is the mother of all F*&@ up.... This was once again proved to me...because of what I did last night. I saw the forecast on weather.com and we were supposed to get like 2-3 Ft of snow...which got me all excited coz I thought I could sleep in late...Mid week and getting to sleep till noon...that's like a dream come true....Being in Akron U for 2 whole years has screwed me up completely...especially since I worked under Dr.Goettler. Don't get me wrong !!! I He wasn't a bad advisor or anything like that...He is one the best human beings I have met after coming here...took care of us like his own kids....paid us very well and would always understand our problems if we had any. Not a lot of advisors do that. He also let us work flexible hours (which is the source of problem I am facing now).  I would work late hours....3 A.M. 4 A.M. and sometimes (with Dr Min's Lab course) 6 A.M. I would then sleep in till 1 or 2 P.M. to wake up right at lunch time. I did this regularly for 2 years which btw screwed up my sleep cycle completely. With great difficulty would I drag myself to Monday morning group meetings which was not like at 8 in the morning...but at 10.....Any self respecting man would be ashamed to think it was early,but, I did.My groupmates Hemant and Nihir would always advice me against an early morning thesis defence coz they thought I would probably sleep through it.  Anyways getting back to last night...I conveniently thought today will be a holiday and I would sleep in late. So I watched TV and spoke to mithali till like 12.30. Even when I slept, I kept thinking about not going to work and this made me wake up every 2 hours or so, to check if the snowfall is getting worse. When I got up at 7.30 today..I was completely worn out. I hadn't slept well the whole night. When I called up my company, I was told that most folks were in and I should be  careful while driving.....So instead of being under my cozy comforter dreaming about the cute chick in Italian job (saw the movie last night)...I was out shoveling two feet of snow......Somehow i think this had to be my day off and am still cribbing about it. The good thing though is i have had yet another busy day at work and will be done in about 4 hours. Tonight i shall just sleep..like a baby....not thinking about tommorow... not assuming anything..... 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First post....been thinking abt it for a while...close to 5 months....ever since I moved to Naugatuck from Akron. Today after seeing a few snaps that hemant sent me....I thought it would be nice to start the blog by writing abt my home away from home, "Akron"......When I first moved to Akron two and a half years ago, it was my biggest move ever...had never lived away from home. To top it off...Akron was the last place I wanted to go..So I did land in Cleveland with a grumpy face and with thoughts of changing the university in a few months......First few days were pretty bad...missing dad,mom, friends...everything that I cherished for 22 yrs......I didn't really think that I would meet people again who would make me feel I was at home again. I would always think..."I had everything in India....why on earth did I make this move?"...little did I know then that two years later I would be referring to Akron as my second home......I think lot of my friends in Akron agree that this is our home here.......  People in Akron somehow do these things which make a your day & days to come. Two days before I left Akron, I was playing Badminton with suneel for the last time, when hemant and sapna left the court and said they had some work to be taken care of......we were supposed to go to this Thai place for dinner...brijesh and priya picked me up and we drove to brijesh's old house...and I had all my buddies waiting for me...to give me a surprise send off party..planned by hemant and saps....we danced all night.....the best moment of the party was when brijesh played "every breath u take" for me......Thanks a lot all guys.....u guys made it special for me one day at a time....I havent named everyone in the post...There are so many guys I need to talk abt...now that I have started the blog I guess have lots of time to do so..and will do so.....Anyways next day, with all the stuff I my car...I was on the road to naugatuck...to start my job....to start a new life....or was I starting a life similar to the one I did I Akron 2 years ago?........That was hoping against hope...coz there can be no place in US like Akron and like the people I met there........  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Akron Trip......  Got back three days ago from a whirlwind trip of Akron. It was like a proper vacation although it was just for two and a half days. Been wanting to go to Akron for a few months now...but weather has been stopping me all along...last time i went to akron it was snow that made me drive back and i ended up staying only for 15 hours driving 16 hours. This time i was waiting with anxiously till the last day hoping the good weather would stay good....and fortunately it didnt let me down. i was supposed to get to work early friday morning so that i could leave work early....but as usual that didnt happen....i ended up leaving work at 4.30 ( a little early...putting extra hours in ot make up for it).....the weather was excellent and i made it to akron at 11.30 or so......  Just before i reached akron hemant called and asked me to reach BW3 and not his place. He also asked me to give him a call when i reached BW3......Now was there a surprise waiting for me...coz somehow i had that feeling...for a moment i thought sapna was back from india....i really couldnt think of anything else......When i reached BW3...i definitely was glad that what i thought while driving was true...SAPNA was back...it had been close to 5 months since i had seen her.......the three of us were together once more.......after a long long time........everyone was in BW3 and we spent the next few hours talking and having fun......  The next day was Valentines day (no i am not making a big deal out of it)......Last year...i was in akron, with all these guys and i was thinking that i need someone.....This year on the other hand i was just happy to be in akron with all my friends....Evening was nice...all of us, except saps (still in recovery mode from jet lag) went out for dinner.....wanted italian but ended up having mexican.....thats abt the only thing that didnt go the way i wanted...then the guys watched "ek hasina thi".....while i snored away to glory........so much so that one of my friends had to stay up all night...i had one of the best valentines in years...i wasnt with all my loved ones but hey, its never perfect...so no big deal.......  Just lazed around all sunday......and come monday was all set to go.....had a nice lunch ......suneel gave me a yearbook...which has stuff abt akron and pictures of all of us who graduated last summer..suneel also gave me some sweets which his mom had made, they also happen to be my favorite....thanks buddy!!!....loved those a lot.....next time i am in mumbai i know whose door to knock on...I started out of akron and the weather was beautiful...nice and sunny and for the first time i was really high spirits on the drive back......just one break for gas and that was it........for some reason i really didnt feel tired....made it back home in record time.....6.5 hrs and 520 miles.....i thought that was pretty cool......that was the end of the trip and i was back at work screwing around with reports...reports and some more reports.....
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Life is puzzling.......  Early Sunday afternoon...which means I have just got up......and the first thing that happens today is that I talk my folks back home.....Some of these thoughts have been hovering around in my head for a while....on and off....but today I just thought I pen them down.......  Why do we leave people that matter a lot to us? Why do we go to a different town/country to do something ? Some people say career, money, achievement....and stuff like that...But why do we have a career? Isn't the basic idea of having a career, a job and money, to make a comfortable living with your loved ones??? Aren't we losing the true meaning of life itself?....We live apart from family, friends slogging our butts off....making money..even though we know we probably would lead a comfortable life, have a good career wherever we were (granted, maybe we could not make money that would make us filthy rich....but hey, we learn to live comfortably with what we have most of the time)......What good is your achievements the people who would appreciate it are not with u?......  Life always has a way to fool around with you......It makes you get used to people,the place and u start to get the eeling "I am in a comfy zone now" and...Then....It throws a surprise at you...Making you leave to another place where no one really cares a damn if u r dead or alive....I could call it "destiny"....But I could also call it "the choices I made" (I can see hemya grinning ear to ear).....But the question that is unanswered is why do we do things that ultimately get us money...but does not give us happiness...I know a lot of us take these decisions.........But I shall stick to my own story.....  YES I have more money today than three years ago...Yes I can buy a BMW....the car I only dreamt of having, in India....I can buy a sports bike or a cruiser....I have seen a few countries now......I have been water rafting, jet skiing, skiing, tubing..and to tons of stuff that I couldn't do in Mysore....But can I see my parents if I want to?....NO...I have to plan a year ahead just to do that.....Can I just go once near St.Joseph's (my school) or K.D. Road and eat the food that I want?...No...Can I come back home to see mama or dad waiting for me?.....NO....when I turn my bike onto my street...Can I see my cats waiting for me at the gate?.....NO...I could drone abt this for a while....but the point is.....It puzzles me because all of us know what we truly want...Our deepest desires are not to own a bimmer but to be happy with our loved ones...yet we move away from them.......  As Tyler Durden says in fight club, "we need to let go of things that truly don't matter"......now if we go by this sentence......Does it mean to say for us family and friends do not matter?....or does it just go to say we are not letting go of money?.....or maybe its more like when he says  "The things you own end up owning you".....I don't know the answer....But am really trying hard to figure out why do we make decisions so that we always end up losing stuff that matters most in our life.......   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ADI IS GOING BACK....................:(  Everytime I look back at the good times I have had playing a game in Akron,one person stands out.....Sunil Adwani (Adi for most of us)....He has been my partner in crime in racquet ball, cricket, bowling, pool, air hockey......U name the game, chances are Adi and me have played it together...I first spoke to Adi in the polymer engineering lobby...that was also the day I spoke to nihir and nishant....Like a lot of people in Akron he was into sports and I hoped that he played something I was good at.....but unfortunately he played tennis....and I sucked big time at that.....but I used to go to the courts with shashi, Adi and the gang......Sashi was more into racqueball which was completely new to us, but he offered to teach us and we gladly accepted.....that is how we kinda started hanging out together....soon we were pretty decent at playing the game and we started to go regularly to the NAT., although Adi was more regular than me coz I would be in sabbatical for a few days every month or so, whenever I felt my game was not on par....We have had some excellent games together with adi kicking my butt a lot of times.....         Come summer 2002 we started to play seasoned ball cricket.....I could go on for days and days about Akron cricket...there is no end to it.....the season is long over but we guys still talk about cricket......its either 2002 season, 2003 season or the next season (sadly I may not be a part of it)....Adi was our best fielder and a Gavin larsen type bowler...line and length...thats all he focused on...and he was damn good at it....Adi, sunny and myself would go to the nets at 5, an hour before everyone and would practice...he loves to bowl and I love to bat....so it was an ideal combination..  Other than cricket and racquetball...We would also go bowling and I think the competition got the best out of both of us...we have had some really really close games....and this actually did manage to push our averages up........  Also really cool was his dance step....anyone in Akron knows what I am talking about....I am stupid enough not to know how to post a picture on my blog...if I did I have some really good pictures of Adi.....Hemya, help me out here!!!!  Adi is leaving to India on Sunday........With him, I will probably lose the best sports companion I have had.......I sit in my office, wishing that could see him once before he left for India....but this damn ice rain will not let me reach Akron......  Adi.....I have had an awesome time with u buddy...I will always cherish the good times we have had together..I am gonna miss your Chai, dance, cricket and every little thing that made u so much fun to be with........I wanna copy hemant's fav quote and say....."May the force be with u"..........All the very best to you dude.....Be happy and enjoy life always....the way we have all seen u in Akron.......        
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
        India's Declaration.......Sachin stranded.......was it the right thing to do???    Well I don't think I need to tell anyone the story......Everyone knows that sachin was on 194 and India declared the innings.....the question is..... was it right or wrong?  I know every sachin fan is gonna jump up and say...."Of course it was wrong"....I don't blame them......Anybody so close deserves to get the double hundred.....But what we really have to think about is one man bigger than cricket?.....Isn't a team game about winning and not about setting personal records.....In the end what matters is whether we were able to beat pakis and not whether sachin scored a double or a triple hundred......no one will care about the one man's score if we draw the test or lose it.....no one is gonna talk about it...but tommorow when we get one wicket to win first time ever on pak soil....generations to come will talk about it.......  It wasn't like sachin did not know that the declaration was coming....he has himself said that they had discussed about declaring an hour after tea and he knew it was gonna happen.......then why does he have to go to the media and complain that he didn't get his chance......Reports say that they discussed it at lunch, tea and also sent ramesh powar twice on the field to send the message across....but sachin never bothered to accelerate his scoring when yuvraj was going all guns blazing...I do not want to paint a picture that i hate sachin....i love the guy's talent...No doubt he is a genius.....but am sorry to say he has not shown the right team spirit this time.I remember a test match when Hick was on 98 and the team declared....he didn't say a word.....not that he couldn't, but he didn't.....I guess because he knew the team's interest comes before his......sachin could have spoken to the management about his thoughts....but he had to go to the media first......Rahul Dravid openly said  that he didn't like keeping...but things did not change...he has quietly accepted the job and he takes it for the team...... where were all the people who are talking about sachin's double hundred then....why doesn't anyone complain about that.....Grow out of the sachin mania people.....  Realize that indian cricket is not about sachin...its about India...how proud are all of us gonna be when we win the test?......would we take same pride if we lost/drew the test and sachin got a double hundred?.....our guys are playing their hearts out to win...the decision was taken in the spirit of winning the game......don't make it a one man show.....  I have one more example which is very apt for this occasion. When I made my debut (2002) for ACC....we had one of the greatest player ACC ever produced........my mentor....Ram mohan Tangirala (our very own version of sachin)...people in the midwest league would worry when Ram walked into bat......Ram had been a consistent top scorer in the league.....winning games for us...To top that, he was an excellent pace bowler.....his only problem was he would party a lot friday/saturday nights and get up late saturday/sunday on the day of the match......one day he woke up late and  consequently turned up an hour and a half late for the match...Even though the it was raining and there was little chance of a game....Suneel, our captain dropped the best man on the team without hesitation.....there were no second thoughts....and he did this in front of the team, filled with a bunch of rookies.....Ram could have said lots of things...but he didnt say a word.....he took in the right spirit......because he was a team man.....I have since developed tremendous respect for these two guys.....Suneel because he did not care for reputations...he did what he thought was right and just..... always...and Ram...because he had no qualms although he was the superstar on the team.....and trust me....we were succesful as a unit, although we weren't the greatest team.....Last year (2003), there were egos flying all over the place....people wanting to feel important...putting their interests in front of the team's and stuff like that......although we had one of the most talented teams...we suffered tremendously...as the win/loss record indicates.  My point is if you are looking to set personal records then a team game is not for you....please resort to playing tennis (singles only) or something like that.....When you play a team game you are expected to take things for the team and make sacrifices....Dont make a mountain out of a mole hill.....Cricket is bigger than every person who has played the game and let it stay that way......GO INDIA........
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Loads of stuff happening..... Its funny that I actually haven't had the time to post.......considering the fact that I would always have tons of time when I initially got to naugatuck.....  Stuff that's happened over two weeks:  1) Completed my first project report for Crompton corporation...my very own polyurethane........took me 5 months to develop one.....of course with some help with my manager......It feels good.....We have always had one bright scientist in the family......my first cousin.....the professor with 25 patents and 115 papers......and the count doesn't seem to stop.....so it does take some work to keep up with the guy....let alone compete with him......but am crawling there......anyways getting back to my project......what started off to be like one product looks like a whole product line and I might be in charge of the whole stuff....feels good......coz now I know there is some contribution from me to the scientific community and I am sure there is lots more to come in the next few years.  2) Its been a dream for me ever since I hit the teens to have a big bike.....when I was in india I tried really hard to get myself a bullet...modify it to make it look like bikes here.....but my dad was a real smart guy......this was the time when I had quit playing professional badminton and had put on a few extra kilos bcoz there wasn't any motivation to work out anymore......my dad said...work out...lose weight and maybe we can think abt it......I think that was one of the finest strategies a man could have ever come up with.......its been 6 years after he said that and things havent changed. But now that I have started working...I wanted to buy a fancy car.....I looked at a bimmer convertible....but things didn't fall in place due to some of my priorities......so it was buying a bike..... now I have made up my mind to buy the Honda Shadow Aero 2004.....after my folks have gave me a go ahead.  3) Am working my first weekend...down in gastonia,nc.......and production environment is completely different than what I have been used to working in R&D......i have already put in 28 hours in 2 days....and I have 5 days to go.....and the real cool part is that I am actually enjoying being here.....I slept real well last night after all the tossing and turning I have been doing over the last week........and if my manager gives me a choice of moving down to gastonia...I would probably take it....coz I have seen more pretty gals in two days than what I have seen in 6 months in naugatuck  4) Visted a cricket team in cheshire, CT.....they have just merged with west haven,CT and now they have a huge team.....but the sad part is that they will practice only one day a week.....not something I like...but the best part was that a lot of them knew abt Akron cricket club (ACC) and have lots of respect for it.....its one more thing abt Akron to feel proud of.......ACC was full of cricket freaks......I am not kidding...these guys will go to any limits to have a good game of cricket....and that's the way I like things....give a 110%.......win or lose.....end of the day I shouldn't feel that I could have done better...I enjoyed every single day of cricket I have played for ACC and would do anything to play a few more seasons for them....but right now I just hope it will work out here.....  5) India beat pakistan today....not that I have to mention it......I bet any indian in any corner of the world knows that.......It just feels so good when something like this happens.....and as always my GURU Dravid had an excellent knock....I have been a loyal Dravid follower for a lot of years now ever since he reoresented karnataka.......I try to play like him as much as possible (not that i am good at it...but i try).........His composure was well known among most ranji cricket followers when he was the captain....I would always feel sad when every damn guy I knew was a tendulkar fan......critisizing dravid for his orthodox play....but when everything fails....its the orthodox cricket that saves the day.....and these days Dravid seems to be proving it all the time.....and he did that again.....scoring 99 yesterday.......he rocks.  All in all its been two good weeks (knock on wood).......and I am in high spirits.......I feel I could write all night today...but I guess it should be a drag reading such a long post and its kinda getting late for me as well........have to get to bed now....have a production run starting at 5.30 A.M. tommorow morning.......
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sad but true :(  I received this from a friend here at work......and what sucks about the email is that some signs actually apply to me.....becoming uncle types is the one thing that I dread....although I was happy that I did find a few that do not apply.......so i guess i am not there yet.....   25 SIGNS THAT YOU'VE GROWN UP :  1. Your house plants are alive, and you can't smoke any of them.   2. Having sex in a twin bed is out of the question.....  3. You keep more food than beer in the fridge.   4. 6:00 AM is when you get up, not when you go to bed.   5. You hear your favorite song on an elevator.   6. You watch the Weather Channel.   7. Your friends marry and divorce instead of hook up and break up.   8. You go from 130 days of vacation time to 14.   9. Jeans and a sweater no longer qualify as "dressed up."   10. You're the one calling the police because those damn kids next door won't turn down the stereo.   11. Older relatives feel comfortable telling sex jokes around you.   12. You don't know what time Taco Bell closes anymore.   13. Your car insurance goes down and your payments go up.   14. You feed your dog Science Diet instead of McDonalds leftovers.   15. Sleeping on the couch makes your back hurt.   16. You no longer take naps from noon to 6 PM.  17.Dinner and a movie is the whole date instead of the beginning of one.  18. Eating a basket of chicken wings at 3 AM would severely upset, rather than settle your stomach.   19. You go to the drug store for ibuprofen and antacid, not condoms and pregnancy tests.   20. A $4.00 bottle of wine is no longer "pretty good stuff."   21. You actually eat breakfast food at breakfast time.   22. "I just can't drink the way I used to," replaces, "I'm never going to drink that much again."   23. 90% of the time you spend in front of a computer is for real work.   24. You drink at home to save money before going to a bar.   25. You read this entire list looking desperately for one sign that doesn't apply to you and can't find one to save your sorry old butt  How many signs apply to you???
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        My "Guru" does it again     "Tendulkar will perhaps end his career with a hundred hundreds. But as Indian cricket stands on the precipice of its own golden age, it must be remembered that Rahul Dravid has made the most difference."    12 years i have waited for days like these.......just goes to show that u dont need a genius to get the job done. Sincere effort and hard work will get u there.....
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Time to move on!!!!    Its me at my philosophical and cribbing best today....Thought I warn some of u before u read on...its been eight and a half months since I have started a new life here in CT...Everything seems to have changed...I do have all the people I had before even now...yet things are different.....Its not like things have changed overnight...I have had some relationships change gradually over the past year...some have changed at a more rapid rate......people with whom I would talk like 3-4 times a day...be it live or over the phone....haven't really been in touch lately...we talk once a week or so....and even then the conversations are short...everyone has moved on...I unfortunately haven't....I seem to be hanging on to certain things which should just be in my memories...  I have had some of my friends tell me I have changed in 8 months...I am more introspective and more serious these days...and seems that I have been losing my jovial nature of late...is it my fault if everything around me changes and I make a few changes accordingly?....Living with none of ur family/friends around u is not something that I favor...Its gives u too much free time (Even though I keep myself busy most of the time) and it makes u think a lot about things which u probably wouldn't have given a thought....relationships somehow have a new meaning...and u begin to understand your importance in each realtionship...Over a period of time I have realised that the more u hang onto something..the only person getting worked up is u...everyone else is leading a perfectly happy life...  So maybe it is time I come to accept the fact that this is how my life is gonna be...its time to break away with things that have kept me tied up emotionally and move on...move to a state of mind where I feel free...as I used to few years ago... 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Folks coming here yeeeaaaaahhhhhh!!!!!!!!!   Day started off very good....just got the news that my folks got their visa approved and they will be coming here for couple of months.........will be good to see them after a year and a half.....its their first trip outside India and i am pretty sure that it will be an experience for them to remember...Anyways its been a while after i have been this excited :)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Debut for cheshire cricket club    After much deliberation whether to join Cheshire or Danbury...i ended up in Cheshire cricket club...the team has been around for couple of years now....they played last season in the league for the first time...but did not have much success...this season they merged with another team...result...31 players...plus me trying to walk in...so i  kinda felt insecure from day one....whether Danbury or Cheshire...my place in any team was not secure....not a good feeling to have especially when cricket is one thing i look forward to every summer....  Anyways back to my first game.....the captain wanted me to be the wicket keeper since i had told him i do some part time wicket keeping....start looked good but didnt last long....in the 5th over i dropped a catch because i was standing closer to the stumps than i should have...and the catch i dropped was their best batsman's...he averaged somewhere in the 40s last season....and he did make me regret it..he scored 55...how many times do u see this kind of a thing happen?...u drop a catch and the guy goes on and on making u wanna kill urself....good part about keeping was i finally got the guts to stand up the stumps to spinners...i actually got a stumping done...donno how that happened...but i guess flukes do happen once in a way.....  End of 35 overs...they had 187 on board....i was very impressed with their batting...all the good balls were well respected.....and anything slightly short...or wide was clobbered...so much so that they hit couple of balls on cars parked outside the ground. So with a big target on board...i was all set to open the innings....  my previous two seasons have been very different from each other...the first season i was just a starter...and my whole goal was to stay there 10 overs....those were my instructions...stay 10 overs knock the shine off the ball....and then Mr.Genius, Ram would come in murder the opposition....never really got big runs...would get out always after reaching double figures..Second season i was more confident...but highly inconsistent...got couple of fifties...but was not really satisfied with my performance...  Back to the start of my innings....started off as my slow self..leaving balls outside off stump (sometimes i think that is my best looking cricket pose)....we had 30 of 8 overs....and for some reason i remembered the columbus game last season..where i stayed in 17 overs and at the break had 14...didnt want that to happen..I also remembered suneel telling me that u really need to hit the ball hard along with timing the ball...so started doing that and thing started working...i got a four of a cover drive..something i have never been able to do before...the outfields in CT are also nicely maintained and the ball does travel...so that helped too..at the drinks break we had 70, i was on 37 and we had not lost a wicket..after drinks i faced an offspinner...not really very comfy with spinners...but was able to play him very comfortably...got my 50 in a few balls...but was starting to tire out....all the extra lbs over winter was taking my toll....finally got out for 61...my highest score till date..giving a lollipop catch...but was statisfied with my innings...but with 57 runs remaining we had a batting collapse...and we lost the game...the end wasnt the greatest end to a nice game...  With the league games starting this weekend...am quite excited now....will be the opener and wicket keeper this season...hopefully i can make more good scores...and with practice here..if ACC guys are ok with me playing maybe i can contribute in some league games for my favorite team as well....Think this probably one of the longest posts i have written....am gonna sign off now...and get some sleep...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        2 months = 200 lbs....    Mom and Dad got here on saturday.....it was quite a long wait at JFK...I got there at 4 and had to wait an hour before they got out...it felt like the longest hour ever...My dad has never been enthu to come down here..so i was kinda expected him to crib all the way to my house about forcing him to come here....But all the weariness of my folks seem to vanish the moment we hit Merrit Parkway....It impresses everyone who comes down to connecticut...Winding roads, lush green trees on both sides of the parkway...its a sight to see in summer/fall and it worked its magic on my folks as well..Dad was like "Everything around here is so clean...except your car!!!"...Made it back home in good time....took them a couple of days to settle down....From the past couple of days i have been getting to eat some awesome food....there was a time few months ago when the food i made would last 2 days...now i am getting to eat a different dish every time....to top that off mom got some awesome sweets from Mysore...and dad and mom are making every effort to pump food into me everytime they see me sitting idle...at this rate i am sure to put on quite a few pounds (to add to the baggage i already have)...but who cares...It feels so good to have family around me once again.....and thats all matters for now...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Travel..Travel..Travel.....        &nbsp;  Been a while since I posted...Rajesh sir reminded me couple&nbsp;of days ago that its been almost a month since I have posted...so am back with my latest update....   Its been a month now with my folks and time just seems to fly.....all of a sudden connecticut seems&nbsp;like a nice place to live in...its been a hectic few weeks with all the travel...travelled to the west coast few weeks ago...Had been to Disneyland, Grand Canyon and Las Vegas....finally fulfilled my mom's wish to see Disneyland, although she had to wait a long long time to see it (30+ years)....it was a sight to see when we reached Disneyland...my mom who generally is the slowest, had an overactive spring in her step which lasted two complete days :)   Both Disney and Grand Canyon were fantasy lands in their own way...We went&nbsp;on&nbsp;a Chopper ride over the Canyon and if anyone wants to realise how small and insignificant we&nbsp;are, I suggest that is the ride to take...The Colorado river flows right in the canyon and the emerald green river is an awesome sight...I was told that there are rafting trips that are organised every summer...supposed to last 5 days and its a level 6 rapid...All you rafting buffs in Akron..what say we move up a level and take a rafting trip in the Canyon sometime soon!!!!!!!!   Las Vegas is an awesome place too...Each casino is designed after a city....there is NY, Paris, Venice, Rome (colloseum and all), Egypt and many more....and the city never sleeps...we had packed streets at 3 AM....I was at my usual best in the casinos...losing all the money I had...But my dad was an another story...taught him to play&nbsp;Roulette..and in no time he was winning&nbsp;money...he made about 100 bucks in 15 minutes...If it was not for my mom I would have been a rich man today :(   I have a few weeks left with my folks...Have couple more Desi&nbsp;addas&nbsp;to cover..Niagara falls and NYC.....and then they head back home :(......Also I found out the reason I am overweight.....My mom seems to use to a bag of sugar and a big bottle of Ghee every 2 weeks and its all her fault.....So guys before you tease me remember...I am just an innocent victim...      
     
    
</post>


</Blog>