<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        100 Things About Me      &nbsp;   1.&nbsp; I have never seen the ocean.    2.&nbsp; I'm a sports junkie.    3.&nbsp; My favorite football team is the New England Patriots has been since 1995.    4.&nbsp; I still sleep with my security blanket that I've had since I was 6 months old.    5.&nbsp; I love NASCAR.&nbsp;    6.&nbsp; My favorite drivers are Elliott Sadler, Kasey Kahne, and David Stremme.    7.&nbsp; My favorite color is pink.    8.&nbsp; Lazy people at work get on my nerves.    9.&nbsp; I'm a waitress.&nbsp;    10. I never waited tables until I moved to Atlanta.    11. I have 2 younger brothers, Brandon-18 and Zachary-5.    12. I'm a Capricorn.    13. I have two tattoos.    14.&nbsp;I have&nbsp;band of flowers&nbsp;on my ankle that I got when I graduated high school.    15.&nbsp;The other one I got when my heart was broken by a boy. It's a sun from the Tim McGraw album "A Place in the Sun."    16. I love Tim McGraw.    17. I saw&nbsp;Tim in March 2003 and had front row tickets.    18.&nbsp;I made a sign that said "Hey Tim All I Want is your Bud Lite"    19.&nbsp;He drank out of a Bud Light and gave it to me.    20. The empty Bud Light bottle is sitting on my entertainment center right now.    21. This is proof that if you&nbsp;try hard enough, you can&nbsp;get what you want.    22. I've never really been in love.    23. My favorite movie is Love and Basketball.    24. My favorite actor right now is Michael Vartan.    25. My favorite actress is Jennifer Garner.    26. My favorite show is Alias.    27. My nickname from back home in Michigan is Sunshine Shelley.    28.&nbsp;I've wrecked 2 cars.    29. Tom Brady is my favorite football player    30.&nbsp;Drew Bledsoe was my favorite, until he was traded to the Bills.    31. I like to change my hair color.    32. I love palm trees, even though I have never seen one.    33. When I decide to go back to school, I want to be a Dietician.    34. My favorite beer is Miller Lite.    35. I love Mucho Bahama Mama's from Applebee's.    36. I love 80's music.    37. I listen to all kind of music, I have over 300 CD's.    38. I love downloading music.    39.&nbsp;Kenny Chesney is another favorite performer of mine.    40.&nbsp;Out of all the music I listen to, country is my favorite.    41. I love to buy pajama's. (Matching ones)    42. I like having alone time.    43. I have 2 best friends back in Michigan, Jenn and Ronda.    44. I miss them.    45.&nbsp;I'm addicted to Soap Net.    46. Sometimes when I go out&nbsp;drinking, I forget stuff.    47. I love the smell of vanilla.    48. I collect diecast cars.    49. I have a scrapbook that I haven't worked on in awhile.    50. The best NASCAR race I've been to&nbsp;is the Food City 500 in Bristol, TN.    51. Kurt Busch won, and I hate Kurt Busch.    52. Dale Earnhardt Jr. fans get on my nerves.&nbsp; "Jump on the bandwagon."    53. I used to be a Dale Jr. and Jeff Gordon fan.    54. My nickname when I was a little kid was Tornado.    55. My cousins Mike and Brian gave me the name because I was a hyperactive brat.    56. I've had 7 different cars since I've been 16.    57. My favorite one was my S-10, because I had alot of fun times with it.    58. I worry alot, sometimes I stress myself out too much about things.    59. I once told a boy I would move home for him.....I was drunk.    60. I've done the "Walk of Shame."    61. I've danced on a bar.    62. I want to learn to play the guitar.    63. I don't know how to play Euchre.    64. I've never seen any  Back to the Future  or  Indiana Jones  movies.    65. I've never been to Florida.    66. The farthest west I've gone is Chicago.    67. My favorite book is  The Lovely Bones  by Alice Sebold    68. I tried the Atkins Diet, It made me gain weight because I cheated alot.    69. I caught the bouquet at my best friend's wedding.&nbsp; I snatched if from another girl.    70. I'm left-handed.    71. My favorite Disney movie is  Beauty and the Beast.     72. My favorite animal is a moose.    73. When I was little I wanted to be She-Ra.    74. I want a yellow Ford Mustang convertible.    75. I was voted "Most School Spirit" in high school.&nbsp; I was our football team's biggest fan.    76. I wish I would have been a cheerleader.    77. I'm addicted to reality shows.    78. I'm a member of the Tim McGraw, Kenny Chesney and Elliott Sadler fan clubs.   79. I only drink diet soda.    80. I used to call soda "pop", now I just call it by brand name.    81. I have 3 roommates, Brennen, Katie, and Heidi.    82. I've known Katie since 1st grade and Heidi since 9th grade.    83. Jose Cuervo is a friend of mine....it usually makes me sick, but I drink it anyway.    84. My dad wanted to name me Stephanie.    85. My mom didn't like it because people would call me "Stuffy" Steffi.    86. She didn't think of "Smelly" Shelley.    87. I've never gotten flowers from a boy.    88. I love M&M's.    89. I have never had a cavity.    90. I once tried to dye my hair blonde myself.    91. It turned blonde, pink, and orange and I had to pay $80 to fix it.    92. I have never ridden on a motorcycle.    93. I have a scar on my lower&nbsp;lip, because I was hit in the mouth with a baseball bat when I was 4.    94. I love road trips.    95. Jenn, Ronda and I used to take one to the U.P. (upper peninsula) every year.    96. I'm a fast reader.&nbsp; I read  Gone With the Wind  in 2 days when I was 14.    97. I get bored very easily.   98. I have blue eyes.   99. I love chocolate. (I want to go try the new brownie batter blizzard!)   100. I hate being late.    
       
    
    
</post>




</Blog>