<Blog>


<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i cram to understand folks making fun of pregnant ppl. how lame.  'touche'... dumasses... anyway, i think my baby and I connect on a level that only a caring loving joyful mother-to-be (like myself) can connect with their unborn child.  like i can tell when shawty want to cuss Guy (babydaddy) out, it is relayed through a swift kick to my pelvis and i proceed to cussing his ass out.  no morning sickness...well at least no more... the first trimester kicked my ass... but the second trimester has been forgiving.  I am extremely tired and the headaches are the pits but im finally enjoying being pregnant.  I still look hella good except for the stretch marks on my ass, breast, thighs and hips....don't sweat the technique... it is all genetic.... my mom's the bomb too.    I haven't found out the sex and if God is willing and I resist temptation, I won't find out until shawty gets here.  just because the ablity is there doesn't mean you are to use it.  I have names already picked out for either sex.  Guy doesn't like the boy names i have chosen but you know what,... his ass isn't carrying a baby in his uterus so i couldn't care less what he wants to name the baby.  the baby names were never a collective decision...it was an exclusive one. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    before&nbsp; urlLink     my breast have always been a small C... now them joints are a solid full D.  thanks Shawty (aka my baby, it etc)!  they will be saggy mangos in a few months but that is alright... ya know why?  because i will have a hungry, crying, moneysnatching bundle of joy to replace them.  life is f'ing grand.  but for real thou... whatever Shawty wants, Shawty will get... when it is begging for an ass whipping, i shall be there to deliver.  i'm going to be on point with my ass whippings too... straight thorough.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi. temp. showing.  flygyrl thought i should do this even if it is for the remainding four months that i am pregnant.... yep, i'm expecting, with child, bun in oven, etc. and loving every minute of it.  i aint ever been know for being sappy so none of that smushy shi will get play on this here blog.  this is a basic ode to baby Shawty until it gets here and the three month after Shawty is born... or until i go back to work....   I will often refer to my baby as it... if you don't like it, don't come by and don't comment either.  I know good and damn well my baby isn't an it and i don't need for you do tell me either.  clear? cool.  now let the fun begin. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been a sawed off adventure telling my ex’s that I’m expecting.&nbsp; You can always tell the ones who are genuinely happy for you and those who think you have driven a stake through their little itty bitty hearts.&nbsp; It is interesting to see in the least.&nbsp; I’m trying to regain some sense on normalcy with the ex’s that are now friends.&nbsp; I don’t want our friendship to be affected but im not performing any backbreaking stunts to prevent their egos from being bruised.&nbsp; Ya obviously didn’t care that much to begin with….. only right after you realized your ship has most definitely sailed.&nbsp; But all well I hope ends well. If not, aww well.&nbsp;&nbsp;   At the club the other night, my boy’s birthday party, his brother, my ex, was there chilling… with his hussy girlfriend… did I say hussy?&nbsp; Yeah, I did!&nbsp; Well hussy must have known that I was the notorious ex that broke her current boyfriend’s heart back in high school for she sure was throwing mad shade.&nbsp; I was like honey, Ise very pregnant but my fist ain’t, so tread lightly.&nbsp; Plus, your ass brand new…. I was her ‘honey’s’ first love… and that I will always be and he will be mine,&nbsp;so chalk that up to your loses.&nbsp; Anyway, back to the ex….He was there and he wasn’t to please with my pregnant state.&nbsp; I guess he was hoping me barren for the rest of my days and I just so happened to break his curse.&nbsp; Evil begets evil, damnit.&nbsp; Plus I got the Lord on my side, so take that.&nbsp;  Side note:  I sure do miss him.  &nbsp;So, I have tried to set up this stupid Upromise crap to begin saving for Shawty’s education.&nbsp; I don’t know if I’m doing this right, but this junk doesn’t seem to be working.&nbsp;&nbsp; I haven’t accumulated a damn cent yet and I have had this crap up for more than a month and I’m the credit/debit card queen, let me tell it. &nbsp;If anybody has been through this Upromise bid, please hit a sista up and help a sista out… thanks!!&nbsp; Shawty says.... 'One.'  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I really got to stop cussing.... i will... before baby is born... and i can because i have will-power, damnit!  
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NOTE:  okay, i do believe in free speech, but if anyone ever questions my mothering and/or my mothering ablity, you are going to wish you hadn't.  if anyone has anything to say about shawty, don't... it will be in your best interest. believe me.  kay? good!  now that is out the way.... so, i went to see shawty wednesday,... i'm 21 wks and shawty is looking marvelous.  eating, yawning stretching, pushing my intestines and bladder out of the way to make room for its one toe.  i stayed strong and resilent agains the pressure of temptation... meaning, i didn't request the knowledge of the sex.   God is always on the side of the right.  from this point on, it is all about waiting for the arrival.... for the meeting of the eyes when that visual connection is made.   nothing is prepared because i really don't know where i'm living... so i have a pile of crap at my mom's house in my old room.  when shawty arrives, that will be our room for two wks until i'm good and tired of my mom correcting everything i do.  i will then bid her farewell and do things on my own.  guy is weakening under the pending arrival... hard ass and so full of it knowing he has never been this in love with anything or anyone as much as he loves this baby.  the baby looks just like him... fat cheeks, sizable head, high forehead and those eyes... how can you not love something that so strongly resembels you?    now, i can sense there is going to be some problems with the grandparents.  naturally, the baby is going to be closer to its maternal grandparents because that is just how things are.  i can see guy getting upset because i'm spending a great deal of time over at my moms with the baby hence hindering bonding time with his mom... i can understand this concern because i would be pissed as well.  but i have never raised  a child nor has he... being a mom, and a daughter of a mom, i am going to trust my mother's motherly wisdom to help me raise shawty. i don't know his mom like that to sit up under her while she tries to school me.  but beleive me, this will be an unfolding saga that i'm not up to deal with now, but when the time comes.  i pray God blesses me with patience between now and then.  alright, shawty says stay up... and so do i. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so... im 20 wks and half way there...  well wait a minute... is there really a half where when you are given a life long responsibility.... i think i would prefer staying pregnant for the rest of my life than having the burdening thought of shaping and molding a black child in today's society.  but God wanted a challenge for me and damn if i got it.  now i love kids... other ppl's kids.  i'm scared shiless wondering anticipating the personality of this here wonder child... i want it to be a certain type of person with the passion for this that and the third.   living vicariously through it...  i think all parents do... you know why, cause we all did and did not do something and that is why we are still longing to correct the mistakes made.... through our children.  does that make us parents losers?  if that is the case, shi  i will be a loser.... you are damn right i don't like working 9 to 5 today just to work 9 to 5 tomorrow.  i want my baby to wizen up to this billshi system and make momma some money.  get ours in this capitalist system :|) damn that... my big ass belly is my 401k plan. holla!! jokes folks, jokes.  I don't need anyone cussing my name... after all i'm rubber and you're glue and i don't care what you have to say any damn way... but i still love you.   So i'm listening to my musiq soulstar cd and there has always been this track that i was digging since day one.. track number 10, Thereason.  now, for the record, i'm not sappy, but i'm in love with shawty,... shawty is my first love... i never knew i was capable of loving any one thing, person or place as deeply, as intensely, as strongly, as unconditionally as i do shawty... I love this baby more than i love ten of me... but back to the story, here is a snippet of the lyrical content in 'thereason'...   Artist : Musiq Soulchild  Title : Thereason  Album : Soulstar  Genre : R&B    [Chorus] All I am and all that I will ever be Is because of you and I am proud to say That you helped make me into what I am today I applaud you for being so patient with me All I am and all that I will ever be Is because of you and I am proud to say No one else could do what you have done for me You mean the worked to me (yeah)   There were times when I was so Frustrated with you I felt I didn't want you no more But then I realized That without you I would be so alone (yeah) Whatever right or wrong and im so glad I did cause  See you cause a changed in my life You turned an empty heart into work of art And open my eyes to the world I would have never known, for that im grateful You are my pride and my joy The closest thing to me next to God above and will for-ever be my first love And im always gonna give my all to you   now if that ain't some gut wrenching, bawl your eyes ducts out, spit on your neck type feelin', i don't know what is... and i wouldn't give it up for the world. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      imma tell you this much... if you are becoming a mom, be prepared to turn into a b.b. (bonafide bitch). everyone has questions about my decisions on having a child, one, two, out of wedlock and three in new york city. now, this might be a surprise to us progressive folks, but there still lie a few dumbasses who deem it their business in finding out the method to my madness. when i first found out i was expecting, all types of emotions went through me in a fing nanosecond and the only feel left within me was anticipation followed by joy. needless to say, i didn't know what the hell i was getting into. i still don't know. but i laid down, did the do, fully aware of the possibilities, and now behaving in a responsible manner. i.e., i don't believe in abortions. had i, this blog wouldn't exist.  not to be preachy, but this is my blog so...   "..... one in three African American pregnancies end in abortion, that over 1,200 black children die every day, and an estimated 70 percent of abortion providers are in minority neighborhoods." said Star Parker, a member of Care Net's board of directors. "Abortion in the black community has become a form of genocide."  - sleep on that.   as i was saying, motherhood turns the average woman into stupen-dor bitch... you don't give a flying f about anything anyone has to say. you don't feel a need to answer any ones questions with words, just actions if it is called upon. you honestly feel like it is you and your shawty against the world and act as if so. in the words of my dear friend Mary 'you gangsta, andrea' why, thank you, Mary. ... *inhale* baby daddy and i parted ways. and i don't give a fuk either, though, i sincerely wish i did. i'm like good... i feel so relieved... not about to put up with any ones shit... trust. and am even less readied to put up with whatever shit you are about to give my child. my coworker told me today that the reason why i don't have a man is because i won't let a man be a man. i said, sure i do.... you can clutch your peanuts and watch football all you want, but i would be one desperate ass b. if i let some man come up in my space and even think about pissing on me... ain't gonna happen. i will cut him clear across the face, father or no father before i let that happened. i will not let my child think that me settling for 'good enough' is even an option. not when i know there is better. even if i'm never with another man for the rest of my life, i can feel comfortable knowing i didn't settle for mediocrity... and i can champion that for my child, if him alone. i can show him better than i can tell him. he would know that his mom wasn't settling for no grade d meat.... subpar treament and lackluster handling. i will not lead it to believe that we do not need love or affection or commitment, but all of these things are well and good in healthy doses. that you cant love no body how ever much you want to love them, but love them only how much they let you. if it is none, then you get your ass to stepping. it really isn't that hard. trust me,... i'm still learning. i'm not looking forward to these discussion... where i'm telling my daughter... 'i could have told you that ni**a was no good' or my son 'she ain't nothing but a scally wag, anyway'. *exhale* i do sound bitter. i'm just so infuriated that he, not me, allowed this to happen. we both grow up without a father and as he tell it, he wanted to stop the cycle. i too, wanted and still want that. but at what cost? i know and feel and live the affects of absentee dad every day of my life... still years later. i wanted more for my child, if just that much more. i can taste the words of 'kiss my ass' on the tip of my lips every time i talk to the sperm donor....every time i speak with him. wanting to ask him... 'what the fuck you want, nigga? stop calling me!... you didn't have a need or want or desire to be all up in my grill ten, fifteen years ago, so what is your need now? leave me alone!' i don't want the animosity or hate or disdain to be felt ... it isn't a good feeling to want to spit in person's face who gave you life. but big up to my momma for saying ain't no way in this hell or that one daddy-o was going to shi on her. holla mama! if i'm taught anything by today's events is life is one big joke that nobody is laughing at.  okay... the rant is over and it is four days since i wrote the above. whew... that took a lot out out of me. i'm less angry today and baby daddy has really been trying to play it cool... if only he knew what i knew....he had the nerve to tell me he is having a hard time coming to terms with change. i'm like your medieval ass... we all do. does he think i'm ready to be a parent... hell nah! probably will never be ready to be one. but i would be damned if my child ever thinks anything less of my abilities. my mom says i am picking fights only because i'm pregnant. i said momma, you and i both know i would pop somebody in the mouth pregnant or not. i got that shi from you.... she just laughed because she knows it is true. the apple and the tree. alright, baby and i are about to bounce. we have to go eat...well i have to go eat... i'm 25wks this coming wednesday. baby is moving like a rolling stone... everyday, my love for shawty grows more intense and i cry happy tears whenever i sing to it or read to it or just rub my belly while it tears in my insides up with the throwing of 'bows... i haven't cried happy tears in ten years plus. I was watching joel osteen last night, you know, the lakeview, tx minster, and he was talking about how when you are done wrong by the haters, God blesses and restores you ten times over... that is why/what Shawty is, a blessing ten times over. now haters, including you, you lame  touche , top that. love you, MsThing!!!  haven't forgot about you either, Joy, Shun and Ranada!!! I will be by soon!! take care and muuaahh! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>