<Blog>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all.  wow im really slackin on the posts, huh?  sorry, to any of you who actually read this.  Life's been kinda blah but stressful at the same time...hate it when that happens.  Grades are coming out...aaahhhh.  i really need a 3.0.  dont laugh!!! thats good for me, and i need it.  so yea, *fingers crossed.*  Omg EVERYONE is hooking up, its insane.  And i dont have anyone :(  and i really want someone.  argh.  o well.  hopefully someone will come along.  :-/.  Yea and one of these new couples i like cant stand lookin at cuz...yea personal reasons.  lets just say that im a little too jealous.  ok, a lot too jealous.  *sigh*  welllll....gotta get some homework done before friends comes on!!! YAY!!! bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wanted: Tall muscular guy who can play ACDC for me on the guitar and who will hold me all night long.  Currently accepting applications. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate it when your relationship with someone like totally changes, especially when you were such good friends with that person.  it totally sucks.  i hate losing friends.  god, y do people have to change??? arg.  I just talked to the person and it was like we had nothing to talk about, and they annoy me now, and im sure i annoy them, and its like a little while ago we were such good friends.  its really sad.  I love her, but now its like i love who she used to be, and it's hard to be friends with who she is now.  *sigh* oh well... c'est la vie, right? and now im sitting at home bored as hell with nothing to do on a perfectly good saturday night.  blah.  sucks suck sucks.  and even if i had something to do I'd have no one to take me.  I NEED A DRIVERS LICENSE SO DAMN BAD!!!  aaaahhhh.    Oh, if anyone knows how to make it so that people can leave comments on here then tell me.  thanks.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey hey.  yea havent written in a couple days.  Nothing too interesting has happened, my life is kinda boring.  I went to San Jose last night with jen and we went to santana row and had dinner and shopped and stuff.  that was fun.  and omg while i was there lauren called me and she was at cafe barronis and the aim deep thoughts guy was at keplers doing a reading or something!!! HAHA how funny is that??? yea i thought it was funny.  and tonight i may go to a party, i havent decided yet.  dude, i need my license sooo bad, 2 weeks from monday!!!!  its like im a burden to hang out with now cuz whoever i am hanging out with has to drive me everywhere.  lol.  oh well.  well, steph is gonna be here any minute, sooo..... bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola.  my daily update.  this thing is kinda cool i guess...i wonder if anyone reads it.  if you do then tell me, cuz i dont wanna be like talking to myself here....  Anyway...today was a normal day.  then i went to dinner with a couple of friends at chevys...that was fun :)  and YAY sadies got pushed back a month so i have another month till i have to freaking ask someone.  im not really stressing, i just dont want to do it cuz its a drag.  o well, i wanna go..soooo.... yes, anyway, this is short, but i need to get to my homework.  SO ill talk to all you fine people later.  MWAH :)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all! ya today was a good day... had PSATs this morning (boring, but not too bad) so i had the rest of the afternoon free.  went to the creamery and had lunch with some friends, that was tons of fun.  oh and rebeccas bf came so i met him.  i guess hes a fine guy, but not really bf material, at least not up to par on my standards.  o well, if shes happy then i guess good for her.  then i went to reginas and hung out, and then went to the soccer game.  and now im putting off hw. Ugh, so we were talking about saides earlier, and i have no one to ask.  its very sad.  the only person that i kinda want to i cant so yea i dont know.  but i hate sadies.  here is my philosophy on the whole thing:  it takes away womens rights!!! thats right, steals em!! see, the only good part (well pretty much the only good part) of bein a girl is that we arent expected to ask the guys out, thats their job.  and here comes sadies, takin that away!!! now what do we have left??? nothing.  ugh.  but im not gonna go single, and i think all my friends r going, so i better find me a guy to ask.  any volunteers??? Well, off to do hw.  blech.  talk to u all later! mwah :)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all! decided to start one of these, at the urging of a dear friend...thanks nornie :).  anyway, weird name, i know, it was inspired by jersey...dont ask.  so yes, hello all!!! i pity you for reading this because it must mean that you are so bored that you have nothing else to do...but while you are hear, yay thank you for reading :).  well, i dont quite know what to say right now... Oh, so my mom and sister just got back from a college fair (i was too lazy to go :-/) and my mom brought me back all this stuff and a few colleges look really cool, esspecially clark and davidson.  And Clark is in new york, which is awesome cuz thats where i really want to go to college, and it looks like maybe i can acctually get in!!...so yes, yay!  Speaking of college...PSATs tomorrow...which means no hw tonight.  saaaweeeeet!! well, im off, ill write more later!  mwah!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey!  the curse of the relatives is still upon me, but only for one more day!!! (well then it will just be a relative i really like so thats ok.)  i guess i shouldnt complain cuz i dont see them that often but aaahh.  i guess i didnt really post about thanksgiving...it was fine, the fights were kept to a minimum, considering everyone was in the same room for an extended period of time...so that was good.  lol when i was little i always wanted to sit at the adult table, and this yr there were no kids so there was only an adults table, and wow, let me tell u, mashed potato fights and turkey jokes made up by a 5 yr old r so much more fun.  but, alas, there was josh *sigh* (hes the hot guy from my last post) and damn good cheescake, not to mention awesome turkey, so i cant complain.  all in all it was pretty good. today we went to san jose to go to the art museum.  my mom works there and we always have to go there when family comes.  i hate it, im so not a modern art person.  so my sisters and i kinda hung out in the gift shop and i talked on my cell phone.  then we went to santana row, but we didnt really do anything there, so then we came home.  and then i took a nap.  pretty boring day... well, i must go deal with my camera happy grandfather now.  ill ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG fucking hot guy at my house (no not a relitive!!!) but yea he came to my house for thanksgiving and hot damn!! and i sat across from him at dinner and we were talking the whole time.  AND he went to tisch (performing arts school at NYU where i want to go!) so he gave me pointers to get in and stuff.  and that also means hes an actor! and hes sooo funny.  and yea.  i just thought id share.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HAPPY TURKEY DAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! whats shakin.  happy turkey day!  well tomorrow.  acctually i guess today cuz its almost 1.  well a bunch of relitives r here...thats always interesting.  it was acctually going surprisingly well until dinner tonight...o well.  last night lauren came and got me and i slept at her house.  that was tons of fun and i got to escape for a while, so it was cool.  the full monty is so funny!!!  well i only saw the first half cuz then i fell asleep but it was funny so far!!! sooo...i dont really have much to say...i just thought id post.  I hope everyone has an AWESOME thanksgiving!!! mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yo yo yo sup me homies.  nothin much here...started soccer officially today.  im not as bad as i thot id be, but im still pretty damn bad.  its fun tho.  so yay.  the entire east coast is in my living room...well ok just a few relatives but believe u me, when my whole family gets together it seems like a lot more people than it really is.  and none of my cousins are coming!!! ugh that defeats the purpous of thanksgiving.  :(.  today kinda sucked, hard apes test KICKED MY ASS!! o well.   yay everyone told me i was really good in the play today.  i love hearin that im really good at something cuz sometimes it seems like im not really good at anything.  and i know they were prolly just saying that, but still its nice to think that i might acctually have some real talent in something!   wellllll, off to do some history reading.  ill talk to all u lovely people later
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey!  so the play is finally done!! woo hoo!!! it went really well, and it was fun.  yay :)  and now i have a shitload of work to do.  yuck :(.  Not much has been going on except the play...friday night some friends came and then we all went to boronnis, and then lauren slept over. that was lots of fun.  ugh, weve been talking (lauren and i) about how much we r gonna miss eachother next year.  its gonna be sooo sad!!!!  lauren, u have to go to colorado so we can see eachother!!!!  i mean, ill go see u anyway, but it will be easier if u were in colorado.  well, i have SO MUCH HW to do, so im gonna head.  ill talk to yall later by the way, if anyone knows how to make it so u can plst comments on here, tell me
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.  loooonnnnggg week!!! and its only wed :(.  had rehersal every day from 3:45 to 10.  talk about way to long to be at school.  and for some reason it is soooooo tiring.  cant keep my eyes open.  but it opens tomorrow and i think it will turn out well so its all worth it.  EVERYONE COME!!! ROAR!!!! OR ILL BITE YOUR EAR OFF!!!!    or something....but yes come, it will be good.  Well i just wanted to post since i hadnt in a few days.  I think im going to take full advantage of my hw pass and get some sleep.  goodnight!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HI!!! whats up??  nothin much here.  Jersey is here.  We are having fun :)  we had play rehersal alllll freakin day.  it was looooooong.  and we do all day tomorrow.  but jersey is spending the weekend at my house this weekend and we are havin a lot of fun.  jersey + sara + cake = oh dear, loud times.  oh and frosted flakes ROCK!!  everyone read jersey's blog (wtf-jersey) because she is updating it right now and it is SOOOO FUNNY!! thats one funny girl.... HAHAHAHAHAHAHAAH!!!!!!!!!! rebecca just went to kick jersey and she kicked the chair and she is like rolling around on the floor right now and it is sooooo funny.  she looks insane hahaha. ok well im gonna go cuz this blog is making nooo sense whatsoever.  actually maybe ill make this really long and entertain u all for a really long time.  Jason esta animado...and not in the energetic sense...if u catch my drift ;).  just fyi.  ok nm on making this long, im going to go.  PUMPKIN PIE!!! WOO HOO! bye
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh...my...god im going to die.  soccer sucks.  well, the conditioning we did today sucks.  i am just not a land port running person.  i swim damnit!  i hae running.  and if its all like that i dont know how im gonna live through the season.  cuz like i just wont have fun, u know?  o well...it will get me in really good shape I just had a good talk with jersey.  im glad everything is worked out.  hehe luv ya! Well, its almost 8 and friends calls!!! yay!!! hasta la pasta 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay, all cleared for soccer.  sad tho...deciding to play soccer means im deff giving up on swimming, which is sad.  oh well, there's always next year, right?  So yea, im all stocked up for soccer, now all i need is to learn to play!!! lol.  wow, this is pathetic.  :-p.  dude, i got home today thinkin it was thursday and all stoked cuz i thot an hr and and a half till friends, but then noo, it turned out it was wed! so sad.  well ive been up till at least 1 or 2 for 3 nights in a row, so im gonna go get my hw done so that i can possibly get to bed at a reasonable hr tonight.  and enchaladas call!!! bye :)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey!! haha yea so ive decided to play soccer.  its kinda funny, seeing as ive never playes soccer, or really any land sports for that matter, and im so uncordinated and dont really run.  lol, but other than that.... now i just have to get cleared so i can start playin.   ooooh god watch out team, im gonna suck!!! o well.  yea other than that noting is really up...blah blah blah.  life's kinda boring.  and i think im lettin all my grades drop which is so not good, cuz i have to at least keep what i got at the quarter...well ill have to work on that.  on that note, off to do hw!! later
     
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow yea im really slackin.  well i havent really been up to much.  Thus weekend i mostly just hung out with Lauren and Maddie...such cool people!! :). Friday night we went to boronnis (sp?) and there were these really hot waiters so i gave one of them my number. and then lauren was a chicken so i gave the other one her number.  lol im kiddin lauren.  but yea, they havent called.  oh well i knew they wouldnt.  OH and im going to not so silent night!!!!!! its the same day as sadies, but now that means i dont have to worry bout askin ne one  :).  so yea, im stoked.  Well, i better go work on my APES progect.  ugh, fucking coniferous forests.  well, ill post later.  hasta la vista.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey!  well, today kinda sucked.  I spent 3 hrs this morning at the DMV getting a new permit cuz my old one expired.  ugh.  and then i spent the rest of my day sleeping and throwing up.  Yea, sorry, sure u wanted to hear that one.  And now ive missed 2 days of school, which means a shitload of work to make up.  :(  So even if im still sick tomorrow im gonna have to go to school.  UGH high school sucks.  I hope college is better.  too bad thats far away.  well, ill quit my bitching and let u go.  adios
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      THE ATARIS CONCERT ROCKED!!!! aaahhh it was soo cool! they are so good in concert.  :-D  and also, driving tests suck.  the end.  period.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude, halloween was tons of fun.  we went out at like 9-10 and all these people were like oh u must be the last of the trick or treaters so they gave us all the rest of their candy.  omg we got like seriously an entire pillowcase of candy among the 5 of us.  and we were all like running screaming thru the streets.  it was fun.  and then yesterday jen and i hung out in sunnyvale.  and we went to toys r us and rode the little tiny bikes with the training wheels all over the store, that was tons of fun.  hey shut up i know we are weird but hey, ur only young once!!!!  and omg i got my grades and i got a 3.3!!!! dont laugh thats good for me!!! so yes, im stoked.  OMG OMG OMG AND TONIGHT IM GOING TO SEE THE ATARIS IN CONCERT!!!!! AAHHHH!!! I LOVE YOU LAUREN!!!!!! im sooooooo stoked!!!  and tomorrow is my drive test, and i get to miss school!! eeee!! so yes, life is good :D well, im gonna go do some hw so i can go tonight!!!!! bye ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey!!  ok, i lied,  im updating.  the truth of the matter is that i just cant stay away from u guys.  ;)  so yea, colorado kicks fuckin butt.  been boarding my ass off.  omg i got the sickest snowboard ever made!!!!!! its the never summer infinity (for those of u who that means something to) and aahhh its the best.  i was riding it yesterday and today, and dude its the sweetest ride ever.  its black and has a dragon on the tail...so sweet!! ya, im stoked.  and the boarding here rocks. so yea, cool stuff :) well, i gotta take off...ill talk to yall later.  mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh, PS.    "You only see Perdiddles when you're alone"  -- A deep thought by me  "hmmm..."
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yay im going to colorado tomorrow!! eee!!! its gonna be so much fun :)  so yea if i dont post for a lil bit dont freak out and think ya lost me, im only like 500 miles away ;) SNOWBOARDING!!! WOO HOO!!! haha anyway, im really excited.  but now i need to pack....NOT fun.  so yea, im puttin that off.  oh merry belated christmas to u all.  hope u all had fun and got a lot of cool stuff.  oh and no one go see elf.  that is such a crappy movie.  (unless u r like 3, then maybe ull get a kick out of it...)  well anywho, i guess i should go.  love u all dearly.  adios
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*... yea, thats it.  just a sigh.   and a smile :)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      haha this license thing is soo cool...lol...i been drivin around so much.  today i drove to freaking bellmont... NOT on pupose i may add...because my sisters and i were meaning to go to the best buy in san carlos to get my dad a present and yea...didnt work out to well.  haha and ive been drivin other people (shhh) but yea its sooo cool! haha.  im a dork, i know, but ive waited long enough damnit! lol.  and vacation is awesome...nothing to worry about.  i cant wait to go to colorado, it will be so much fun.  yay.  ok well, imna go...just wanted to say hi...i hope u r all havin a good break, miss u all.  mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY I GOT MY LICENSE!! WOO HOO!!!  hehe im sooo happy! and it only took me 4 tries :-/  but yay i finally got it.  eeee!!!   so now to u ppl who always have to drive to the boondocks to pick me up, u dont have to ne more, lol.  well, i think im gonna go drive somewhere!! i already drove to ale's and back today by myself, its fun driving by myself.  i feel so powerful.  well yay! i just wanted to post that.  i hope everyone is havin a good break.  mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      IM SO FUCKING BORED!!!! omg soooo bored, NOTHING to do.  such a loser, home with nothing to do on a sat night, lol.  i dont even have anything to say...  well i hope ur all havin a good break.  nothin to say so yea...bye
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yay its break!!! finally!! yea ive had no time to post cuz ive been so busy studying.  but yay no more finals!! ugh im so glad its break, im sooo ready for a break.  gonna sleep and just hang out for the first week, and then im goin to colorado the second week.  im sooo stoked, its gonna be so much fun.  and a lot of ppl are comin and ya.  yay! oh oh and hannuka starts tonight!!! woo hoo!!!  so yes, life is good.  :) i dont have much to say, soooo gonna go.  adios
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I found a line and then it grew I found myself still thinking of you I felt so empty and now I'm fine But still it's burning, when will you be mine?  Too much of the same stories in our lives I think it's time for change, don't you? Too much of the same stories in our lives I think it's time for us to walk away from here  Look at me still in your mind Our memories so intertwined Well you broke through and found your way And so did I no need to stay The same old picture, tried and true Been through there, lets looking for something new  Do you remember lying on the beach so late at night Do you remember running through the sprinklers that night Do you remember all the songs that I have wrote for you  I remember,the way you made me feel when I was with you I remember,the smile that always brought me back to you That look in your eyes, I never thought that this could be untrue
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      finals suck.  soccer sucks.  fuck, just 4 more days....
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! another big study day...but this one was good :)  i went to D's review, that was good.  and then susan and i went to stanford and we studied apes over lunch at uno mas (which we discovered acctually isnt uno mas!!!) for a really long time, and that was awesome.  and then we did our xmas shopping.  yay.  omg i got so many presents, i spent soooo much!! but xmas rocks, what with all the presents and stuff.  but HANNUKA IS STILL BETTER!!! lol.  well, jsut thought id say hi.  im gonna go.  adios mis amigos
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      life sucks.  finals suck.  studying all day really sucks.  spending a day without getting dressed or anything in sometimes a good thing tho :).  and now im tired.  but im waiting up cuz jen is coming over.  crazy girl.  she decided to come over at like 12:45.  am that is.  she should be here by 1:30.  good times, good times. Dude i was having this thought.  and its kinda weird cuz it came at a time when i hadnt stopped studying for a couple hrs, and now its gonna come out even weirder cuz im tired as hell.  but anyway, here goes.  so i was listenin  to ms payne talk about how she doesnt really see her high school friends anymore yesterday, and i was thinking about that today when i just couldnt take any more apes.  and i thought, all my friends now just happen to be the friends i have during this brief period in my life.  they rnt my friends as an absolute...just, the friends that i have now that i may never see again.  like, thats just weird.  cuz these people are my friends, and i cant see myself moving on and having another batch of friends...or the same for them.  it seems like a waste almost, and weird that people who are so close can just poof, move on.  but really, what if i go to school on the other side of the country from some of my best friends, and we swear to keep in touch, and we email during freshman year of college, and make an effort to see eachother when we r home during the same time,  but then we kinda stop having time and pretty soon we arent friends anymore.  and i am making NO SENSE.  i have no idea what im writting, but bassically it seems like these r gonna be my friends forever, but what if its really just my high school friends who i see at a reunion and im like oh hah wow i remember that person.  it just seems weird.  and sad.  and i need sleep.  stop reading this!!!! bye
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      finals suck ass.  ugh, and studying is so boring.   my day so far: woke up 1t 9:30 and hung out with jersey jersey left at like 10:15, so then i went back to bed but i couldnt really sleep 11:30 decided to become productive 1:00 acctually become productive its 2:30 and ive been studying spanish for an hr and a half and now im really bored yea so my day has been so boring.  and i want to hang out tonight but i think im just gonna stay home and study. my mom wants to go to the movies with me though, so i might take a break and do that, i dont know. anyway, studying is SO much better when u r doing it together, but we didnt have our semi-annual study session at stephs cuz we rnt taking any of the same finals...oh well, tomorrow im gonna go to a history study session and then study apes with susan at starbucks! the best possible way i can think to study apes, so its all good. well, im off to start on a super mega study guide for apes.  wish me luck, and if i dont return, check under the mountain of papers and books on my bed to make sure im still breathing.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      what a day...what a day... so i got home today and i got my PSAT scroes, and i got the equivilant if like a 1230!!! im soooo stoked!! dude but better yet, i got in the 99th percentile in writting!!!!!! dude, ive never been the BEST at anything, lol but i got better (or equal to) everyone in writting!!!  and like 95% all in all of all college bound seniors.  so yea i was really happy and like jumping around stuff.  lol. And then there was the dance.  it was ok, it had its moments.  Like dancing on the block to ACDC with katie and chintz, lol that was so much fun, and yea.  but it wasnt great.  and then i got kinda pissed right there in the middle...lol...but we wont talk about that :-p And now Jersey is here.  we just had this convo where we both just started crying.  lol we r such a depressed bunch...but oh well, it was kinda good.  got some stuff out of our systems. Well, i guess id better get some sleep, cuz i have a whole weekend of cramming to do, startin early tomorrow (well, early for me, which means before like noon, lol)  AAAHHHH FINALS AAAAHHHHH well on that note, goodnight and happy studying everyone. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      DOES ANYONE WANT TO BUY A TICKET TO NOT SO SILENT NIGHT???? IF SO LET ME KNOW ASAP!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      grrr!!! being sick sucks!!! i slept for 19 hrs today tho, lol, that was cool.  but i feel like shit and i missed school the week before finals!!! not cool!! so now im totally stressing.  blah.  but its all ok because im going to not so silent night on friday!!!! woo hoo!!!!!! well assuming that i get better and we can work out the issue of getting up there.  but yea, rancid and offspring!!! woo hoo!!! all of u ppl going to sadies suck, cuz the concert is gonna be so much better.  (i hope.)  well, back to trying to feel better. oh, and pms sucks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yay we won our game.  3-1, woo hoo.  lol i totally shouldnt have played tho. as if i wasnt sick enough, now i have a worse cough and im gettin chills and im losing my voice.  blah...i cannot miss school.  oh well... but better news, my mom had coffee with sarahs mom today.  (for those of u who dont know sarah is my best friend of 8 yrs who was shipped off to one of those reform boarding schools and i havent seen her or heard from her in like 7 or 8 months.  bassically hell).  anyway my mom had coffee with her mom even tho she is still all pissed at her and probably always will be, but just so she could get info about sarah.  apparently we can start writting eachother in january.  i cant see her until september tho.  thats almost a yr, making a grand total of a yr and a half without seeing her.  thats horrible, i can even explain.  but at least we can start writting soon...and my mom got me some pictures of her which is good.  oh and apparently in english she had to write a paper about someone important in her life and she chose me, and she has 8 pages about me so far.  lol, its good to hear that she still thinks about me cuz sometimes i wonder if maybe shes moved on and doesnt really think about me ne more, whereas i think about her and miss her so much, all the time.  god i really just need her in my life right now.  like really bad.  *sigh* c'est la vie, i guess...as much as it sucks. well, off to drown myself in tea to try to get better!!! mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Every time we lie awake; After every hit we take. Every feeling that I get; But I haven't missed you yet. Every room mate kept awake; by every sigh and scream we make All the feelings that I get; But I still don't miss you yet Only when I stop to think about it.  I hate everything about you, why do I, love you? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      fuck, do u care about my feelings at all?  call me selfish but id like to feel like i actually mean something to u, maybe even be important.  but no, i guess im not and i guess i just have to live with that.  i guess i have to deal with the fact that the relationship i want to have is just in my head.  if im just gonna be taking up time and space then forget it.  im prolly gonna delete this one soon because, honestly, who am i kidding?
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm its been a little while.  nothing to interesting is up...on saturday i was gonna go skiing but i hurt my stupid ankle and i didnt think i could ski on it so i couldnt go.  so i was bored all day instead.  oh but i played some soccer, so that was cool.  then yesterday i went to rehersal and them marrissas cuz we were SUPPOSED to work on the history thing but no one else showed up.  freakin lazy people.  so we just hung out and then i can home and did my hw.  and now im fuckin sick.  grrr...i hate being sick, and i cant miss school cuz we have finals next week and ive already missed enough school.  im so worried about my grades...they have to stay at least what they were at the quarter or else im fucked, but but i think they all went down.  bah.  i need to start making this thing more interesting. hmmm...well im gonna go. adios
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      kill me.  just fucking kill me.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ALOHA!! whats shakin people.  Nothing much here, had service day today.  We went to a homeless shelter and helpped out.  It always kinda makes me sad going to those places, esspecially when i see kids, cuz i cant imagine how horrible it would be to grow up like that, without a home.  And the kids were sooo cute!!! i went into the daycare center and these little kids, they were prolly about 3, started laughing and talking to me, and they were like r u a mommy?? do u have a kid?? and i was like no.  and this other one was like do u have a mommy? and i was like yup.  and then he was like do u have a daddy? and i was like yup.  and then he was like lucky, i dont.  it was soo sad, this was the cutest little kid.  yea but it was fun, and the kids were so happy to just have me sit down and talk to them.  unfortunately talking to the kids wasnt what i was supposed to be doing so i didnt get to for that long.  so i organized a food closet (fun but a lot more stressful than it sounds!!!! lol) omg there were so many rasins, it was INSANE!!  and then jen and guilly and i came up with and put together some art projects for kids for tonight.  that was cool.  Jen is gonna make a great kindergarden teacher some day, lol.  I hope that doing all this good work today gave me some karma so that somebody up there has decided that its ok to let me pass my drivers test tomorrow! ITS HIGH FUCKING TIME!!! i hope third time is the charm, because if i fail three times that is just ABSURD, not to mention i have to go back to drivers ed.  but we wont talk about that.  because im gonna pass.  well, i have hella work to do so i need to get going.  Later!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      GAH!!! my comments thing didnt work!!! if ne one knows y tell me!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey!! god im gettin so bad at updating this.  oh well.  so i had my first soccer game today.  yay, we won, woo hoo! and i played up top, which is weird cuz i thot i was defence, but o well.  and lets see...oh yea i take my driving test on thursday!! I HAVE TO PASS!! omg seriously, i HAVE to.  :-/.  so i will!!! muahahaha. yay tomorrow is service day which means no classes!! and it SHOULD mean no hw, but i do have halla work to do.  omg look at the time, i better go do it.  later
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today started out to be a complete bummer, but then it turned out to be pretty fun.  so i was gonna go skiing but the fuckin bus never came so we were at school from 4:30-7 AM THAT IS and waited for the bus but then we left so i went to santa cruz with regina, quinn, becca, and jason.  we went to capitola and got breakfast and then we went to the boardwalk.  we were like the only ppl there and so it was a lot of fun.  then we went to the mall in capitola for a little while, and then since we were all sooooo tired from being up since like 3 am we came home and slept.  and now im about to go see perfect score.  sooo...fun stuff :)   OH yesterday i had a meeting with the college councelor.  NYU might not be happening...fuck.  but ithaca might and she told me bout other colleges.  oh and she predicted my sat score to be like hella good.  so yea. just thot id mention that wellllllll i gotta get goin.  ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      an ode to my dear friend lauren   lauren is a cow obsessed insanely cool wonderfully funny very fast swimmer. she (had) a white bravada named benny and has a dog, who some report bares strange resemblance to a pig. however aside from liking cows, being cool, cracking jokes, swimming, driving her benny and petting said pig-dog, lauren spends much of her time making delighful music on her guitar which as far as i know has no name. among her favorite songs are some eric claptan song that a 12 year old looking guitarist from somewhere in eastern europe can play and metallica stuff. and aside from all this lauren is moral, always right and moves a lot cuz shes lived in like all 50 states or something  by rebecca  :)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello.  whats up.  nothing here.  boring day. parents gone till tom night tho :)  so yea house to myself.  ummm...yea nothing to say.  boring post.  bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my tadpole...he's dead...poor frankie *tear*
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yo wassup.  just got back from a team dinner at buca de beppos...hella good.  hehe yay lauren left me a message...yall should follow in her footsteps, shes a good kid ;) lol. so yea, nothing really new...just thot id post.  yet again.  so yea, bye
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyyyy...in study hall right now.  so much fun.  not.  but a comfy couch....and yay i just had advisory and got my grades and i got my 3.0! yea yea i know that is shitty but ive reached a goal so yay.  k well um, nothin to say, just kinda bored so yea.  omg i fell asleep at 8:30 last night.  and then i woke up at 10 and went back to sleep at 10:30. so much sleep.  yet im still tired...hmmm...im always tired.  and the couple to my right (no names... :-p) is goin on and on with the pda and the baby talk...aahhh!  tortellini for lunch...mmm garlic bread...ring bell!!!!  im so happy that i have sa study  hall with lauren this semester.  finally get to freakin see her during the day.  she is reading "experience the world's religion" right now...hmm... muy interesante...  there is a stampede of singing middle schoolers running up the stairs...the strange goings on at this school....  this is like my longest post so far... see what haappens when i get bored?  well thias comp is spazzin (stupid macs...) so im gonna wrap this up.  hasta la vista, babies!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey.  wassup?  nothin much here...pretty boring day....except i went to the doc for my foot and its like a bad sprain and i cant play till fri.  o well.  and um, other stuff that i dont feel like posting. sorry.  oh, dude, btw in case u havent noticed i have comments now...that means feel free to leave some!!! if anyone even reads this that is....
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so the play is over.  yay i guess...although that means no more drama for this semester...so thats sad.  drama is the best class ever.  o well.  but it went well.  better today than yesterday, but pretty good both days.  and now i have to do all my hw that i havent touched this weekend....   I swear that I can go on forever again Please let me know that my one bad day will end I will go down as your lover, your friend Give me your lips and with one kiss we begin  Are you afraid of being alone Cause I am, I'm lost without you Are you afraid of leaving tonight Cause I am, I'm lost without you  I'll leave my room open till sunrise for you I'll keep my eyes patiently focused on you Where are you now I can hear footsteps I'm dreaming And if you will, keep me from waking to believe this  Are you afraid of being alone Cause I am, I'm lost without you Are you afraid of leaving tonight Cause I am, I'm lost without you   i hate feeling lonely... :(
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if this is u  you are right, you don't no me, but i no you, and i just figured out dat da girl i raped was ur lil sis...no joke as her bout it maybe then you can figure out who this is  then im going to fucking kill u.  no joke.  im gonna find out who u r and kill u.  so ud better take it back right this fucking second.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      got a freakin sprained foot.  hurts like a biotch.  ugh and so much hw, and i have to be at school at 7 tomorrow!!! dude but the worst: FRIENDS IS A RERUN TONIGHT!!! what the hell is this nation coming to.  frankly im more than a little upset.  fucking abomination.   anyway, gotta go do my hw.  yuck.  ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have comments now (thanks lauren!!!) so post one if u read this
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey all! im acctually in a really good mood today..hmm.  might have something to do with the fact that i have no hw! woo hoo!  hehe someone really wants to go to formal with me, but cant, which is a bummer, but hey that counts for something!! and he was so sweet and yea like made my day, hehe.  stupid mun... oh and my grades didnt drop as much as i thot they did which is good.  still dont know my gpa, but im pretty damn sure its still above a 3.0, so yay! and now im just lyin here waiting for that 70's show to come on cuz i can acctually watch seein as i really have nothing to do.  what a great feeling.  so yes, i'm happy :).  good times.  well, im gonna go for now.  ill talk to u later.  mwah! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      shitty ass soccer game today... i need a date for formal!!! anyone???? and a dress.  that would be good too.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh one more thing...  whenever i step outside, somebody claims to see the light it seems to me that all of us have lost our patience. 'cause everyone thinks they're right, and nobody thinks that there just might be more than one road to our final destination  but i'm not ever going to know if i'm right or wrong 'cause we're all going in the same direction and i'm not sure which way to go because all along we've been going in the same direction  i'm tired of playing games, of looking for someone else to blame for all the holes in answers that are clearly showing for something to fill the space, was all of the time i spent a waste 'cause so many choices point the same way i was going.....  so why does there only have to be one correct philosophy? i don't want to go and follow you just to end up like one of them and why are you always telling me what you want me to believe? i'd like to think that i can go my own way and meet you in the end.  but i'm not ever going to know..........  fuckin AWESOME lyrics 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm, havent posted in a while, huh?  sorry bout that.  lets see.  just had a four day weekend, busy as hell.  partied and had rehersal and hung out with friends...ooh and i got a tadpole!! his name is frankie, and i might just be raising him for lauren, or i might keep him when he turns into a frog.  it depends.  but yea it was a total spur of the moment thing. hmmm, rewinding, lets see whats happened since i last updated... got all my finals back...all in all did pretty well, im kinda nervous for grades to come out this week tho. AAAHHH! they gotta be good. oh dude, the last thing that i wrote was that sarah sent me a present...it was a book of a bunch of memories she has with me...every chapter is a story about something we've been thru together.  theres like 12 stories in there, starting with the day we became best friends and ending with the last time we saw eachother.  i like started crying when i read it, i miss her so much.  i get to write her soon, so im happy about that.   hmm, well i guess if something life changing had happened i would have posted it, or at the very least would remember it right now, so i guess theres nothing i really gotta post...nothing i can think of at least... OH!! everyone come to the drama 3 play this weekend -- saturday at 7 and sunday at 4.  DUDE! im not kidding! come!! dont look around, im talking to YOU!!! yes, come, its gonna be good.   well, on that note, i think ill leave all u fine people.  have a good night.  mwah
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sarah sent me (well, sent her mom to give to me) a belated bday present! omg that makes like my month (at least).  god i miss that girl so bad.    SO FUCKING BAD!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why am I fighting to live, if I'm just living to fight Why am I trying to see, when there aint nothing in sight Why am I trying to give, when no one gives me a try   Why am I dying to live, if I'm just living to die  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deep down it hides Making life a grind I dreamed of this so long This used to feel so strong  Now I wait  Wish these thoughts would go away I hope I dream of you Cause it's taking my life away No I don't hate But these thoughts won't go away I hope I dream of you Cause it's taking my life away 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everybody.  HAPPY NEW YEAR!! so im back from the ol CO.  it was fun.  snowboarding kicks ass. lauren ended up coming up and we had so much fun.  i taught her to ski, shes sooo good!!!! ya and my cousins came...they r sooooo cute!!! so yes, it was fun.  omg but yesterday we had to fly out of there...and we origionally had a flight out of this air port that was like 30 mins away but then it was cancelled cuz the weather wad too bad, so then we were gonna go to another airport but we couldnt get a flight out of there in time or something, so then we ended up going to this other airport, and it was supposed to be like an hr and a half or 2 hrs away, but it ended up taking us 5 hrs to get there! we were in the car for 5 hrs!!! omg so long, and then like a 3 hr flight.  man, was it hard to get out of there.  o well but now im home.  and doing nothing.  my mom just took rebecca to the ER cuz we think she broke her rib or sumthin, so i guess i need to go take my sis somewhere.  so yes, im outa here.  ill ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yea and the people from the ronald mcdonald house called me today and they r interested in having me volunteer so yay! ill prolly have an interview like next week sometime  k now im done :)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i used my hannuka money to get the phone!!!! omg its so fucking cool!!!! its a camera phone and its color and its soo cool!!! and omg i set its ring and it can ring a song, but not just like the tune like the real song wih the words and everything, so it rings bump bump bump.  haha its so cool.  its got everything.  i love it.  yay :)  oh, same number for those of u wondering...  k back to work, just wanted to rave bout my new toy :)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      greetings from my bed, where i lie sick and procrastinating on my english essay.  how goes it?  so, is $150 too much to spend on a hella cool cell phone when i have one that works?  i think it might be.  but did i mention that it is HELLA AWESOME?? and is a cool flippy phone and has a camera and is color and all that and is REALLY COOL? hmm...  dude, who reads this?  if u read this leave me a comment, i want to take a count.  i dont care who u r, just leave me a comment.    well, i dont have much to say so i guess ill get going...  sayonara dude.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Romantic, hopeful, and composed. You are the Sonnet. Get it? Composed?       Sonnets want Love and have high ideals about it. They're conscientious people, caring & careful. You yourself have deep convictions, and you devote a lot of thought to romance and what it should be. This will frighten away most potential mates, but that's okay, because you're very choosy with your affections anyway. You'd absolutely refuse to date someone dumber than you, for instance.        Lovers who share your idealized perspective, or who are at least willing to totally throw themselves into a relationship, will be very, very happy with you. And you with them. You're already selfless and compassionate, and with the right partner, there's no doubt you can be sensual, even adventurously so.       You probably have lots of female friends, and they have a special soft spot for you. Babies do, too, at the tippy-top of their baby skulls.    hmm...interesting...  i am sick, and that sucks.  and so does this fucking english paper.  baaaahhh  been in bed all day, and this paper is getting no where.  i guess ill go finish it and probably fall asleep while trying to do so.  adios 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      is it me or is it you , something isn't right  of all the things that we could do we just wanna fight someday i will find the courage to embrace you someday i will find the strength to erase you  some days i think i'm nothing without you sometimes i wish that i could just kill you what a way we live our lives it's hard to breathe 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dude.  got mail from ithaca today, where i really wanna go.  yay! that makes me happy.  shhh dont tell me that they send it to everyone!! cuz im sure they dont!!!  :-p  i think im getting sick.  thats not cool.  off to delve into the fascination that is statistics.  sayonara.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my house is shaking...and i have a big, not easily shakable, house.   im so exuasted.  and so much work.  gaahh...  im off
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's a place off Ocean Avenue Where I used to sit and talk with you We were both 16 and it felt so right Sleeping all day, staying up all night Staying up all night  There's a place on the corner of Cherry Street  We would walk on the beach in our bare feet We were both 18 and it felt so right Sleeping all day, staying up all night Staying up all night  If I could find you now things would get better We could leave this town and run forever Let your waves crash down on me and take me away  There's a piece of you that's here with me It's everywhere I go, it's everything I see When I sleep, I dream and it gets me by I can make believe that you're here tonight That you're here tonight  If I could find you now things would get better We could leave this town and run forever I know somewhere, somehow we'll be together Let your waves crash down on me and take me away  I remember the look in your eyes When I told you that this was goodbye You were begging me not tonight Not here, not now We're looking up at the same night sky And keep pretending the sun will not rise  Be together for one more night Somewhere, somehow  If I could find you now things would get better We could leave this town and run forever I know somewhere, somehow we'll be together Let your waves crash down on me and take me away 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      naps are good.  so are good grades on history tests.  and so are crushes.  tehe ;)  thats all for now folks...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i re read to kill a mockingbird while i was away.  that is such a great book.  ill post the greatest quotes from that book eventually...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      duuuude, im so jet lagged.  today i slept till like 12 and then went to the movies and then came home and slept some more and then woke up and had dinner and now im trying to stay awake.  fuck i have to do english hw.  oh 50 first dates is not worth ur 9 bucks by the way.  it does have its moments, but i didnt like it.   I got mail from the US military academy.  ya baby.  my college search is over.  k well im gonna try to stay awake long enough to do some hw, and then crash.  adios. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been here before a few times And I'm quite aware we're dying And your hands they shake with goodbyes And I'll take you back if you'd have me  So here I am I'm trying So here I am are you ready  Come on let me hold you touch you feel you Always Kiss you taste you all night  Always  And I'll miss your laugh your smile I'll admit I'm wrong if you'd tell me I'm so sick of fights I hate them Lets start this again for real  So here I am I'm trying So here I am are you ready So here I am I'm trying So here I am are you ready  Come on let me hold you touch you feel you Always Kiss you taste you all night  Always Come on let me hold you touch you feel you Always  Kiss you taste you all night Always  I've been here before a few times And I'm quite aware we're dying  Come on let me hold you touch you feel you Always Kiss you taste you all night  Always Come on let me hold you touch you feel you Always Kiss you taste you all night Always 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey!! im back from spain.  it was sooo awesome! so much fun.  i had a blast.  did sooo much.  sightseeing, shopping (thanks leila for showing me h&m!!!) hanging out, lot of eating, hehe.  spanish tortilla and paella (sp?) is soo good.  lot of fish and pork tho, not really my cup of tea.  we started in madrid, and there we went to some museums and then hung out and shopped and did some sighteeing. then we went to toledo.  toledo was this gorgeous old little town, reminded me a lot of italy.  then after we went to granada... granada rocked, it was this little town with all these little tea shops and stands and stuff, and the alhambra, this old arab castle, was cool.  then we went to sevilla.  awesome town, so much shopping and stuff to do.  then cordoba...saw a mosque, did some shopping and walkin around...pretty cool.  then we took an overnight train to barcelona.  i loved barcelona...soooo much to do.  so much culture and then las ramblas, the big shopping street was awesome.  some sketchy people there tho...i dont know about some of them.  but yea, sooo much fun.  hehe and its really cool cuz the legal age there is 16...didnt drink or ne thing tho...of course not im a good girl 0:-)  i want to study abroad over there or something.   so yes, it rocked so much.  and now im dirty and tired from a 2 hr and then another 11 hr plane ride...tho i slept most of the 11 hr one.  i dont know y planes make u tired even when u sleep.  o well.  im off.  hasta luego!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey.  boring day.  school was boring and i was like dead all day.  but then after school i went and hung out in menlo park with some friends.  that was fun.  it was nice to hang out with steph...i havent hung out with her, or even really talked to her in such a long time.  good times.  spain in 2 days!  jersey we r gonna have so much fun!!! watch out spaniards, here we come!!! hehe, but yea, im stoked :)  and now im off to do what little homework i have (woo hoo) and accctually get some sleep.  later.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally I figured out But it took a long, long time But now there's a turnabout Maybe 'cause I'm trying   There's been times, I'm so confused All my roads, They lead to you I just can't turn and walk away   It's hard to say what it is I see in you Wonder if I'll always be with you But words can't say, And I can't do Enough to prove, It's all for you   I thought I'd seen it all 'Cause it's been a long, long time But then we'll trip and fall Wondering if I'm blind  Rain comes pouring down Falling from blue skies Words without a sound Coming from your eyes  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      slept till 4 today...that was nice.  i should have gone to school or at least woken up and taken care of all the shit i needed to do but o well.  i was planning on doing the latter, but i never woke up.  o well it happens.   going to spain in 3 days!!! im so stoked, its gonna rock.   um ok thats it.  bye. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      12:35 am and all is weee-eeelll!!!   (aside from this fucking history paper...)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omfg formal was soo awesome.  i had the time of my life.  it was seriously like one of the best nights i can remember having in soooo long.  i danced my ass off for 3 hrs straight non stop. litterally. and everyone looked so pretty :).  ahh i had so much fun just dancin and stuff with friends.  and i learned that dancing crazily with girlfriends to slow songs is sooo much more fun than dancing to them with a guy.  hehe.  oh, and single people rock!! power to the sinngle chicks!!! *clink shirly temples*  hehe good times, good times.  im happy it ended up being so much fun cuz i kinda wasnt sure.  and when we got there were like hardly ne people, but we started dancin and more people came and yea it ended up rocking.  so yes, a good night :).  acctually im prolly the only one who had THAT much fun...but o well, lol.   no one ever get the mini burgers at dennys.  jersey made that mistake, now lets no one repeat it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay formal tonight!  and gunn sadies last night.  that was fun.  :)  my day today: woke up at like 12:15 gonna shower and do pre-pre getting ready stuff hair appointment at 3:15 make up at 4 laurens to get ready dinner at 6:45 formal 8-11:30 dennys after  yay fun day...well i hope formal is fun...yes, it will be :)  well, im off.  ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      friends is deterierating.  its so sad.  :(.  o well.    the last post was weird...  yay dance tom and then formal on sat...fun stuff!! lets just hope my foot is better.....  k well hw time.  ill ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey hey.  que pasa.  im bored.  in study hall...blah.  no lauren and becca u rnt boring me!!! :-p  now ur hurting me!!! stop!!!! lauren is poking me and playing with my ear...   axcf dzdszadc sxazdczdcx cx  cbhzzc cbh kuiolgtyucfvn gvhgvhjhjbjgvvkv  that was the brilliant literary stylings of lauren and becca.  lauren is big ballin.  she just whipped like 100 bucks out of her pocket.  *yawn* im so tired.  ITS A NEW FRIENDS TONIGHT!!!!  YAY!!!!  bout freakin time.  k this post is pointless and im really tired so yea, i guess ill wrap it up  oh, let me just say, i hate crutches.  ok, now im done.  i want an orange.  hmmm   bye
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'Cause I want someone to share my smile  To share the pain  To be there when the sea turns gray  To share the joy  For better or worse..... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      aahh im on crutches!!! im a gimp!! no!!! this sucks.  well, im gonna be off them by friday because aint no wooden sticks gonna keep me from dancin ;)  lol.  yea the field trip today was sooo booooring!!! the highlight had to have been the very animated game of bs at lunch. or the 3 hrs of nap time i got on the bus.  yea, that was good. and now i need to write a spanish essay that was due yesterday.  i swear i had no idea it was due.  :( welllll, hasta la vista
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dude, im so not down with this rain.  my power better not go out.  but then, it goes out at the blink of an eye up here. stupid boonies...  yay i dont have to do ne hw tonight if i dont want to cuz field trip tomorrow...going to freakin salinas to go to the steinbeck museum or some shit...better than school i guess.  ugh i hate it when things change between people, esspecially when it was fine how it was.  better than fine in fact.  *sigh* :-/
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there r some stupid fucking people in this world.  what the fuck.    on a brighter note, yay go patriots!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dude, i wanna go to the mall...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AAHHHHH im undergoing looking-at-colleges overdose!! some one save me
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* awesome song...  Beauty queen of only eighteen She had some trouble with herself He was always there to help her She always belonged to someone else  I drove for miles and miles And wound up at your door I've had you so many times but somehow I want more  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved She will be loved  Tap on my window knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful I know I tend to get insecure It doesn't matter anymore  It's not always rainbows and butterflies It's compromise that moves us along My heart is full and my door's always open You can come anytime you want  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved She will be loved  I know where you hide Alone in your car Know all of the things that make you who you are I know that goodbye means nothing at all Comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tonight was a good night :)  i hung out with lauren.  we went to in and out and that was fun.  haha we were sitting there eating and lauren has her burger in one hand and her fries in the other, and her shake is in front of her and she just starts laughing and i look at her and she's like, its just so beautiful! haha it was so funny.  and then we went to see starsky and hutch.  so fuckin funny!!! great movie.  and then we didnt want to go home so we went to borronnis and sat and talked and drank hot chocolate.  good times.  im in a really good mood now cuz... well lauren knows why ;)  k well im off.  well after i post some awesome lyrics.  night all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      when depressed, buy shoes.  shoe shopping solves all :)    that was a public service announcement from the almighty sara.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if anyone knows a fast way to get $375, please tell me.  because im at a loss.  fuuuuuuuuuuuck.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just dont care anymore. i really dont.  dont ever fuckin talk to me again.    yea so hi.  i crashed my car today.  i slipped cuz the roads were wet.  it wasnt my fault really!! my bad drivin didnt get me into this one!! lol.  so yea, i get to drive the tahoe till my car gets fixed.  lucky me.  haha regina and i suck at canoing.  it was funny.  she says its cuz i cant canoe but thats not true!! but yea, canoing around and lookin at mud sure beats sitting in class.  even if it did throw out my shoulder.    well, i have a shitload of work to do, and some fuckin asshole just put me in a pissy ass mood, so im gonna go.  bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yo wassup? im in study hall. hahahahaha lauren is shoppin online for "arizona wear" and so she's like ok time to buy! and she whips out this tiny little keychain credit card.  haha i guess u have to be here, but it was funny.  grilled cheese in 20 mins!! im so bored.  nothing to do.  say hi lauren! k lauren doesnt want to say hi.  we r talkin bout what to do for jersey's bday.  fuuuuunnn stuff. baboons here we come! haha. there is a poster here with muhammed ali that says "impossible is nothing" i dont know if that means something deep that i dont get, or if his english wasnt too good and he was meaning to say nothing is impossible and it came out impossible is nothing.  yea i try to figure that out like everyday.  hmm, im a dork :-p.  ok well, im gonna go cuz this comp is pissing me off, and i might go to lunch early.  ok well bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a clean car now, yay!  well, the outside anyway...  blah, im tired and stressed.  not a good combo.  o well...not too long till summer.  then im a senior!! and then im a second semester senior, and nothing will matter anymore!!  i cant wait for that.   ok well off to do...something productive.  bye.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jen and my college search:   caliqtpi16: U HAVE TO GO TO PENN STATE caliqtpi16: U CAN MAJOR IN TURF MANAGEMENT!!!! caliqtpi16: hahahahahahahahahahaha Damsil13: HAHAHAHAHHA caliqtpi16: u can get a bachelors degree!!! caliqtpi16: wow caliqtpi16: there really is a college for everyone Damsil13: damn straight  caliqtpi16: u can also major in mining caliqtpi16: didnt mining die? Damsil13: i thought so caliqtpi16: me too Damsil13: and if not dont they have little kids in 3rd world countries that do that sort of thing?  hahaha wow, good times.  our college trip is gonna be fun.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow.  3 hour sat diagnostic test.  wow.  that was boring.  im in a daze.  wow.  stupid freaking test.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just had my first sat tutoring...y i need to spend so much time to conquer this stupid test, which is stupid in itself because it requires so much energy just to conquer, i dont know.  o well, as long as i get into college i guess... hung out with jan and ariel yesterday...that was fun.  we went to the mall and then we just got movies and came here and hung out.  ariel is the #1 barbie!!! lol.   going to see the gunn play tonight and...ya thats it.  then i need to spend THREE FUCKIN HOURS tomorrow takin this stupid diagnostic sat test.  uuuugggghhh i think id rather...well raher do ne thing really.  blah.  k well, ill ttyl.  *mwah*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey, another borig day in the life of sara.  school was school.  after school i went to palo alto with some ppl to get crapball tea, cuz i discovered that i like it without the crapballs.  Who'da thunk?  dude this university in london sent me this thing and the first thing they said was "Richmond rewards high caliber students like you with merit scholarships."  dude, these ppl think i can go study in london on a scholarship.  not gonna happen, but its nice to have options, right?    lauren and i are the latino lovers!!! haha good times, good times. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mystic river is a damn good movie  you know some people really suck at being there for u.  i mean really.  what the fuck.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo yo yo.  sup?  went snowboardin yesterday in tahoe, was hella fun.  and we taught regina to snowboard and shes so good! hehe.  dude and it was so warm.  i was snowboardin in just my t shirt.  cool stuff  leah got into priory. good for her, but poor girl.  o well maybe it will get better once carlson isnt dean ne more.  OH YEA! CARLSON ISNT GONNA BE DEAN OF STUDENTS ANYMORE!!! WOO HOO!!!!  so, i need to redy my hair cuz its turnin blonde, soo im thinkin im gonna die it dark with blond highlights.. what do yall think? lemme know.  k wellll i need to go get some work done before i have tutoring.  uuuggghhh SAT tutoring... :(  *mwah*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay i got the job!! they said they didnt even need to call me back i got it! yay!!  im gonna be hanging out with kids.  sweeeeet.  well its sorta a job, its volunteer, but yea.  yay :)   oh! and i got jen a 6 foot stuffed bunny!! well, maybe its 5 feet...but in ne case its huge!!!!! i made a huge scene tho cuz i took it off the shelf and all these huge bunnies came crashing down on me and the shelf was really high and the bunnies were really big and i tried to get them back up there but they kept falling.  yea, it was funny.    avoir mis amigos  (oooh im goin bilingual on ya!!!)  *mwah*
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eeekk got an interview in 2 hrs.  i really want to get the possition.    so i cut during study hall and lunch today with lauren and went to jamba juice.  i never do that, i dont know y i did.  i think that i wanted a jamba juice isnt a good enough reason...o well, didnt get caught so no biggie.  i need to shape up and get my act together if im gonna bring up my grades this semester. like, seriously.  well i need to get a little work done.  ill ttyl.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn dude, i havent posted in a hella long time.  :-/  yea so i was sick last week...that really sucked.  but im better now, and my voice is almost all the way back. right on.   wow, u think id have something to say after a week...but you'd kinda think wrong...  oh i have an interview at the ronald mcdonald house tomorrow. i really hope it goes well.  its so nice to have afternoons free.  i can just like go get a jamba juice or chill at starbucks, or today i went to stanford.  or i acctually have time to take a nap. nice to have some free time during the day.    ok well thats about it for today... ill talk to yall later. *mwah*
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dude i almost fainted today...that so was not cool  stats sucks.  need sleep.  leaving.  bye. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tears flow like an overdue storm falling down my cheeks, the arid mountains sunburned from too much exposure to the artificial heat of a rare winter And I see your face in the puddle they form Staring up at me with those piercing eyes as if they are tugging at my soul trying to catch the waterfall eminating from me,  the substance of your life But as they fall faster the puddle turns to a lake slowly drowning the beautiful image of you I hear you calling to me out to me as you sink down, down deeper into the creation of my sadness and fear
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey, its me.  duh.  its 11:15 and i still have several hours of homework.  but its one of those nights where it doesnt seem like i could concentrate on my homework if i tried, which i have, and i dont feel like going to sleep any time soon anyway.  so i think im gonna update u all on my life instead of continuing my futile attempt to write an essay on something i dont know about in a language i hardly speak, just to get into bed and not be able to sleep. dont u all wish u were me?  so this weekend jen and becca and i took a road trip to davis/sacramento.  IT WAS SO MUCH FUN!! first time bein all on my own, and didnt get into too much mischief.  i think thats a pretty good accomplishment.  anywho, it was a blast.  we looked at UC Davis (for jen) and then stayed in a hotel in sacramento.  uc davis was hella tight, although i dont think i could go there, its way too big.  but its like a little town, its cool.  and jen really liked it so that was cool.  and yea. hah funny things on the trip: (if ur not jen or becca i dont think ull care but i feel like recording them) roadtrip! ROADTRIP! ROADTRIP!!  yea.. i dont see that getting old... FUCK FRUITRIDGE!!! omg we r soooo making bumper stickers!! oh and I SURVIVED 5!! hahahaha the sex chair!!! EEEWWW!!! you touched the sex chair!!! you have sex on u EWW!!! hahaha *at the taco bell drive through* jen in an indian accent: excuse me we'd like 3 hamburgers... and the convo goes on hahahaha.  "a big fuck you to our country!!!"  haha CHINESE FIRE DRILL!! its like a sushi bar over here! haha wtf??? omg and so many more that i cant think of right now and that no one cares about  oh and a news update: my car officially has a name: MEL! only took like 7 months...  oh and yea jen acctually did it.  she officially turned me onto country music.  its a miracle.  i tell u, that girl has talent.  speaking of which, i have to post an awesome song.  acctually, awesome doesnt do it justice.  its great.  its the sweetest song ever written, hands down.  perfect lyrics.  (and yes, its country.  so DEAL)  Well I'll never forget the first time that I heard That pretty mouth say that dirty word And I can't even remember now What she backed my truck into But she covered her mouth and her face got red And she just looked so darn cute That I couldn't even act like I was mad Yeah I live for little moments like that That's like just last year on my birthday She lost all track of time and burnt the cake And every smoke detector in the house was going off She was just about to cry until I took her in my arms And I tried not to let her see me laugh Yeah I live for little moments like that I know she's not perfect But she tries so hard for me And I thank God that she isn't Cause how boring would that be It's the little imperfections It's the sudden change of plans When she misreads the directions And we're lost but holding hands Yeah I live for little moments like that When she's laying on my shoulder  On the sofa in the dark And about the time she falls asleep So does my right arm And I want so bad to move it Because it's tingling and it's numb She looks so much like an angel That I don't want to wake her up Yeah I live for little moments When she steals my heart again and doesn't even know it Yeah I live for little moments like that --Little Moments by Brad Paisley  omg its the sweetest song ever written.  i want to be that girl to someone, someone who doenst love me just because they think im cool and pretty (though if they thought i was cool and pretty i wouldnt complain :-p) but who loves all the little quirks about me and everything.  those little moments.  because really, thats what life is made of, and when u look back on it, its those perfect little moments, when ur lying in his arms and hes running his fingers through ur hair and whatever u were worried about before doesnt matter anymore but life is ok right then, and if you could stay like that forever, then it would just always be ok.  or when ur lost or u burned the cake or whatever and he loves u for that too.  i hope thats the case.  if so, im a fucking lucky girl.  well i am a fucking lucky girl, but yea.  ;)  anyway, i think its time to get to work.  if you r still reading you should get some kind of reward. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      howdy. que pasa?  nuthin much here.  uneventful day, but a good afternoon :).  now lots of work... arg what else is new.  THERE IS A NEW FRIENDS TONIGHT!! WOO HOO!!!! high freakin time. its been like 2 months.  but theres only 3 more till there is no more friends!!! forever!!! oh, how will i ever deal?  its a sad, sad time ladies and gentleman...  i'm goin to davis tomorrow.  that should be loads of fun :)    k time to go.  sayonara dudes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nevermind, crisis averted thanks to my AWESOME computer skills!! haha right....
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i fussed with my blog and now my comments r gone!! no!!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lordy lordy lordy.  sat diagnostic tests suck.  humans were not meant to sit in one place for 3 hrs straight, let alone think about obscure things that are not needed in life.  AND THE SAT IS IN A WEEK AND A HALF!!! AAAAHHH!!! mm hmm, im just a little stressed.  just a tad.  summer needs to hurry its ass up and come.    dude, check out this site http://www.costofwar.com/index-college-scholarships.html its hella fuckin scary.  i mean seriously, what is this world coming to?  how is it so hard to see that educating children is so much better than killing them?  and if 3 million scholarships seems too extreme, how about one million and using the rest of the money to feed and shelter those in need instead of bombing and killing them?  think about how much better the world would be if all the money that america is using to bomb iraq and all that shit went to eduacting people, or feeding hungry children,  or providing medicine so that some countries where 50% of infants die have hope for a future.  this might seem really idealistic and impossible, but there has to be some way to help instead of hurt.  some way for the powers that be to see how many scholarships and things could be made possible with the money we are using to kill people.  call me a rambling hippie, maybe i am.  but i dunno, that just kinda struck somethin in me. leave me a note and tell me what u think.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just got a letter from sarah! freakin unreal man, i havent been able to hear from her in so long.  it sounds like shes kinda changed, but shes still her.  just more...at peace with everything, haha i dunno.  but it was sooo good to get a letter from her!! and now i know she hasnt forgotten about me, lol.  and she gets to call me in june!  that will be good.  today was hectic.  missed way too much stuff when i was sick.  i want to take a nap but i have a lot of work to do.  bah.  o well.  dude i know what im gonna do! im gonna make a smoothie!! hell yea man.  ok ill talk to u lata!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      umm... what happened to that post from dc that was posted twice?  weird....
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow i need to update this more...  so im back.  what a busy week.  12 colleges in 7 days.  my faves were prob dickinson, clark, and syracuse.  i also liked tufts, dunno if thats too much of a reach for me tho.  acctually i liked a lot.  i liked ithaca too, though i was a little dissapointed cuz its been like my fave for a while and it wasnt AWESOME but tsok i still liked it.  and umm...ya.  now im home.  and swamped.  but im starting the fuck it movement, which started with catching up with lauren at starbucks tonight.  good times.  her new car is AWESOME!  muy coolio.  although im a little dissapointed in u lauren because uve gone to the other side!! but thats ok, i know ur an SUV girl at heart.  as u put it, u lost ur virginity to an suv.  haha (no people thats not literal! :-p)    went to the gunn prom last night, that was fun.  good times.  i was thinkin last night when i was just in his arms how lucky i am and how im all happy now.  hehe.  yes i know ur reading this hun, and yea u make me happy!! hehe. k im a dork but its ok.  bahaha.  :-p  and now i have to go do some hw cuz fuckin school starts again tomorrow.  bah, the seniors only have 25 more days of class! not fair man.  o well that will be me next yr.  woo hoo cant wait.  umm... k screw the fuck it movement, i think the i need to get into college movement is a little more important.  and that means i need to do hw.  fuuuuck.    well, ill see yall on the flip side! (whatever the hell that means.  i heard that today and thot it sounded cool...)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woah dude... havent updated in a hella long time.  sorry bout that...if anyone really cares.  lets see whats new? im fuckin sick right now.  seriously, i think im gonna die.  yesterday i had a fever of 103...not cool.  today it was like 100 when i woke up but now its gone so i guess thats good.  i still feel like crap tho. they thought it was strep throat but i got tested yesterday and its not... so umm... on fri i spent the night in the city with jersey cuz her bday was sat.  happy bday jersey!! shes 17 now, woo hoo.  sat we went shopping in union square...boy did we go shopping.  i bought so much.  and then sat night we partied (lauren, me, mike, jersey) for jersey's bday...haha partied pretty hard ;)  we saw some major baboons if u catch my drift!! (haha prob only lauren gets that one, but am i right lauren?? nice visit from ol' mary jane the baboon!! hahahahah!  ok enough of that)  what else.. i still dont have my car back!! peice of crap car people, i miss it!! :'(  and um.. so i leave tomorrow to go to the east coast to look at colleges... well first im going to DC for passover. i hope i feel better, all the yelling that is bound to happen due to all of my mother's side of the family all thrown into one house wont help my headache... although the fights ussually take place at thanksgiving, not so much at passover.  but then off to look at colleges.  im kinda like having a crisis about where i want to go now, cuz up until now i was lookin at small liberal arts schools, and thats primarily what im looking at over there (all but nyu which is sooo not happening)  and now i dont want to go to a small liberal arts school. but it sucks cuz the schools i want to go to are all way out of my range, and i cant really find a school that is right for me that i like and that i can go to, but i dunno i like the ones im gonna go look at so maybe ill fall in love with one, who knows. right now what i want to do (keep in mind, this changes about every other day) is go to uc santa cruz for a yr and then transfer to nyu or somewhere... but who knows.  and do i really wanna do the college app thing twice?  o well it will all work out...hopefully... i say ... a lot huh? dude erika is so fuckin funny..i just read her livejournal thing and omg that girl cracks me up!  she is way too cool to be a freshman  well and some other stuff... good stuff... that some ppl know... yea im happy... :)  um, well i need to try to venture out of bed now (dun dun duuuunnn) to pack.  uuuggghhhh... :(  yea long ass post.  im gonna go now.  bye!!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow history overload.  i like never study for one thing for so long... if i dont ace this final after my 10 PAGE OUTLINE STUDY GUIDE THING im gonna be one unhappy camper.  jen and i have too much fun studying together.  eesh.  jon is mean and is taking her from me in a little while.  :(  i think we r gonna take a nap.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo!  so jen is here... good times.  last nite we studied history till 2.  haha good times, believe it or not.  the greatest was after i was falling asleep and jen poured water on me and then she dragged me out of my closet with my pants half on telling me i couldnt go to sleep till id faught the korean war.  hahahahahaha.  yea...  so graduation was sad.  then laurens party was cool. last night we (lauren and becca and i) were gonna go to the movies, but then we were passing great america and then we decided to go there instead.  that was fun but we only got to go on one ride b4 it closed.  o well. then we picked up jen and drove around listening to caress me down lord knows how many times.  then we came home and studied history.  we were so productive! yay go us!  then this morning we woke up at NINE!! yes NINE!!! turns out the sun is up that early, who knew?  yea so then we went to school to get my history book and then had a great adventure at bianchinnis involving a baguette war and half a pound of turkey.  and... now we need to work!    jen and my letter to the UN:  to whomever it may concern: we have a proposal to solve the palistine conflict.  follow our instructions and there will be no more fighting. first, measure Jerusalem. then, make a river in the middle.  (note: make sure the middle of Jerusalem is the middle of the river, or someone will bitch that the river is on their side).  then, get a bunch of crocodiles and electric eels, and put them in the river.  there: jews and arabs and coexist in one holy and croc infested land. Respectfully yours, Sara and Jen.  o ya, sara and jen saving the world one treaty at a time  ok NOW its time to work.  BYE!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    more pics from carnival...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    more pics from carnival...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omg im so pissed.  the debate went so badly.  the other side sucks and wont even debate the correct topic -- we kept getting off on when life starts and all that and we r not there to discuss babies we r up there to discuss the womans right to choose.  not if its right but who gets to choose!!! and did we ever touch upon that ONCE??? NO!! gah and they said we were PRO DEATH!!! PRO DEATH!!! i know im just up there for my grade and all but it really is somethin i feel strongly about, so i mean callin me pro death is a personal attack.  and like my buggest pet peeve is when i have something i really want to say and people wont listen to me.  i HATE it when people wont listen to me, which is like y i got so mad, cuz no one would listen to me.  i was like screaming after class.  it takes  LOT to get me that mad and worked up.  gah.  im pissed.  and the kicker, i think they are winning.   AAAAHHHH  but then i got a chai shake.  and that made things a little better.    oh and my theology class sucks cuz they cant follow directions and put the right things in the right folders so that i can edit and compile it all.  gsh, just a stressful day.    i think its time for a well deserved nap.  good night.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Along the edges, colors blur it seemed familiar. While you read your magazine, I was counting all the markers.  And California seemed to draw you like a siren From a postcard, in a letter, or a frame of film melting.  Under you, I feel your breath move in, out slowly.  Under you, let go completely feeling you take over me. Take over me.  A Hollywood flat where we'd laugh about our fortunes  Well we had jobs in this bar down at 3rd and San Vicente. And Ramen Noodles at 4:30 in the morning,  When we barely could survive, I was never more alive.   Under you, I feel your blood flowing out slowly.  Under you, let go completely feeling you take over me. Take over me.  You moved in slow degrees A sudden memory You're a Leonard Cohen song  But every now and then I'd swear I see you standing on a sidewalk,  In a restaurant, from a taxi passing by.  Under you I feel your breath move in, out slowly. Under you let go completely feeling you take over me.  Take over me 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    found this pic in the bin of reject yearbook pics...  i think its pretty cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ben and me yesterday... so cute!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    becca jen and me yesterday... another cute pic!!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nothin like eating a half gallon of ice cream out of the carton in the middle of safeway to cheer up a friend... esspecially when said friend's mother thinks you are 7 people in a suburban. hahahahaha.  good times.  fun night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was a fun day.  in the morning we had junior senior breakfast.  that was fun.  the seniors got us picture frames with diff quotes and proverbs in each one... we got them flip flops, sorta as a symbolic shedding of the dress code apparently.  julie was sorta a bitch about it saying it was a crappy present and theirs to us was so much better... but w/e we all know shes a bitch.  then there was senior chapel... that was ok, but then there was the whole senior innitiation thing where the juniors moved into the senior seats... dun dun dun... haha that was cool.  woo hoo class of 05 movin on up!! :-p  then there was yearbook distribution... the yearbook is hella cool this year.  cool stuff.  and like the coolest pic ever of 5 of us made it in there and that was really cool.  and ummm yea.  and then there was carnival.  we made a truse (sp?) on the water fight thing... so we just hung out and signed yearbooks and fun stuff.   and then tonight i had a meeting for working at the ronald mcdonald house this summer... im working 3-6 on thursdays (while im here) sooo yea...  i need to write my spanish story.  that sucks.  ill talk to yall later 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have something to say.  cosmo magazine is totally degrading to women. they say they r all aboy women power -- bullshit!  the entire magazine is about how to change yourself in order to make men like you.  as if a woman needs to somehow conform to be what a man wants her to be.  they never once say be urself and if he doesnt like u fuck him (my personal philosophy).  no, instead they use all 314 pages to tell how what u need to do in order to make every man fall madly in love with you.  and women read this magazine religiously, every moment believing their cruel lies that they need to somehow change who they are, who they have become over their 20-something years of life, in order to please men.  it totally goes back to the old view that women need to do whatever they can to please men.  i thought we had come out of that period, but according to the most popular women's magazine on shelves, our society is still subconciously guided by these principles.   yea...im getting my english project done... 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    everyone before prom
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    las chicas before prom
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Prom!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i can put pics on here now! thats so cool! me again... ill put some other ones up eventually...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was fun.  school was fine, and then after school ben and katie and i went to starbucks and then to katies house to see her pigme goats.  yea, she has pigme goats!!!! they r goats, and they look like goats, but they r the size of a cat!!!! omg they r so cute!! and when they baaah or whatever it sounds like a little baby lol.  yea they r like the coolest thing ive ever seen.  and then the little one kept running away haha.  ben and i were getting such a kick out of them.  and then i drove ben home and bought some chips for apes tomorrow and now here i am.  and i think im acctually gonna do some work tonight *gasp* first time in a while.  after tomorrow only one more week of classes!!!! yay!!!! thursdays r so sad without friends.  the week just isnt the same.  *sigh*.  o well.  anywho, im gonna get going.... hasta la vista!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    hey! look who it is!!! well isnt this just spiffy!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CONGRATS TO ZACH FOR GETTING HIS LICENSE!!!! :-D  so, funny story.  so this morning i had a quiz on the scarlet letter, which i havent been reading.  rebeccas read it, tho, so we decided that she would go to my english class and take it for me, and id go sit in chem for her.  it would be ok on my end cuz im not sure mr tang even knows i exist, and he deff wouldnt know that im not rebecca.  so we were gonna do this and we were like walking to the classes and then becca decides no cuz ms eikmeier isnt that slow and would prolly realize.  so we didnt end up doing that, but we almost did.  k so not that funny, but hey, my life isnt too entertaining. oh and ben talked to fr maurus and made up some bullshit excuse as to why it would benifit him to come to my history class from now on instead of doing busy work in AP bio, and fr maurus bought it, so now ben gets to come to history with me :)  hehe poor kid, im such a bad influence, huh ben? hehe :-p oh and YAY FOR LAUREN!!! :-p  ok well i actually have hw today *gasp* so i think ill get crackin on that.  talk to yall lata 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was entirely uneventful.  ben skipped bio and came to history with me :)  hehe and we were throwing these thingys at eachother the whole time but i missed a couple times and hit some other ppl... lol, good times.  sadly i think thats the most interesting thing that happened to me today.  another night with hardly any hw  (or maybe just harely any hw im doing... but i really dont think i have a lot..) so i think im gonna go hang with mi novio for a bit.  yes, yes i am.  ok time to go.  later gators. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     first you were like dude!! and then u were like duuude, and then u were like duuuuuuuude... HAHAHA
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im so in love. i just thought you all should know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omg prom was so awesome.  i had a blast.  the boat was really cool (despite some rockin, lol) and goin under the bridge and all it was so pretty.  it was a lot of fun.  small dance floor but it worked out fine.  and everyone looked really pretty :) and the dj played all requests so it was really good music.  yaaa, good times.   not too much hw today.  gotta do that and then clean my car.  bath time for mel!! way beyond time for that.  i wonder what ill find... hmmm...    well im gonna get to it.  ill ttyl.  and for the love of god it wouldnt kill people to leave a comment once in a while! :-p lol bye
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG OMG OMG OMG!! i just got my SAT scores!!! i got a 1260!!! thats really good for me cuz i was aiming for a 1300 which i was like so sure i was not gonna get, and thats only 40 points away and im really happy with it.  and its above average for almost all the schools im looking at so im SOOO happy!! and for all u people who r like o no i only got a 1350 i need to retake it, screw u, cuz this is good for me!  yes sooo, that like made my day... and i got my nails done today.  french manicure (fake, hella long, haha) and my toes r painted pink to match my dress.  JERSEY, WE SO PURTY!! hehe.  omg and i got the COOLEST earings to wear to prom.  they r so big, they like go to my chin.  haha but they r so cool.  yea.  so stoked.    thhhhhats all folks! ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was entirely uneventful.  i dont think anything worth talking about happened today.  so why am i posting, you ask?  well, you raise a good question.  the answer is that im pretty good at talking about absolutly nothing.  as most of you know from unfortunate experience.   i might have another night with no hw.  wow.  what is this world coming to? tomorrow im getting my nails done with jersey for prom, and then friday is a half day and then PROM!  will rock.  i cant wait.  :-D  im really punchy right now.  im talking to jersey and i keep cracking up.  like over nothing.  lol.  im weeeeeiiiirrrd.    ok time to go.  hasta luego.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMFG the APES AP was AWFUL.  man it was so bad. i mean, some of it i knew, but some of it i was just like wtf.  and the essays...  not pretty. but o well, its over.  and the rest of my day was good. after the AP i went and got lunch with regina and susan and jen, and then we went back for F.  then i spent till 9 with Zach :)  and now i dont have any hw basically except to read (well... read the sparknotes...) for the first 10 chaps of scarlet letter... aaahhh...   im sleepy, so im gonna go.  ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They tell you where you need to go They tell you when you'll need to leave They tell you what you need to know They tell you who you need to be  But everything inside you knows There's more than what you've heard There's so much more than empty conversations Filled with empty words  And you're on fire When He's near you You're on fire When He speaks You're on fire Burning at these mysteries  Give me one more time around Give me one more chance to see Give me everything You are Give me one more chance to be... (near You)  Cause everything inside me looks like Everything I hate You are the hope I have for change You are the only chance I'll take  When I'm on fire When You're near me I'm on fire When You speak And I'm on fire Burning at these mysteries These mysteries... 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey all.  so today i skipped the first 3 periods cuz i decided my time would be better spent working on some stuff at home.  it was good, i didnt miss ne thing at school, but i got 7 pgs of english done, so now i can mainly focus on getting ready for my AP tomorrow.  man im gonna bomb that thing.  im not even kidding, i really want to pull off a 3 but i think thats wishful thinking.  *sigh* o well... cest la vie, right?  maybe mr clarks lucky gum will help.. yea he gave us cards and "lucky gum" today.  good stuff...  and prom is on firday!! yay!! something to look forward to :)  its totally gonna rock.  :-D  aight, im off.  ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ooohh... pretty new templates.... ill prolly play around for a while till i find one i like... right now i like this one :)  im going insane.  studied apes for 9 hrs today.  on top of the 7 hrs i studied yesterday.  THATS 16 HRS THIS WEEKEND!! AND IM STILL NOT DONE WITH THE 42 PAGE FINAL!! fucking insanity.  this is gonna kill me.  the AP is in... 33 hrs... i think.  omg.  im somewhere between half asleep and punchy, in a bad state to be doing hw in.  yet, i still need to somehow do this essay test (basically gotta write 7 pgs for english).  i want to die.  bad sign when u wake up stressed and feelin like u can get thru the day, right when u open ur eyes.  4 weeks and it will all be over.    o ya i decided im goin to amherst this summer.  it should be fun.  tho 5 weeks is a long time.  but o well.  well i need to go work. AAAAAAHHHHHHHH *screams head off*  bye.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its so lonely being up late by myself...  i just thought id share.  im lonely and this makes me feel like im talking to someone... or something...  k back to work.    ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  haha funny convo with jen: me: well does it smell like sex??? jen: uuuuhhh i dont know... u smell it! me: well i wouldnt know either! *looks around suspiciously* jen: right... SMELL THE CHAIR!! hahahahahahaaahh good times, good times... im laughin bout that right now, was just talkin to jen bout it, so i thought id post... love u jen!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      RACHEL DIDNT GO TO PARIS!! AND SHE TOLD ROSS SHE LOVED HIM!!! YYYAAAAYYY!!!  um yea it was the season finale of friends.... it was SOOO SAD! but it ended well... yea.  its so sad its over.  im such a dork, but it really is sad!!!  gonna miss that show.  im gonna have to resort to reruns, which ive seen every one of!!! :'(  and yea my parents are in ny, which is hella cool.  we (we being my sisters and i) r on our own for 4 days, which is hella tight.  partaay!! well, not really but thats ok.    i been so stressed.  AP next week, and im so not gonna pass.  and so much other crap going on.  end of year or almost end of year stuff and all that, just hella stress.  not to mention i get stressed over nothing, so when there is acctually something to get stressed over, it gets ugly.  yea.  well, i have soooooo much history hw its not even funny, so i gotta jet.  ill talk to yall later.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And I'd give up forever to touch you Cause I know that you feel me somehow You're the closest to heaven that I'll ever be And I don't want to go home right now   And all I can taste is this moment And all I can breathe is your life And sooner or later it's over I just don't want to miss you tonight   And I don't want the world to see me Cause I don't think that they'd understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am  And you can't fight the tears that ain't coming Or the moment of truth in your lies When everything feels like the movies Yhea you bleed just to know you're alive   And I don't want the world to see me Cause I don't think that they'd understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am    the goo goo dolls rock so much.  aahhh greatest band.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fuck.  fuck fuck fuck.  i had a review today from 5-7 for the ap, so i come home at 3 and take a nap and i set my alarm for 4:30 so id wake up and go and it didnt wake me up, so i just woke up at like 6:30.  shit, now mr clark is gonna b hella mad at me and think i just bailed on the review and i really needed it too.  fuuuuuck.  today was not a good day.  :-/  leave me some love, i need it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everyone has this on their thingy so i think ill continue the trend... dont fill it out if u dont want to, its kinda stupid, but yea im bored so reading what people have to say might be entertaining.  (fill it out in a comment... but wait... no one ever leaves me comments!!! :( ) but yea um, here.   1. Who are you?  2. Are we friends?  3. When and how did we meet?  4. How have I affected you?  5. What do you think of me?  6. What's the fondest memory you have of me?  7. How long do you think we will be friends?  8. Do you love me?  9. Do you have a crush on me?  10. Would you kiss me?  11. Would you hug me?  12. Physically, what stands out?  13. Emotionally, what stands out?  14. Do you wish i was cooler?  15. On a scale of 1-10, how hot am I?  16. Give me a nickname and explain why you picked it.  17. Am I loveable?  18. How long have you known me?  19. Describe me in 3 words  20. What was your first impression?  21. Do you still think that way about me now?  22. What do you think my weakness is?  23. Do you think i'll get married?  24. What makes me happy?  25. What makes me sad?  26. What reminds you of me?  27. If you could give me anything what would it be?  28. How well do you know me?  29. Do you wish to get to know me more?  30. Ever wanted to tell me something but couldn't?  31. Do you think I could kill someone?  32. Are you going to put this on your blog and see what I say about you?   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, you know how i said last week was the worst week?  well i lied.  this one is gonna take the cake.  aaahhh i never kne it was humanly possible to be so stressed out, and for such an extended period of time.  it needs to be summer soon, cuz i swear i may not make it.   haha its ale's bday tomorrow and i just asked her if shes gonna be home cuz im gonna go stop by with balloons and shit, and she totally forgot it was her bday.  lol she NEVER remembers her bday, shes so funny.  she also doesnt ever know how old she is.  lol.  it would have been funny if i stopped by with ballons and she still didnt remember it was her bday, she would have been like ummm u got issues girl.  lol.    i got the pics from davis! some are just plain weird, we took a lot of the sex chair.  haha.  but i FINALLY got the freakin kodac cd thingy to work on my comp.  its hella cool.  yup yup.  ok, well im off.  adios. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i got a prom dress! yay!! its soo pretty, i really like it :) but its too big, so i need to get it taken in a little.  dont ask me y i got a too big dress, its a long story.  but yea, its really pretty :) haha and ariel is never going shopping with me again.  lol, im so difficult. :-/ o well.   zach is grounded this week.  that sucks.  but at least that means i cant distract him from studying... i guess...  ummm, yea... thats it.  off to finish the great gatsby.  great book, but it kinda loses a little appeal when u have to rush to finish it.  o well.  soo ya, see yall lata
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall.  havent updated in a while.  sorry, last week was the week from hell.  test, shitload of work, 4 hour sat tutoring sessions, mental breakdowns, the list goes on.  anywho, yesterday i took the sats.  that was not fun.  but, one less thing i have to worry about.  now i just have to worry about how i did, which sucks too, but its better to worry about something u cant do anythin about cuz then its out of ur hands.  wow my mom just (as in right after i typed that) came in and gave me the sex talk.  heres the recap, word for word: mom: "it seems like you and zach are getting pretty serious, and thats great --"  me: mom we're not having sex mom: ok -- me: and we r not planning on having sex mom: ok, but that might change.  and if it does i want you think really hard about it.  and im not sure its a good idea. me: OKAY! mom: and if you decide its just something you have to do, i want you to talk to me about it so i can make sure you are safe me: uuhh... ok... [yea fuckin right] mom: BEFORE you do it me: ok.... [again, ya fuckin right] mom: promise me? me: uhh... ya... mom: sara!! me: yes!    well that was interesting.  like im really gonna tell her anyway.  i kinda feel bad promising her something i have no intention of doing, but o well.  anyway, where was i before that little interuption.  oh ya, sats.  so after the sat zach and i went to santa cruz.  that was a lot of fun.  then we just spent the day together.  good times :)  now i have to do a bunch of hw, go to a surprise party for cynthia at 2:30, then go prom dress shopping with the lovely ariel.  fun stuff.  well, except having more hw than my brain has the capacity to comprehend.  on that note, i better go do it.  its been real. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i had to go to my aunt's funeral today.  it was really sad.  i didnt think i was gonna get overly emotional because i wasnt that close to her but i got really sad.  i think it had mostly to do with all the people i am close to crying and stuff.  but yea.  it was sad, as to be expected of a funeral...  then i hung out with my cousins during the reception.  and talked to my uncle who is in social work and said he will give me a job when i finish college! woot!  we will see if that holds true in 5 years but yea.  woah, 5 years??? 5 years and im done with school and will have a career??? no way.  ok thats weird.  then i went bowling tonight with jen and jon and becca.  good times, as always.  dancing around and bowling extremely badly (though i would have won the 4th game if evil jon hadnt gotten a strike at the LAST MINUTE!!! bah!)  then we went to dennys for a minight snack, and now jen is here and we are chillin.  like a villian.  becca is passed out on the chair in her room and jen is in the kitchen eating penut butter.    tomorrow (well... today.... but yea) i have to pack and shit and then i leave thursday am!!! aaaaahhh!!   ok well thats bout it.  oh jen doesnt like the red in my hair.  that makes me sad.  o well it washes out in 6-12 washes.    now thats it.  arivadichi!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lazy day.  slept till 3.  very nice.  then hung out with jen for a bit, and then went to dinner with regina and becca at fosters freeze.  then regina and i went to the batting cages! it was so much fun!! lol i wore a catchers helmet with one of those face masks cuz i was scared a ball would hit me.  i looked funny :-p we were really bad but it was really fun.  then we went to reginas house and put red streaks in my hair.  we were gonna do her tips but never got around to that.  then fuckin drama with jason.  well it didnt have to be drama but knowin me it was.  i thought it was too much trouble to be mad at him, and now it seems its too much trouble to forgive him.  whatever.  guys suck.  then regina decided we had to hang out with him which was altogether too akward after talking to him.  but yea. whatever. i dont care anymore.    i have to go to my great aunt's funeral tomorrow in palm springs.  :(  its kinda late and i should probably get some sleep, but i dont want to.  maybe ill go watch 10 things i hate about you.    i miss zach so much.  im not gonna last 6 more weeks without him.  *tear*  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for zach:   Its a big mistake 50 days, 3 months away Id be laughing today But your voice on the phone gives me no reason  Dont take from me My heart is barely beating Dont take from me Im falling down  All I want to do is lie in bed with you All I really ever need is you All I got to do is give up all I have to be with you  Its a different day 1500 miles away Why would you want to stay? So take a look around  All I want to do is lie in bed with you All I really ever need is you All I got to do is give up all I have to be with you  All I want to do is to be close to you All I want to do is to be next to you All I want is you to give up all we had to be I cant remember why Im here If youd let me spend my life with you  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      havent updated this in a while.  nothing is really new.  im leaving tomorrow for dc and then i get back on sunday, and then im going camping monday and tuesday, and then leaving thursday and gonna go to NY with my dad for a few days, then go to my umass thing which starts next monday.  so im gone june 24- july 30.  loooong time.  tonight was really sad cuz im not gonna see zach till july 30, so like 6 or 7 weeks.  cuz hes leaving sat and isnt coming back till im gone to umass.  reeeeaaalllly sad.  :'(  but we r gonna talk on the phone every day :)  im gonna need like 100 calling cards and he is gonna have one hell of a phone bill, but its ok.    what else is new??  BFD was awesome.  yellowcard rocked.  and nfg though ive seen them now 3 or 4 times... but they are always good.  and yea everyone (almost) was good and it was a lot of fun  OH and sarah called me!  yay!!! and she is doing ok.  and im gonna get to see her in september!!! woo hoo!!!!  k um i guess thats pretty much it.  everyone needs to keep in touch while im gone, i will have my cell and AIM and all that good stuff.  MWAH!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow, interesting night last night. started off good and fun (everyone needs to read jens entry in the communal blog (planningshenanigans.blogspot.com) about our adventures mini golfing and such, cuz it was just so great and she is better at writing about it then me so just see what she has to say).  so yea that was awesome, greatest game of mini golfing ive ever played.  well "mini golf" is a stretch after all of our rule changes... and so is "playing" seein as we r so bad... but like i said, read hers.  so yea then after that, there was a MAJOR CRISIS involving a shitty bf (jen's, not mine) a pool hall, san jose, and some roads that dont really exist, a dead cell phone, and a really big fight.  i dont want to spell it all out.  it was bad.  there were tears.  it got messy.  we wont speak of it.  so yea, gonna go to lunch with jen and becca and maybe regina and maybe ben... well if we ever decide where to go.  man i love summers... wake up late, do whatever i want, stay out late... thats the life.  anyway im gonna take off.  adios. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Breathe in for luck, breathe in so deep, this air is blessed, you share with me. This night is wild, so calm and dull, these hearts they race, from self control. Your legs are smooth, as they graze mine, we're doing fine, we're doing nothing at all.  My hopes are so high, that your kiss might kill me. So won't you kill me, so I die happy. My heart is yours to fill or burst, to break or bury, or wear as jewelery, which ever you prefer.  The words are hushed lets not get busted; just lay entwined here, undiscovered. Safe in here from all the stupid questions. "hey did you get some?" Man, that is so dumb. Stay quiet, stay near, stay close they can't hear... so we can get some.  My hopes are so high that your kiss might kill me. So won't you kill me, so I die happy. My heart is yours to fill or burst, to break or bury, or wear as jewelery, which ever you prefer.  Hands down this is the best day I can ever remember, I'll always remember the sound of the stereo, the dim of the soft lights, the scent of your hair that you twirled in your fingers and the time on the clock when we realized it's so late and this walk that we shared together. The streets were wet and the gate was locked so I jumped it, and I let you in. And you stood at your door with your hands on my waist and you kissed me like you meant it. And I knew that you meant it, that you meant it 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bllllaaaaahhhhh im so bored... im acctually sitting at home doing nothing which is somethin i havent done since the summer started.. hmm ya  been hangin out with lauren a lot... and zach... fri night i hung out with zach and then slept at laurens... and then yesterday i hung out with lauren till like 2 and then went to zachs and hung out with him.  yep, good times.   so tonight my parents are having a "function" -- one of their political dinner party things.  usually i can escape these things but tonight i have to be here.  when i acctually have plans.  well, plans to make plans.  with jen who was STOLEN FROM ME by jon.  seriously uncool.  but yea.  so that will be fun (not).  but guess who is coming?? BEN!! AS IN JERRY'S FRIEND!! AS IN THE ICE CREAM MAN!! ya turns out someone my parents know knows him or something.. and hes a democrat i guess... so he is coming and bring some ice cream!! so yea thats pretty cool, so i guess its not all bad.  but man can these old democratic fogees be boring.  at least they're not republican.  :-p if anyone wants to come over and meet ben u r all invited.  *puppy dog eyes*  WE CAN CRASH THE "DEMOMRATIC FUNCTION!!  ummm... im a dork  so my room is really hot.  and i want to get out of it and go somewhere.  my sister wants to go to the mall so maybe ill be a nice sister and take her.  i miss zach.    im out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ITS SUMMER!!!!! IM A SENIOR!!!!!! WOOOO HOOO!!!!!!!!  yea, im stoked.  so yesterday i got out at 10, and then i drove around aimlessly for an hr and half cuz lauren said shed be at her house at 11 and wasnt!!!! but then i met up with lauren and mike and ryan and becca and we went to great america.  good times.  except for mike sucks to have riding shotgun.  and he tickles u on rides.  :-p  then last night we just chilled.  and this morning i had to get up to go to a meeting... blahh... im now im just hanging at home bored.  jen is MIA.  as usual!  gah.  yay for lauren!! she has a bf!!! yay!! and hes cool and she likes him and he likes her and its all great.    well, im boring today.  so im gonna go.  hasta la pasta  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, the history final thuroughly sucked.  i studied way too much for it to have been that hard.  :(  o well.  i find out how i did tomorrow... eek..  just an english final tomorrow, which i am hours and hours from being ready for, and then im done!! YAY!!!  but gettin thru this english final is gonna be quite a feat...  so, my aunt is really sick, and has been for a while, and shes gettin really bad. and my dad just told me that they decided that they are going to disconect the feeding tube, which means she is gonna die in like a week or 2.  really sad.  sadder for a lot of other people who r a lot closer to her, but yea, sad.   speaking of sad, so becca and regina find this one eyed dog today and they call the shelter who has them call the police and the police took it away!!! they just like dragged this little one eyed dog by the collar and that was the last they saw of it. i dont know y but that made me sad.  maybe its just that time...   omg i have to tell u the sweetest thing.  Jen's bf shows up at her door last night with 2 roses (he didnt have the money for a dozen but he didnt want to give her just one) all the way from SAN CARLOS which is like AN HOUR from her house to say hi and he hoped she did well on her finals.  HOW FUCKIN SWEET IS THAT?? yea,  i thought so too.  so lets see.  i need to write an essay on various relationships in american lit, complete with quotes that i need to MEMORIZE and then either change my essay on symbolizm in scarlet letter or wrte a new one on somethng else.  that sucks.  beyond belief.  and im tired. and lazy.  AND SO READY FOR THS YEAR TO BE OVER.    one more day. just an hour and a half. i can do it.  right??  i think so...  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      o lordy.  ths history final is worse than i thought.  and i was already thinkin it was gonna be pretty bad.  only one person in A period got an A and that was tim who doesnt count cuz he always gets As.  ahh... apparently just knowing all the stuff from tbhe book isnt good enought -- great, what did i study all weekend then? o well, i guess i should stop bitching and study... im not really sure what i should study, but i cant just sit here.  got prom pics today.  they are ok.  maybe ill scan them into here a little later.  2 more days... i can do it!!!  aight, im off to freak about my history final and study for english.  and then freak some more. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just dyed my hair... kinda fucked up the hightlights :-/  o well.  it still looks ok.  lauren is here, we r having a hair dying extravaganza.  we just died her hair like maroon.  shes rinsing out the dye now.  ahh i hope it doesnt look bad!!!  so yea i studied all day and then went to kinkos to make my spanish book an acctual book, then came home and slept for like an hr then lauren came over and we dyed my hair.  then we went out and we brought zach a starbucks and bought hair dye for lauren.  then we came back and did my highlights and dyed laurens hair.  eventful day...  lol after i got back in the car after giving zach his starbucks and stuff she was like awww u have the cutest sweetest bf :) hehe ya.. i love zach :)  anywho, its late, and i still need to get up in the am even tho i dont have to do anything at school all freakin day!! how pointless!!!! just let me sleep damnit!  o well, after thursday its all over! woo hoo!! cant wait.  ok, well, been real.  im off.  *pray for laurens hair!!*
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A hundred days have made me older Since the last time that i saw your pretty face A thousand lies have made me colder And i don't think i can look at this the same But all these miles that seperate  Disappear now when i'm dreaming of your face &nbsp; I'm here without you baby But you're still on my lonely mind I think about you baby And i dream about you all the time I'm here without you baby But you're still with me in my dreams And tonight it's only you and me &nbsp; The miles just keep rollin' As the people leave their way to say hello I've heard this life was overrated But i hope that it gets better as we go &nbsp; I'm here without you baby But you're still on my lonely mind &nbsp;I think about you baby And i dream about you all the time I'm here without you baby But you're still with me in my dreams And tonight girl its only you and me &nbsp; Everything i know,and anywhere i go It gets hard but it wont take away my love And when the last one falls  When it's all said and done  It gets hard but it wont take away my love &nbsp; I'm here without you baby But you're still on my lonely mind I think about you baby And i dream about you all the time I'm here without you baby But you're still with me in my dreams And tonight girl its only you and me 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leavin all the fights and all Summers getting colder Drive all night to hold you tight Back to California &nbsp;--sugarcult 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    laura lookin soo cute!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    yours truly
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me, jyoti, chelsea, alexandra, and ceci before the club
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my lovely roomate, nicole
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    nicole, me, becca
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    nicole and jyoti
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    allegra, leyla, alexandra, and chelsea before the luau
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    chillin in boston (jyoti, alexandra, allegra, me, nicole, chelsea, laura)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me, laura, leyla
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    chillin (alexandra, becca nicole, leila, me, laura, helen)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nevermind on the pics.&nbsp; ill post them some other time.&nbsp; goodnight all &nbsp; and yay lauren is an adult now!!! happy bday lauren :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey.&nbsp; tis me.&nbsp; all alone.&nbsp; cuz my roomate is in new york.&nbsp; kinda nice, but kinda lonely.&nbsp; i went clubbin tonight, it was a lot of fun.&nbsp; yep yep.&nbsp; and tomorrow im spendin the day with my mom which should be nice.&nbsp;  &nbsp; i feel like puttin some pics up of my awesome friends.&nbsp; so i will.&nbsp; but i havent quite figured out how to put up more than one pic in the same post, i dont quite know if thats possible.&nbsp; so its gonna take a couple posts.&nbsp; but yea, here r some pics... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall.  sup on da west side?  i hear im missing good beach weather... that blows... it freakin rains in summer on this side of the country... who knew?  ah oh well, its still cool over here.  my mom is comin to see me on saturday, that will be cool.  i miss everyone a lot, maybe seein her will make that better.  though i want to see my friends and zach and everyone.  miss u guys tons.  whoever u guys are... if anyone reads this... hmmm.    dude i fuckin bombed my apes ap.  not cool.  i wasnt expecting to do well, but it would have been nice if i had done at least decently.  ah well, such is life (as my friend laura over here always says.  shes a kick. shes from jamaica.  lots of people over here are really cool.  ill get into them later when im not being annoying and keeping my roomate up.  i do that a lot.  not sure shes too keen on me.  ah well. cool girl.) that was a long parentheses.  well like i said, my roomate is trying to sleep so ill wrap it up.  id love to hear from u guys, i miss u all.  dont party it up to hard without me now... ;)  later gators
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i got the goo goo dolls cd today... it kicks major butt  im bored. my roomate is asleep.  she is always asleep.  maybe ill go to sleep soon.  call me people.  i miss u guys tons!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She's a good girl, loves her mama Loves Jesus and America too She's a good girl, crazy 'bout Elvis Loves horses and her boyfriend too  It's a long day living in Reseda There's a freeway runnin' through the yard And I'm a bad boy cause I don't even miss her I'm a bad boy for breakin' her heart  And I'm free, free fallin' Yeah I'm free, free fallin'  All the vampires walkin' through the valley Move west down Ventura Boulevard And all the bad boys are standing in the shadows All the good girls are home with broken hearts  And I'm free, free fallin' Yeah I'm free, free fallin' Free fallin', now I'm free fallin', now I'm Free fallin', now I'm free fallin', now I'm  I wanna glide down over Mulholland I wanna write her name in the sky Gonna free fall out into nothin' Gonna leave this world for a while  And I'm free, free fallin' Yeah I'm free, free fallin'   best song ever written... im gonna learn how to play it on the guitar!!! well if ceci ever gets around to teaching me.... but yea... its free fallin by tom petty btw for those freaks who dont know....  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woah dude.  long time no post.  yall prolly thought i died or somethin... anyway, im in mass... its really cool.  i take psych in the am for college credit... its a lot of work but its interesting.  then i take improv in the afternoon... fun stuff the people here are soo cool.  ive made a lot of really cool friends.  yup yup.  so im havin a good time... lol not much to say...  well, i miss u guys!!! so call me or somethin!! or if u find urself in the western mass area, drop by for a cup of coffee ;)  hasta la vista
     
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha so last night we r driving around...  Sara: *playng with the handcuffs in laurens backseat* lauren?  if i put these on myself and i made them really tight and they hurt, would you take the keys out of your car so i could have the handcuff key to unlock it? Lauren: yea Sara: really? you would? Lauren: yup Sara: wow, thats the mark of a true friend.  pull over to unlock my handcuffs. Lauren: I wouldnt pull over, id wait till i got to where i wanted to be. Sara. oh... fuck u then!!  various inuendos going on about sara's big cup and lauren stroking jed's (laurens car's) stick and jen sucking Lauren: *Pulls out her home run cherry pie* IM ABOUT TO HAVE A HOME RUN!  k u had to be there...  CARESS ME DOWN!!  this is sara signing off.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so we're sittin here trying to be productive and failing so what do we do when we stop being productive?....that's right we become random......complretely and utterly lost in the works of our random minds.....take my friend becca over here.....to the left of me actually....yes well thinks it would be nice....nay COOL....if she had "a whole suit of magnet" so that when she went into a magnet room she could float....like a big floating ball of becca...and magnet....says sara...to my right....ok im done...good day
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaha funny things happen when jen and i are up late studying history:  Damsil13: ok u me and a bunch of dead dudes Beccs116: sounds like a real party Damsil13: hahahha yea u never kno Beccs116: therye not too hot Damsil13: HAHAHAHA Damsil13: LOL Damsil13: dude thats the best pun ever Beccs116: get it cuz dead people are cold Damsil13: hahahah ok u killed it Damsil13: hahah u  killed  it    Beccs116: breakfast tomorrow Beccs116: be there Beccs116: dont be a waffle Damsil13: HAHAHAHA Beccs116: theyre square right? Damsil13: hahahha yea Damsil13: i think so 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SOMEONE PLEASE TEACH ME THERMODYNAMICS!!!....please???
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and sara. sara too.  gosh im always left out... :-p haha just kidding.  this will be fun...
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok this is the new communal blog created by Jen and Rebecca. If you want to be in on the action let us know. otherwise just come and read our valuble life lessons.  ~Rebecca~
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay jen!! im so happy old rusty is back. its so exciting. i did enjoy being your taxi though, so maybe i can drive you around for old times sake anyway.... yeah dude but is so cool he/she/it is back and driving through those sprinklers was so fun! yay ok yeah you are MIA by the way and its not cool. hey that rhymes.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      RUENITED AND IT FEELS SO GOOOOOOD.....REUNITED LIKE I KNEW WE COULD......or sumthin like that.....thats an old song by the way...i didnt just make that up...but anyway onto bigger and better things such as.... OLD RUSTY IS BACK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!BACK WITH A VENGEANCE! MWAHAHAHAHA but seriously im so happy you have no idea. i have rules though, for hte new transmission....cause it has to get "broken" in so yea....i cant go over 65 for one....WHICH SUX MY ASS....cause if you kno me u kno that i have the need for speed....corny but oh so true....so yea it sux....oh nad dude so i was on the freeway yesterday and these assbites KEPT honking at me....i was even in the slow lane for godsake....its like ok usually i would be one of those said assbites but if you think about it i WAS in the slow lane and i WAS going the speed limit....i had to purposely get behind one of those big rigs so i could blame the lack of speed on him....im devious like that....yea so that was hella annoying...but anyhoo MY TRUCK IS BACK....i need to throw a party in the back of my truck...like a reunion party....all who read this are invited....so the party will be in my truck.....and then we'll migrate somewhere cooler and then yea have a bash in its honor....maybe i'll even put banners on its sides for all to see!....dude totally..ok you people have to help me now! Gotta get back to cleaning...lata gatas 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was just attacked by a fold up hamper. no joke. the thing exploded and smacked me in the face. my chin will never be the same. my mom told me she got me a laundry bag, but no!! it was a lethal weapon!!!!!!! at least sara got a good laugh out of it....
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BAHAHAHA I AM THE MASTER!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im jen!! i have a name now!!! bahaha yay :)  thanks to sara. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im becca.  i have my own name now.  thanks to sara.  the ms. fix-it.  stay tuned for jen!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I dont like Asia.  I mean ive never been there, but i dont like it.  The people are fine, but their country sucks."  Im not even gonna touch that one...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo loyal fans....ok fine im kidding myself we probably dont have any loyal fans. although if you are maybe you should comment. ok well thats not the point. lovely jen and jon seem to have fixed the thing about my name so this should say "becca" at the bottom. how nice. i have a name now. lets see if it works, shall we?
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so when we all get together to have lunch, its interesting to say the least.  namely Jon:  Jon: i can break them up everyone else: no, no we've tried Jon: oh i wasnt thinking of conventional ways... i was thinking more along the lines of a napsack and a baseball bat  Mike: K I'll buy the plane ticket, you take care of the rest Jon: Plane ticket? i was gonna strap his ass to a donkey!  Jon: sweetie, LET GO! hes gonna hit himself and hes gonna go home with a black eye and his mom is gonna be like what happened? and hes gonna be like i punched myself in the face with a ketchup bottle.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hah. you have the power to make fake things in my name and i have the power to delete them! muahaha! clever though, jen. very clever. and i want to know how to make it say my name, since you got it to!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      k so becca has to be the shenanigans and use this account cuz she doesnt have a blogger account... unless she still has her old one... but jen as long as u joined, just sign in as u and not as our name, and then this blog will be there, and it will ay posted by jen, or whatever ur name on there is.   I GOTTA HEAR ABOUT THIS BRADY CHARACTER!!! ASAP!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn jen, this whole name thing didnt work cuz now we are both the shenanigans. oh well. its a cool name. sounds like u had fun at the lake, and yes you came through. :-D. ok yay happiness.  ~Rebecca~
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so I just checked my email....will this sign my name now....will i no longer be known as the shenannigans and upgrade to my true and rightful name? who knows....the shadow do...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmmmmm well it seems my boyfriend is gettin around on here. Just what have y'all been up to while i was gone hmmmm? Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm? jk anyhoo I went to Jersey's lakehouse/cabin thingie which was fricken awesome. We went skinny dipping at like 12!!!!!! Midnight that is. But yes it was fun....fricken cold though....but fun. So I've decided that when on a floatie I go the pace of a pregnant snail in its third trimester. So yea just thought you should know these things. Oh something kinda cool there was this doe...as in a deer....a female deer...lalalal...ok anyway...that was living under hte cabin....yea scared the living shit out of us like twice...but it was fun. So yea....yea..... BECCA I CAME THROUGH!!!!!! ok that was lame....but yea....ttyl ~Jen
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well this whole making my own name thing didnt work out so well. not for lack of jon trying though (thanks jon). so oh well, when it says "the shenanigans" thats just me (Rebecca). that can be my name. theyre planning me....i guess...never mind that doesnt work. ok im off
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyyyy so now we it says who posted where it says posted by at the bottom.  so this should say posted by sara.  k so now u know who is posting (whoever you are, if we even have any readers out there)  thanks jon.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so im pickin up where jen left off (hi, its sara now).  so anyway, she didnt finish talking about that one stupd hole... this stupid site only lets u post a little at a time.  so anyway. i bowl my ball (after hitting it in the water 3 times) and am all excited that it made it over the stupid bridge.  so i look up and see jen bounding backward, inches away from the water, golf club in hand, yelling "ILL SAVE IT!! COME BACK YOU DAMNED BALL!!" so this was all too much.  so i plop down on my ass in the middle of the hole, (in the puddle the whole fiasco created none the less) and im laughing hysterically and im like I... HAVE... TO... PEE!!! but i was laughin so hard i couldnt get up.  wow, lots of weird stares.  so we FINALLY finish this hole, and on the next. so this next hole is one of those windmill things.  and see you have to just get it over this hump and hit the windmill and then ur ball comes rolling out underneath (these caused some issues, namely not beng able to find the place where our balls came out, but thats another story) so anyway, on this windmill one, there is this little door in the windmill and if you make it in there its a hole in one. not an easy feat mind you.  so jen, thinking she was safe seeing how badly i was playing, was like if you get it in that little door, you can have a hole in zero!! so what do i do? I HIT IT IN THE DOOR ON MY FIRST TRY!!! yea, it was awesome.  so i get a hole in zero.  haha and then the people who started like half an hour after us caught up to us (yea we were playing pretty slowly what with all the interuptions and rule changes.  see, jen plays where if you hit it out of bounds u get to start back at the begining and ur back at one.  so i hit it out on like my 8th try (yes most people play where you stop at 6... we play where u stop at 15... and then we started playing where if you get to 15 you can start counting backwards) so yea i hit it out and what happens?  i put it back at the begining and im back at my first hit.  good rule.) so ANYWAY these people caught up to us so we needed to start playing faster.... oh yea and then jen is standing in the middle of the hole on the phone and i hit my ball and it totally smacked her in the ankle, and shes like FUCK YOU and we look up and there were a lot of little people there.  yea....  so it was fun.  except, acctually, it sucked, because the clown left.  thats right people, no more clown.   if you read all of both of these entries, who the fuck are you and whay dont you have a life???? yea... you can comment, though you you are probably speachless by now  ps. jen likes you. she says you are dedicated. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so weird things happen when Sara and I hang out. Take Golfland for example. Miniature golfing, good ol' family fun....fun for everyone really. You'd think that Golfland would be safe from us. You really would....but they made one vital mistake...yes, yes my friends they made a bridge. With water. Underneath it. BIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIG MISTAKE BUDDY! So sara and i are just playin a nice friendly game of golf when all of hte sudden we find ourselves at this watery hole. So I go and hit it over np. Then there was Sara. Sara my freinds has "issues" with hitting the ball and not the astroturf. In fact, from now on we'll have to call her one wrist sara due to an unfortunate golfing incident. When she did hit it though, she hit it in the water and went "fishing". Like literally. The ball went under the bridge and what does sara do? Use her hand to get it out you say? Yea, wrong. She uses her golf club and says "Im going fishing" Really now. Then she gets to start over back at one cause see I play that if you hit it out of bounds you get to start over. I think its ingenius, most think it cheating. To hte latter I say fuck you! Ok so anyway I suggest to Sara to bowl it over, so she goes throws back her arm and lets that sucker fly. Well, unfortuanetly she let it fly a little too hard and so it went over but hit hte back of the course and then came barreling back towards hte bridge. Seeing its immediate danger I went barreling over, golf club at the ready...like a hockey player i was....except that in tryin to rescues sara's shot I forgot that I would be rrunning over a bridge and as such almost fell in to the little river. Luckily though time slowed down in one of those RUUUUN FOOOOOOREEEEESSSSTTTT RUN moments and I saved my ass and sara's ball. It was brilliant, bloody brilliant. Ok so all that drama was just one hole.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it wasnt my idea for that to be our name, in fact it was jens and i just happened to agree...but anyway i decided that it was stupid a while ago and tried to change it but these people dont let you change your name thingy...at least im not computer literate enough to figure out how one might do such a thing. so i guess we are stuck with this name. oh well.  ~Rebecca~ p.s. why do we have to scroll down so far to see this stuff?? someone fix it!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you guys... its really stupid that our name on here is the shenanigans... like it says posted by the shenanigans... cuz we arent shenanigans, we are just up to shenanigans.  it should be like the shananigan planners or the weirdos or i dont know.  or we can jsut leave it cuz it doesnt really matter.. but yea becca is a dork  ~*Sara*~
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *HUG!!!*  you remind me of the donkey in shrek: oh man, I CANT FEEL MY TOES!! wait, i dont have any toes!!! i need a hug :(  haha that was sooo lame since i just asked jon to ask u what that quote was... but then i remembered it so its all good  yes, yes we are weird jen.  in fact, not sure ive met too many people weirder.  if i did i think they would scare me.  yup yup.  well we are both talkin to ur bf right now cuz HE JUST STOLE YOU FROM ME!!! oh i am so getting you back bitch.  just u watch!!  ummm... BYE!!  ~*Sara*~
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so dude...don't think I ever got your message sara...did I end up helping you? hmmm....perplexing...okay so yea sara you and I are really weird. That's all I think I really have to say.....hahaha....okay that was just lame...fucking sweatshirts.....damn neckholes shrink on yea....i have a headache.....i need a hug ~Jen
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      JEN!!!! WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU??!!?? I NEEEEEED YOU!!!!! YOU THINK DEEPLY AND WE NEED TO THINK DEEPLY FOR THIS DAMNED HISTORY FINAL! YOU ARENT PICKING UP YOUR PHONE!! AND THE MAN TELLS ME U HAVE NO MORE MINUTES ON UR CELL PHONE!! o wait, that means u cant call me. unless u can call out of area now.  which i dont think u can uuuhhhh... o well u wont be reading this anyway.  but if you are, I NEEEEEDDDDD YOU!!!!!!  ~Sara the fucked
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so becca god im so sorry........i just got ur text too.....i dont know if you left a voicemail but if you did i cant check it....i dont even have enough moola for that....but anyhoo yea so call me tommorrow at around eight pm your time if you can......actually anytime from eight on and we'll talk about stuff.....CAUSE I FUCKIN MISS YOU! AND UR 3,000 MILES AWAY AND SAD...that is not right....and i cant drive old rusty to see you!....well i could....but ...hahha yea what am i saying? old rusty wouldnt make it to the ca border....tee hee....not to mention i dont have money to buy more minutes for my phone and im gonna spend what like hundreds of dollars on gas? wow i think these things through....yea so yea......one min....SARA: CALL ME TOO! ur time slot is anywhere from 5-8 pm ur time....hahahahha time slots...this is great....ok so yea.....my arms hurt....i feel like an old granny...call me maisy and put me to pasture cause im done........OMG THERE ARE SO MANY FUCKIN HOT GUYS AT HTE&nbsp; GYM......hmmmm i wonder if jon reads this....lol......AND I THINK THEY'RE HOT....ME!!!! That says something....lol....ok well later :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow Jen, wow. All im going to say is that im going to the gym with you when i get back. so dont break the trend cuz im gonna join you. whatever this desease is that you have, its contagious online or some shit cuz im cathing it too. OH GOD WE ARE ALL GOING TO DIE!! anyway, IM GOING TO SEE YOU IN 2 DAYS!!! YAY!!! WOO HOO!!!! actually 3 because its jons bday on friday so i wont tear you away from the celebrations. im off to go write a manifesto even though i have no idea what the fuck a manifesto is....  *by the way, this feeling isnt going away. i cried myself to sleep again last night*  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this person who calls themselves jen: what have you done with my friend?? the real Jen! WHO WOULDNT GO TO THE GYM IF YOU PAID HER IN SLURPEES! jen ur sick honey.&nbsp; ill be home soon and give u whatever meds ur not allergic to.&nbsp; this is serious.&nbsp; very, very serious. in other news... YES, I AM ALMOST HOME! WOO HOO! ALERT THE MASSES! yea... im excitied, i miss u so much!  well i need to o study for a fuckin psych test, see u soon! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ATTENTION FELLOW WRITERS: My cell has no minutes left and I'm lonely. CALL ME.....that is mostly all..........ummmm........yea so YOURE ALMOST HERE....UR ALMOST HOME......THREE MORE DAYS.....YAYAYYAYAYAYAYAYAYYAYAYAYAAY.....in case you cant tell im having withdrawal issues.....yes yes well....ummmm....god damn i have nothing to say....dude OH DUDE IVE BEEN GOING TO THE GYM!!!!!! ME!!!!!!!! JEN!!!!!!! Good god what is this world coming too. So yuppers hit me up word yo! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i sorry.&nbsp; really.&nbsp; :( he an asshole who should have his manlyhood cut off before he can use it on anyone else.&nbsp; i think that should be allowed.&nbsp; or we could just do it in a back alley somewhere... i like where this is going... 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "REMEMBER YESTERDAY- WALKING HAND IN HAND LOVE LETTERS IN THE SAND- I REMEMBER YOU THROUGH THE SLEEPLESS NIGHTS AND EVERY ENDLESS DAY I'D WANNA HEAR YOU SAY- I REMEMBER YOU"   someone shoot me. now. life sucks ass. *tear*   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i cant get over it. i should. i know i should. but i cant. shit 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      caliqtpi16: if u talk to jen tell her i mean it caliqtpi16: dont be a lover without a safty cover caliqtpi16: no glove no love caliqtpi16: shes not responding Beccs116: hahaha Beccs116: yeah shes eating jons food caliqtpi16: oh caliqtpi16: ok caliqtpi16: so tell her i mean it Beccs116: yeah she knows caliqtpi16: i dont want to be aunty sara Beccs116: i told her dont do anything i wouldnt do caliqtpi16: well... Beccs116: but that might limit her... Beccs116: ok  caliqtpi16: that doesnt leave much Beccs116: dont do anything you wouldn't do Beccs116: hows that 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damsil13: EW Damsil13: EW Damsil13: EW Beccs116: what??? Damsil13: i jsut saw like the ugliest guy on my computer Beccs116: hahahahahaha Damsil13: picture michael jackson crossed w/ raissa Beccs116: where was this guy Beccs116: HAHAHAHAHA Beccs116: OMG Damsil13: im not even kidding Beccs116: dude have u been watching freak porn? Damsil13: WTF Damsil13: HAHAHAHAH Beccs116: well whered u see him? Damsil13: lol no i saw him on a pop up Beccs116: ah ha Beccs116: a "pop up" Damsil13: i did!  Damsil13: yes Damsil13: for freak porn 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damsil13: I Damsil13: WILL Damsil13: BE Beccs116: whew Damsil13: BACK Beccs116: yes im sure you will Damsil13: with a vengence! Beccs116: with a vengence Beccs116: OMG Damsil13: HAHAHHA Damsil13: LOL! Damsil13: HAHAHAHAHHAHAAHAH Beccs116: WE ARE SO ON THE SAME WAVELENGHT Beccs116: DUDE Damsil13: dude!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Beccs116: by the way it took me lkie 10 minutes of writing and rewrithing that word Beccs116: and i still spelled it wrong Damsil13: me too Beccs116: no not vengence Damsil13: wait Damsil13: oh Damsil13: jajaa Beccs116: wavelength Damsil13: jajaj? Damsil13: haha Beccs116: hahahha Beccs116: jajaa? Damsil13: wow that happens a lot to me Damsil13: fuck ou Damsil13: ou/ Damsil13: shit Beccs116: hahaha Beccs116: shti! Beccs116: aaahh 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i officialy have delayed responses to posts on here....but sara honestly how long have you been taking drama? how many shows have you perfomed? and you ask for luck?! LUCK?! U ASK TO BE WISHED LUCK?! You should know better! iT'S BREAK A TOE! God woman honestly i dont know why i put up with you.....hahaha oh yea i remember now.......woooo doggy u make a mean salsalito turkey sandwich.....but still......im not angry with you sara., im just dissapointed.  P.S. BREAK A TOE! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      that is so lame. mine so wins. frito lay does NOT own krispy kreme. fat kids love krispy kreme 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok now i see its an all an all out war up in here....well UR ALL GOING DOWN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! CAUSE I LOVE YOU LIKE THE FATTEST KID IVE EVER SEEN (600LBS) LOVES HTE WHOLE FRITO LAY INDUSTRY! Now this is why that kicks ass: FRITO LAY OWNS EVERYTHING A FAT KID COULD EVER WANT AND IS INTERNATIONAL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! MWAHAHAHAHHAAHHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAH.....ok that is all 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yall. sorry my internet was down for a while. anyway, I LOVE YOU LIKE ALL THE FAT PEOPLE EVER LOVE THE ENTIRE WORLD!! ALL THE CHOCOLATE AND CAKE AND DONUTS AND SHIT IN THE ENITRE WORLD!! no one can beat that. i am the ultimate winner. yay. (p.s. jen doesnt count because shes a genius and i cant compete with a genius.) (p.p.s. both the times i wrote genius in that last sentance i first spelled it jenius. im speshul.) ok, anyway, back to the post. sara: Sayonara dude is from the channel 104.9 work release program commercial. See ya on the flip side i interpet to mean when the moon and sun flip sides and its morning. (all this creative writing shit does weird things to my brain and i start thinking deeply and shit....weeeeeeeeird) Jen: my classes are as follows:  Drama through the ages/writing for theatrical performance  English  Humanities  Apes  Global Issues/ Weight trainging (im dropping both of those)  Religion in film and lit  &nbsp;  i dont know if thats the actual order because apparently this wasnt a real schedule so much as a list of classes that i will be taking so i dont know how the inner workings of ms martin's head....work. K, anywhosers (yes jen ANYWHOSERS. hahahaha your mable comment was priceless. hahahahahha priceless. thats another old people word!!!) i have a short story to write and im a bit behind on that. by the way i think i have used more parenthases in this post that ive ever used in my entire life. oh yeah and another by the way: i get to take a feild trip to time magazine tomorrow for my journalism class. yay that should be cool. ok, by yall. shit im talking like richard 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAYAYAYYAAYYA.....If these are written the way they'll end up being than i FINALLY have a class with you sara!!!!!!!!!! ok well here's my sched:  psych/writing for theatrical performance AP Calc english humanities religion/econ AP Bio APES 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yall. sorry my internet was down for a while. anyway, I LOVE YOU LIKE ALL THE FAT PEOPLE EVER LOVE THE ENTIRE WORLD!! ALL THE CHOCOLATE AND CAKE AND DONUTS AND SHIT IN THE ENITRE WORLD!! no one can beat that. i am the ultimate winner. yay. (p.s. jen doesnt count because shes a genius and i cant compete with a genius.) (p.p.s. both the times i wrote genius in that last sentance i first spelled it jenius. im speshul.) ok, anyway, back to the post. sara: Sayonara dude is from the channel 104.9 work release program commercial. See ya on the flip side i interpet to mean when the moon and sun flip sides and its morning. (all this creative writing shit does weird things to my brain and i start thinking deeply and shit....weeeeeeeeird) Jen: my classes are as follows: Drama through the ages/writing for theatrical performance English Humanities Apes Global Issues/ Weight trainging (im dropping both of those) Religion in film and lit  i dont know if thats the actual order because apparently this wasnt a real schedule so much as a list of classes that i will be taking so i dont know how the inner workings of ms martins head....work. K, anywhosers (yes jen ANYWHOSERS. hahahaha your mable comment was priceless. hahahahahha priceless. thats another old people word!!!) i have a short story to write and im a bit behind on that. by the way i think i have used more parenthases in this post that ive ever used in my entire life. oh yeah and another by the way: i get to take a feild trip to time magazine tomorrow for my journalism class. yay that should be cool. ok, by yall. shit im talking like richard
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yea and heres my classes (i dont know my exact schedual, like what classes are what period, but yea) &nbsp; drama throughout the ages/writing for theatrical performance psych/econ theology/film and lit english 12 chem humanities 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH OH OH well everyone knows dutch chocolate is better than german chocolate, so I LOVE YOU LIKE THE GROSEST FATTEST KID IN THE WHOLE WORLD (THINK FAT BASTARD 30 YRS AGO) LOVES THE GREAT NATION OF HOLLAND!&nbsp; i just almost wrote dutchland...&nbsp;  HAHAHAHAH about the anywhosers game thing.&nbsp; dude im totally laughin.&nbsp; i think my roomate now thinks im weirder than she already did which im not sure is even possible... &nbsp; anyway, just poppin in to say hello.&nbsp; i have to go get ready cuz im in an improv show tonight!! aaahh!! wish me luck!  &nbsp; sayonara dude.&nbsp; (what is that from???) 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anywhosers? Sorry I just caught that one in ur post becca....anywhosers......sounds like some old fogey game...."hey mable whachu wanna play ternight?" "anywhosers...its hte cats meow" "aaaaw quit ur sass talk" "go suck an egg grandma!" ok so yea im done.....thats a phrase by the way...i didnt make it up...it goes "teaching ur grandmother to suck eggs"...i dont get it....do you guyz get it? its supposed to signify when ur teaching a master or something that certain thing. Like if i tried to teach a world famous chef to cook....so yea....really dont get it... 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hah! You really thought you could defeat me? NEVER! MWAHAHAHAHAHHAH. Ok here it is: I LOVE YOU LIKE THE FATTEST KID LOVES ALL OF GERMANY. BOOOYAAAHHHH GRAAAANDDDMMMAAAA! beat that! you so cant....ive got german chocolate on my side...mwahahaha....ok so yea......so nuthin much has been goin on.....im reminding myself of a beached whale....just lying around....occassionaly trying to flip over....failing......spurting water....yes yes....i need that whale shirt of urs sara...u kno the one.....hahahha yea so anyhoo CALI IS FUCKIN AWESOME....hint hint.....ok ummm what is there to say? things w/ jon r goin good.....he's...well.....he's jon....hahhaaha so yea that explains that part of my life.....ummm yea so post ur classes u guyz so i can compare and shit........ok well i wanted to make this more interesting and longer but yet again i was forced to become a lumpy potato.....you know something funny? i cant think of potatos anymore as they should be thought of....all i can picture now is my former phone...hahahhha ok yea so gots to go...lata gataz 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if yall wanna see some pics i put some up on my blog... jen i know you are still trying to top my awesome hershey comeback... mwahahaha 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok ok ok i got it... I LOVE YOU LIKE THE FATTEST KID IN THE WORLD LOVES THE ENTIRE CITY OF HERSHEY, PENNSYLVANIA!!&nbsp; yea, take that 50 cent!!&nbsp; lol anywho... its finally a nice day here in the ol MA, really hot.&nbsp; so jen ill see if i got my schedual tonight... hopefully we have a class together for the first time in like 3 yrs!! or however long it been since freshman yr!!! when we only had crap geometry together.&nbsp; o well.&nbsp; i remember u had a 95.7 in that class and it was back when we listened to Z (remember that horrible station? that only played like 5 songs over and over?&nbsp; man im glad that got kicked off the air.)&nbsp; but yea, im bored cuz all my friends are in boston, and i stayed behind to have lunch with my mom.&nbsp; call me sometime.&nbsp; oh i need to send u that bowling in canada card.&nbsp; thats a hoot.  and hi to becca too.&nbsp; i hope ur having fun over there.&nbsp; stop meeting guys!! if anything happens i wanna hear about it.&nbsp;  wellllll ill talk to yall on the flip side! (what the hell does that mean anyway???) 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so lesson for the day: no more reading blog in library....get weird stares when one starts crackin up......yes yes well hmmm what is there to say but I LOVE YOU LIKE AN UBERLY FAT KID LOVES THE WHOLE PILLSBURGHY INDUSTRY! HA! BEAT THAT BIAAAATCCCCCHHHH!&nbsp; ok yes so that was my moment of glory. anyhoo well im glad we're gettin a hold of each other now....it was touch and go for awhile there and that was so not cool....but anyhoo....hmmmm oh GUESS WHAT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I GOT A 4 ON MY FRENCH AP!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! (we wont talk about hte 2 on chem).........BUT YAYAYAYYAYAYYAYAYAYAYAYAYYYAYAYAYYYAAYYAYA......i was so excited.....so yea check in w/ whoever u can concerning the mail to see if you guys got ur scheduals or for you sara to find out (if your really want to kno) what u got on the AP. so yea just some heartfelt news. hmmmmm what else is new? oh dude becca our pasta place is callin to me man.....i like tried to eat there through osmosis....soakin up the scent...it was really quite sad......many odd stares but yes i have a time limit on this thing and its almost expired so i gtg.....lata gatas....."a desert filled with mouth parts" has anyone heard that commercial? cracks me up everytime....shit two minutes left....ok bye! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey all. dude jen your post made me laugh so hard. hahahaha i miss you so much. anywho dont even complain cuz i wish it was beach weather here. its raining so damned hard. and of course i didnt bring my raincoat cuz where im from it doesnt rain in the summer!! so it didnt occur to me that there are places in this country where it actually rains this time of year. damn. anywhosers, keep callin me. i miss you!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay hi jen!! i just got off the phone with u...but yea.  i miss u tons!!!  and im sorry im over on the other coast and im MAD about missing the beach weather because i went to the beach the other day and there was no sun!!! what is up with this coast!!! its been like 85 degrees and raining!!! k im not so boring that i need to talk about the weather.... but yea.  im glad the potato has been ousted and the phone is now workin... mm hmm  well, i love you like a REALLY fat kid loves a WHOLE BAKERY!!!! mwahahahahahha beat that bitch.  ok i miss u.  and becca too.  and yea.    MWAH!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, ok, ok...so im a lazy bum who doesnt post....so shoot me...yeesh....tee hee just kidding....ok wanna here something really lame? like uber bad? im posting this from teh fuckin library. thats right. the library...cause my internet...heell my whole computer has gone kuhbloowey..hahahha that was fun to type....and there are a bunch of brats screaming and my privacy screen is SO not working....i am NOT feeling the privacy in this room..umm building like thing...yes.....yes well both of you suck cause ur across the fricken country....stupid east coast...stupid umass...stupid columbia....well i hope y'all are havin fun at ur respective stupid colleges....home is pretty much the same....u guyz arent missing much....awesome weather though...perfect beach weather ya know? but is there anyone to go to the beach with? no. yes that was bitter. so my phone should be working now...i checked the potato sara and it is no longer in service. not ot worry though...we gave it a proper potato burial...IN THE OVEN...MWAHAHAHAHAHHAAHHAHA.....ok yea gross cause that things been on there for months....anyhoo it was retired and in its place we have an ice cream scoop...although mr scoopy isnt quite up to snuff so i think we're replacing him with teh can opener....who knows what will be the next phone after that...i need to hold auditions...get references....god i am sop bored....have u noticed yet? anyhoo now becca....that truck party when u get back is SOOOOOO happening...i even cleaned my room up so thats its livable....its on! anyway i  think im done now....so i'll just close with I LOVE YOU GUYZ LIKE A FAT KID LOVES CAKE! mwahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey im here... yall havent posted in a while.  anyway keep this up so i know what u guys are up to and yea... ill try to keep postin to.  miss ya! oh and jen, ur phone is always busy!!! u need a new potato i think...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall...im in new york and im checkin up on this thing but no ones really posting...saras got too many cool friends over there at umass i suppose and jens....well WHERE ARE YOU JEN! anyway i figured id just post something and say hey...and that yall should keep this up too. ok yeah dont know whats with all the yalls but...yes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yea, does anyone read this?  if u do leave us a comment and let us know.  or if anyone else wants in on this, if you are cool enough then maybe we can work somethin out.  i havent talked to my affiliates about this one but if u r damn cool and u want in... 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      does anyone actually read our blog or do we just talk to eachother? hmmm i wonder if anyone else is letting themselves into the wacky world of jen, sara, and becca. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      party in my basement.  me, becca, jen, ariel, lauren, mike, and the biggest bag of popcorn ive ever seen.  im talkin all the popcorn from mikes movie theater.  oh the humanity.  jen is talking about her boyfriend butt-boy.  poor guy.  we might make a cake and eat the batter.  mmm hmm.  i just thought id post and share the madness that goes on when we all unite in my basement  parting words: somebody told me that you had a boyfriend that looked like a girlfriend that i had in february of last year.  DAMN SKIPPY!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>