<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    First Photo :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://thek.blogspot.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Two more close friends left the company today :( Anyway Atul, Biju I wish both of you all the best :)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My company lost two real good guys today, who are close friends on mine (Bisu and ranjan) :(  I wish both of them good luck :)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink ftp.runnet.ru 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.reactos.org/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://groups.google.com/groups?q=%22parameter+sniffing%22+%22bart+duncan%22++group:microsoft.public.sqlserver.*&hl=en&lr=&ie=UTF-8&oe=UTF-8&group=microsoft.public.sqlserver.*&selm=uBWmjRecBHA.163%40cppssbbsa01.microsoft.com&rnum=10    Aha, some one here spent 4 days on digging a SP because of this bug  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. Started using RSS Bandit, lov it ;) 2. Started using the w.blogger to blog, pretty gud ;) 3. Planning to take up MCSD exams, thx to bisu for all the gyan ;)  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Read the Book: "Who moved my cheese" One of the best books I have read !!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.ynithya.com/taxcalc/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink SQL Server 2005 Express Edition   urlLink Visual Studio 2005 Express Beta Products   Few other articles read today:  urlLink Daily Build and Smoke Test   urlLink Continuous Integration   urlLink Continuous Integration with CruiseControl.NET and Draco.NET 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Digital Pen   Logitech IO Digital Pen - MINT IN ORIGINAL BOX  The pen that remembers everything you write!      * Digitally capture handwritten notes, drawings, and ideas     * Handwrite appoints & action items into Microsoft Outlook or Lotus Notes     * Keep all your information organized in one place on your PC  Logitech IO automatically      * Files notes and drawings in Microsoft Word     * Enters appointments and to do items into Microsoft Outlook     * Sends e-mails via Microsoft Outlook     urlLink    Digital Pen&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://microsoft.sitestream.com/teched2004/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Note to self:  from:  urlLink Joel    Stay away from having a resume like: - Used VB to code user controls. - Coded business objects. - Built data access layer.  and put in stuff like: - Implemented screen to improve user data entry times. - Refactored application to scale up to support three times as many users. - Rolled out application to 1000 users on time and on budget.  i.e. - Slant your accomplishments to show how they helped who you were working for.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I din't do it yet, posting it as a note to self.   urlLink Yahoo to Gmail   Also check this site   urlLink http://gmail-is-too-creepy.com/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haha's ePragmatic practical solutions   urlLink http://epragmatic.blogspot.com/   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Jokes    Winners never quit and quitters never win, but those who never win and never quit are idiots. - unknown  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Got a gMail Account today and to my surprise yahoo also increase the mailbox size to 100 mb ;)  Gmail's search is damn good :) hope google adds all the additional stuff like  Photo album,  Briefcase, Notepad, Calender, Tasks, Chat --> call it Ghat ?  Yada Yada :)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://bhavyasmitha.blogspot.com/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Duhhhhhhhh&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey, this must be the coolest tool from a long time, Imagine this On the "Machine 1" you use the digital pen instead on a mouse and when you say copy on a file, the in-built flash memory on the pen will also copy the file (using bluetooth), On "machine 2" use the same pen and browse to proper place and say paste :)    urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/technology/3774747.stm 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.undefined.com/ia/archive/000158.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Check this survey on slashdot ;)   urlLink http://slashdot.org/pollBooth.pl?qid=1122&aid=-1 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Microsoft has a good way of honoring individuals who have made good contributions to the company's success, thats is to rewarded them with this title "Distinguished Engineers" ;-)    urlLink http://www.microsoft.com/PressPass/exec/de/default.asp 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Folks u can hear "Radio city" on ur PC by playing this url in Windows Media Player.    urlLink mms://216.133.247.146/radio4   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://muralir.blogspot.com/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         urlLink     Click to join IcodeGeeks    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.hanselman.com/blog/PermaLink.aspx?guid=a0a65e0c-5ef8-41e4-a566-1739b4428aa5 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://srinivasancv.blogspot.com/   And a fantastic quote at the right time, thx to CV;-)  To be successful follow this rule said by Mr Narayana murthy, founder of infosys.  "Love your job not your company because you will never know when your company will stop loving you"
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had 29 Inch high definition TV with direct DishTV Connection ;-). Attached to a hi-fi system with wall mounting flat speakers and a good bean bag (hot chips ?)    Current zunk that I have:    1. Mini DV - JVC camcorder   2. Canon S200 Digital camera  3. Yashika 120 zoom normal camera  4. Creative MoVo 64 MB mp3 player  5. Archoas Recorder 20 GB  6. Motorola StarTAC mobile phone  7. Computer (1GB RAM, 120 GB HDD, 2.7 GHz Hyper threaded processor, CD burner/DVD Drive, firewire card)  8. LG Golden eye TV with a PIP(pic in pic) and surround system.  9. Auto cook whirlpool Micro-Owen.  10. Electrolux Aqua flow Refrigerator.  11. Electrolux front mounting washing machine.  12. Philip's shaver, drier and pressing box.  13. Mini FM player (costs 20 bucks and it's my wife favorite gizmo).    Wish List    1. "Microsoft XP Tablet edition" enabled laptop.  2. Digital Photo frame ;-)  3. Hi-Def TV with hi-fi attached.  4. Smart Phone  5. Spot Watch  6. Good Video+TV Tuner card.  7. Creative Sound card.  8. GPS unit (not for next 10 yrs in India ;-( )  9. Logitech Quick Cam with a flexible web camera stand (Sound sensitive?)  10. Microsoft wireless keyboard and mouse.  11. Canon multi function scanner, fax, copier, color printer with photo print option.  12. Noise canceling head phones ;-)  :-)  Did I miss something. . . . ?  Browsing all eCommerce sites to find all the zunk is a nice way to divert yourself from all maiming that's happening to your mind :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Bookmarklets:  Bookmarklets are free tools to help with repetitive or otherwise impossible tasks in your web browser.   urlLink http://www.squarefree.com/bookmarklets/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Zindagi aur maut uparwale ke haath mein hai, Jahanpanah. Hum sab rangmanch ki kathputliyan hain jinki dor uparwale ki ungliyon se bandhi hui hai. Kab kaun uthega koi nahin bata sakta. Ha ha ha.  Few others from the same movie:  Kisiko Dekha , Apna sa laga , use choo kar dekh liya , do pal baat kar li.. Bas Babu Moshai  Zindagi badi honi chahiye, lambi nahin  Maut tu ek kavitha hai, Mujhse kavitha ka vaada hai, milegi mujhko Doobti nafson mein jab dard ko neend ane lage Zard sa chehra liye chand uphak thak pahunche Din abh paani mein ho, raat kinare ke karib  Na andhera na ujala ho, na abhi raat na din  Jism jab kathm ho aur rooh ko jab saans aye Mujhse ik kavita ka vaada hai, milegi mujhko  Agli Mulakat yahin hogi.. Itni Jaldi Parda girne nahi dunga  Clip  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My dear friend Arvind's favorite poem :)   If you can keep your head when all about you Are losing theirs and blaming it on you, If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you But make allowance for their doubting too, If you can wait and not be tired by waiting, Or being lied about, don't deal in lies, Or being hated, don't give way to hating, And yet don't look too good, nor talk too wise:  If you can dream--and not make dreams your master, If you can think--and not make thoughts your aim; If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster And treat those two impostors just the same; If you can bear to hear the truth you've spoken Twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools, Or watch the things you gave your life to, broken, And stoop and build 'em up with worn-out tools:  If you can make one heap of all your winnings And risk it all on one turn of pitch-and-toss, And lose, and start again at your beginnings And never breath a word about your loss; If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew To serve your turn long after they are gone, And so hold on when there is nothing in you Except the Will which says to them: "Hold on!"  If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue, Or walk with kings--nor lose the common touch, If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you; If all men count with you, but none too much, If you can fill the unforgiving minute With sixty seconds' worth of distance run, Yours is the Earth and everything that's in it, And--which is more--you'll be a Man, my son!    --Rudyard Kipling 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ability is to look at a blank page, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;And create a poem. Ability is to stare into the eyes of fear,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;And come out stronger because of it. Ability is to walk into a room of strangers, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;And come out with friends. Ability is to admit you are wrong,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;When you are wrong. Ability is to get back up,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;When you fall down. Ability is to believe,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;When everything seems lost.   Ability - a simple word, with a complex meaning. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For many, ability is never found, but for all ability is within. Ability stares everyone in the face at one time or another. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Whether your ability is how well you shoot hoops, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;How well you flip at dancing, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;How smart you are at school. You have ability. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For some, ability is lost by never trying. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Whether never trying to shoot one more time, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Never trying to bend a little more, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Or never trying to score higher in school.  Ability is within. Ability is yours. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink An Introduction to Data Structures   urlLink The Queue, Stack, and Hashtable   urlLink Binary Trees and BSTs   urlLink Building a Better Binary Search Tree   urlLink From Trees to Graphs   urlLink Efficiently Representing Sets 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Service Orientation and Its Role in Your Connected Systems Strategy 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Portable printer :)  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://weblogs.asp.net/Varad/archive/2004/07/17/186117.aspx 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Put a hole to your coffee cup, to make sure no one uses your coffee cup :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.aspnetresources.com/blog/ms_redesign_showcase.aspx   urlLink http://www.aspnetresources.com/blog/ms_redesign_genesis.aspx   urlLink http://www.aspnetresources.com/blog/ms_redesign_restructuring.aspx   urlLink http://www.aspnetresources.com/blog/ms_redesign_dust.aspx   urlLink http://www.aspnetresources.com/blog/ms_redesign_final.aspx    urlLink final 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Snooze&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    ATUL's fav personality&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Have you booted your computer ?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink gizmodo   urlLink the-gadgeteer   urlLink GadgetMadness   urlLink Cool hunting .  urlLink nechbi   urlLink shinyplastic   urlLink firstadopter   urlLink akibalive   urlLink panbo   urlLink shinyshiny   urlLink everythingusb 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      0. Open windows media player 1. File --> open URL  2. Paste http://www.kannadaaudio.net:8000 3. Have fun !! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink      urlLink Review 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink       Now look at my good old StarTAC bought about 3 years back, now it does not even fetch rs.500 :(   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink      urlLink Walk on water 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its almost 1.5 Years old and it's already an outdated model ;). I have about 1 GB of photos using this camera. (K match me if you can [1.5 years = 1GB of photos]).  urlLink      urlLink      urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>