<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink UGA may have lost its name .  This is the latest offensive maneuver is a pretty strange war between the University of Georgia and it's former fund-raising organization, the UGA Foundation.  Here's a brief lesson in the history of these two rivals  1.  last year Michael Adams, UGA's president, refused to extend the contract of Vince Dooley, the long time athletic director  2.  the UGA Foundation, filled with old frat boys, started whining and boo hooing and decided they wanted UGA to fired Michael Adams because they love Dooley.  3.  the Board of Regents that governs the University System of Georgia backed Adams and told the UGA Foundation that they can't influence school policy.  4.  the UGA Foundation decided that if they can't have it their way, they would just not pay Michael Adams the part of his salary that they normally provide.  This is analogous to them saying that if no one was going to play with them, they would take their ball and go home.  They also tried to hold their collective breath until someone paid attention to them, but no one did.   5.  the Board of Regents finally decided they had had enough and they  urlLink fired the UGA Foundation .  6.  the latest step and the title of this post.  the UGA Foundation now has the trademark to the term "the University of Georgia" and they are holding UGA hostage.  If the Board of Regents goes through with firing them, they will force the university to change it's name.  This is a pretty good move if you ask me.  It's going to ensure that firing the UGA Foundation won't be an easy process and all of this will have to resolved in court.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What an exciting day!  We just released the latest test for The Intelligent Shopping Process at  urlLink Autotrader.com.   To see it, enter your zip code and click "Find Your Car."  This will take you to the new search form.  We have made it much easier to find the car you want.  Before you had to enter at least a year and make which meant you had to have done some research somewhere else.  Now, you can search for anything you want.  We have options to search for new or used cars,  for particular body styles, by a price range, etc.  We are finally starting to live up to our commercials.  Remember, "I need a car... a blue car... no a truck."  Now, look for blue cars or trucks.  I was fortunate to be one of the developers who helped to create this, and I think it's the beginning of the future for Autotrader.com.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    a picture from Shannon and Daniel's wedding.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is the subflooring beneath my toilet.&nbsp; urlLink      I found this damage when I went into the crawl space to change the airfilter.  Something told me that I should check out our plumbing to make sure everything was alright.  I noticed that some of the pipes were wet and then looked up and saw the horror.  I had Ashley test the faucet, toilet, and shower.  When she flushed the toilet, it poured down the side of the pipe like rain.  Apparently, this has been going on for some time.  Wood does not  urlLink rot  overnight.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I'm a closet American Idol fan.  So what...  I'm really looking forward to next week's final.  I was pulling for Latoya until she got cheated by the state of Hawaii.  Now, I think I would like to see  urlLink Diana  pull off an upset.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      That's a good question.  You should find out like I did.   Just click on the link above.  The BlogThis bookmarklet is a very useful little tool.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm 27, I'm not old... but I can't convince my body to feel the same way.  I played in a  frisbee tournament last weekend and noticed some pain in the outside of my left  knee.&nbsp; It didn't really seem to bother me, so no big deal.&nbsp; Then I go  to frisbee on Thursday and played for two hours.&nbsp; Everything was fine at  first, but then I gradually noticed a tightening in my knee.&nbsp; By the end, I  was limping to the starting end zone.&nbsp; I had to ice it for 20 minutes and  take ibuprofen to get the pain to go away.&nbsp; I did a little research on  WebMD and decided that I have  Iliotibial Band  Syndrome , or  runner's knee. Ok, so now it's time to figure out how to  stretch , but I'm sure my wife will be  glad to give me some free lessons.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I found this  article  on  slashdot .&nbsp; It seems that some researchers at Berkeley have developed a virus that attacks the HIV virus.&nbsp; It's amazing where biotechnology is going.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My efforts to secure a  urlLink GMail  account are proving  fruitless. I really want to beta test GMail.&nbsp; And every article that  I have read has just whetted my appetite further.  I'll tell you what  has not worked to get an account.&nbsp;   Using my Blogger account for the first time - didn't work. Creating a beta group on the new  urlLink Google Groups  - nope  Oh well... I'm not  so desperate that I'm willing to buy an account on ebay, so don't feel too sorry  for me.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's only taken me two years, but I finally decided to bite the bullet and get a blogger.com account.  I don't plan on updating it very often because I really don't have that much to say.  Maybe I'm just not as aware of the world around me as I should be...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's the gist of the article: Internet Explorer has some significant security flaws that enable hackers to access a user's computer and install malicious software.  US CERT, the US Computer Emergency Readiness Team, is recommending that IE users turn off Active X and restrict Javascript or switch to any other browser.   My suggestion is to switch, and I have a great recommendation for a replacement.    urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      6-27-2004 update Ashley and I visited my grandfather today, and he looked really good.  He's weak from the surgery, but that can be expected.  The heart problem from my last update seems to be related to the IV they had in his chest.  The assumption is that the IV might have caused some heart irritation which made his heart race. They moved it to his hand, and he has not had any heart trouble since.  6-25-2004 update My grandfather has been in ICU all week and was doing fine until very recently.  Today his blood pressure dropped critically low. Please continue to pray for him, that God will watch over him, give wisdom to those who are caring for him, and continue to provide my family with peace.  6-14-2004 original post My grandfather is undergoing lung surgery on Friday beginning at 8:30am.  I know there aren't many people who read this blog, but if you stumble upon it before then, please pray for him.  Pray for the doctors.  And pray for his family.  We need God's peace, and we need his reassuring presence. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is an email that I sent out about an article in the USA Today about a contemporary Christian magazine - Relevant.  ---------- Forwarded message ---------- From: Daniel Norton   Date: Thu, 24 Jun 2004 16:24:49 -0700 Subject: Re: No communicado To: james-michael smith   Cc: 01Jill Sims  , russwmills@wmconnect.com, anorton@gmail.com, dfunkanopolis@hotmail.com, jeremiah2216@yahoo.com, nturner@duluthumc.org, susanstofer@hotmail.com, ji_lee17@yahoo.com, jeffadelman@bellsouth.net, gadog4life@aol.com, christiantrotter@comcast.net, footyak@aol.com, sedgwick@securenym.net   Hello everybody!  I just read an article in the USA Today (and I'm not a general peruser of USA Today because it's usually all drival) and stumbled on a really cool article about a magazine editor who is trying to reach people in our generation who are Christians but are fed up with the whole denominational bullshit.  It's a really great article, and I am definitely going to have to check out the magazine, Relevant.  Here's the article online:  urlLink ">http://www.usatoday.com/life/lifestyle/2004-06-23-christian-mag_x.htm   D  p.s., for those who are offended, sorry for using the word "bullshit."  It's really the only word that describes how I feel about the current state of the mainstream church, and it always bugs me when people use cute cover up to their curse words like "arse" or "ace" or "booty" 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I posted this article so that I could read it at my leisure.  I'm hoping to eventually install Linux on a computer that I build.  I've got lots and lots of computer parts in my closet.  I just need a computer case and power supply to complete everything.  And then lots of free time to put everything together.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ashley enjoying a margarita glass... &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am the proud owner of a  urlLink GMail  account.  So what is GMail?  urlLink http://www.wired.com/news/business/0,1367,62897,00.html  screenshots: urlLink http://www.extremetech.com/print_article/0,1583,a=126254,00.asp     Like all geeks, I have been drooling over GMail since Google announced it on April 1.  What we all want is to be part of something revolutionary from its inception.  Google is THE hot company right now.  They have taken the lead in developing the future of computing.  They are already in the works to develop a desktop application that can incorporate their search technology into searches on your computer.  Think about how convenient it will be to have an application that would return documents on your computer, or emails in your mailbox, or links to relevant sites all with the press of a button.  The beauty of GMail transcends the 1 GB of storage. Gmail has Google's search functionality built in.  Instead of deleting old emails, I can archive them.  By archiving, I have a permanent record of every email conversation that I have ever had.  I can find every email that I've ever sent or received from a particular friend, or I can search for emails within the last week that that have URLs in them.  I can find emails with attachments, that has certain words but not others.  It's incredibly powerful and functional.  And the ads aren't intrusive.  Most of the time I don't even notice them.  Of course, GMail is not without controversy.  People are making a really big deal about the fact that they scan the emails so they can attach ads that correspond to the conversation.  It has raised a big stink with some consumer advocacy groups.  urlLink http://zdnet.com.com/2100-1104-5230750.html  I don't think it's that big a deal because I don't write a lot of emails with terroristic undertones, so I don't think Big Brother will ever care about what I'm writing.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm a little nervous about this, but I've agreed to compete with Kevin (Autotrader.com) and Chris (CEI) in the  urlLink BALANCE Bar Adventure Race Series  Atlanta event on June 20.  It's a 20 mile (sprint) adventure race that will include mountain biking, running, and kayaking.  In addition we have to complete up to 10  urlLink Special Tests .  Past tests have included a rock wall, archery, knot tying, and puzzles.  It is going to be intense, and I am out of shape... but might as well try to win one for the Gipper.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Today is my  brother's 22nd birthday.&nbsp; Happy Birthday!   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Congratulations to the Georgia Department of Transportation.  For your diligent and thoughtful efforts to increase Atlanta's gridlock and to generate scorn and mockery, you are the 2004 Dumbest Georgia Government Agency.  This was the closest vote in history.  The DOT just squeaked by the Georgia Department of Education whose decision to change the term evolution to "biological changes over time" generated a lot of humorous press that shined the world's spotlight on our wonderful state.  The Department of Education has successfully run one of the lowest ranked school systems in the country for years.   The DOT won because they consistently manage to make life worse for the people in Atlanta.  Their lack of planning, lack of support for an effective mass transit system, and gross mis-management are shining examples for the rest of the world.  They have one of the  urlLink highest budgets  of any government agency, but they are unable to improve the transportation anywhere in the state, especially metro Atlanta.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    the bathroom now&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I'm writing this, there are 38 minutes left on this auction and I'm the high bidder.  I've been looking for a good road bike for a few weeks, and this is a great deal on a Trek 1000.  It's a good bike with a decent component set.  But it beats doing 30 mile rides on my mountain bike which is what my dad and I have been doing.   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Here  is the schedule of the upcoming rides for our new Atlanta biking group.  This group was the brain child of Kevin Ketts, but it's starting to grow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some of my friends from UGA have started an email group just to blow off steam and write about life in general. The group started small with about 5 or 6 people but has recently grown in size and scope. We have started running into headaches trying to manage to keep everyone on the list. "Is Lem's email at Juno or Yahoo?" So to keep things more manageable, I created the Yahoo Group: ugaforums  It's restricted to just our group of UGA friends, so if that's not you, sorry!  If that is you, you can request membership below                                      Powered by  urlLink groups.yahoo.com    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink     this is, of course, copyright of  urlLink http://jibjab.com   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    picture of the Golden Gate bridge from my recent trip to San Francisco&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Roadcycling.com - Cycling training - Knee Pain and Bicycle Position   Yeah, my knee is still bothering me.  So, I'm doing a little research and thought I would post some of the information that I'm finding.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Sage - RSS and ATOM feed aggregator    Are you tired of going to 10 different websites to get the latest news?  RSS is a way to collect and view all the latest headlines in a single place.  RSS is simple an XML feed that is constantly updated.  Sage is an extension for Firefox that converts the XML feed into a simple HTML page.  So now, I can see all the latest news headlines in one place.  I have collected the RSS feeds from the New York Times, Yahoo New, CNet.  It's simple and convenient.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ashley and I have decided it's time to get a dog.  We want a dog that doesn't shed and is low allergy.  Normally, this would leave us with a very narrow selection: poodle or terrier.  But thanks to the effort of some dog breeders in Australia there is another choice.  Below are some links to site about the Labradoodle (a low allergy mix between a standard poodle and a labrador.)  ---------- Forwarded message ---------- From: Daniel Norton   Date: Sat, 3 Jul 2004 18:30:47 -0700 (PDT) Subject: labradoodle info To: dnorton@gmail.com, anorton@gmail.com  about  urlLink about.com article   urlLink National Geographic article   urlLink dogbreedinfo.com   Breeders  urlLink breedersclub.net   urlLink http://www.labradoodle-dogs.com   urlLink http://dir.yahoo.com/.../Labradoodles/    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've created a  urlLink UGA Football  blog.  This will be a place to discuss the latest college football news as long as it revolves around UGA.
     
    
</post>



</Blog>