<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because  urlLink some dumbass got in the pool while they had diarrhea .
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kevin Smith's  Clerks  is celebrating its 10-year anniversary. If you have not seen this movie, stop reading this and rent the damned movie. You will be vastly more entertained than any offering that includes Ashton Kutcher.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They get they ass knocked out. Mike Tyson, formerly known as the baddest man alive,  urlLink was put down for the count by unheralded heaveweight Danny Williams earlier tonight . This brings the end to Mr. Tyson's career that is vastly overrated by almost everyone. The only name fighter he defeated was Larry Holmes and he was well past his prime when he fought Tyson.  The only way Mike can even imagine to get out his  urlLink $38,000,000 debt  would be to A) fight Tonya Harding in Celebrity Boxing III, IV, V, VI, and VII or B) hope and pray that Jimmy Kimmel will make him a lifetime co-host. Sadly, the more likely option is A.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I still do not understand the hoopla that was sent over the Democratic Convention. It is a better example than Leno that the applause button works. Now please do not think that I am conservative cock because I have the same criticisms of that other convention.  The whole problem with these things are as follows:   1.  There is no reasonable debate or criticism of what the speaker talks about. Hell, the man on the stage could say that rape should not be a crime and all you would hear is "Clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap."   2.  Every person in the audience (the delegates) are mindless drones. If the speaker seems riveted and starts yelling into the microphone, the audience seems completely filled overjoyed. Case and point, John Edwards going on and on about the rich nation vs. poor nation. This from a man that belongs to the upper echelon (aka the top .01%) of this country. What does the audience do? "Clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap." If the Republicans want to have a better convention than the Democrats, they should just bring in Steven A. Smith. The crowd in attendance will go crazy over his blabber.   3.  These always cut out down on Keith Olbermann's airtime. If you are not watching Countdown with Kieth Olbermann on MSNBC at 8 ET, why are you not? He brings wit and intelligence to a time slot filled with arrogant fools (*cough* O'reily *cough*). The oddball and keeping tabs sections of the show let Keith spray his sardonic humor at the all too easy prey. If you only have one hour of your time to spend watching the news, Countdown should be the hour you waste it on.   4.  Nothing newsworthy ever happens in these. It is just as idiotic as preempting any program on television for the Presidential State of the Nation speach. The motto I always think about when watching these is, "Do it before you palaver over it."  Those are all the dilemmas I can think of right now. I will probably have more to come the next time I post something here. If not, well I guess I lied. Oh well.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having absolutely nothing to do in their lives,  urlLink two men wear thongs through Wal-Mart . Handcuffs issued.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This would be the one for it:     (Courtesy  urlLink RedXHosting.com )
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The 2004 Democratic National Convention Site has an add for  urlLink Bush/Cheney on the bottom of its webpage . 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meet stalkers new favorite tool,  urlLink IM Watching .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are you getting sick of using just idiot and moron to put down a fellow retard? Well go ahead and go over to  urlLink Funny Mean Names  and you will have a bigger and better insulting vocabulary.
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's  urlLink Jesus Dance .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just another case that America is becoming a complete police state.  urlLink A scientist was arrested for eating a candy bar.  Further down in the article it explains a 12-year old was arrested for eating a french fry (or a freedom fry for you idiots).
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out  urlLink this pathetic site . In it is a 26-year old man who is still a virgin and is willing to take offers from women to take that honor away from him. Of course he leaves us with some great things about himself. Some of these masterful quotes include,   "I am a virgin for one simple reason: the dream of making a Web site just like this."   Yep, sure you are.   " Interests:  board games, roadtrips, gambling, naps, strength training, Seinfeld, politics, philosophy, SQL, Christmas lights, weather patterns, political maps, business and entrepreneurship, passionate love-making, romance, debates and discussions."   Boy this guy is a keeper. One thing I know the women love are board games, a programming language, Christmas lights, weather patterns, and politcal maps. I still can't figure out why he is still a virgin.   " Biggest "Accomplishment":  finished second in the 2nd grade spelling bee."   Do I even need to comment on this? I did not think so.   "I follow a very low-carb diet."   Height:  6'0"  Weight:  237 lbs    Mr. Atkins must be rolling over in his grave. You, my man, are the poster child for this latest diet trend.  Ladies, are you still attracted to this male? Well go ahead and whore yourself to him. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The new fashion trend,  urlLink skinbags . Now I feel glad for having no fashion sense.
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink A priest and a nun have been convicted of disorderly conduct for getting it on in a parked car with tinted windows. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anthony Anderson, once star of a cheesy daytime teenager show on NBC where he played a high school basketball player,  urlLink has been charged for rape .  Of course Yahoo! then shows its excellence by showing a picture of nonrelevant eyecandy just below the picture of Mr. Anderson.   UPDATE :  urlLink Here is the mugshot .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And guess what that amounts to? Just another  urlLink stupid sex question .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alabama is one of the oddest places in the world. Like how about  urlLink this 12-foot long, 1000-pound hog .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In a recent study,  urlLink 28% of people were fooled by fraudulent e-mails . Now I know that the majority of my audience is teenagers who most likely do not know how many digits are on a credit card so my advice is probably not worthwhile to anyone who will read this. But since I like to post at least something everyday, here it is anyway.  Do not trust outbound links in your e-mail box. Even if it is a valid claim and the site is the same as it appears, it will be more worthwhile to just open up a new tab (and if you do not know what that is, please stop using Internet Explorer) and type in the site that it claims to be.  Just to see how easy it is to be fooled, go ahead and take  urlLink this survey .
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink They both do not like to get pooped on .
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Heather La Bella, the LA Spark's tactical marketing director, is going to pose nude for Playboy . Apparently it is her belief that this will increase the teams's and, to some extent, the sport's popularity.  Her way to attract the potential fans is to hold a WNBA basketball while she is being photographed naked. Now the reasoning with her logic is idiotic because...   She is not even a player in the league. It would be one thing to actually have a player pose for a photoshoot to get popularity, but this person is the TACTICAL MARKETING DIRECTOR. What is the likelihood people will ever see her at a game? If there is a number equivalent to that answer, it would look a something like 0.    Her way of advertising the WNBA to the Playboy audience is to expose a WNBA ball in the photos. Now as a man I am very sure that my male cohorts will be staring at some other round objects if they are looking Playboy.  Secondly, the problem with only the WNBA ball is it will provide no incentive to actually like the WNBA. Take for example last year's Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue where [insert anorexic model here] posed provocatively with sheep. Let me ask you a question. Did you want to go out and buy some sheep after looking at that? Of course not. You wanted to look at some more naked women. That is all this Playboy ploy is going to amount to. It will have no actual value to the Sparks or the league.   Of course with the way the league is going right now, maybe Heather needed a little extra cash and this was her excuse so people would not ridicule her. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you like your teeth ultrabright. How about some all natural white juices? Read about it  urlLink here .   This is not an advertisement, it is in fact a disturbing story.   UPDATE:   urlLink TheSmokingGun.com  has  urlLink the entire ten pages of North Carolina administrative proceedings  on the dentist.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         My life is rated PG.  What is your life rated?  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9/11 Commission: "We believe we are safer. But we are not safe."  Ben Franklin: "Those who sacrifice liberty to become more secure, lose both liberty and security."  What I have been wondering is if anyone actually believes they are more secure than they were before 9/11.  Take for example if you were walking down a crowded street and you saw some Arab looking people. In our current society (in USA at least) we (as in the caucasian majority) probably will label these people as terrorists simply on their stereotype.  And of course the government is not trying to help us. With the current color scheme of terrorist threat they always warn us of looking out for suspiscious looking people. So what pops up into our heads? A Muslim male with a beard and a towel on his head.  Of course the other alternative when we see such a group is to do everyone's horrid impression of the Apu character on the Simpsons.  It is no wonder why they hate us.  So what does all of this have to do with security? Well by doing this we are making millions upon millions of people hate us more. Does hate make us more secure? I did not think so either.  Then there is the civil liberties we have given up just to "protect" us. I could go on and on about these, and maybe I will on a future date, but simply the gain (if there is any) far outways the negatives.  So let me ask you one more time, do you feel more secure now than before? I definately do not. In fact, I feel less and less secure under the current methologally of making us more "secure".
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read the story  urlLink here . (Thanks to Queen Pinky and Fark.com)
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently  urlLink bulls' balls are becoming a delicacy in Philadelphia .
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Michael Jackson is going to have quadruplets .
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Obviously grammar is not your forte` "Wes" but that's okay.  Fine, you can ridicule my mistakes in grammar as long as you are a saint in that department. Oh wait, what's this? "Of course, I am talking to a person  who's  big picture is to steal shit until he gets caught, at which point will become a permanent resident of a state penitentiary where he will join "The Sisterhood"." Great use of grammar.  Then of course he has to insult my comprehension by saying,  "Your comprehension seems to be limited." This from a man that has Ashton Kutcher as an acting god. The same Ashton Kutcher that on  urlLink his imdb.com forums  has the following quote, "Asking if Ashton Kutcher can act is like asking if Marlon Brando has any plans on cutting an album of American Funk Classics." With your critiques of illustriousness, I would not want to achieve your form of greatness.  That is just one point that points towards his own lack of comprehension, but I have one more. In the first quote I mentioned, he says that my life goal "is to steal shit until he gets caught". Now boys and girls, please look at the top of this blog. What is the name of this page? It is Señor Sneer. For the men and women that do not know any Spanish, that is translated into Mister Sneer.  So obviously with the name of Mister Sneer you would think that people would not actually take my work literally. Nope, the man that insults my intelligence, takes everything I say to a tee. Fine, at least now I know who I can scam money off of.   Me : The world is going to be destroyed unless you give me all your money.  "winner" : Oh my god, it is going to explode.  Me : Uh, I said it was just going to be destroyed, but I guess it could explode. But you can stop it. You can be the hero! Just give me your money.  "winner" : Oh, ok. Here you go (hands over wallet).  Me  (walking away): Dumbass.  Hmmm, maybe I should stop the flame wars. This guy could make my life a whole lot easier.    UPDATE : "Winner" changed who's to whose after reading this.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      According to  urlLink this study , 7% of Americans don't bathe at all.  In other news, Bubba not seeing as much action as he used to.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The "winner" became incensed and has countered with  urlLink this post .     In it he poses some questions. So I thought it would be adequate if I were to answer his queries. "moron...imbecile...is that the best you can do?" Hurray for you. You figured out how to make a question mark. With all of that thinking, you must have forgot you have to press the shift key before to make a, in a way you can understand, big letter.   To answer your question, piss infected mongolian whoremonkey is the best I can do. "Why name calling?" Because it is funnier that way. "Is it some superiority complex or have you just not moved passed the middle school mentality?" Yes it is a superiority complex and yes I have moved passed the middle school mentality. In my middle school days, I would have came back with your all too common cliches. Did you have to look it up? Or did you figure it out all by yourself? If I looked it up, I would have used addle-pate, dullard, dumb cluck, dunderhead, ignoramus, lunkhead, schnook, or simp.  There are all my replies. Now let the flame wars ensue. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You may have heard about it. If you have not, welcome to America.   If for whatever reason you don't have a gmail e-mail address already, just go ahead and post a comment with your current e-mail address included and I will send an invitation your way.  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Fark  Headline:  urlLink Your ally, Saudia Arabia: Where you can rape your foreign maid, then have her jailed for having an "illegal pregnancy"   My Choice for a Headline: In a surprising move, Kobe Bryant planning to play for Riyadh Nomads.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tattooing in of itself is a tolerable form of self expression. But of course there are many ways to screw it up. Some common examples of this are putting some dumb whore's name on your ass for the rest of your existence, having more symbols on the body than pores, and marking yourself with a college university's logo that you have never even attended. Then there is one that surpasses them all, tattooing yourself with the cross.  These same people that do that infathomably idiotic thing are also proud supporters of their local church. This means that they are some form of catholic or christian. In these two forms of religion, the only source of knowledge is The Bible. Now let me pose this simple question, what does The Holy Bible say about tattooing oneself? From  urlLink Bible.com :  "Ye shall not make any cuttings in your flesh for the dead, nor print or tattoo any marks upon you: I am the Lord." So basically they affirm their religious beliefs by sinning against that same religion. That is like saying you love someone and the way you show it is slap in them in the face twenty times (unless of course they are into bondage).  After you consume that conundrum, I must ask you this simple question. What is the last thing Jesus wants to see when he comes back (if he returns)? You guessed it, a cross.  So by what they believe to by an avouchment towards their beliefs, they in reality sin against their religion in general and also piss off their Lord on a personal level.   I can see it now up in heavens:   Angels : Um, Jesus weren't you supposed to return to Earth like four years ago.  Jesus : Well as long as my supposed believers keep showing off those damned crosses, I am never going to return. I hope they all burn in hell. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally, people in higher places are fighting for the people.  urlLink Wired  is reporting that the Senate is debating whether cable and satellite television providers should allow customers to actually choose what networks they want.  For the record, the channels I would pay for are:  Comedy Central ESPN ESPN2 ESPNews ESPN classic FX Nick at Nite (not Nickelodeon) NBA League Pass NBA TV TBS The Travel Channel TNT TRIO  The channels that get the boot in the ass:  All 8,413 women enpowerment channels Idiots are cool (aka MTV, VH1, Spike) We worship rich people (E!)
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Why waste originality when a truism will suffice   That was  urlLink this person's  response to the following quote,  urlLink "One man's cliche is another man's....uh....cliche." .  With that out of the way, I will tell everyone that is willing to listen my reasoning why this person would be regarded in public schooling as "special". First of all, he cannot even end a sentence with punctuation. Is that a question he is trying to pose? I don't know, there is no question mark. So I must assume that a series of idiotic statements that will form a SPED-like poem. But of course there is no way to tell.  Secondly, "truism" and "cliche" are basically the same word. But one of them sounds less harsh than the other. So just to make himself feel superior and lift his microscopic self esteem and ego, he uses the former.  Thirdly, he argues that using a cliche is a good thing. This in turn makes it fairly easy to believe that this imbecile has the following conversations:   Random person : How was your day?  "winner" : OK, I just have to take it one day at a time.  Random person : My day was fantastic.  "winner" : Well, every dog has its day.  Random person : Actually there was one thing that did not work out as expected. My dog broke her foot.  "winner" : Doggone.  Random person : But I did hook up with that girl across the street.  "winner" : Well, that takes the cake.  Random person : That wasn't all, then my dog did her dog on the porch all night long.  "winner" : Oy, vey!  I could go on and on, but you get the point. This person is a moron and this post is simply moronic.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink You have to see it to believe it .
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again, I am bringing out the classics. So once again, he is one more former post.  Well not much happened today except for this one little thing that I would like to quibble about.  Today the person that inspired me to create this blog said that she would like to read a book about my life. Well I was very appreciative and was about to thank her when this imbecile next to me chimed in to say something to the effect of “I would not like to read that, he does not do anything.” (well it was more derogatory but you get the idea)  Well this had incensed me because it follows this basic idea, "I go out more and try to socialize with my fellow idiots, so my life is better than yours." Well thank you moron. I cannot believe that anyone would believe this once you know more about who said this. You see the person that said that comment is a wannabe. He is so much of a wannabe that he goes out and drinks (alcohol) about every night and then comes to school the next day and tries to make it seem like he had a blast.  Now I have been under the influence of alcohol before and lets just say that I am never going to do that again. (Now for all you alcoholics who say that it gets better well bullshit because I know many former drunks that always ponder why they continued to drink.) First of all the only sensation you get from this is becoming an utter simpleton. Now there is many better solutions that I will suggest for people that like to drink. You could get a gun out and shoot yourself in the head because you are a complete idiot or you could bungee jump off a bridge and forgot to bring a rope. Now those would be fun times wouldn't they?  With all those joyous things that come out of being drunk you also get all those damn deficiencies that come to your body. Now I will not list off all of these because I bet you remember some of these from those stupid DARE classes, but here is what you lose when you get liver cancer.   What the liver does  Stores and Mobilizes Energy Controls Blood Sugar (Glucose) Regulates Glycogen Regulates Fat Storage Aids Digestion Produces Bile Regulates Blood Clotting Produces Several (Non-Reproductive) Hormones Manufactures Cholesterol (a certain amount of cholesterol is beneficial) Filters Blood Eliminates Bacteria Breaks down Drugs Produces Vitamins Stores Minerals Produces Essential Immune System Factors Monitors, as Well as Manufactures, Countless other Blood Proteins, to Maintain the Proper Levels of Numerous Chemicals in the Body  Then once you are done with all those little things like debilitating cancers you have to face the wrath of having to lay down some money for this precious liquid. Now how do you get this money, well you have to work. And with this retard the only job that he can do is hard labor. So a basic synopsis of his life goes like this:  1. Work 10-12 hours a day lifting 100 lb bags 2. Waste his money on the great alcohol 3. Become a complete moron 4. Pass out 5. Wake up 3 hours later 6. Continue cycle until age 35 when death is upon him.  Oh hurray with all those benefits (being a moron) isn't it time you thought about drinking your life away and complaining about my peaceful life you completely useless fool.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I have not posted anything as of late, and Steve Silver's roll call is coming closer and closer to this blog, I have decided to republish some of my old work. So without further ado, here was my ranting on the news media:  Is it just me or is the world news the most depressing thing that you can watch today? Every time I tune into the world news I see that another bomb has gone off in Baghdad and/or the Iraqis are resisting the American forces with more resilience every day of the week. Now personally I could care less about the whole Jews vs. Palestinians enigma, but for the elderly people of America this is basically all they cherish.  This brings me to what I believe causes depression in all of America. It is the world that is around us (especially the deplorable middle east). People over the age of 35 usually have children and are relegated to the inner dwellings of their homes. They cannot go outside because they have offspring (which is deplorable in its own right). So thus they must stay inside and guess what the main appliance is used in America is. If you guessed the toaster, you are a moron, GO AWAY! Now if you have any idea of how lazy America is today, you would have guessed that the television is the most used.  Now you might be asking, "Yeah so what if the TV is used the most, there are plenty of options for people to watch." Well if you haven't noticed, the TV schedule is not geared at all to the older people. Just switch to any channel and I bet you will not see anyone over the age 65 on your TV screen that is not a grandparent of some pin head.  There is one exception to this though, the news on TV. The television networks news is a collection of retired geezers that would not be able to work unless he/she gives out carts at Wal-Mart. Now I do not have an issue with geriatric men and women, but I do have an issue with the way these geezers present the news. They make life seem to be a cripid, horrid life that is a struggle to live just one more day. If you think life is this way or that life is tough just follow my guidelines of how to make it easier:  1. Do not do anything except the following: 2. Eat 3. Take a piss 4. Take a dump 5. Take a shower 6. Go to bed 7. Repeat steps 2-6  With my guidelines you will have a peaceful life. With my principles for life, you will not have to listen to people that say that the apocalypse is coming around the corner. So now back to the TV news. Here is an outline of the main ideas of what will be presented on these asinine shows:  1. Five die in Baghdad from bomb 2. $80 billion will be spent on the war (they will try to make this seem like an extraordinary feat) 3. Britney Spears is ruining young American girls 4. Cancer is happening more often 5. Close up of one of the ugliest people in America who will jabber on about the good ole' days 6. Show ends  Now that seems very mournful so here is what I want the news to portray:  1. Womens' breast are becoming bigger and thus men like them more 2. The anchor will make a mockery of world leaders. Then once this show has the highest ratings, the actual politicans will have to go on this show. This is when the anchor will question them to see how pathetic their lives really are. There will be a laugh track on this so whenever these sleezebags answer any of the anchor's questions they will be baffled and confused until they shoot themselves in the head. The laughtrack will be played after the riddance of this flunkey and everyone will revel as the scum bags will all be gotton rid of. 3. Men in the world rejoice as women try to become more hip and thus sluttier. 4. Girls jumping on trampolines (or for you ladies I suppose there could be some beefcake in there)  With my current plan everyone in America would be jubilant and there would be no more cynics like me.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually I deleted this blog a while ago, but since  urlLink Steve Silver  is going to do a blogroll, I am going to start blogging again.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I currently do not understand why people are left shelter less. It is really a sad debacle in all senses of the words. There is so much sympathy and empathy that I have towards these forlorn individuals that I cannot portray it in an emotional way."  Now that is what I would say if I were some imbecile that does not understand the true meaning of why these people are without a home. The real and truthful reason why these men and women are this way is they are complete and utter fools. There is no other to describe it.  First of all, I must explain myself. I am an upcoming high school senior that desires to become a bum. Now you might be wondering why I would want such a decrepit life. Well it is plain and simple, I am a lazy man. And there is nothing lazier than being a bum.  Now when I grow up and get into the “real world”, the hobos will be doing things very differently. The bums of my generation will be regarded as true champions. We will be, as in the modern lingo, “big pimpin”.  “How are you going to do that?” you may ask. Simple, the homeless people of my era will be habitual thieves. Everything that I steal will be of luxurious quality.  In this modern day and age, whenever people drive by a bunch of homeless people they feel sorry for the person and to some extent feel glad that they are not one of them. Of course, when I become a bum, these same people will admire us.  You will regularly hear such things as, “Holy shit honey, that bum has HDTV.” or “Damn, a Porsche, how does he do it?”  You might be wondering, “What if you get caught for stealing those expensive items.” Well it will involve a simple measure, prison. Now I have created a simple chart of life before and after prison,            OLD BUM WAYS   PRISON LIFE     housing   no home    warm and cozy place to live, even get a bed     income   begging for money   It is all free.     food    a couple pieces of cardboard, maybe   Three meals a day     health   None   Doctors around the clock, since they expect some shit to go down.     sex life   No one wants to sleep with your smelly ass.   Bubba will always love you.        Plus you get the added bonus that the cops may not find out it was you abducting all the materials.  (Actually I wrote this piece before, then I deleted it. It was funnier before.)
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink A topless beach in Romania is going to disallow women from exposing their particulars .    "Women over 60 are set to be banned from going topless on a popular beach amid claims that they are ugly and put off tourists.  Police at the Eforie Nord resort in Romania said they had received complaints from holidaymakers about older women stripping off.  A spokesman said: 'After a certain age, women should stop going topless so they do not make it unpleasant for others.'"   If I were at a topless beach, I too would be complaining about 60 year old women being there (of course the opposite sex would be complaining about me disrobing also, but that is not relevant). Unless that 60 year old women had  urlLink this page on IMDB.com  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This blog  has listed the horniest real (non-cartoon) characters in television history. Inexplicably, Peggy and Bud Bundy (Married with Children) and Christian (Nip/Tuck) did not make the list.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ESPN, the same network that showed the Bobby Knight debauchery and a  urlLink show based on idiotic cliches ,  urlLink has deemed the slang word "lez" offensive . Being a good hearted citizen, I did not even know what the hell "lez" was refering to. So the article later refers to saying that it means lesbian (now I feel like a complete moron).  I am not that smart so I'll just refer to  urlLink George Carlin's seven dirty words . 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I wish. I have been continuing my run over at  urlLink Pokerroom.com . I started out with $1,000 in play money and now I am up at $115,000. It is unbelievable. I am the luckiest person alive. There is no way to explain it.   In fact, I am feeling so damned lucky, that I am going to predict the Powerball numbers. So what the hell, here is my prediction for the upcoming Powerball numbers.       4   15   21   22   47    18       There they are with the first five being the white and last one being the powerball. If someone wins with this combination, please tell everyone at the press conference about this blog.  Thank you and goodnight.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Read this caption .  Yahoo! has changed the caption. Here is what it originally said:   "Team USA's Allen Iverson ( urlLink news ) is mobbed by his teammates after making the game-winning shit in their 80-77 win over Germany in an exhibition match in Cologne, western Germany, Wednesday Aug. 4, 2004.(AP Photo/Hermann J. Knippertz) " 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was playing No Limit Texas Hold 'Em over at  urlLink pokerroom.com  and I was doing great. i just won a hand that quadrupled my hand. I was ecstatic.  Of course there was a way to bring that down. Also over my shoulder on television was tonight's game between the Oakland Athletics and the New York Yankees. The game was 6-4 at the start of the 9th, then Octavio Dotel blew the save. I did not see what occurred, but I did hear what the commentators said.  Actually that is not exactly correct, I only heard some of the things they said. Anyone that is familiar with sabermetrics will know that whenever the Oakland Athletics do not completely destroy a team, the commentators will question why they do not play small ball. Now I do not have a problem with it. That is their opinion, and they can be wrong if they want to. But ESPN's telecast went too far.  Chris Berman, who just like Stephen A. Smith should not be allowed near a microphone, was torturing the audience with his idiocy. There is nothing worse than listening to a game that he does (and I have heard Michael Kay do games). This time though he outdid himself. Once Mr. Dotel blew the save, I heard something to the like of this conversation between Mr. Berman and some other dope.   Berman : Now what would Bill James say about that?  Idiot : Ha, ha what you don't like sabermetrics?  Berman : Don't get me started with that stuff.  Idiot : (Rambles)  Berman : Let me just say one thing, there are lies, there are damned lies, and then there are statistics.  Of course that is what my ears deciphered. Once it hit my brain, it was translated into, "Let me just say one thing, there are idiots, there are damned idiots, and then there are baseball analysts."  Before my brain could figure that out though, my arms were sent into convulsions to find the damned remote and change the channel as fast as humanly possible. So I changed the channel over to my favorite baseball team on ESPN2 (The Padres) who were playing the Phillies.  Fast forward to the 3rd inning where Adam Eaton was struggling with a man on second and another on third with Doug Glanville up at the plate. David Justice, the announcer, keeps pounding on to the audience that the wise thing to do is to try to advance the runners over and play small ball. This, from a statistical (sabermetrician) standpoint, is a dumb way to go. So what happens?  Doug Glanville does not take the advise and bam hits a long triple (which would have been a home run if not for playing in Petco Park). Do you hear Mr. Justice rebuttal his argument? No. He does not even mention it.   So what is the moral of the story? Idiots will always follow what has been done the longest Slavery, following politics, and moving the base runner over by a bunt (unless of course it is when there is a man on third with 0 out, then the bunt is a wise move) are all classic examples of this.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eric Neel, an excellent sports writer, is right on the money about  urlLink The Streak . It is just plain overrated. Actually all baseball stats that include something that involve the word "consecutive" are just plain pointless. Like this year when ESPN touted Ken Griffey Jr. as having 7 straight games with a HR. They played this more than when Barry Bonds hit 73 in a season. Which is more important?  Of course the 7 straight games with a HR is not even that bad of a stat. There are even worse oddities that you will see. Some of these stats include "Dallas has defeated San Antonio seven straight times when the game starts at 6:07 PM on a Tuesday" or "Mike Mussina has an ERA of 2.5 while starting day games at Yankee Stadium against the Brewers". And if you think I am making this up, you must not watch and/or listen to enough sports broadcasts.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Dave Chappelle has signed a 2-year extension for $50 million . Most will argue that is too much for a TV personallity to make, but I say this is money well spent. The $50 million alone was justified by the sketch where the following was uttered, "Does Wayne Brady have to choke a bitch?" Still the funniest sketch ever produced.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The now defunct archives of this blog used to carry something that I feel very strongly about. That is the whole same sex marriage argument ( urlLink Missouri, being the first in line, has banned this type of marriage ). Now most believe that the argument is for or against the banning of gay marriages across this nation. I believe that to be complete blasphemy. The third option on this should be for the government to deregulate marriage.  One of the fundamentalist qualities of this democracy is the separation of state and religion (now that is not what the republic was for, but that a whole other topic). Now can anyone please explain to me why the government regulates the holy sanctuary of marriage?  The only reason why a person should get married in this country is because of the tax benefits that belong with it.If this were the case, the majority of the people in this country would find marriage a waste of time. Now you could say that people want to adhere to their religion, but lets face it people, the majority do not follow their religion too wholeheartedly. Just take for example the percentage of people that have pre-marriage sex. That is not condoned by any major religion, but yet the overwhelming majority does it.  So again, I must ask why is marriage still regulated by the government? Please if anyone has an answer to this, post it in the comments section. I will be intrigued by the answers to this.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink N'Sync will not release a new album this year .
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shaquille O'neil, the former LA Lakers superstar,  urlLink may have to testify against his former teammate Kobe Bryant in his upcoming trial . Apparently Kobe's hands mysteriously found their way up a female's chest while at one of Shaq's parties. Here is the details from the article,   "Bryant allegedly made unwanted advances on a waitress during at a party held at O'Neal's home, it said.  ...  [Sports Illustrated] claimed that Bryant asked [a 22-year old waitress] to step outside and molested her at the party at O'Neal's home in Orlando, Florida in October 2002, eight months before he was accused of raping by a woman in Colorado on June 30."   Maybe the whole trial is not sealed on Kobe's side just yet.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Onion  has interviewed Robert Smigel, the genius behind Triumph the Insult Comic Dog, The Ambiguously Gay Duo, and Lookwell (and the interview is not a parody, at least I think so). It is a must read for any fan of his.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The usurper known as Madonna is having marital problems . Not to seem like an asshole or anything, but thank goodness. I can't imagine what it must be like to have sex with the devil.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Italian National Basketball team is currently defeating the USA National Basketball team by a score of 41-35 at halftime. This is not a fluke either. The whole reason being that the Italian team has the willingness and ability to shoot from the perimeter.   The USA, arguably the most atheltic team ever, is inexcsably walking the ball up the floor. If they do this during the Olympics they will not get higher than 4th place. You see this team was inexusably assembled no perimeter shooters. Of course, international rules permit basketball to be the way it is supposedly to be played with actual zone defenses allowed. So the Italian team has shown this throughout the first half. And the USA team was responded with clank, clank, clank.  Another problem is with the rotation problems. There is no way anyone can argue starting Lamar Odom, Allen Iverson, and Stephon Marbury over Carmelo Anthony, LeBron James, and Dewayne Wade. Allen Iverson and Stephon Marbury are virtually useless with a zone defense on them and another person on the bench, Shawn Marion, is just useless everytime he steps on the floor. Brent Barry or Ray Allen should have been invited over Shawn Marion.  The whole reason why the first and the second Dream Teams were so dominant is that they would push the ball up the floor at every opportunity. They knew that they could score on anyone in the open court. Of course that was when the NBA was watchable. Now the NBA is forced to play some game that lets players take four steps to become open, but yet cannot score with any regularity.   The EuroLeagues on the other hand are what true basketball should be. Everyone on the floor can shoot. The all defend reasonably well. All the players on the team actually have skill instead of just "upside" and jumping ability.  If the Detroit Pistons played the champion of the Euro League Finals, they would get their asses handed to them. Plain and simple.  I am sorry if this does not interest anyone, and/or if this does not make sense, I just needed a place to vent.   5:00 left in 3rd : Italy up by eight Although USA has finally figured out in the last three possesions that by pressing the action and going on a fast break offense works against a less athletic team.   Start of 4th : Itally still up by eight. USA had it down to four, but this Versilly (don't know how to spell his name) guy drained two straight threes. This still looks like an upset.   8:24 left in 4th : Italy now up 13. Being a cynic, I now see China, Lithuania, Germnay, Serbia and Montenegro (Yugoslavia), Italy, and Spain as better teams than the US. Hurray, for 7th place in the Olympics.   5:00 left in 4th : Italy is running away with it now, up by 21.   Its Over : 95-78, nevermind about 7th place,  I am beginning to wonder if USA can beat ANY country (we only beat Puerto Rico with this current team) in the Olympics.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instead of women humiliating themselves while on Howard Stern just to get a better pair of staring items,  urlLink women now can just join the  global  American armed services  for their plastic surgery needs.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hotmail  urlLink has upgraded its e-mail account capacity to 250 MBs . That is still 1/4 the amount that  urlLink gmail  offers (also  urlLink Spymac ,  urlLink Walla , and various other outlets offer 1 GB of storage. But lets face it, gmail is from google and google provides the best user experience known to man today).  Along with the more storage, they promise a more better spam filter. Of course you can take that worth as much as anyone has donated to me using the paypal donate thing to the right (and yes I will continue making references to this every day until someone actually ponies up some dinero). Hotmail has, and in my opinion, always will be the leader in spam profits. How else can you explain that so much spam gets past its "filter" and yet it blocks off known newsletters? Take for example that every time I check my e-mail there is a message from "Cindy" with no subject. You would think after reporting this to Hotmail at least a dozen times, they would figure out this is spam. Nope, still get it at least three times a week.   So I must ask you, can anyone explain why this occurs without saying Microsoft (the owner of Hotmail) makes money from the spam? Yeah, I did not think so.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Try out some  urlLink neurobics . Basically it is a way to exercise your brain. Three easiest exercises you can do include:     Use your non-dominant hand as you go through your morning rituals, such as combing or styling your hair, getting dressed, brushing your teeth, and making your breakfast.    Close your eyes as you shower and use your sense of touch to locate your soap and wash yourself. Your brain must then rely on your other four senses to complete the task.     Turn the pictures on your desk or shelves upside down.  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To start out my series of reviews on books I have read, I would like to start with the all-time classic  urlLink Roots by Alex Haley . This book back in the 1970s was accompanied by a  urlLink TV miniseries  that evolved into the highest rated program in the history of American television. Also the miniseries brought  urlLink The Reading Rainbow guy  into everyones' homes.  urlLink Roots  goes from generation to generation starting with Kunta Kinte during his African childhood to Alex Haley during the Civil Rights movement.  In the first 250 pages, Mr. Haley goes into great detail about the life of Kunta Kinte with his African heritage and his subsequent capture and endeavors as a slave. It is truly compelling as you can feel the joy of Kunta's childhood and then the shock of being taken away from his home and the only way of life that he knows. Once Kunta comes over in a decrepit slave boat, he fights and struggles against the society of the white man. This leads to some severe punishment (I will try not to spoil it too much). But even with all of the hardships that Kunta faces, he still tries to counter the way that they force him live. This happens for around the first ten years he is in America. Upon him being there a whole decade, he finally gives up the hope that he will see Africa again. So he decides he must bond and mate with a fellow female slave. This occurs, and thus Kunta finally has a daughter.  Kunta tries to pass on his heritage as best he can to his offspring. He tells her not to trust the white people as they are evil. Of course, being a daughter, she disobeys and hangs out with the slave owner's daughter. Everything goes fine and dandy with this relationship. Hell, the white girl even taught her how to read and write. This would seem to be a valuable skill, but in the end that was her demise. When she turns 16, Kunta's daughter and her boyfriend find a map that outlines the area. Being that she can read and her boyfriend cannot, she tells him what the map says. The following night, the boyfriend tries to escape, but is caught. When the authorities find the map with him, they ask him if he knew how to read. He says he is not able to. They then torture him until he points out that Kunta's daughter knows how to read and write and that she was the one that told him what everything on the map meant. Having dark skin and being able to read pretty much a horrid predicament to be in back then. So as her punishment, she was shipped off to the local slave auction site.  I feel that I have already spoiled too much, so I will stop with the detailed review. Five more generations ensue and five hundred pages go on. It is truly entertaining throughout.  There is only one problem I have with the book. It says it is nonfiction, but yet there are direct quotes from the people. There is only one way that is possible. That is to assume that for over two hundred years all relatives had a biographer by them every second of their lives. That is just about as likely as a person actually donating money to me by using that paypal donate thing to the right.  All in all, this is a great  fictional  account of the lives that these people had.  urlLink Roots  has so much distinctiveness that it is surpassed by few in its quality.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the dumbass scale  urlLink this guy  has to rank above and beyond anything anyone has ever done.   "Po Dong, 29, a dock worker at the Thai port of Samut Prakan, attempted intercourse with his wife, Kate, on Thursday night.  When she refused he stayed up all night drinking whiskey and made another attempt on Friday, Samut Prakan Police Major Narong Simsawat said.  When this attempt at intimacy also was rebuffed, Po Dong flew into a rage and severed his penis with a pair of scissors. He then cut the severed member into several pieces and stabbed himself in the stomach while screaming abuse at his wife."   Now please excuse me while I cower in fear at the thought of anyone doing this.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Scientists say eating far less food will extend your lifespan . They even go as far to say,   "In the fractious field of aging research, the benefit of reducing calories is one of the few areas of agreement. This means much more than just skipping dessert. It's taking relatively severe steps, such as slashing calories by as much as two-thirds or eating only every other day, which increases life span, studies suggest."   As a person that once only ate one meal per day with no snacking at all, I find it would be very difficult to not succumb to eating at least one thing per day. Of course, that is not to say that I do not believe it will work. So as I sit here doing nothing productive, I feel I might as well try out the extreme experiment. So from this point on I will not eat anything else the entire day and continue that every other day.  Another related note is that there is  urlLink another study suggests many cosmetic items actually might cause cancer . (Sorry, for the registration thing. Just use ihateregistration@dumpit.com as e-mail and thissucks as password)  Unlike the first story, I don't believe that these items are the cause of cancer. It is more of the person using them than the products themselves. In my personal belief, the people using these are very stressed about their love lives and thus resort to using cosmetics to attract that story book lover. When they cannot find this person, they result to becoming increasingly more stressed about their lives. With more and more stress, the body develops some agents that fight and fight against itself which results in cancer. Of course I am no doctor nor am I even intelligent, so what do I know?
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Those that have been with me for a while might have noticed that I am becoming more of a blogger (in the sense that I update several times a day with shorter posts) than my past one long piece per day. The reasons for this are twofold.  First of all, I am now a  urlLink TotalFarker . This basically means I get about 1000 links per day to all the news links around the globe. It is truly a great experience. I sit in front of the computer basically all day and find myself enthralled by all those farking links. This in turn is why I am posting a lot more simple one line posts with a link. I figure that I should share all this wacko news with my audience.  Secondly, I am in the stage of migrating to a better experience than the one that you are currently at. What does that mean? Well lets just say that you will no longer have to type in some foreign extension (.tk) because I will soon be having my very own .com site. Also, (hopefully) I will be able to migrate away from  urlLink Blogger .  Thirdly, I am stuck inside the house most of the day. This limits the amount of things I can criticize about. During the school year, I would simply bitch and moan about all the little nuances that I noticed along the way. Now all I can do is start an  urlLink imaginary battle , belittle some political things that I do not care about, or write some movie/book reviews (which I will probably be doing soon).  I hope that makes some sense. If not,  urlLink pray now that your children do not look like this woman when they grow up .
    
</post>


</Blog>