<Blog>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    sunburnt&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      diagnosis...  multiple sclerosis.  this thing isn't even a goddamn tumor.  guess i'll have to change my description on this blog.  i don't understand at all.  i feel like sisyphus or prometheus--damned, only without any grandiose cause.  did i bring this on myself?  could i have eaten better?  exercised more?  drunk less?  technically i'm still waiting.  of course i'm still waiting.  dr. grady said that the neuropathologist wants to do one more stain, and that should take about a week, but both he, the neuropathologist, dr. pruitt, and everyone who has looked at/been consulted with my case is of the opinion that this is MS.  dr. grady described it as "that's some good news", but the truth is, i would have rathered it be cancer.  cancer is curable.  multiple sclerosis is not.  with cancer, they could have just gone in my head and removed the problem.  with MS, the problem is my own body.    i've been reading a lot, and it's probably all of the wrong literature, about MS and the odd thing is that none of my symptoms are MS symptoms.  there has been no weakness or blurred vision or "droopy limbs".  only the seizures and near seizures and the blocked vision and the almost intolerable and certainly constant headaches.  so what if they're wrong?  what if this isn't MS at all?  what if this is some freakish yet-to-be-discovered abnormality that will strike me dead before i'm 30?  truth be told, lightning or a car could strike me dead before i'm 30.    another thing i've learned through my independent study is a lot of statistics.  85% of MS cases are diagnosed as relapsed-remitting.  within 10 years, 50% of those cases become secondary progressive, which means that they get steadily worse.  there's no remission--it becomes a matter of managing the disability instead of going back and forth from attack to a-okay.  from what i understand, each attack, or relapse, does irreparable damage.  so if i'm 27, and within 10 years i'll be 37, let's just say i'm a little pissed off that my life has been kicked in the balls like this.    okay, "a little pissed off" is the understatement of the year.  MS won't kill me, and brain cancer could have, but now i have to live the rest of my life waiting for the next relapse to impair me just a little bit more.  i'm so angry and full of rage about this that i can't even think of anything appropriate to write.  i feel like i'm on some sort of pendulum swinging back and forth between wanting to cry myself dry and wanting to put my fist through the wall.    ---  my grandmother just called.  i love her dearly and think she's one of the truest and kindest and most amazing women in the world, and the sound of her voice did well to diffuse the mood i was in a few minutes ago.  we cried together in our conversation.  i've never really cried with her before.  perhaps i've been too busy being "granddaughter" to actually let myself be vulnerable to the one woman in my life who has seen way more than i could possibly throw at her.  i feel brokenhearted right now--i could barely speak to her through my tears.  and her tears?  i just can't handle that.    i think this is all i can write for tonight.  i'm a wreck.  i should probably get some clarity on this before i try to write any more.  there have to be some positives--i just don't see them right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      still waiting...  with headaches all the time.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      episode...  right now i am weak and dizzy and tired but not sleepy and a little shaken up.  i've had this really awful headache on and off since midday yesterday.  when i woke up today i took 3 tylenol extra strength and went to church.  during and after the headache was still bad--hurting the most in the front behind my eyes, but sometimes moving around my head.  i called dad, who told me to call dr. kearney who suggested that i go into the ER at HUP so they can track what's going on to see if there has been any change.  meanwhile, the headache was awful, and i started feeling numb off and on and i thought that a seizure was coming on.  i was convinced of it--to the point where i cleared everything off the bed in case i started to convulse.  i had stean call dr. grady's answering service and explain what was happening to see if we could get his advice.  i guess one of the benefits of being chief of neurosurgery is that you get your weekends off, because the doctor on call called back.  but in the time between i started to feel better.  before that, though, it was so terrible--i was confused, my thinking was crazy, i felt weak and light all over, i thought i was becoming paralyzed--but i didn't want to go to the hospital because i knew that all they would do was put me on a stretcher and stick an IV in my arm and leave me there forever and then run some tests and leave me there for another forever and then run some more tests and i just hate that whole process.  maybe i should have gone in; if it happens again i will go in.  the only thing i would stand to gain would be access to a sedative to ease the almost intolerable level of anxiety that i'm feeling.    i'm so afraid.  i'm terrified.  i don't understand what is happening to me and i don't know what i can do to make it any better.  i'm forced to sit here and wait and hope that things don't complicate themselves any further.    cancer.  multiple sclerosis.  brain tumor.  this has been going on for a month now and i have heard a lot of terms thrown at me from a lot of different directions.  i don't know what to make of this or where to start putting the pieces together.  all i know is that none of this feels real.  i keep waiting for it to pass, like a dream or a bad movie.  soon i'll wake up or the credits will roll and this will be over and i'll be able to return to life as i knew it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      research study...  the MRI i had done this morning is part of a research study that penn is doing that uses spectroscopy with MRI technology to help diagnose brain abnormalities without having to do surgery (i.e., a biopsy).  even though i had already had the biopsy done, there's still some confusion as to what this thing is, so i fell right into the category of patients that meet criteria for this study.    the scan lasted almost an hour--about twice the amount of time for a typical brain MRI.  a typical MRI uses a 1.5 tesla magnet, this one uses a 3 tesla magnet (by the way, terms like "spectroscopy" and "tesla" mean absolutely nothing to me).  at one point in the scan, the MRI tube SHOOK!!!  holy crap.  i hate MRIs.  i've never been claustrophobic in my life, but being stuck in a tube that is so small that the top is only inches from my eyes is just a little too much for me.  just thinking about it makes me anxious--think being buried alive but with an opening at your feet.  it's miserable, and quite a challenge to spend an hour trying to distract yourself from thinking about the fact that you're in a little tube with loud knocking and buzzing noises all around you.  anyway, it's over now.  i made it through.  and hopefully this will be the last of the MRIs for a while.  i got my biopsy slides from graduate hospital on thursday and dropped them off to dr. grady's office on friday.  i was told that i'd hear from dr. grady "mid-week".  so here's to more waiting...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      more tests, more waiting...  my neurologist is pretty keen on this MS idea.  it was her first thought when she looked at my MRI films, and even though my symptoms aren't consistent with those of multiple sclerosis, i think she's leaning towards that as a viable diagnosis.  but she, just like the neurosurgeon i saw this morning, says that we need to do more tests, that we don't know enough yet to decide what to do.    multiple sclerosis?  holy crap.  now i've gone from bad to worse.   i go from kill-me-quick deadly tumor to won't-kill-me-but-i'll-wish-it-did lifelong debilitating illness.    i don't know anything yet.  i shouldn't get ahead of myself.  i do know, though, that the inside of my left elbow, where the phlebotomist took blood today, hurts like god almighty.  nothing like having your innards searched with a giant needle until the blood starts flowing.    and i thought 2003 was bad...  i shudder to think what 2005 will bring.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      second opinion...  new doc, new thoughts, bad news.  he says it looks like a grade 3, according to the MRI and the radiology report and the fact that it wasn't there 2 years ago.  i'll get some more specific MRI scans done in the next day or so, and he wants my biopsy slides to be reviewed by the penn neuropathologist.  his other theory is that it could be multiple sclerosis.    he showed me on the MRI the places where the tumor has infiltrated the healthy tissue.  i hate it i hate it i hate it i hate it i don't understand how this is happening and today i feel ready to fall apart and just die from the sheer magnitude of this.  what the fuck.  what the fuck.    at any rate, the tumor must come out as soon as possible in my opinion.    i'll see the neurologist/neuro-oncologist at 2:00.  i was hoping that i wouldn't need her, but it looks like i may after all.  i hate hope.  i hate these glimmers of something better that pop up in the haze of really bad news, because everything is so uncertain anyway and i wish i was never told that it could be a lower grade.  i wish it had never been suggested to me.  i told myself not to believe it could be true until there was more supporting evidence, but i went and did it anyway, and now i feel so fragile and terrified and foolish and deceived.    cancer.  you know, in all honesty, i had steeled myself up for it so much last week when i was told i had it, i did a really good job convincing myself that this wouldn't be a big deal and that i would beat it no problem.  i was ready and determined and wanted to just get started with it.  and then when i was told that maybe it wasn't cancer, this small part of me (this is about as honest as it gets here) was almost disappointed that i wouldn't have the chance to fight that fight.  i guess it's as if i were all riled up to go to war, and then i was told that the battle got called off.  it's stupid, but there's this transcendency that comes with the title "cancer survivor", like those folks know more than the rest of us could, they've seen the other side or something.  i wanted a piece of that.  i wanted to see what those folks get to see.  there's no challenge in having a benign tumor, just a little bit of a scare.  but now that the prospect of cancer is back, holy shit--what was i thinking?  i don't want this.  i don't know if i can handle this.  i'm more frightened than i've ever been of anything ever in my life.  i've got to figure out a way to keep things together so that i can fight this.    is this what i get for feeling like the jilted soldier?  did i bring this on myself?  because now i feel defeated and i haven't even started.    oh my god.  someone tell me this isn't real.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      gustave courbet, waves...  let me go way back for a minute, to my inspiration to start keeping this weblog.  the week i got out of the hospital, my dad came to visit.  i don't think anything could have been better than having him here.  he went through so much of this with my mother and he's always had the wisdom and perspective that i lack to help me keep things from getting bigger than they need to be.    one of the things we did while he was here was to make use of my VIP tickets for the "manet and the sea" (or as dad called it, in one of his groan-worthy but terrific moments of wit, "old manet and the sea") exhibition at the philadelphia museum of art.  dad enjoyed it, but i found the exhibition to be colossally boring.  part of it could have been that i was feeling miserable and depressed and overwhelmed and exhausted on the day we went to see it, but i've spent a lot of time in that art museum and i can say objectively that this was not one of their better shows.  besides, old manet's paintings were only about 30% of the works on display.  the others were done by his contemporaries or by folks who some curator decided inspired his seascapes somewhere along the way.    we got the audio tour headsets so we could migrate ever-so-slowly with the masses of people who also got the audio tour.  i didn't use mine.  it was nice and quiet in there with everyone else listening to their headphones.  i'm not one for impressionism and i lose patience quickly with crowds.  and this situation was exacerbated by my inability to see to my right (have i even mentioned this yet?  the tumor is has limited my sight so i have no peripheral vision to my right.  instead of having a normal field of vision, i'd say i'm probably at about 80%.  from what i can tell, this is not likely to change any time soon).  major exhibitions at major art museums are so clumsy.  the works are laid out with a path in mind, generally chronological, but you end up bottlenecking with the same folks listening to the same audio tour spiel and you never really get any peace.    so i wandered around, checked out the paintings with the smallest crowds, took advantage of the spaces where they became available.  and i found myself face to face with a painting that brought me to tears...  "waves" by gustave courbet, 1869.  i will freely admit that i don't understand visual composition or the balance of color or chiaroscuro or pointillism et cetera, but this painting filled me with a sadness that was so familiar to the sadness i was already feeling.  the image is simple--giant waves crashing on a sandy beach, empty except for a small deserted boat.  you can see other boats way off in the distance.  but what got me was the sky--it was blue at the top of the canvas, but as it fell to meet the sea, the clouds congested and darkened, making this mess of sea and weather and blue and grey right in the middle of the image that made me want to dive right into it.    it was like the beginning of _the voyage of the dawn treader_, the painting in lucy's room.  it struck me and i must have stood in front of it for 15 minutes.  it was so beautiful and i felt so small and so... ...afraid.    i walked around a bit more in the exhibition, but i kept coming back to the courbet.  so many thoughts were in my head and i realized that things are going to happen to me in this whole brain tumor process, i'm going to feel things and see things and do things, and it's probably a good idea to start writing those things down.  i said in an e-mail to valerie sayers last night that i want this experience to change my life.  i don't really know how one goes about changing one's life, but i would think it is something that happens one step at a time, and probably pretty undramatically for the most part.    so that's that.  emily's brilliant how-i-survived-brain-cancer weblog, inspired by a silly painting.  though, it seems that it's always the small things that move the most mountains.  we'll see how this goes.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      google's pawn...  i was just about to close my blog, left open in another window, and i noticed two listings in the ad bar at the top of the page...  one was for an epilepsy study and the other was for an anti-seizure medication.  i must be hallucinating, right?  how could the internet have infiltrated the sanctity of my home?  so i clicked on the refresh button...  an ad for gamma knife radiation therapy, with "related searches:  brain cancer".  damn.    i'm so naive.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      anaplastic astrocytoma...  diagnosis?  grade three, malignant tumor.  standard therapy includes surgery and radiation, followed by chemotherapy.  there will be regular MRIs and regular check-ups.  i am now a cancer patient.    lots of weird things about this.  first of all, the chemo could last one and possibly two years.  dr. neff says that chemotherapy for brain tumors typically isn't so strong that one loses one's hair and gets really sick.  but still...  chemo...  i keep thinking of myself looking like gollum--green with a really bad combover...  the really awful, heartbreaking risk with this is that because of where the tumor is, i could lose my ability to read.  not to see or speak or spell or write or comprehend, but my ability to see letters and translate those letters into the concepts they represent.  i wouldn't be able to read!  it's not just about books, it's about menus at restaurants and price tags at stores and news headlines and whose number is on the caller ID and subtitles on foreign movies and using the internet and reading a map and absolutely everything about going to law school!  and almost as heartbreaking, a very close second, is that it is dr. neff's very strong recommendation that i postpone law school for a year so that my treatment doesn't interfere.  it only makes sense, if i can't read and all.  but i told him i wasn't willing yet to commit to that decision.  he said he'll support me whatever i decide to do.    stean and i spent over an hour and a half with dr. neff, going over what to expect and how things would work and who i should talk to and what all of this meant.  i was glad i had the prior warning so that this didn't come as such a shock.  i honestly felt (and still feel) okay about it.  cancer.  no big thing.  this is just one of the many many obstacles that life will give me to overcome.  true, this one will be a little more difficult than others, but it's nothing i can't handle.    but...  here's the weird part:  as stean and i were leaving, headed back to work, my cell phone rang.  it was dr. neff, calling to tell me that while we were meeting, the pathologist had called to say that his diagnosis of the anaplastic astrocytoma was not conclusive and he believed my tumor to be of a lower grade.    huh?  so now it's grade two, benign brain tumor?  and that radiation and chemo stuff is irrelevant?  so, dr. neff was going to take the slides to a different lab to get a second opinion.  good grief.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      grade 3...  tomorrow.  finally tomorrow i'll get the pathology results.  in less than 24 hours i will know and i can start moving forward.    i talked to dr. neff today, who went to the lab himself to find out what was taking so long, and he told me a lot of stuff about cell growth and stains and blah blah blah, and then he said, "we'll know for sure when the report is finished, but it looks to me like we're dealing with something a little worse than i had first thought, but not as bad as it could be." and of course i wanted to know what that meant.  so here goes...  as i understand it, tumors are categorized as grades, ranging from 1 (very benign) to 4 (very malignant).  originally, he had thought that this was a 1 or a 2.  after these tests, it looks like a 3.    i had an appointment with my primary care doc today that i had made a while ago, before all of this happened, to see if  (of all things) she could prescribe me some acne meds so i can clear up my skin before schoss's wedding in july.  ah, vanity.  so i went, with a much different agenda than when i set up the appointment, and i told her all of this, and she said to me, "that's cancer.  you know that, right?" and i said (crying, of course, because i seem to burst into tears all the time now), "yep."    but then she said, "well, we have to get it out."  not, "oh you're going to die", but "we have to get it out", as if it's a bad houseguest who is drinking all of the beer.  so maybe it's not so bad.  i mean, it's bad, obviously--i have brain cancer.  but maybe i'll survive it.  i mean, obviously i'll survive it.  but maybe this won't be as bad as i fear.  she thinks that what dr. neff will suggest will be surgery to remove as much as can be removed, then radiation and possibly some chemotherapy.  i say bring it on--let's get this bastard out of my body before it invites its friends.    now, before anybody gets fooled into thinking i'm being really strong despite just having gotten a preliminary cancer diagnosis, let me just say that i freaked out earlier today.  and i cried in my doctor's office.  and tomorrow, when i hear all of this in it's actuality, i will probably cry again, and then freak out.  but now i'm in a good moment.  it's a beautiful day, i just took the dog out for a walk, she got peed on by a great dane in the dog park.  things could be worse--at least i wasn't peed on.    (i mean, sure, i could tell you how the whole time today during the baby shower we had at work for one of my co-workers i was thinking about how maybe i'll never know what it feels like to be pregnant or to have a kid to ground for doing something stupid, but you've read enough of that in earlier entries and it's all terribly boring anyway.)  things will get worse.  and they'll get better.  and then they'll get worse again.  and then they'll get better.  my goal is to make sure they spend more time on the better end than on the worse.  and that ultimately they end on the better.    the big C.  right behind heart disease for the biggest killer.  well, screw you, big C.  you picked the wrong brain (quite possibly the worst pun ever made) in which to crash.    one more thing (and i hope i don't die and suddenly these blog postings become something that gets distributed to my family at the funeral), i went to confession this afternoon.  i went because more than anything, i'm looking for some courage and some peace of mind and somewhere to draw some strength.  so i fell back on the most basic of my catholic grade school tenets--need help?  talk to a priest!    well, as i should have predicted, it didn't exactly turn into the soul-cleansing moment of clarity i hoped it would be.  despite my attempts to explain to the priest, who was a very kind man and very well-versed in the chatechism, that i didn't know what to do with my fears and my weakness at a time in my life in which i wanted faith and strength, he went through the 10 commandments to make sure we covered all of my sins.   sigh...  what was i thinking?  it was the sacrament of reconcilliation!  at least now i can go forward with a clear conscience, except that i don't really feel repentant for having "fornicated".  he told me as my penance to read psalm 86.  i haven't done it yet.  could it be that my solace and strength could be in that psalm?  i won't put that expectation on it, but i'll try to be open to whatever it has to tell me.  and, despite the 8 to 10 years that have passed since i've gone to confession, i still managed to recite the act of contrition verbatim.  damn right.  see that brain tumor?  you ain't got shit  (oh well, there goes that clearing of conscience for the swear words).    tomorrow and tomorrow and tomorrow...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      nineteen days...  in my PDA i keep cutting-and-pasting "dr. neff appt." from one day to the next.  everytime i call to verify that they have gotten the pathology results from my biopsy, they either tell me that the pathologist needs a few more days or that he's out of the office or something else that sounds totally made up to me.  it has been nineteen days since the biopsy.  i've gone from contentedly waiting to increasingly paranoid.  in my mind (i hate that all equivalent phrases--in my head, my thoughts, whatever--now carry this stupid irony) this thing has fingers like the tree in _poltergeist_ and is rapidly taking over all facets of neurological function.  soon, i'll be a vegetable and i'm sure to be incontinent.    [the dog just plopped herself down on stean's dirty laundry--i'm glad he's not here to see this]  carrie, one of our MCAT teachers, stopped by the office yesterday and talked to me for a while.  she said that there are many many different types of brain tumors, and if the pathology doesn't get it right, the treatment for some type of tumor that i don't have could kill me.  this makes me feel only slightly better.  did i mention it's been 19 days?  another fun fact:  it's been 22 days since my seizures.  19/22nds = way too long.    a brain tumor?  i mean, a fucking brain tumor???  i read (i have to stop reading things about this) that only 16,000 people get diagnosed with a brain tumor per year!  16,000?  that's not even enough people to get enraged about!  it's like a minor human rights violation, the kind that gets overlooked for the bigger ones that impact more people, the somalian refugees, the apartheids, the breast cancers, the heart diseases.  jesus.  who the hell gets a brain tumor?    nothing feels normal anymore.  nothing.  not even sleeping.  not even taking a shower or going to the bathroom or watching a movie.  i always feel like i'm on medication and i constantly think about it.  i might die from this.  i'm 27, hardly an adult.  there are things i want to do.  like this stuff:  graduate from law school  love my career marry stean be a good mother run a marathon grow my own garden play the piano  see?  these aren't extravagant or unrealistic.  i just want to be given the chance to get old.  i've never wanted to get old more in my life.    i'm seriously so angry and afraid and confused over all this stuff and i know that having the answers that these tests will provide is not necessarily going to make anything better, but at least it would feel like progress.  maybe i died in the biopsy and this is my hell--i'm damned to sit around and wait for results that will never come and just feel terrified and uncertain.    deep breath.  okay, some positive things.  even if i have to force myself to think of them.   i've been going to church.  i don't know what it does or what i believe within its context, but as a friend said, when i ran into him after easter sunday mass, "it just makes you feel better."  i cried so much during good friday services.  i don't know what came over me--i just felt so overwhelmed.  i didn't blubber or anything, but there was a pretty steady stream of tears.    i'm getting more comfortable with the idea of losing my hair.  and i think i've decided that i'm not going to be one of those everyday wig-wearers.  that's just silly.  unless i have a giant scar, but i shouldn't get too ahead of myself.  i paid all of my bills a little ahead of where i thought i'd be this month.  always positive.   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the spotless mind...  due to my inexplicable fascination with elijah wood (by the way, newest celebrity crush?  mark ruffalo--brain tumor survivor), i've been wanting to see _eternal sunshine of the spotless mind_ for months now, regularly checking it's imdb.com listing for release date information and reviews (although i couldn't care less for the charlie kaufman hype).  tonight we went to see it, stean and i and our friend jenn.  we sat about 2/3rds of the way back in a relatively empty theater.  i got a headache pretty early on, par for the course with these anti-seizure meds.  but then about 40 minutes in, the aura started.  it happened during a sequence in the movie in which the music had a lot of squeaky stringy instrument sounds, combined with a lot of flashing edit cuts and the screen seemed to get really big and imposing.  i covered my eyes, hoping that whatever was being triggered would be evaded, and i reached for the carbamazepine, thinking that if i could get some drugs in my system it could keep things from getting to seizure point.  (i kept thinking about all those stories about kids seizing because of the flashing lights in video games.)  there was no seizure, thankfully.  between the meds and the eye covering and the getting up and leaving the theater, things settled down.  i did feel confused and upset for a while, but that subsided, too.   the pre-seizure.  it's the strangest feeling, the most difficult-to-articulate feeling.  i tried to describe it to stean (my hero, who paid for our movie tickets and who left with me without the slightest complaint even though for once he was actually enjoying a movie i wanted to see), and i can think of only one thing that comes close, something from my younger, more foolish days, back when i thought i was invincible, a feeling that has been completely eradicated from my understanding of life in the past few weeks--it's like a bad drug experience.  everything feels immediate and crippling, as if you can feel yourself sliding away, but you're powerless to stop it.  it ain't fun.     we walked home.  i cried a lot.  the randomness of disease leaves me reeling.  i grew this thing--this tumor happened in me.  call it a mutation or a fluke or just plain bad luck, but its cells are derived from my cells.  how unfair...  my entire life i've been this nerdy smart kid.  gifted classes in grade school, skipped 5th grade because of high IQ, good at standardized tests, hell-bent college bound as a teenager, have toyed with the idea of joining mensa.  i feel as if my greatest attribute, the part of me of which i have always been most proud, is now betraying me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      suzanne...  when my father was here last week, at a moment when i was at the computer, i scrolled through the music on my computer to play some songs.  one of my selections was "suzanne" by leonard cohen.  my father told me, "i wanted to name you suzanne, you know."    !!!  somewhere in a parallel universe i am so much cooler because i am named after a leonard cohen song.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      on the way to work...  i just ran into a girl i used to work with when i was doing part-time telemarketing at the art museum.  it was so nice to see her, she's such a cool girl.  i didn't say anything to her about the tumor.  why should i?  it's good to have people not know.  god i hate this.  this is so strange and convoluted and abstruse.  do i tell everyone?  does my life need that level of exposure?  and how do i deal with it with the people who do know?  i want to talk about it all the time.  it's all i think about right now.  i took the dog for a walk on monday after work and we went to the dog park and while i was watching her run around, i had this moment of realization that i had forgotten about the tumor.  but of course, that moment of realization brought the thoughts back.  it's like one of those really distracting high school crushes that you wish you could stop thinking about, but it's always there.  always on your mind, if you will.  in all truthfulness, thinking about it is all i want to do.  i know that this is going to teach me something and that it can change my life forever.  what i will learn and how those changes will manifest is yet to be revealed.    it's been 15 days since the seizures.  15 days isn't a lot of time.  it feels like an eternity.  so much has happened.  so much will happen yet.    going back to an earlier thought, i want to talk about this all the time.  it is the single most important thing in my life right now.  however, it is not the single most important thing for anyone else.  not even my dad, not even stean.  this is my brain, and my brain's little guest, and it's up to me to situate my need to talk about it within the larger context of life's goings-on.  it's unfair for me to talk about it with people all the time.  it is the kind of thing that makes people uncomfortable because there are no answers, no correct responses.  i remember so well how things happened when mom died.  the first week or two, people were so kind and thoughtful and they asked how everything was going.  but after that, they moved on with their stuff.  it's completely natural--i'm guilty of it myself when the situation has been a friend's.  but unfortunately, things don't get better so quickly for the one who is grieving.  this totally feels like grief--it has the same patterns of ups and downs, there are moments when i want the coldness of this situation to embrace me and there are moments when i just want it to sit next to me and be quiet.  but i can't get rid of it.    last night on my way home from ceramics i got really sad.  in class everyone's pretty quiet, working on their pieces.  the past 15 days have been uncharacteristically social in that people have been around, have wanted to know updates.  but for three hours last night i was back in an element that didn't include this tumor.  and, of course, i thought about it the entire three hours.  and as i was walking home i felt lonely and sad and i wanted to talk to someone.  so i scrolled through the numbers on my cell phone and the only one i felt that it would be okay to call was my brother.  of all the friends i have, all the people who have encouraged me to call any time if i needed to talk, the only person i felt i could bother with it was my brother, who was at work and couldn't really talk.  i've never really been good at leaning on people.  i guess that might be one of the lessons this will teach me, too.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      interlude...  i had planned to finish telling the story about the hospital and all of that funness, but i'll get to that someday perhaps.    here's the thing.  i know this is only 2 weeks old, i know that it takes time to accept and adjust and all of that crap, but i'm sick of this already.  on my way to ceramics class tonight i got lost.  I GOT FUCKING LOST!  i've been taking classes at this place for well over a year and i totally blanked on the address!  i hate being on this anti-seizure medication.  i hate it so much.  it makes me forget things.  it makes me dizzy.  it makes my brain slow.  forgive me for not seeing the tradeoff.    what if this is how it is now?  i'm starting law school in the fall.  in less than five months i'll be realizing the goal i've had for years.  and i'm sitting here waiting for the goddamn pathology results on a biopsy that was done a week and a half ago and i'm slowly becoming a complete moron just so i don't have another seizure.    i'd rather run the risk.  i'd take the seizures over being stupid.    i don't want this to be happening.  not to me.  not at all.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the hospital...  i spent tuesday evening through midday saturday in the hospital.  until my biopsy on friday, i was in room 461, in the telemetry ward, which is like the middle ground between your regular run-of-the-mill hospital room and intensive care.  the primary difference is that in the telemetry ward, you're hooked up to a heart monitor all the time and a nurse comes in every 4 hours to check your vital signs.  during the first few hours i was there on tuesday, i wasn't allowed out of bed at all, so i had to use a bed pan to go to the bathroom.  few things are less graceful than urinating in what looks like a shallow, plastic, upside-down cowboy hat while you're mostly horizontal in a bed and connected via wires and 5 electrode pads to a heart monitor.    every 8 hours i took my dilantin, 100 mg, in time-release pill form.  i was given IV fluids to keep me hydrated and, although i had no restrictions on my diet, i was fed the blandest, most visually uninteresting food ever served.  the truth was that i didn't have much of an appetite anyway, so it was probably for the best that they brought me food that i didn't care for.    on wednesday, when it started to be obvious that i wasn't going to be able to go home for another day or so, i began the process of letting people know.  my father already knew, and had passed along news to family.  stean knew, and had told a couple of our closest friends.  i sat there in a hospital room in the middle of the day wondering who do i tell and how do i tell them.  i didn't really call many people at first.  i was in and out of the room all day having tests done.  first a CT scan of my head, then an MRI.  and finally an EEG.    and then they told me...  there was something in my brain.  i saw the MRI film--it was undeniably there--a smallish white thing in my left occipital lobe.  what it was they couldn't say just yet--it could have been an abscess, or maybe a cyst, and of course, there was the possibility that it was a tumor.  highly unlikely, they told me.  most probably an abscess, and they could drain it easily enough, prescribe me some antibiotics, and send me on my way.  but first, more tests...  so thursday i had CT scans of my abdomen and pelvis, and a test whose name i forget but that involved my remaining totally still for 42 minutes while a giant metal disc rotated slowly around my head.  holy hospital bills, batman, i thank god that this didn't happen six weeks earlier, before my health insurance benefits kicked in with my new job.    and the questioning.  constant questioning.  most of the time the same questions...  did you soil yourself during the seizure?  have you been out of the country recently?  do you have any prior history of seizures?  do you abuse drugs or alcohol?  have you hit your head recently?  the answer to all of the questions was no.  this all came completely out of the blue.    i was able to tell more people, and asked them to make some calls.  friends came to hang out in the evening.  i called my friend jessie.  our phone conversation went like this: emily:  hey, um, so, i had a couple of seizures and i'm in the hospital now.  there's something in my brain. jessie:  what?  which hospital? emily:  graduate jessie:  i'll be there this afternoon.   and she was--took the train down from new york and stayed for two nights.  took care of the dog and cats at night while stean stayed in the hospital with me.    i was scheduled for a biopsy for midday on friday.  brain surgery.  they'd put some sort of metal halo on my head and use a CT scan to set the exact coordinates for the drill to put a small hole in my skull, into which a small blunt needle would be inserted that would push the healthy brain tissue aside and puncture the unwelcome mass.  then they would extract cells from the mass--if they got liquid, it's a relatively easy fix and everybody's happy.  if they don't, then we start to have more serious conversations.  early that morning i had the last of my tests done, a CT scan of my chest, which, like the scan of my abdomen and pelvis, was totally free of disease.  this was a good sign, because it meant that there was no cancer elsewhere in my body that could have metastasized into my brain.  i was hopeful that i'd get out of this experience with nothing worse than a small bald patch as a souvenir of the biopsy.  when the time came for the biopsy, my neurosurgeon (my neurosurgeon?!) asked me who i wanted him talk to after the procedure.  i appointed stean and jessie and our friend joe.  they rolled me into the operating room and i met the anesthesiologist and everyone who would be involved in the procedure, then they put me to sleep.  i woke up with the halo on my head, en route to CT scan again.  i remember the whole episode--i couldn't move at all because of my giant metal headgear.  i had the scan, they took me back to the OR, i had just enough time to start getting nervous about the procedure before the anesthesiologist did his magic and i was out.      when i woke up, the halo was gone, my head felt dull and throbbed slightly, all was blurry (i didn't have my glasses with me), and one of the residents was there saying, "emily?  everything went well, but it wasn't an abscess--we didn't get fluid."  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the beginning, the seizures...  last tuesday, i was in a cab on my way to a lunch meeting with my boss and two of my coworkers.  we had to make a detour so my boss could pick something up and i started to feel really dizzy.  i thought it was motion sickness, so while my boss was running her errand, i got out of the cab to get some fresh air.  we had stopped on a small hill, and i kept losing my footing and stumbling a bit.  i had gotten motion sickness enough times to know that this was unusual.  my boss came back, and thinking that the feeling would pass, i got back in the cab.  we made it about 4 blocks up the road and i was feeling increasingly nauseous and light-headed, so i asked the cab driver to let me out and i told my co-workers that i would just walk the rest of the way (it was about a 20 block walk to our destination, but all i could think at that point was that i wanted out of the car) and meet them there.  i got out, feeling incredibly out of it and dizzy, and called stean, just because i felt so awful and needed to tell someone.  i probably spent a minute or two on the phone with him and then the right side of my body started to twitch so i hung up.  my co-workers had gotten out of the cab and had come back to check on me.  i got really nervous--my right leg, arm, and eye were all twitching like mad and my peripheral vision on my right side started to tunnel and flash, as if someone were holding a strobe light directly at the side of my head.  my head was spinning, everyone was asking me if i was okay, if i was hungry, if i wanted to sit down, if i wanted to go to the hospital (coincidentally enough, we were a block away from a hospital).  someone ran off to get me something to eat.  i sat down on the ground and held on tenaciously to a fence to try and steady myself.  and that's the last thing i remember.  i regained consciousness in the emergency room wearing a hospital gown, with a plastic hospital id bracelet on my wrist, an IV in my arm, and electrodes on my chest.  i have never in my life felt such fear.  i had no recollection of how i had gotten there or where i had been before.  it was as if i had just come into existence at that moment.  i was very awake very quickly.  one of the nurses called me by name and told me that i had just had a seizure.  i started crying.  i didn't have seizures.  i've never had seizures.  it just wasn't possible.  he asked me if i knew what day and year it was.  i had no idea.  i stared at him, trying desperately to pull that information out of my head, but i honestly didn't know.  it was such a simple question, but i couldn't answer him.  he told me that it was march 23rd, 2004 and that it's very normal to come out of a seizure feeling disoriented and confused and that i would start to feel like myself soon.  but i was so afraid.  i didn't recognize anyone around me.    i settled down, and my co-workers were allowed into the ER to see me.  i made sure that someone called stean and my dad.  stean got to the hospital quickly.  things seemed okay for a bit, but then i started to get the "aura" that i had earlier in the day, before my seizure.  sure enough, i went into a second seizure, after which they loaded me up with IV dilantin and a sedative which pretty much put me out for the rest of the afternoon.  because of the second seizure, i was admitted to the hospital so some tests could be run to figure out what was going on.      
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      blandly going where...  four weeks now.  still can't completely taste anything i eat.  it's not like it's life-threatening or that it leaves me significantly disabled, but it's unbelievably frustrating and annoying.    saw ESotSM again and i'm convinced that i'm in love with this movie.  i file it into the very solipsistic category of "showing up in my life when it is most needed/relevant".    when i lived in boston, settling into myself after the silly, idealistic, romanticized notion known as "college", i spent a lot of really good time by myself.  i would take the T into the city and explore, wander around for hours.  i'd have my headphones on, listening to whatever suited my mood.  me at 22.  god, i was such a baby--it feels like lifetimes ago.  but these moments were and are so valuable to me because they are the world as it is most beautiful, the world on my terms.  lately i've been looking for those moments again.  i can't tell if it's some sort of retreat into what feels best or a regression into what feels safe and insulated.  it may be that both are true and neither is bad.  the other day i was walking through rittenhouse square on my way to the gym and this group of young parents were guiding their small children through a game of t-ball.  it was the loveliest thing i've ever seen.    i'm not really sure where i'm going with this, but ESotSM puts me in that place.  i have this favorite emotion, and i know it's kind of lame to have a favorite emotion, but i love feeling enchanted, but in a heartbroken and melancholic way.  like "famous blue raincoat" by leonard cohen or "trains across the sea" by the silver jews.  like that gustave courbet painting _waves_.  it's this feeling that casts the perfect light on how fated and transient and broken we all are, but also is able to celebrate that very vulnerability.  ESotSM falls in that category.  so does _magnolia_.          i told stean the other night, as i was crying myself silly, that i feel like the velveteen rabbit.  like i'm going to be thrown away because i'm full of sickness.  stean reminded me that the velveteen rabbit was made real because of that experience.  the weird thing is, i believe that will happen to me, too.  but i have to get through this whole thrown-away part before i can make it to the resurrection.  and it feels like i have a long way to go before i get there. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      eternal sunshine...  finally saw "eternal sunshine of the spotless mind".  i thought it was beautiful.  i think i'm obsessed with it.  i'm going to see it again this afternoon.  there was something about the theme of fighting to keep your experiences yours even though that control has been given over to someone/thing else that hit home pretty hard.    i told stean that he and i are joel and clementine, and he (reluctantly, because he says i analyze things too much) agreed.  sometimes he's j and i'm c and other times i'm j and he's c.  perhaps it's just a movie with some truth to it for those of us who have imperfect relationships, to remind us that those imperfections are what make the relationships worthwhile.  ...oh, and i've decided that i'll dye my hair as red as a crayon after amy's wedding.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      nose to the grindstone/balls to the wall...  i just wrote out this long post about this giant melee that's been brewing at work this past week and then deleted every bit of it.  it's just not something that's worth remembering.    the one point i'll note is this:  in the midst of sitting through a childish attack by my boss today inspired by a miscommunication between her and the guy who reports to me that she blew way out of proportion, i found myself wanting to blurt out in my defense, "woman, do you have any idea what i've been going through in the past couple of months?!  do you have any idea of the kinds of horrific thoughts that constantly drift in and out of my head?!"  i know that i've met her head-on a couple of times when i've felt that she was making demands that were unrealistic or short-sighted, and each time i've done it, she's reacted personally and has attacked me personally.  i know that perhaps my biggest workplace weakness is knowing when to keep quiet and how to speak when i must... but good god--in my own defense, my first impulse was to fall back on this stupid disease?!  how sad have i become that i would allow myself to let this become my scapegoat!?  how irresponsible and petty am i?!  where is my head these days?!    ugh, i just did it again--wrote out a discourse on the bizarre injustices of my workplace.  not.  worth.  remembering!  shift.  scroll.  delete!  okay, nine weeks.  nine weeks from today i give my notice.  i just have to behave for nine weeks.    hey!  nine weeks ago today i had a brain biopsy!   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      imperfect decisions...  dr pruitt called yesterday.  there was no presence of the oligoclonal bands in my spinal fluid that would have confirmed the diagnosis of MS. but, just because it doesn't say that it is MS, that doesn't mean that it confirms that it isn't.  i've reached a weird point in the past few days.  i want to go on as normal, but i can't.  i don't even know what i have.  and now i've had two tests (the spinal tap and the visual evoked potential) that have been negative for multiple sclerosis.  so then, what the hell do i have?  is it MS?  is it an MS-like occurrence?  is it something else altogether?    these are the things that i think about when i try to fall asleep.  i think about what this means for the rest of my life.  i think about who i'll become as a result of this disease.  i think about how i will be limited as a result of this disease.  i still feel afraid.  i suppose there is always an element of fear in what we can't know.  when this was a tumor, dr neff said i'd have to make "imperfect decisions".  dr pruitt said to me when i finally talked to her this morning that we were making an "imperfect decision".  in the midst of so much ambiguity, i just want to hear something absolute.  so, after dr p called yesterday, i called back and left a message with her secretary saying that i have a few questions.  she called back yesterday evening, of course when i wasn't able to get to the phone.  but she called again this morning, at about 8:30.  i missed her call originally, but called her right back.  i told her that i know that tests can't always confirm or rule out diagnoses, but i have this patient (as in one who is cared for medically, not as in one who is okay with waiting--i am certainly not that) need to put a name to what is going on with me.  so here goes...  Clinically Isolated Syndrome (CIS) consistent with demyelination (MS).  i have probable laboratory supported evidence which suggests multiple sclerosis, but i've only had a single demyelinating event.    so, while the spinal tap and the evoked potentials did not confirm MS, the MRI and the biopsy did.  presenting with seizures.  looking like a tumor.  good god.  makes my head spin.  almost literally.    basically, i will probably have another episode within the next year or two, so dr p wants to go ahead with the avonex to better my chances of not having another episode.  i should be on the avonex next week.  an imperfect decision, but given what we know, it seems like the best one to make.  in the meantime, she's going to push up my MRI date (currently scheduled for june 8th) by a week so she can see what is going on, then put me on steroids to lessen the inflamation so i can (hopefully) get my sight back.  apparently, the steroids will send my appetite through the roof and i'll get all revved up.  um, great?    at least i have a name.  at least i had the ambiguity confirmed by someone who has a lot more knowledge than i do.  at least i'm going to be doing something about it.  somehow all of this doesn't really offer me any relief right now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      61 days...  it was march 23rd, about this same time of the day, when i woke up in an emergency room.  i just sent an e-mail out to friends who have been so good and patient about sending me messages to check up on me, messages to which i've been too absent-minded and distracted to respond.  in it i described the past two months as the most bizarre and out of control of my life.  that is most certainly true.    i thought at first to describe these past two months as the worst of my life, but i can't say that that is true.  i've had some of the worst and most fearful moments of my life in these 61 days, but despite the head-swimming and the reeling and the panic and the denial and the madness, i've been shown real, unbelievable beauty...in the world around me, in my friends, and in myself.  i wanted this to change my life and it is doing that.  i've described myself on this weblog as not being the same as i was a few months ago.  it would make a lot of things in my life easier if i could go back to who i was on march 22nd, but given that i can't do that, i think what i've been given in return, or maybe what i've found as a result has proven to be nothing short of amazing.    it's like this:  in my old life, i would have never thought that i could deal very well with having a brain tumor diagnosis.  but when i had a brain tumor diagnosis--even a malignant brain tumor diagnosis--i was scared and i cried a lot and i freaked out, but when the dust settled, i was strong and ready to beat it so i could get on with my life.  and then, in the wake of that brain tumor diagnosis, a situation that i viewed as temporary, when doctors started talking about multiple sclerosis, a situation that would become part of the rest of my life, i wanted so badly for it to be a tumor.    i've had this mantra that i've been using with any pain or anxiety or fear or sleeplessness--"this will pass".  i say it over and over and it truly makes me feel at ease.  but MS will not pass.  MS doesn't pass.  and when that MS diagnosis finally came, i felt destroyed and betrayed and damned.  but, the more i've learned about it, the better i've felt.  and as i said in that e-mail i sent out to friends today, knowing that this is a disease that has a lot of ambiguity in how it affects different people, it does me no good to live any other way than as if i'm going to be fully functional for a long time.    i'm reading this book called _One L_ by scott turow.  it's a terribly mainstream book to read for the soon-to-be law student, but i'm reading it out of curiosity and the need to read something relevant to my life that isn't about MS.  it's about turow's first year at harvard law school in the 70s, and it makes the experience out to be almost physically painful--12 hours a day of studying, upped to 20 hours a day during exam time; cutthroat classmates; pretentious professors; never seeing non-law school significant others.  now, i'm not going to harvard law school...on purpose.  i don't want that kind of environment.  but i'm excited about the school i've chosen and i'm excited about immersing myself in being a law student.  and even if it gets even remotely close to what turow has described, i can't imagine it being any worse than what i've just gone through.  so, pitt law, bring it.  piece of cake. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      rubber ducky, you're the one...  dr pruitt called yesterday evening.  her message said that my white cell count from my spinal tap shows evidence of inflammation.  she said there were 23 white blood cells in the spinal fluid, where normally there should only be 4 or 5.  i don't know what this means.  she called me again (i think by accident) this morning, and i asked her if she wanted me on the steroids to diminish that inflammation (which seems like a good idea to me), but she wants to wait until she gets the final spinal tap results--the one that will indicate the presence of protein bands (evidence of demyelination).   she said she's going to call in the avonex prescription today and i should be able to get started on it next week.  good.  the sooner the better.    when i was in the hospital, two of my friends from work visited me with a basket full of stuff, including a pez dispenser with an ernie head (as in bert and ernie).  cosby (my dog) got hold of the basket at home and chewed up the pez dispenser, but managed to leave the ernie head intact.  so now the ernie head resides on top of my computer at work, on top of a little plastic dinosaur.   so, yesterday i noticed this weird little yellow thing sticking on ernie's mouth.  upon investigation, i found it to be a tiny drawing of a duck on yellow paper.  well aware that i don't work with a single soul who would do something so charming, i realized that stean was here on saturday doing some part-time work.  so i called him up and asked him if he had given the ernie on my desk a rubber ducky.  he said, "you just now noticed that?"    i feel like i've been delayed in noticing things about him a lot lately.  i'm glad he's had the patience with me to wait for me to catch up.  because, of him, i'm awfully fond.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      single process...  i just dyed my hair pink.  manic panic hot hot pink.  that's right--i am officially still a 16 year old girl.  i feel liberated.  i think i'd like to have pink hair forever.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      strange magic...  oh my good grief!  in all of the tests and procedures that i've undergone since this fun began on march 23rd, NOTHING has been as unbelievably weird as this blood patch.  seriously--not a spinal tap, not a research study MRI in which the tunnel started shaking, not even a freaking brain biopsy compares to how surreal and bizarre what i experienced today was.    don't get me wrong--it worked, or at least i've been vertical now for nine hours, and while i still have a weird headache below and behind my right eye, i'm not crying and i'm not ready to pass out from the intense pressure i was feeling before.  what i seem to have traded my awful headache for, however, is the oddest back pain i could possibly imagine.  more on that later...    i had a one o'clock appointment.  i spent my morning in my pajamas trying to make sure my half-assed insurance company would cover the blood patch procedure and having a text message conversation with my sister about why she is so much better off without her manipulative, selfish boyfriend.  got the former straightened out.  don't have the power to even make sense of the latter.  anyway, felt okay enough, after having taken a caffeine pill earlier, to take the subway to presbyterian medical center for the procedure.  got there a few minutes early, good thing since presby has possibly the most inane layout of any hospital i've seen yet.    found the department i needed, checked in, and then the headache came back.  i sat and slouched (to try to take off some of the pressure) and waited and by the time they called me to head back to the examining room, i felt absolutely justified in being there for this procedure.  i had to fill out one of those new patient forms that included the following three questions (not verbatim, by the by): 1.  circle the number below that represents your pain at its worst: 2.  circle the number below that represents your pain at its least: 3.  circle the number below that represents your pain right now: and of course, the numbers were on that oh-so-ambiguous 1-10 scale.  i honestly don't know how to answer those questions and i hate that scale.  because isn't it all relative?  i suppose that pain is a relative thing.  totally subjective.  the worst pain i've ever felt was in the hours after my brain biopsy, when it felt like a nuclear bomb had hit my skull and the fallout was radiating out from the impact site all over my head.  so i guess that would be a 10?  and obviously 1 would be pain-free.  but how do i qualify the other numbers on the scale?  i propose the following new scale: a) no pain b) annoying pain, but not anything that's going to disturb my life c) pain that i wouldn't call out of work with, but that would keep me from meeting friends for drinks afterwards d) pain that i'll go to work with, but that will end up sending me home in the middle of the day e) pain that will keep me from leaving the house f) pain that makes me cry g) pain that makes me cry and writhe and wish that would make me pass out there.  i could answer those questions on that scale.  they would be the following:   1)  f 2)  d 3)  f but i think what i circled was, respectively, 8, 2, and 7.  anyway, so a neurologist came in and asked me some questions, and then left me alone for a while.  this gave me some time to reflect.  my reflections were as follows (warning:  some language is extreme.  my apologies, but i wasn't exactly having a good time):  jesus god what is going on with my life?  i don't know how many more doctor visits and tests i can handle.  i'm sitting here in a shithole examining room with a headache because my spinal fluid is leaking?!  this is all just too unreal.  it's too stupid to be real.  i can't even go through with this it's so stupid.  but it's kind of rude to just leave.  and besides, i already paid my copay.  but sweet christ they're going to patch me up with my own blood!  it's all very economical and all but, hey, is that a helicopter?  this place gets its own helicopter?  it sounds like the landing pad is directly above my head.  that neurologist was an ass.  i don't like it here.  this is the first thing i've had to do, besides MRIs, without someone here with me.  that's not a big deal.  it feels like a big deal.  i wonder if i can put my feet up on this table.  (big noise).  that wasn't a good choice.  jesus.  i'm scared.    and then the anesthesiologist (galapo was his name--pretty young, lots of arrogance) came in and told me to lie down, probably because i looked like an idiot all slouched in a chair.  he re-explained the process, asked me if i had questions, and then we went into the procedure room.    i had to strip down to my skivs and put on one of those hospital gowns.  in the room, i laid (27 years old and a grammar stickler and for the life of me i can't remember the rules about lie and lay)  down on my stomach on the table with my left arm extended above my head.  they cleaned off my back and my arm with soap and then betadyne.  the betadyne smelled bad.  it smelled like betadyne.  i said, "with all due respect, this room is a little scary."  i felt terrified.  dr galapo said, "it's scary?"  and i said, "nothing.  i'm just a little nervous."  but it was scary--it looked like a storage closet qua operating room.  what i could see from where i was lying was the fluoroscopy monitor (so they could see both the prior needle mark and where the new needle was going) and to the right there was this crate of six green oxygen tanks.  the difference between this room and the other rooms where i've had invasive procedures (the spinal tap at HUP and the biopsy at Graduate) was almost extreme.  those rooms were clinical and white and oozing with sterility.  this room felt dark and cluttered.  i don't doubt its cleanliness, but it was lacking in medical ambience.    there were four people other than me involved in the procedure.  two men--the neurologist who had talked to me first, positioned at my back to put the blood in, and dr galapo, who was training/attending/supervising/whatever they call that; and two women--one who i never really saw and one who was (my favorite because she was the nicest) posted at my arm to get the blood out.  now, this happened to me right before they put me out for the biopsy and before dr kremens started the spinal tap--i started to feel really fearful and almost out of control, like i was being experimented on and couldn't escape.  it got resolved in the biopsy by putting me under.  it got resolved in the spinal tap by my asking the doctor about a billion questions.  but this was weird because i felt so outnumbered, i was lying on my stomach and couldn't see what was happening, and i didn't feel that the blood patch was 100% necessary--i kept thinking that maybe if i waited another day the pain would go away on its own.  i had the kind of feeling that the world was getting really small and existed completely within that procedure room.  i wasn't myself.  i didn't feel that i had any control over what was happening to me.  i really was terrified.  the only thing i had any say about was whether i was going to lose it right there in a relatively simple procedure.    although the moments are fewer and farther between, i still have blips of realization that what i'm dealing with here is my central nervous system.  this isn't like a broken leg or even like a bad heart.  if this gets messed up, i'm not me anymore.  i could lose a kidney and still be emily.  i could have open heart surgery and still be emily.  in matters of the brain, i have so many questions about what makes me me.  i'm already not the emily that i was two months ago.  i feel the need to mention things to stean that someone should know on my behalf--like how claustrophobic i get in the MRIs, but if i'm blindfolded, and can't see how close the space is, i'm okay--in case something happens and i can't say things for myself.  i'm sitting here right now, feeling this awful tightness that is my own blood intentionally misplaced inside my epidural cavity, thinking about all the things that could go wrong because of some mistake--a stroke, an aneurysm, an embolism, i could die in my sleep.  this is a colossal waste of my energy, but deep down, no matter how brave or strong or relieved or informed i am in my multiple sclerosis, i'm still a kid in the dark, surrounded by unfamiliar noises.  this is what i will have to work hardest to live with--the inevitability of the unknown.     they got my vertebrae up on the monitor.  it looked like an x-ray.  i asked where the spinal tap had been done and dr galapo pointed out a grey line.  he had the neurologist do the patch one vertebra up, which didn't make sense to me, and i probably should have asked about it, but i didn't.  i only have one needle mark in my back, though.  i don't remember having been given anything to numb the skin, but i must have been, because they put a decent sized needle into my back and i only felt pressure.  i could see the needle on the monitor, and once it was in place, the woman doctor numbed my left arm at the inner elbow with lidocaine and inserted the needle.  i watched.  i've never been squeamish about needles or shots, but there have always been receptacles on the other end of those needles with either something going in or coming out.  this needle just sat there in my arm for a bit, then she opened the valve and suddenly my blood was running down my arm and i felt like the room had just been spun like a top.  i told her i'd better not look at what she was doing for now, but i could still feel my blood, all nauseating and warm, running out of the needle.    she put a vial on the end of the needle and it filled with blood.  then she handed it off to the neurologist.  the blood would have to be injected quickly or else the blood would start to clot and be useless.  dr galapo said i would start to feel something in my legs and head as the neurologist put the blood into the needle in my back.  i didn't feel anything at first, but then felt a tightness in my lower back.  it hurt, so i said "ow".  and dr galapo told the neurologist to stop for a bit.  and then once the pain wore off, he put the rest of the vial in.  but i was still okay, so in went more blood, until i felt like my upper half and my lower half were going to curl up like one of those fortune telling fish.  it wasn't pain, really.  it was painful, but it was more of a tightness.  that makes sense, i guess--fluid was being injected into a space that didn't exactly have or make room for it.  28 cc's.  28 milliliters of my own blood now resides in my back.  and it sat there and congealed and plugged up the leak, just like it was supposed to.    maybe it was having had ridiculous headaches for 5 days straight.  maybe it was the procedure itself.  maybe it was the smell of the betadyne.  none of it made sense.  they cleaned up my skin, and that was it.  i had to lie down for about half an hour.  then i hung out for another 15 minutes or so, just to make sure the headache was gone.  after that, i got my stuff and walked out.  the appointment was at 1:00.  i left at 3:30.    now it's after midnight and i feel like i have a giant rock crammed into my lower back.  it's not muscle sore or skin tender.  my actual innards hurt.  this should break itself up in the next day or two.  blood patch.  it's a terrible name.  terribly uncreative.  at least "lumbar puncture" sounds clinical and exact.  blood patch?    no more of this please.  i want the bruises in my arms from having blood drawn to go away.  i want my vision to return.  i want to be able to taste my meals.  i want to feel like things are starting to norm.  i'm so tired.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1 out of 1000...  came home from work this morning because i was sitting at my desk in tears with my post-spinal tap headache.  i tried, i really did.  and although i'm not thrilled with my job, anything was preferable to the thought of spending another day lying down in my house.  i was okay for the first hour of being awake.  and by the time i got to work i had a little headache, but totally tolerable.  unfortunately it got worse and worse until i nearly snapped at people on the phone for talking too much and it became painfully obvious that i didn't need to be at the office.    the bad part is that i'm supposed to be in DC tomorrow for a meeting of all the gung-ho princeton review directors in the region.  the plan was that karen and anne and i would leave after work in a rental car and would stay overnight in arlington.  i've been honestly looking forward to that part--spending some time with those girls outside of the chaos of work.  but unless i can lie down for the whole drive and the meeting tomorrow, it's kind of silly for me to go.    i had called dr. pruitt's office first thing in the morning, to let her know i was still having headaches and that my sense of taste is all messed up.  i went home at about 11:00, after sitting forever in my boss's office, in a slumped over position, my fingertips pressed against my temples to try to find some relief from this godawful headache.  my boss, who is ever in her own world, wanted to show me pictures from the executive director meeting, until i said to her that i was in a lot of pain and needed to get home where i could lie down.    dr. p called at noon, told me to stay horizontal and to call her at 4:00.  she said that dr. kremens had told her that my spinal tap had been very easy and sometimes when those things are too easy, i.e., if there isn't really any bleeding, small leaks of cerebrospinal fluid can happen, resulting in low pressure in the head.  if the headache was still there at 4:00, she wanted me to have what's called a "blood patch" procedure, where blood is drawn from my arm and then injected into the spinal tap site.  the blood clots naturally and forms a glue, clogging up the leak and relieving the headache.    so, 4:00 rolled around and the headache was still there.  i called dr. pruitt and she said she was going to order a blood patch for tomorrow.  so, i'm not going to DC for any meeting.  i called work to talk to my boss, and told her that i'd send an e-mail to the women who had arranged the meeting, cc'ing her and her boss, explaining what was happening, and passing along my apologies.  she, on the other hand, felt that that message shouldn't come from me, that it should be from her and be as vague as possible.  not the approach i would have taken or that i felt was appropriate, but she's my boss and i'm not exactly up for pissing her off these days.    tomorrow.  relief in sight.  and i shouldn't take caffeine pills in the evening because they keep me up waaaaaaaayyy too late.    i read on webmd.com that 1 out of 1000 people who have spinal taps need to have a blood patch done to stop up a spinal fluid leak.  leave it to me to get something rare.  jesus christ.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      (this is) spinal tapped...  so, that whole waiting-until-august-to-get-an-appointment-with-my-neurologist thing worked out.  i got in to see dr. pruitt on tuesday, spent about two hours with her talking about the disease and what we would do about it and what it would mean.  she wanted me to have a spinal tap (official name:  lumbar puncture, which honestly doesn't sound much better), because, as she said, that's what the textbooks say to do.  i asked her if the results of the spinal tap would change her thoughts about putting me on "disease modifying drugs", and she said no.  but she wanted the test done so that we had all of our bases covered.  then i'd start on a once-a-week intramuscular injection called avonex.    i asked her why this was first being diagnosed as a tumor and she said that MS lesions typically aren't biopsied, but when they are, the cells look weird because of the inflammation.  since most pathologists aren't coming into contact with biopsied MS lesions with any sort of regularity, things get read as low-grade tumors (i.e., what happened with me, and this is certainly in line with the excruciatingly long amount of time i had to wait for the pathology report).  i also told her that in all i've read, seizures aren't listed as onset symptoms of MS and asked her what that meant.  she said that, although it's a rarity, she's definitely seen patients who have found out they had MS through seizures.  stean said to me, when we left dr. pruitt's office, "leave it to you to have something rare."  leave it to me.    the spinal tap was done yesterday (friday), and the procedure itself was a piece of cake.  it was done by dr. kremens, who i believe may be the nicest doctor ever in the world.  the looked like my cousin ben, only maybe 25 or so years older.  and, as luck would have it, he was an attorney for seven years before he decided to go into medicine.  so i talked to him about law school the entire time he was doing the tap.    here's how the spinal tap was done...  first i was positioned so that i was seated but leaning all the way forward, curving my back as to maximize the space between the vertebrae.  dr. k found the space in my back that would be best to do the tap, about in line with the top of my hip bone (note:  the spinal cord only goes about 2/3rds of the way down the spine, so there's no danger of hitting any major nerves with a spinal tap), and marked it with a pen.  then i got two shots of lidocaine, one shallow, and one (which stung like hell) fairly deep.  once the numbness set in, he inserted a thin hollow needle (i think he said it was a 22 gauge needle, which is smaller in diameter than the post of an earring) into my back that had attached to it a tube and i'm assuming (of course i couldn't see any of this) some sort of valve system that would allow him to drain the cerebrospinal fluid.  i asked if i could see my spinal fluid when he was finished and he said i certainly could.    (at this point in the tap, i started thinking about how unbelievably messed up it was to have a freaking tap installed into my back.  this feeling was not unlike the experience i had in the hospital when i was connected to the IV and the electrodes.)    he took four vials of spinal fluid from my back.  four vials of clear and colorless fluid.  i don't know what i was expecting my spinal fluid to look like, but i didn't think it would look like water.  i guess i thought it would be more body-colored--yellow or pink or red or something full of stuff.  dr. k said that if it had been cloudy or colored, that would have been some sign of bleeding or infection.  i asked if he could tell anything about presence of MS from eyeballing it.  he said, as i suspected, that needed a microscope.    and that was it--he cleaned off the betadyne, put a band-aid over the puncture site, had me lie flat for a little while, and that was that.  i felt fine when it was finished.  no headache, other than the rush to my head when i was able to stretch out from the curved-up, head-down position i was in for the tap.    adrienne was my ride to and from the hospital.  she was in town for the week, and she brought me an autographed picture of will ferrell which, as soon as i can find a suitable frame, will be featured prominently above my mantle.  spent the day with her, watched movies, she beat me in scrabble (further proof that i'm being as honest as possible here--i don't take scrabble lightly).    the headache started to set in around late afternoon.  and it stayed with me all weekend.  this was the weirdest headache--like an extreme version of a sinus headache; my brain felt like it was a balloon in a vaccuum-sealed container in somebody's science-experiment demonstration of how pressure works.  when i would lie down, it would subside, but sitting up or standing was pretty much out of the question.  it had me in tears a few times, partially from the pain, and partially from the inconvenience of having to spend my entire weekend lying down.  this headache didn't respond a bit to any sort of pain medicine, certainly not to the two aleve, the four aspirin, and prescription strength ibuprofen i tried to treat myself with.    i thought it was gone by saturday night, but it must have been the influx of caffeine during the day, because sunday morning it was back.    oh, and did i mention that i've lost my sense of taste, too?  i'm almost positive this is because of the carbamazepine, but it's exceptionally annoying and has made eating miserable.  food has become tactile and bland, and kinda nauseating.      
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      no more waiting...  august!  AUGUST?!?!  what kind of neurosurgeon's receptionist tells a newly-diagnosed MS patient she has to wait until august to see the doctor?!?!?!  jesus.    i called mary ellen at dr. grady's office and left her this big long message about how i'm sure she understands that this is a scary time and i have so many questions that need to be answered and if at all possible could she intervene and get me in to see dr. pruitt as soon as humanly possible.  i've been very nice up to this point.  i think it's time i start to get a little pushy to make sure i'm getting what i need.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      faith...  last week, on the day that i called out sick, dave and i were sitting in washington square park for a while, talking about the stuff that we talk about.  and one of the things that came up was his trip out to san francisco one summer that turned out disastrous.  i won't tell that story here, as it isn't mine to tell, but the gist is that it is a classic tale of one getting one's hopes up, even though there isn't a lot of evidence to support that hope, and then having those hopes and all of their  expectations thrown unceremoniously in the trash.  it might also be helpful to add that this story is also one regarding matters of the heart.    so, we were talking about that and laughing about how important and earnest things felt at that point in our lives and about how impossible it is to recognize that some things really don't matter while you're standing in the middle of them, feeling like lloyd dobbler in _say anything_.  and i mentioned to dave that most of the stories in life don't have happy endings.    how odd is that?  it's true--most of the things we want don't end up happening the way that we want them to happen.  we believe and dream and tie up so much energy into wanting to get the right boy or girl or needing to be in the right place or find the right job and rarely do things work out that way.  we can't will them into existence by sheer force of desire.    but why do we follow these dreams?  even when all rational and logical signs are practically screaming that they're not going to pan out?  people are completely blind and kind of stupid, but the possibility, no matter how remote, that things just might work out in our favor keeps us going.  and then the resolution those desires get always comes in some other form.  when we're finally able to let go, or to accept the way they do work out, we walk away, a little disappointed, but better for having gone through it.  somehow, those big wants that once consumed us turn into character building learning experiences; tiny stumbling blocks in retrospect that make us stronger along the way.  fodder for stories told among good college friends.    so is it the ambiguousness that motivates us?  is it the not-knowing that compels us to see it through to the end?  is hope our downfall and our triumph?  maybe that's why we cling so tenaciously to faith.  it's the one thing that we desire that can never be truly resolved.  never in this life.  sound hopeless?  not to me.  sounds beautiful.  makes all of the ambiguity seem a little more comforting.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      defeat...  good god, never have i felt so humiliated in my life as i did last night.  i'm not even sure why i'm writing it, other than that i want to remember it, and that it will most likely happen again, and somehow that makes documenting it worthwhile.    we were sitting in the living room, stean and i.  just sitting there, not doing much of anything, and i started to feel so tired and out of it--i would go into stares in which my eyes would start to blur, and i would have to jar myself out of it.  so i leaned my head forward and covered my eyes with my hands and then i started crying.  not like a sad cry or an angry cry or even like a scared cry.  it was as if i had to unleash something, get something out in the open.  it was an ugly cry.  it was as if the cry were having me.  i cried and cried and cried.  and i felt like i needed to get away from the room with stean and the dog and the cats so i got up--still crying--and walked toward the stairs.  stean didn't move--he said something like, "i'll let you be--i know you need to go through this." i felt so weak and powerless and i tried to climb the stairs, but it turned into more of a crawl.  and the tears were all over me and my nose was running all down my face and i felt like i needed to get away from everything.    i only made it to the landing on the second floor, so i curled up there and cried and cried and cried and cried, tears and snot everywhere, forming puddles on the ground.  i kept saying over and over, "what do i do with this? what do i do with this?"  i don't know if i was talking to god or myself or if these words were part of the crying that was possessing me.  it was so surreal.    all of this has been surreal.  or hyper-real.  if i let myself think about it, it's as if i'm watching myself go through it--as if i'm in the corner of the room looking at me talking to people or reading about it or having a headache.  seeing myself with multiple sclerosis from afar, because i can't do it yet from within.  god, i don't know what's going on.  a couple of months ago i felt that i had a path, a plan.  i knew what was going to happen with my life, at least in the next few years.  but that has all been taken away from me.  i can't say for sure that i'll make it through the rest of may without taking any sick days, let alone be okay to wear an orange bridesmaid dress in amy's wedding in july or--sweet christ--start school in august.    i want to have babies and i want to have a happy career and i want to grow old.  i want to do these things without assistance, without drugs.  that is absolutely not possible anymore.  i've been so heartachingly aware of the people i see who walk with canes or walkers or who are in wheelchairs, particularly if they're younger than the age that one would expect to see someone using those aids.  all i see is myself.  i see me in the wheelchair.  i see me with the grocery bags tied to the front of my walker because my hands aren't free to carry them.  i see me, compromised and incomplete; bionic and sick.    "what do i do with this?"  over and over and over.  my sobbing must have sounded so awful.  from in my head it sounded hollow and discordant and unfamiliar.  i was so ravaged with this fit, but i felt somehow detached from it.  i was lying on the ground in the fetal position, my head soaked by the puddle it had created on the floor, staring at this rubbermaid box stean has with a bunch of odds and ends in it.  not thinking about it, but staring at it.  it was the only calm in the storm of noise and tears and snot and anguish streaming out of my body.  but the calm felt that it was mine, while the torment belonged to someone else, something else.  my body, maybe?  or maybe to that girl who just got the multiple sclerosis diagnosis and who was told first of all that it was a brain tumor.  that girl, emily.  i don't know her.  i don't know what to do with her.    i would calm down, catch my breath, try to rub some of the tear-puddle into the hardwood floor.  i'd get a moment's rest, and then it would start up again.  i don't even know what i was feeling.  all i could think was about how much i wanted to scream.  so finally, i did.  and then, i got up, went into the bathroom and washed my face, and cleaned up the puddle.    it didn't pass that simply, of course.  i went downstairs and collapsed into stean's arms and burst into tears again.  and here i am, about twelve hours later, still reeling a little bit, and definitely embarrassed by the whole scene.    dave and i were talking the other night about why memoirs/autobiographies are worthwhile.  the act of writing about oneself seems so amazingly selfish to me.  i am under no delusions that this weblog exists for any reason greater than my own selfishness.  dave, however, my MFA-trained writer-friend, and possibly my dearest friend, said that it has to do with creating a truth.  people write about themselves because there is something about their experiences that is true.    i think back on what struck me most when this whole thing started 47 days ago.  there were two things i needed more than anything else--to be able to talk without limits about what i was feeling and thinking and experiencing, and to have someone talk without limits to me who had been through what i was entering into.    those have been the hardest needs to satisfy so far.  and so there you have it--i guess that's why people write memoirs.  and why people read them.  we live in a world that's so communal and yet so lonely.  the difficult stuff, the stuff that throws a spotlight on our imperfect nature, doesn't have a manual.  it's why the self-help industry has been so successful, but in all truth, nobody can tell us what specific steps we need to take and then all will be okay.  we just have to realize that we don't know much of anything and then go through the hard stuff head-first and on our own.  i think that loneliness is absolutely necessary--how else do we figure out what we're made of?  but we need to hear those stories that tell us that other people came out on the other side okay.  because we can't possibly handle our frailty and our loneliness without a little bit of hope.    (i now officially sound like an idiot.  if i'm not careful, i'm going to start throwing around words like "self-actualization" and start using aromatherapy.  so i'll stop for now.  i've said enough.)    i may not know the answer to the question "what do i do with this?" for a long while, but hopefully someday i will.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      blindsided...  talked to dr. grady yesterday.  he said the following: "your diagnosis is multiple sclerosis".  so, so much for the maybes and the we-don't-know-yets and the guesswork.  i've got MS.  now my life will be different.  for the rest of my life, i'll have multiple sclerosis.  it could be really bad or it could be easily manageable.  i don't know.  and i won't know.  even if i have another relapse soon, i won't know how bad it could be.    there is so much unknown about a disease (disease!!!) like MS.  les, my boss at my job in boston, went downhill quickly after his diagnosis.  other people go for years and years and years and years without any noticeable symptoms.  obviously i'd like to experience the latter, but just like i didn't get to choose whether i had a brain tumor or MS, i don't get to choose the course that my disease (DISEASE?!?!) will take.  i just want to get in to see dr. pruitt as soon as humanly possible and get started on some sort of treatment plan.    when my phone rang, i was outside with dave and jessica and stean.  and while i was on the phone, joe and laura showed up.  at the time, having all of those people around was too much--i had to leave and take the dog for a walk so i could escape from the words that had just been exchanged in my living room--but i think it was probably for the best.  what good would it have done me to have been by myself?  of course, i wanted stean there, and he was there--he came inside with me while i spoke with dr. grady.  and then dave came in to see how things had gone, and he was able to tell jessica and joe and laura, something that i don't know that i would have been able to do so soon, even though i wanted them all to know.  i called dad and daniel, but calling someone is different than having to tell someone in person.  on the phone you only hear a voice, and vocal inflections are relatively easily controlled.  in person, someone's facial expression will always give away what he or she thinks.  i wasn't ready, so soon after that phone conversation, to have to read my friends' facial expressions.  i know that crowd to be compassionate and encouraging and optimistic, but still, it's an MS diagnosis.  it's not pretty.  none of this has been pretty.    but do you know what stean said?  when i told him how the conversation with dr. grady had gone, he looked at me and he said, "okay, so what's our next step?"  this is so tough for him, too.  but how amazing that he's doing this with me!  that he sees this as changing his life, too!  he hasn't batted an eye at any point in the past six weeks, and i have no reason to think that he will.  i'm lucky.  i'm truly truly blessed to have alongside me the people that i have.    another thing that dr. grady said was that it is his opinion that having MS is a much better diagnosis than having a brain tumor.  i asked him if that included a benign brain tumor and he said absolutely.  joe said the same thing--that he's glad, personally, that it's MS and not a tumor.   so i've got two doctors who see this as somewhat positive.    ...but then, i had a medical student, one of my MCAT teachers, holler after me as i was leaving the office yesterday, "it's better to have a brain tumor than MS because a tumor can be operated on!"  no shit.  but this was not something about which i had a choice.  this was not something that i could let myself wrap in my preferences.  it is my preference that this doesn't happen at all.  it would have been my choice to be completely normal.  i called dad after she had said that to me (i was blazing mad at just how unknowingly insensitive it was) so angry at her and at me for ever having talked to ANYONE about this.  because as soon as the words leave my mouth, the news is no longer mine.  it is free to float around and take its own form and it has the potential to be heard totally differently.  and that's something i have to learn to accept, because this isn't the first time this will happen.  the world is full of people who believe that they know more than anyone else.  i believe that the vast majority of the things that people will tell me will be done so out of some motivation to be helpful or encouraging, but i have to learn to be very selective about what i listen to.  dad said that grandma is all full of this idea that i can cure myself with bee venom.  i guess, if that's what she needs to think in order to bring some sort of peace about this for herself, then that thought is worthwhile.  but under no circumstances do i need to make my decisions according to what people who aren't intimately involved in this process (specifically, me and my doctors) have to say.    at least i can still go to school this fall.  i want to learn how to make this diagnosis a motivator for me, how to turn it into something that will make me want to work harder and use my energy for good things.  that's no small challenge.  but then, neither is multiple sclerosis...  i have to believe that i am up for this, simply because i'm foolish if i let myself believe that i am not.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      sinking in...  i bought this book today about dealing with the first year of a multiple sclerosis diagnosis.  god, i can't even read it--the words don't even register.  i'm trying to find out about this disease so i can make informed decisions and so i can have informed reactions, but everytime i begin to read up on it my head starts spinning.  i can't believe this is real.  i think i'd rather die than be paralyzed.  i'd rather die than dwindle slowly away.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      avonexed...  it starts tonight.  i'll give myself the injection in just a few hours.  and i'm TERRIFIED.    see, it's like this...  right now, in this pre-medicated moment, at which point i am not yet undergoing treatment for multiple sclerosis, this medicine, essentially, is perfect.  it can do nothing but good.  it's all hypothetical, theoretical, ideal, pure.    as soon as that needle enters my leg, it is no longer perfect, it is real.  it's either going to work or not work.  and that ambiguity is absolutely terrifying.    so, here goes nothing...  here goes the rest of my life...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      punchy...  never in my life have i wanted to punch someone in the face more than i do to this one girl that i work with.  seriously.  i ain't lyin'.  perhaps it's the steroids, but i just have this maddening urge to just right hook her across the nose.    i do think it's the drugs, but it isn't totally unwarranted.  when i got to work this morning, she was downstairs waiting for the elevators and i smiled at her.  she looked the other way.    there is only so much i can tolerate of people treating people as if they aren't also caught up in this whole big mess of a world with them.  i just spent five days in a place where people acknowledge each other with a wave or a smile or a kind word.  and to come back and be treated again like a non-entity just because i don't think it's funny to make light of absolutely everything that goes on?    i CANNOT WAIT to get out of this office.  these people are so negative and bitter and downright rude.  i feel so much more happy and at peace as soon as i walk out of the office door every day.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    caitlin and me atop the light house on bald head island.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      4:27 am...  i suppose if you take my regular sleep schedule and back it up a few hours, then i got a full night's sleep.  still, there is something disturbing about being awake so early.    i sometimes feel really tired and dizzy and puny in the evenings.  i'm truly not sure what is the cause of this--could be the drugs (i'm hoping it's the drugs), could be the onset of summertime, could be the disease.  i really don't understand yet how this disease works.    so many things in life right now are riding standby to this MS.  simple things--dishes, laundry, being in touch with friends; but bigger things, too--things that have to do with plans for school in a couple of months.  so many things that need to get done.  but when i'm at work all day until 7:00 or so, and then when i get home and i'm too exhausted to move, the time doesn't just present itself.    the dog is downstairs crying right now.  ah, parenthood...  i am awake now.  there is time now.  it's way early.  i forgot at least two meds last night because i slept through when i normally take them.  ugh.  too many pills.  too many chemicals.  i currently have active prescriptions for five drugs.  what would i like most in the world right now?  to see how i feel when i'm not on any drugs, to feel like myself.    i suppose it isn't so bad.  it could be much worse.  but i watch people in their normal interactions and i feel like i'm never going to have those again--it's like being drunk without the weird sick part, just the dizzy and out-of-it and a little bit of social insecurity.  please let it be the drugs.  i'm on the verge of going to this family reunion/vacation thing and i'm very much looking forward to it, but i always get this mild freak-out in the couple of days before i know i'm going to be with family.  it's not that i don't like my family or that things are weird around them, it's more that time spent with family is not a normal part of my day-to-day life.  there's something a little jarring about being with those that you are most like.  i'm very much looking forward to seeing family (it's my dad's family, the mcnallys).  the occasion would have been for my cousin's wedding, had my cousin's fiancee not called things off about a week ago.  but the rooms had been reserved and arrangements had been made, and so it has become an excuse to get together anyway.    dad and linda keep telling me that "there are a whole lot of people who want to see you".  i have mixed feelings about that.  first of all, well, i want to see them, too.  but secondly, i don't want to spend the four days i'm away answering questions and feeling like some sort of special case.  (and what if i get tired all the time and don't feel up to it, like i've been feeling in the past couple of days?  ugh.)  in all truthfulness, it will probably only be like that at first, and then in spurts in smaller conversations, which is okay.  i guess i don't want to lose focus that the reason for the visit is my cousin, and even though he's not getting married anymore, this is/was still a pretty significant time in his life that deserves to be honored.   dr p would tell me if i shouldn't be going to school this fall, right?  she would let me know, she would give me her professional, physician's opinion, right?  because i feel really scared about it, that i'm not going to be able to make it, that i'm going to invest this time and energy and money, which is really borrowed money and what if i don't have the energy for what the experience will demand of me?    but i can't stay at my job now.  i just can't.  i suppose i have some sort of responsibility to myself to move forward with what i want to do.  god, but i'm so scared.  there are so many things that have presented themselves since march, so many unexpecteds and disappointments.  i have no way at all of knowing what is to come.    i read this entire blog about a week ago.  my initial motivation for keeping it was so that i could have a record of what i've been going through and so i could see how far i've come.  i can't say that i've come very far at all.  still the same fears, the same weaknesses, the same doubts.  they may have taken different forms along the way, but i haven't yet grown past them.  physically i don't feel much better, either.  i don't want to die.  i don't want to live in some sort of compromised way, either.  it seems, though, that i have no choice.  i haven't felt uncompromised in three months and what hope do i have or regaining that normalcy?  i should tell dr. p, i guess.  i should tell her more of how i feel.  but i don't want to be some sort of whiny baby patient who complains all the time.  at the same time, i don't like having to sit here with my tiredness and my dizziness if maybe there's something that i can do about it.    i've been trying so hard not to ask this throughout all of this, but right now i'm feeling very much "why me?"  thoughts in the early morning.  still not 5:00 a.m. yet.  i think i'll fill out some student loan forms.  maybe do some research on student health plans.  stean is sleeping upstairs.  i think i probably messed up his sleep, too, with my jerking myself awake every hour or so and being tangled up in the covers.    i wonder where he is with all of this.  i know it's not easy for him.  if the tables were turned, i'm not sure that i could stay with someone with a life-long, possibly debilitating disease.  i don't know that i have the strength to watch that happen.  why does he stay?  why would he want to be with someone who takes things to heart so much and gets so upset and afraid and who turns a headache into a death sentence.  i can be a terrible patient.  i was a terrible patient this weekend with the IV.  i get teary-eyed all the time.  i'm most definitely going through some depression these days.  but still, he's here.    maybe he sees me as his one-way ticket out of philadelphia.  he's needed an opportunity to leave this city for years, and he's found that in me and my law school endeavors.  or maybe he feels committed to me because we have all of these freeloading pets--a dog and two cats that half of the time i'm ready to just let wander out the door and fend for themselves in the world.      the obvious truth is that he's here with me because he loves me.  there's something he sees in me that is more important than disease or disability or anxiety.  holy crap that's a big deal!!!  i mean, where do i put that?  how do i process that in the midst of all the selfishness that i've been feeling lately?  i love him, too, and if this were him and not me, i would undoubtedly stay by his side.  i can't lose sight of how important it is that i have him with me.  i need to get over my stupid illness-obsession so that i can be more mindful of the good things going on right now.  stean is brilliant.  i'm practically the luckiest girl ever.    (is this the balance?  i get to be with someone like him but the trade-off is that i have a stupid disease?)  i can't write anymore right now.  i'm not saying what i'm thinking and i'm not really thinking things that are worth being recorded.    new beastie boys album out today.  i'll sneak out at lunch and pick that up.  and tonight i'll get my laundry done and get packed and tomorrow i leave for NC and a few days' escape.  good things.  there are good things.    i'll go crawl back in bed with stean, just for a minute, while it's still quiet out and before the sun comes up.  i need to put my arms around him and tell him that i love him.  we'll see each other through this, i know it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      big words...  talked to dr. p.  she said that the fact that i seem to be tolerating the steroids well "speaks well of [my] equanimity".    goodness.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    my catheter, now that it's over&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dear weblog,  in reading over recent posts, it has come to my attention that you must take me for a total paranoid basketcase.  to you i would like to first, apologize for not being more democratic with my ranting and raving, and second, let you know that it's only because i feel so safe in your arms that i am able to give you my lowest and most neurotic moments.    truly--take it as a compliment.    to the rest of the world i am a normal, healthy human being.  but to you, i am my most fragile, my most vulnerable.  so, um, i promise to, um, tell you about more uplifting and goodtimes things very soon.  just bear with me.    love, the one who can permanently shut you down if you complain
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dripped...  you know, i'm neither good at, nor qualified for, self-infusion of medications.  i damn near screwed it up today, too.  i got everything working, but i had to hold my arm (which is in some mighty hematomous pain right now) in just the right position to get the medicine to drip into it.    jill (my nurse) came out last night and switched the IV.  she put it in my right arm.  apparently i do have really crappy veins--people in the know keep telling me this.  she was going to stick my left hand, so at least i wouldn't have a catheter stuck in my writing arm, but i didn't want it so visible since i had teacher training today.  so in my right forearm it went, and out of my right forearm it came when the drip finally dripped today.  but now it's all done!  i'm finished with the IV phase of my steroid medication!  my vision hasn't returned, though.  i guess i was hoping that after dose #3, i might notice some change...  maybe it takes a few days more.  today is sunday.  this week i have to do a ton of silly work at the office in the span of not quite 3 full workdays, and then i leave wednesday at 5:30 for north carolina for four nights and four days with the family.  i'm currently annoyed with my sis (hi caitlin) for dyeing her hair pink (copycat), but i'm sure i'll get over that.  or else i'll burst into a steroid-induced rage at some inappropriate moment and start speaking in tongues and seizing.    it wouldn't be the first time.    well, it would be the first time with the steroids.    whatever.  i've never in my life been more aware of how necessary vacation time is.  never.  i seriously think if i weren't on the verge of having this time away from doctors and work and philadelphia, i'd most certainly be on the verge of a nervous breakdown.  i damn nearly killed both stean and me earlier trying to get the IV drip to work.  damn near killed us both.  let me just, for the record, state--i should not be given the responsibility ever again to administer my own IV drugs.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      saline flush...  i feel like such an idiot.  i'm a bucket of nerves right now.  i just tried to get things all set up for my medrol infusion, and as i was doing the saline flush before i hooked up the medicine, i freaked out because of a small air bubble in the syringe and pulled back the plunger and filled the tubing with my blood.  (!!!)  so i called the nursing service and the woman i spoke to said she would page the nurse on call, but i sat and waited and waited and cried a little and freaked out and waited, and knew my blood was clotting, and thirty minutes went by and i didn't get a call back.  so i called the nursing service again, and was told that they were trying to get a hold of the nurse on call, and they would try another nurse.    so a few minutes passed and the phone rang and it was jill, the nurse who set things up yesterday.  and she walked me through some steps and as it turned out, the IV line is clogged and now she's on her way here.  i feel like the biggest moron ever because she wasn't the nurse on call, and now she has to come fix my blunder on her day off and she was audibly unexcited about this and god why do i have to be such a paranoid baby about tiny air bubbles?!    i can't even articulate how hypersensitive (or how much of a hypochondriac?) i am right now with this thing in my arm.  i feel EVERYTHING, even things that don't exist.  it's like this port into my vascular system has rendered me defenseless to all things bad, and the plastic safeguards built into the tubes couldn't possibly be working properly and i'm sure to suffer death by embolism any moment now.    ugh, it's like i can feel the air bubbles moving around.  it makes me feel sick and dizzy and really really frightened.  i'm looking at it now--this mess of tape and tubes and clamps, all stuck to my arm.  who am i?  what has happened to me?  when will this stop?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    me and iv&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      IV...  i currently have some IV works installed into my left forearm.  there's an IV pole in my living room, and a bag full of medical supplies and two bags of solumedrol on my bookshelf.    this is all too weird.  why do they let regular people administer their own infusion therapy in their own home?  it just doesn't seem like a good idea to me.    also, i'm a little keyed up from the steroids.  i could run a marathon right now.  i could re-organize my cds and books.  i could clean my house.  i could finish the perhaps permanently on-hold project of painting the ceilings.  i will, of course, do none of these things.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      confirm the diagnosis...  here's the message dr. p left on my cell phone voice mail last night:  "hi miss mcnally, this is dr pruitt.  i do have your brain and cervical spine MRI reports. the cervical spine is fine, that's good news.  the brain MRI in fact shows a couple of areas different from the one that they were concerned about initially that take up the dye and essentially nearly virtually confirm the diagnosis, in which instance i think you should have a course of steroids because the appearance of these two small areas with the dye to me means we might as well just try to turn it off perhaps the easiest way to reach me this evening would be..."  so there it is.  i had gone to see ESotSM last night with paula (it made me cry this time); dr. p had called at some point when i was in the movies.  i listened to her message as i was turning my key in the lock to get into my house last night.  i got inside, and fell apart.  stean wasn't home, the house was dark.  i think i kinda stared at my phone for a while and sobbed.  two more spots.  my spotted mind.  i don't understand any of this, really.  i suppose there are hundreds of potential spots that could happen in a brain, and i suppose it is good news that there was nothing on the cervical scans, but jesus christ.  jesus christ!  that's it, right?  no more hope that this isn't going to turn into MS...  and that hope disappeared so quickly.  i got barely a month between the diagnosis of spot number one (may 7th) and the discovery of spots two and three.    i called dr p back.  it was about 10 o'clock, so i paged her, thinking that if it was too late, paging her would be less disturbing than calling her home number.  and i don't want to be an annoying, freaked out patient (even though "freaked out" is a mild way of putting how i feel right now).  she called me back almost immediately, and we talked for fifteen minutes or so.  i told her that i was scared, that i had burst into tears when i listened to her message, and i asked her if those two new spots meant that things were getting worse.  she said no, it just meant that things were still active, and she wanted to put me on steroids to get rid of the inflammation.  she asked me if i had felt okay and i told her i feel like i'm on anti-seizure meds, but other than that, no symptoms.  she said i wouldn't be feeling symptoms--these are very small lesions on the right side of my brain.  she told me that she's seen patients who have started off much worse than me who had a few things happen quickly, and then things settled down.  she said this could very well settle down with me.    (what she didn't say, and i'm sure it is true, is that there are patients who start off with much better than me and for whom things do not settle down.)    so, i'll do an IV course of medrol for three days.  a home health nurse will come to my house to set things up, and i'll give myself the drug for one hour three days in a row.  then i'll take 10-12 days of oral prednisone.  dr. p says the steroids will make me feel, in her words, "revved up".  given that i get uncomfortably anxious if i have too much coffee, i'm expecting to need a new xanax prescription to get me through this.  but it will clear up the inflammation.  and i'm hoping my vision will return.  and then i can ride my bike!  and maybe even get taken off the carbamazepine!!!  i really like dr. p.  she's brilliant, and while her version of compassion is what you would expect from one who is extremely intelligent, she's still been good with me.  last night on the phone she told me she didn't want me to hang up the phone and start crying, because, while this isn't good news, it is still much better than what i was being told initially, and there is no reason why i can't continue with my life and my plans for school.  she said this only further evinces that we're pursuing the right course of treatment and i am only days away from beginning the avonex treatment.  but despite the doctor's orders, i cried when i got off the phone with her.    when stean got home i was still a mess.  i had been on the phone with dad for about an hour, and dad said some wonderfully hopeful things, but i wasn't at that point ready to hear them.  i'm still not ready to hear them.  i said to stean, as we were all in the kitchen (all of us = stean, me, dog, and cats), "this moment, this is the best i will ever be--it's only going to get worse."  it's only going to get worse.    there will only be more spots on my brain.  never less.  those three that i have will never go away.  even if there is a cure, the damage that will have been done up to that point will never be undone.  i've been thinking a lot about the MRI films from april of 2002.  my poor brain--so clean and untainted at that point.  god, that's such a stupid thing to say, but those two years have gone by quickly, and if i go 2 years with nothing, and then 3 months with 3 spots, what does that mean for the rest of my life?    i have got to figure out a way to stop feeling so fearful all the time.  i'm a mess of neuroses--my brain is messy on all levels.  i've become claustrophobic.  i'm probably mildly depressed.  i think about my own vulnerability and mortality all the time.  i honestly want to run away from my life, my self.  unfortunately that is just not possible.     right now i'm not sure that i can handle this.  best case scenario--if things stay the same forever, i'm not sure that i can handle it.  my brain.  i have a brain disease!!!  i mean, i know it could be so much worse--it could be ALS or alzheimer's or something, but knowing that things could be worse does not make me feel better.  i feel resentful and jealous of all the people around me who are healthy.  i feel angry that i'm now being forced to think about things like pre-existing conditions clauses in health insurance policies or what i'm going to do with my used needles on the avonex.  that's fucked up and wrong.    spots in the ground look like lesions.  people, especially women, in wheelchairs or using canes or walkers immediately look like me.    i'm getting rid of my pink hair on tuesday.  it's not really pink anymore, except in a few places.  i'll have boring brown hair again.  the thing is, i don't want to look like everyone else anymore.  i don't feel like everyone else anymore.  i don't even feel like me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MRI-tunes...  spent last night getting a brain and cervical spine MRI done at HUP.  i had first gone to drop some materials off for work at our classroom site at penn and had some time to kill so i went to a used book store and purchased the following:  _illness as metaphor_ susan sontag _the moviegoer_ walker percy (when dave passed through town last week he highly recommended this.  it was $2.  i couldn't pass it up) _encyclopedia brown, book 1_  totally.  encyclopedia brown.  for $1.50.  perhaps the cheapest good present for stean i've ever purchased.   so, got to the radiology dept at 9:00 for my 10:00 MRI time.  read some of the sontag book and waited.  and started to get nervous, so i took an ativan, which kicked in too soon and i wanted to fall asleep.  then i got nervous that it would wear off before i actually needed it to keep me from being nervous.    i was the only person in the reception area waiting room.  i suppose everyone else had cooler things to do with their friday night.  finally my name was called and i was led down a hallway that was approximately 1/2 a mile in length to the area of the hospital where the MRI machines, or "magnets", as the nurse called them, were located.  i had to do the usual--change into a gown, remove all metal, put my stuff in a locker, blah blah blah.  the weird thing was that they made me wait in a waiting area in which two men were sitting.  this shouldn't be a big deal, but i've only ever seen single sex waiting areas after the whole strip-to-your-skivs-and-don-this-gown step takes place.  i guess i was just longing for the privacy of sisterhood, rather than hang out in a small waiting area where two fully clothed men were watching a baseball game as i'm sitting there in a knee-length hospital gown wearing nothing underneath but my skivs and my grey calf-high socks with the blue stripes and my sneakers.  humility, thy name is emily.    as it turned out, the two fully clothed and unhumiliated men were waiting for their wives/girlfriends/womenpals, which prompted fight-the-power thoughts in my head about how the hospital should have a stricter policy protecting patients' privacy when wearing hospital gowns and that if stean had been there with me i wouldn't have needed him to wait with me DIRECTLY OUTSIDE OF THE MRI.  geez, he could have waited in the main reception area.    mostly, i felt self-conscious because i hadn't shaved my legs.  i always forget to do that before these things.  mental note--don't forget next time.    and then the MRI...  it was longer than usual, about the length of that research study MRI.  it was a brain and cervical spine scan, dr p wanting to have more of the central nervous system checked for MS plaques.  she also wanted me to have a thoracic scan, but my dipshit insurance company wouldn't cover it.  she (dr p) said that if the cervical scan finds anything, she'll do what it takes to convince my insurance company to cover the thoracic, too.    maybe it was the ativan, or the pure oxygen that was being pumped through the MRI chamber, or the way the whole process is starting to feel routine, or some combination of all of the above, but the experience was much less scary, and almost enjoyable this time.  i felt safe, whereas every other time i've felt like i was being buried alive.    the MRI process is loud, and the radiology tech gives you earplugs before you lie down on the table.  the MRI sounds like a knocking or a buzzing or a chirping, depending on the scan.  but there's a rhythm to each scan, sometimes steady, sometimes increasing in sound/intensity.  the scans last from 45 seconds to four minutes per cycle, and each cycle has a unique noise.  it doesn't sound nice, particularly when you think about how the noise means that a giant magnet is making pictures of your brain.   i spent my time in the MRI chamber thinking about two things.  first, about how the process basically renders my skull and my skin and my hair and my blood vessels completely invisible.  the MRI sees the brain ventricles and the grey matter and the sinuses and the eyeballs, but not the stuff that contains them.  that is unbelievable.  and it does so as a magnet!  i'm a smart girl, but i have no idea how a magnet can see my brain, and in such detail that i can look at the films and see the weird mushy, wormy looking texture and follow my optic nerve from eyeball to occipital lobe.  weirder still is that the magnet can see through my neck and shoulders to the cervical spine!  and if i were having the thoracic spine scanned, too, the magnet would see past my ribs and lungs and heart to my spinal cord!    all of these mechanical miracles, and yet i have an incurable disease...  the other thing i was thinking about, and this is definitely a result of the ativan and the oxygen, was what words the scans sounded like.  in a way, it was like being inside a kraftwerk song--robotic, evenly paced, nerdy, even a little scary.  my sister used to do this thing, before she got too teenagery, where she would say the word "girl" over and over into her fist, so that her lips were covered entirely.  the result was this weird see-and-say-esque noise that sounded like "doy".  i think this was some kind of bizarro thing that girls do at camp late at night in the cabins, high on junk food and independence.  but the MRI noises sounded a bit like that.  sometimes they sounded bleepy, like an old-school hand-held video game.  sometimes they sounded like someone was knocking from inside the machine.    but the words i was imagining, and at times i swear they were actually being spoken to me by the MRI (again, folks, i was under unusual chemical influence) were real words.  the MRI was talking to me.  now, in my normal and sober state, all i remember is that i was being spoken to.  i can only remember one series of words that were said--"this is it this is it this is it".  i figured this was what the machine was saying to me as it scanned the part of my brain that is swollen with my MS lesion.  am i losing my mind?  the answer could be yes--both literally and figuratively.  see earlier post--i don't feel much like myself.  and this was 10:something on a friday night and i'm going through this magnetized ridiculousness as, now, a matter of course, a part of my life, this thing that i do.    i got my contrast injection, had about fifteen more minutes of scans, and that was that.  i was awakened from my drug-induced near-euphoric slumber by a nurse telling me i did a great job (did a great job?  i didn't _do_ anything).  it was the equivalent to the house lights coming up after a concert performance--eyes readjusting to the light, stiffness from being still for so long--my philip glassian radiological procedure.    but that's not all, oh no.  that's not all.  i went to the dressing area to regain my pride and my clothing.  and then...  ...i swiped a hospital gown.  yes, i know--this is wrong.  it's stealing and whatnot.  i'm not going to try to justify my actions.  i stole a hospital gown.  but i really liked the print on the material, it gave me some ideas for sewing projects.  i mean, i've spent enough time in that hospital already and taking a gown off their hands isn't going to set them back too much.  they have about a million of them.  besides, i was high from breathing straight oxygen for 45 minutes.  it seemed like the best thing to do at the time.  your honor, i am guilty.  take it up with my insurance company.  not only was i high enough to stuff a gown in my bag, but also i decided that the best way to get home at 11:00 at night would be to walk.  i walked the 22 blocks, staggering like a drunk, talking on my cell phone.  but i made it home safely, was greeted by the dog and cats.  had some oreos for dinner.  fell right asleep.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      delayed fallout...  sometimes i swear my brain moves.  i can feel this quick, brief, electrical movement, like having a twitchy eyelid.  i can usually feel it on the left side of my head, on the top, about three inches ahead and an inch over from where i had the biopsy.  i don't know what it means, or if it means anything.  i'm sure next i'll be waking up as a giant cockroach.  maybe i'm just going nutso.    or maybe these little electrical impulses would be seizures if i weren't on the carbamazepine?  ha.  i hate the carbamazepine.  it has made me an idiot and a clutz and i wake up in the morning with the speed of an iceberg.  i always forget to take it on time, too.  i take it evenly spaced because i'm constantly remembering about an hour or so after i'm supposed to take it.  i guess it all works out somehow.    here's something i think about a lot:  i feel like i've lost my relative sense of time since the seizures.  that feeling i had when i woke up and had no idea what day it was hasn't entirely left me.  ugh, it was the worst feeling.  and its memory is so vivid, unlike most of the events of that day--the nurse, a guy in his late 30s with really short grey hair and grey stubble on his nice, but no-nonsense face.  he had a white t-shirt underneath the scrubs with sleeves that were long enough to peek out past the green.  he seemed to just appear at my right side and he said, a little sternly because when i regained consciousness i immediately started panicking, "emily, do you know what day it is?"  emily, do you know what day it is?    i would never have imagined...  i never would have thought i couldn't answer that.  it's such a stock are-you-okay-and-competent question and i couldn't answer.  i've felt compromised ever since.  i doubt my awareness of days and dates.  i have to double check that i've written the month and the year properly.  god, i hope this is a side effect of the carbamazepine, but i worry that it isn't.  i worry that this is what it's like for people with brain diseases, this is what it's like for me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dwindling weekends...  it's saturday evening, "a prairie home companion" is on the radio.  stean is here reading.  this is completely opposite of what we should be doing.  our total number of weekend days (weekend days only being saturdays and sundays) remaining in philadelphia is four, and our weekday evenings are quickly being spoken for by friends and obligations.  somehow, though, rushing to get everything packed and ready feels like too much in this moment.  i know i'll be getting things done later in the evening, but now, i just want to be here listening to the radio, with my dog asleep by my side and my boyfriend feeding his comic book addiction by my other side.   yesterday i saw the neuro-opthalmologist, who said my eyes look perfectly normal and he isn't able to offer me any insight into why i'm still having headaches every day.  i've got to get a new prescription for my vision, though, and also new contacts, more expenses for which i don't really have money to cover.  i've got to do it, though.  i have to.  i've been wearing my glasses, which are weaker than my contacts, but my contacts are so old and dry that they're murder on my eyeballs, especially in the humid, hot, dirty summer air.   in the visit with dr l, after he put the drops in my eyes that would dilate my pupils, he brought two residents in with him and asked if it was okay if they looked at my eyes.   i said it was fine.  so as dr. l was going over my history with them, when he got to the point about how i was at first diagnosed with a brain tumor, one of the residents said "wow", kind of in a "hey cool!" sort of way.  this, of course, was inappropriate, so i said, with the intent of putting this kid, who was about my age, "yeah, it's been an interesting year."  the other resident was more in touch with things, and showed some empathy.  i swear, don't they teach bedside manner to these med students in these fancy med schools?  whatev.  it's cool.   but here's the part i wanted to write about.  this morning stean and i went to breakfast and he was telling me about the boyfriend of this girl who i hesitate to refer to as a friend, even though stean would do so (he's much more kind and forgiving than i am) and about a story of him (the boyfriend) when he was in africa for the peace corps.  and it made me think that maybe someday, when we're older and retired, that doing some work for the peace corps might be a really good thing to do.  cut to last night, when i was at tattooed mom's with a girl i work with and a friend of hers.  this particular colleague of mine demonstrates zero tact and zero attention to what is appropriate or respectful.  so she was kind of announcing to her friend about how i had some sort of tumor or something in my brain and how i was partially blind and disabled and stuff.  but anyway, her friend, who has albinism, was telling me that he has a friend who has MS yada yada yada and he used the word "degenerative".  it wasn't meant in some mean way, it was just said in a matter of fact, one disabled person talking to another sort of way.  but,  degenerative ?  ugh.  it's such a harsh, ugly word.   so, here i am this morning with stean, he's continuing on his story about the guy in the peace corps, and all i can think of is the word "degenerative" and that word is just swimming around in my head, hovering in front of my eyes and ears, with a weird echo effect.  degenerative.  and i think of my idea that stean and i join the peace corps when we're retired and i realize that for me it just might not be physically possible.  so what do i do?  i start crying, in the middle of the 10th street pour house.  not sobbing or anything, but definitely tears.   the thing is, blog, i'm very very very much in denial.  whenever i try to think about what it means to have this disease or how it could possibly effect my life down the road, it's like my brain freezes up and the world around me gets sucked in really close.  i was ready to have a brain tumor--i was up for it and i knew what it would expect of me.  with this, there's really no certainty except that there is uncertainty.  it's like god is playing on my worst fears.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       magnetized...  had another MRI last night.  my wait time was nil--i didn't even have enough time for the ativan to kick in before they were putting me back inside the ol' tube.  it's amazing how frightened and anxious i get in the middle of that magnet, which by the way, is called a bore ( urlLink http://electronics.howstuffworks.com/mri.htm ), even though i know it's just a harmless test and that i can get out of it very easily if need be.   i still swear that my brain twitches.  maybe it's just electrical current running through things at different points, but i can feel my brain move, like a reflex or a jolt.  i have to remember to ask dr p about this when i see her on monday.  i'm sure she'll think i'm insane, but i don't care.  or else i'm being paranoid and a hypochondriac...  the really bad part about my MRI is that before i left the magnet area, i glanced over at the screen that had my scans up and there looked like a lot of little white spots.  now, i can't be definitely sure that it was my brain, but it would make the most sense that it was my brain, since it was me they had just scanned.  i also can't be definitely sure that what i saw in a split second was an accurate reading of the image.  it could have been the ventricles or something that were causing lighter patches.  but i definitely saw a large white patch, which is probably the stupid lesion that's been with me since march 23rd, and maybe it's never going to go away and i'll never regain the sight i've lost and i'll be on this carbamazepine for the rest of my life, too.   i'm tired of things being for the rest of my life.  jesus god.   in other news, my brother and i got the same letter from my grandma about how she's worried that we're falling out of god's graces because of the lifestyle we're leading right now.  i could be wrong, but i'm pretty damn sure she's talking about how we both live with our significant others (the only other option is that she's upset that we don't vote republican).  this, mind you, is the third letter i've gotten this year from my grandmother criticising something i've allegedly done that has cast a shadow of shame and hellfire on my soul.  frankly, i'm hurt and offended by it.  realistically, however, my only recourse is to respond to her with love, because i know in my heart that she's only acting out of love for me and the duty she feels to her own beliefs and to me as her granddaughter.      
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      take this job and shove it...  just put in my notice at work.&nbsp; it was disappointingly disappointing.&nbsp; i've been looking forward to that moment since i accepted this job back in november (after my way un-fun 8.5 months of unemployment), and it just kinda happened...uneventfully.&nbsp;   but it's done now and my last day is formal (august 13th).&nbsp; so i guess i'd better be definitely&nbsp;leaving, because my landlord knows i'm not renewing my lease, my employer knows i'm not going to be here, and i've put down money on a place in pittsburgh.&nbsp; la la la law school, here we go. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      later than i think...   well.&nbsp; well.&nbsp; well.&nbsp; i've not been the best about keeping up with my posts.&nbsp; much has gone down since i last wrote.&nbsp; stean and i have a place to live in pittsburgh, i got my laptop computer (am writing on it now -- holy crap wireless internet is the awesomest thing EVER!), i have my class schedule and my first law school assignment (to read _a civil action_ ugh), amy and nick are married (!), my cousin and his ex-fiancee are back together, and at this point i'm less than 4 days away from putting in my resignation at work.&nbsp;   let me just for a bit do some writing about last weekend, when i returned to good old south bend, indiana, with orange bridesmaid dress and dutiful boyfriend in tow.&nbsp; stean and i flew into chicago on the 15th, and got a ride with brock and metzger to south bend.  we stayed on campus in st. ed's that night.&nbsp; i had no idea that being in a dorm as an adult would actually be fun.&nbsp; maybe it was the nostalgia factor, or maybe it was just the novelty of it all?&nbsp; signs point to nostalgia, however...&nbsp; those dorms have a smell about them.&nbsp; i don't know if it's the old wood or the cleaning products that are used, or the generations of boys who have slept in them, but there is a distinct and benignly comforting scent to all of the older dorms at notre dame.&nbsp; stean and i slept on plain sheets in single beds with the ND-issue blue wool blanket.&nbsp; it was quaint and cute and heartbreaking, all at the same time.&nbsp;   and oh, notre dame.&nbsp; god, i've turned into one of those sentimental alums who force their families to return to campus as if making some sort of spiritual pilgrimage.&nbsp; i dragged stean all over the place, pointing out where i studied and where my classes were and where my friends lived.&nbsp; also, i forced him to agree with me that notre dame is THE MOST beautiful school on the planet.&nbsp; had he disagreed, he may have found himself a single man.&nbsp;   thursday night we had dinner with the schosslers and some of the perdiews at this pizza place which isn't as good as rocco's (closed for the summer) but was still pretty good, then went back to amy and nick's room and visited and laughed and nick told us all about&nbsp;the concept of "balls from the back", a notion that i don't want to explain but that i do want to remember, for my own reminiscence's sake.&nbsp; and pam came out and met us at the mariott bar.&nbsp; she's all engaged now, i suppose she's next from that group of friends to take the walk down the aisle.&nbsp; pam gave stean and me a ride back to campus at the end of the night, and before we went in to the dorms, i asked stean to go with me to the grotto to light a candle (if you don't know what the ND grotto is, here:&nbsp;  urlLink www.nd.edu ).&nbsp;   ...you know, it's been ten years since i was a college freshman, and all of the important events of my life have happened within those ten years.&nbsp; i've lost my mother, i've moved on my own to a new city--twice, i've fallen in love and have had my heart broken, i've been without&nbsp;a job, and of course the big one--i've been diagnosed with a life-altering disease.&nbsp; in some respects, i am a completely different person than the girl who first set foot on that campus in august of 1994.&nbsp; that felt really real when i was in south bend last weekend.&nbsp; i'm gone through a lot of change.&nbsp; but despite it all, the things that have remained constant--the relationships i have with my college friends, the way the great hall in o'shaughnessy looks in the afternoon, the feeling i get when i know i'm surrounded by good people and good things--are an amazing relief.&nbsp; somehow, in all of the changing i've done as a result of intention and circumstance, i've managed to hold on to the fundamentals.&nbsp; i don't know, maybe i'm talking nonsense here.&nbsp; i'll get back to my weekend...  and so stean and i each lit a candle at the grotto.&nbsp; it was really quiet--only a couple of kids on the benches nearby (the campus was AWESOME without all of the students around--it gave me license to feel all nostalgic, kind of in an invisible sense).&nbsp; and as i stood there watching the candle i had lit in the midst of the hundreds of other little flames, asking god to help me find some peace and strength in the midst of so many unknowns about my health, i started to cry (i'm starting to cry right now, too), thinking of all of the times i had gone to that very spot as an undergrad to try to give my troubles away to a tiny bit of fire...  i have overwhelmingly fond memories of college.&nbsp; my grades were an embarrassment and i skipped too many classes and i had crushes on just about every boy in the school at one time or another, but those four years were really really good.&nbsp; i guess one of the things that made my little candle-lighting visit to the ND grotto so emotional was remembering that the times that the grotto came into my life during those four years were the times when i needed to ask for some divine intervention, the times when things were not so good.&nbsp; a lot of those times had to do with mourning my mother's loss.&nbsp; i guess in hindsight, i'm very fortunate to be able to see those moments as part of my college experience--they never got to the point where they controlled my college experience.&nbsp; i can still say, even though losing my mother was completely devastating, that there was a whole lot of good going on in that period, too.&nbsp; i'm lucky to have had the friends and environment that i had.&nbsp;   on friday we stopped in at the basilica, and again i was moved to tears.&nbsp; perhaps this speaks more to my spiritual fragility than anything else, but that church is so affecting and there was an organist and a vocalist rehearsing in the choir loft and when out of the silence began&nbsp;"crown him with many crowns" it simply broke my heart.&nbsp; it was like being in a magical but forbidden place, like heaven itself--i felt the need to touch everything a little longer than usual, to breathe in the air&nbsp;a little more deeply than usual.&nbsp; i wanted to take it all in and hold it inside, as if maybe something in that space, in that fancified building, was&nbsp;going to give me the answers to all of the questions that have been crowding my heart in these past months.  i can't say that it helped or made my life better or anything like that, but being at notre dame for those few days was, just like my thoughts on my days as a student there, really really good.&nbsp; the rest of the weekend had great moments, too.&nbsp; stean and i met valerie sayers for lunch on friday at lula's (which opened back in my day, and it's nice to know that it's still there), where i had perhaps the best salad i've ever had in my life.&nbsp; valerie looks great, and it was awesome to see her and visit with her, especially since she's been such a great cheerleader for me lately.&nbsp; also, it's cool to have reached the point where i can talk to an old professor like a fellow adult, where all of the preconceptions and formalities have for the most part fallen away.&nbsp; i think on some level, i want to be valerie sayers.&nbsp; stean told me as we were walking back to campus after lunch that he thinks that valerie and i are a lot alike and i took that as a great compliment.&nbsp;   friday night was the rehearsal and the rehearsal dinner (at the lasalle grille).&nbsp; the food was awesome (unfortunately, better than the dinner at the wedding, but oh well).&nbsp; amy gave us bridesmaids lockets with two chambers in them and our first initials engraved on the front.&nbsp; jessie and i decided that we're going to put pictures of our celebrity crushes in our lockers.&nbsp; jessie and i are also presently engaged in a "nerd-off".&nbsp; it's not the reason i've been wearing my glasses lately, but the glasses-thing is an asset.&nbsp;   after the dinner we met up with other folks on the 3rd floor bar of the lasalle grille.&nbsp; tony and carlo showed up, and tony silva and the boston crew, and pam and joe, and jen c.&nbsp; we could have all been wearing crap and could have been together in a prison cell and i still would have been as happy to be with all of those guys.&nbsp;   saturday was breakfast with amy and the other girls, then hair and makeup, then dressed, then pictures pictures pictures, and the wedding itself, which was beautiful with the flowers and the service and even the orange dresses (!).&nbsp; i managed to get through my reading, from song of songs, about my beloved is like a stag, a bounding gazelle, and come my beloved come, all with a straight face, and amy and nick looked so happy and at peace all weekend long.&nbsp; despite my differences with nick, i gotta say that based on things on their wedding weekend, i was okay with letting him marry my friend.&nbsp;   the reception had ron as a special surprise guest, which was not only awesome for me because i haven't seen ron in many moons, but it meant that stean wasn't the only man of color in attendance.&nbsp; dancing was good, company was great, i discovered that if i take aleve regularly, it offsets the headaches and i can drink more than 2 drinks.&nbsp; just don't tell my stomach!  and&nbsp;then there was the after party and the late night visit to nick's patio (as in the diner, not as in the groom) and the breakfasting the next morning and the hangovers and the hugs and the saying goodbyes.&nbsp; and i'm so so so so so completely grateful that i don't have a brain tumor and that i could have that time with those beautiful, brilliant, funny, amazing people!  alas, and now i'm back, with 3 weeks before the move and so much to do.&nbsp; but i won't think about that now.&nbsp; now i'm filled with happy memories of last weekend, and of college, and thoughts of how fortunate i am to have these people in my life, even if i only see them seldomly anymore.&nbsp; now i'm going to fall asleep thinking about the good things, which have always seemed to outweigh the bad.&nbsp; i'm going to believe that the good will always win out, and that whatever the bad may bring, i'll manage it for the best.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      independence day...&nbsp;  it's certainly been a boring fourth of july for me. not much going on at all, no hot dogs or hamburgers, no fireworks (which is honestly for the better because the experiences i've had going to the art museum for the fireworks have been way disappointing), no sunburns. we were supposed to spend tonight with joe and laura, but i haven't heard back from joe, so i guess those plans are null.   spent yesterday with chris and jenn in the jersey suburbs. we stopped in at a pier one that was having a big moving sale and i ended up buying four glass heads for $15.90. four glass heads! the size of my own head! oh, the possibilities are endless! put a bulb in them and call them headlights? make them into fish bowls? endless!   have now taken two injections. they're not so bad. it's a little unnerving feeling the resistance my own flesh and muscle has to the needle, but it only lasts a few seconds and then it's over.&nbsp; it's a lot easier than i thought.&nbsp; good thing, too, because i've got to live with these injections for a LONG time.&nbsp; a long time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      warning and reprieve...  this morning i was late to work.  about an hour or so later i got an e-mail from my boss saying that i need to make a point of being on time for work and if i can't manage to do that for the time i have remaining, then we need to talk about the consequences.   the consequences?  i have eight days left with this company!  i had half a mind to write him back and say, "look buddy, i'm running late ALL THE TIME.  if you wanted to make an issue of it, you should have done so before i gave my notice!"  it's a damn shame, however, that it doesn't matter that i work through my lunch break or that i stay after 6:00 not infrequently.  all that matters is that i make it in before 9:00?  ugh.  i'm glad i'm leaving.  the sad truth is that i've been waiting for these last few days since i accepted my job.  back in november i knew full well that come august, i'd be out of there.  at no point was my heart in it.  but now that i'm leaving, now everybody expects me to give my all?  um, sorry, but no.  i have too many other things demanding my energy and attention to devote it all, or even a majority of it, to the job from which i've officially resigned.   so maybe this means i'm a big slacker with no work ethic.  maybe this makes me sound like the laziest twentysomething in the free world.  i don't care.  the truth of the matter is that my name will be dragged through the mud regardless of how much i bust my ass in these last two weeks, so what incentive do i have to try to smooth over the wrinkles that have been there before me and that will certainly be there after me?  i plan to continue the way i've been going-i'll do what i can, but that's it.  i'm not going to be a martyr for the princeton review.  no way.   in other news, i had my last visit with dr p on monday.  she's definitely my favorite doctor ever.  she's got these weird quirky things about her that i just love!  like, she carries her prescription pad with all of these other papers all folded up and held together with a binder clip in the pocket of her doctor coat!  and when she pulls her hair back, it's never back neatly, it's always kinda lumpy, in a total function-before-fashion way.  and, she talks in double negatives--like, she would never say, "i think that's something that you should do", rather, she would say, "i think not doing that would be the wrong course of action."  she's brilliant, a little disorganized, and i trust her completely.  in some ways, she's what i aspire to be.  i never thought that i'd find a role model in my neurologist!   or perhaps i should say i never thought i'd have a neurologist.  monday morning before the visit, i worked myself up into a frenzy of panic and anxiety over what i feared would be the results of last week's MRI.  i had originally wanted to go to the visit by myself, but i was such a wreck by mid-morning that i called stean and asked him if he would go with me.  i had a really bad feeling that i was going to have very bad news, that dr p was going to tell me that there were many more spots on my brain as shown by this mjost recent MRI, and that would mean two very bad things:  one, that the avonex wasn't working, and two, that my MS was still actively attacking my brain.   i even cried at work.  i e-mailed my dad, and he called me at the office, and since there i share an office with three other people, my only illusion of privacy comes from turning around to look out the window.  and i was upset--way upset.  i was absolutely convinced that i was on my way to a discussion with my doc about further complications and alternate methods of treatment and i didn't think i could handle it.  not now, when i'm so close to beginning school, when i'm so close to my goal.  i was feeling overwhelmed, more so than usual, struggling for balance amidst work and packing and moving and bills and health insurance and a still-new diagnosis.   things are going to get better, right?  they will settle down soon, yes?  so, as you've probably guessed, the news was not bad.  when dr p called us into the examining room, she took one look at my face and said, "you look worried", to which i responded something like, "i have a really bad feeling about what my last MRI showed, so could you just tell me its results now so we can get that part of the visit over with?" and she said, "well, your last MRI looked pretty much like the one you had before."  i.e., no new spots, so either the avonex is doing its job or the activity has ceased for now, and either of those options is great!  i'm sitting here thinking right now, with milo plopped in a heap of white fur sleeping on top of a box full of stean's stuff next to me, that if things had been different, if my diagnosis had in fact been a brain tumor, this moment could be something something else entirely.  i would be on chemotherapy, possibly would have had brain surgery, meaning not just a little patch of short hair, but an entire head's worth, if my hair hadn't fallen out from the chemo.  god, i could even possibly have died, if the tumor was particularly aggressive!  i could be dead right now!  i just finished reading "middlesex" by jeffrey eugenides.  it was very good.  i didn't want it to end.  there was this part in it that i keep thinking about, and in thinking about it i'm not as scared as i thought i would be, and i'm not sure what to make of that.  the narrator is talking about the death of the grandfather, who has suffered a stroke and who has lost his ability to speak so he carries around a little writing tablet so he can communicate.  his mental faculties are deteriorating and the book says, from the grandfather's point of view, that he had always believed that a person had a soul, but as he starts to see his ability fade, he starts to realize that his brain is an organ just like the heart or the lungs or the liver, and it has the same vulnerabilities.  when the brain gets sick, the memory goes, or the ability to read or think or process information.  in essence, a person loses who he/she is, and it causes him not to believe in god anymore.  i've butchered the way the book says it entirely, but that idea is something i've been thinking about fairly frequently since this diagnosis.  what if we don't go on to something bigger or better?  what if we just stop?  it wouldn't be that bad--it would be what it is.  i can't decide if it's depressing or not.  i just can't decide.   well, i should get to bed.  even though one of my co-workers dared me to come in late again tomorrow, it's probably not in my best interest to do so.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      two weeks left...  this time fourteen days from now i will either have arrived in pittsburgh or i will be well on my way.  there is so much to do i really have no choice but to call out of work at some point.  i'll have to coordinate that with when the boss is going to be out.   pittsburgh.  law school.  finally!   man, i haven't washed my hair since friday morning and it's really gross right now.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>