<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've&nbsp;wasted a good amount of time&nbsp;indulging&nbsp;in an internet quiz addiction tonight, but at least&nbsp;I did a decent amount of packing Sunday.&nbsp; And yesterday I took care of a lot of phone calls and getting a new cell phone and stuff like that.&nbsp; On Dan's suggestion I called the theatre to see if anyone might want to make a few bucks helping me unload my truck on Sunday.&nbsp; Luckily, I was able to talk to a 2003 Journeyman who's up for the challenge (YAY!).&nbsp; That's really a good thing for me, because I was going to have to take off work early on Monday to meet the movers who were going to seriously overcharge me (2 hour minimum!) for what would really boil down to 15 minutes' work.&nbsp; I also called the electric company to get the utilities up and running in my name.&nbsp; I think I've almost gotten everything done that I need to.  I still have to clean out my car and pack up my clothes in my room.&nbsp; I think I might be able to pull that off tomorrow night.&nbsp; I hope so, because we're supposed to go out to dinner on Friday.&nbsp; I am going into work late tomorrow so I can go film a demo commercial in the morning.&nbsp; That should be fun, I hope.&nbsp; And if the demo is approved, I'll have an excuse to come back into town and shoot more commercials.   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's common knowledge at this point that Krystof and I hit the rocks a few months ago, and have been teetering on the edge of divorce ever since.&nbsp; In all the turmoil, I've been forced to look at what I actually want in a partner.&nbsp; I think I may have figured it out.   I want the guy who shows up uninvited and unannounced to cheer me up when I'm having a bad day.&nbsp; I want the guy who plans out the details of a surprise trip for my birthday or just because.&nbsp; I want the guy who calls to see if I got to my destination safe and sound.&nbsp; I want the guy who never thought of making stained glass but thinks it sounds cool and would give it a shot to see if it might be fun; I&nbsp;want the guy who thinks it is, even just because it means he gets to spend time with me.&nbsp; I want the guy who takes surfing lessons with me even though he's embarassed as hell.&nbsp; I want the guy who tries the new restaraunt.&nbsp; I want the guy who wakes up and thinks, "How can I make Jackie happy today?"&nbsp; I want the guy who hands me the remote and puts his head in my lap on the couch.&nbsp; I want the guy who reads the labels and says, "Oh, it's got gelatin in it... let's try another brand."&nbsp; I want the guy who loves the way I laugh.&nbsp; I want the guy who loves his family and wants one of his own.&nbsp; I want the guy who never forgets his family's birthdays.&nbsp; I want&nbsp;the guy who not only has patience with kids but has fun with them too.&nbsp; I want the guy who helps me cook up hare-brained ideas about owning my own restaraunt.&nbsp; I want the guy whose dreams happen to coincide with mine.&nbsp; I want the guy who puts his arm around my shoulder when I start to cry over the sappy movie he agreed to see with me.&nbsp; I want the guy who reads and inspires me to read.&nbsp; I want the guy who picks up a bouquet for me at the grocery store.&nbsp; I want the guy who reminds me to change my oil.&nbsp; I want the guy who squirts me with the hose when we're washing cars together.&nbsp; I want the guy who lays down in the middle of the park to look at the sky and cuddle.&nbsp; I want the guy who thinks art exhibits are a great date idea.&nbsp; I want the guy who takes me to the beach on a whim, even at night.&nbsp;&nbsp;I want the guy who cares about how other people feel, but doesn't give a damn what they think.&nbsp; I want the guy who buys his friends the best (not the most expensive, but the best)&nbsp;Christmas gifts.&nbsp; I want the guy who pulls over to see the "The World's Biggest Peanut."&nbsp; I want the guy who is more concerned about my meal&nbsp;than the waiter's convenience.&nbsp; I want the guy who drives across town in the middle of the night because he just had&nbsp; to see me.&nbsp; I want the guy who's enthusiastic about my suggestions.&nbsp; I want the guy who brags about me.&nbsp; I want the guy who defends me.&nbsp; I want the guy who thinks time and freedom are worth more than money.&nbsp; I want the guy who never stops learning.&nbsp; I want the guy who takes me to glam rock concerts and actually thinks they rock.   Thing is, "the guy" isn't whipped or obsessed or anything like that.&nbsp; It's a two-way street.&nbsp; I'd be "the girl" who wakes up every morning wondering how I could make him happy.&nbsp; I'd be just as willing to try new things as I would want him to be.&nbsp; That, to me, is the point of a relationship.&nbsp; It's funny that despite all the changes that have come over me in recent months, I still  want  the same thing I always did.&nbsp; It's just that now I know how important it is to stick to my guns and  get  it.  There was one day a few weeks ago when I saw this really old couple standing at a bus stop.&nbsp; He had one arm around her and the other holding her hand.&nbsp;  That  is what I want.&nbsp; I want to be 80 years old and still snuggling.&nbsp; I want my adult children to whine, "Aw, get a room!"   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>