<Blog>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Alrighty, this last week, has been a living heck! I've been deathly sick, and then, my best friend and i are no longer friends! So, yeh, i've had better weeks! I mean, i went, and apologized to kasi, and i just don't see why she was goin off on me and why she wrote that way harsh blog! It's stupid!..i mean, hello, she says that we're best friends and all, but yet, when it comes down to it, she says that i have to have all the guys, and be "lil miss thing"...i mean, if this is what she thought about me, then, obviously, she didn't know me well at all!...i mean, dagum...your best friends aren't supposed to be the people who think that about you, or, at least, that's what i was told! But, it'll all work out...it better....or else i've spent every night almost for the past two weeks, cryin...and i don't normally cry..over things like this!..so, yeh, it better work out...but, i'm gone! Bye Bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys!....Ok, kasi, i don't know what the heck you're problem is, but for you to tell me that, is completely rude. I would never even THINK about sayin the stuff, that you said to me, to you! And the whole deal with the russ thing...umm, you told me to go for him, and you told me that you didn't like him! And yes, i did tell you that i didn't like Brandon, and i don't!...and i did tell you to go for him, but, then, the truth came out, and you found out that i didn't want you to date him! And with the whole rusty and allison thing...there was nothin between me and rusty! I talked to him one night....AT CHURCH.....b/c i had hardly nobody else to talk to! And for the record, i never said that you couldn't talk to brandon as friends, but, i just said that it upset me that you would like..go to the  movies and go places and everything with him!....and it bein behind my back...at that! And hypocrite?....omg kasi....you're the one bein the hypocrite! Who'se the one that swore that she'd never date an ex-boyfriend?...yeh,that was you....and i just don't get, why you wanna go back on your word? And for you to tell me that i'm just tryin to get attention...c'mon kasi...who'se the one tryin to get attention now?...kasi, i came to you Tuesday on the computer and said that i was sorry for everything, and that i was tryin to get over it, and all, and then, i get back on Thursday, and i've got  you yellin at me, i've got christine yellin at me, and then you just bust out that you're datin brandon! If that's not wantin attention i don't know what is! And you're sittin here tellin me how everybody is sayin how you should be mad at me?..well, everybody that i've talked to, says that you shouldn't be mad at me, and that you shouldn't be doin what you're doin! I've talked to ppl in upper grades about it, and they said that they can't believe you're doin what you're doin...i've talked to ppl in college, and then, i've also talked to some adults! And i've only had one person tell me that maybe i shouldn't be as upset as i am....but, they still told me that you should'nt be doin it! And, i've had a couple of people tell me that they think that brandon is only datin you to get back at me...but, you know, i dunno! And for you to sit there and tell me, that i'm used to gettin all the guys, and bein lil miss thing...and for once i'm not...honey, lemme tell you somethin, you know good and well, that i don't think that! You know that i don't think i could get all the guys...you know this kasi massey, but yet, you choose to sit there, and write hurtful things..b/c you feel threatened! That's the only reason i can get that you would still be writin crap like this..after i apologized, for somethin i don't even need to be apologizin for! You, obviously, feel threatened by me!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Alrighty, well, i found out today, that kasi and brandon are goin out! Yeh, i'm pissed....b/c she knew good and well, that it upset me that her and brandon were talkin in the first place! But, i guess people now days, weren't like people before! I mean, people used to be sincere, and when they'd been friends with somebody for almost 4 yrs, and they'd promise never to go out with or do whatever with ex-boyfriends, they meant it, and they wouldn't! But, people now days, are different! And the thing is....i've got people who i thought were my best friends, doin this crap...i've got people goin off on me, b/c i'm upset! I mean dagum, every single person i've talked to about it, said that they would be pissed! I mean, i'm not gonna lie about it...i am suuper madd! I mean, i do not like him, in any way, but, it's the fact that she was my best friend, and he's an ex-boyfriend, and yes, i realize that it's EX...but, it's the fact that that's like an unwritten rule....best freinds just aren't supposed to date ex-boyfriends...and yeh, last year, i did it to kasi, but, kasi said that we swore we'd never date the ex-boyfriend if we had feelins for him, or if we just, were upset by it or whatever, and last year, kasi said that it was ok, and that she didn't like the guy i dated. Well, she brings it up, and she told me that it was fine...and that she didn't like him, so, i dated him, but, then again, we did only date for like a week! I just don't see how she could do this! She says that she doesn't want me to be mad at her...but, yet, she does this! And, i mean, it's like...she crossed over into territory, that shouldn't ever be crossed by best friends! So, by her doin this..i'm guessin i do need a new best friend, b/c we're no longer best friends! I guess i'm lookin for a new best friend?...but, i gotta go now, bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! **HAPPY TURKEY DAY!!!**  Sorry i haven't written in a while, but, i've been thinkin alot, and just...goin through stuff! Alrighty! Kasi and i...got things i guess, sort of worked out! I mean, i just, couldn't argue with her nemore! I can't argue with anybody right now! My self esteem and everything, is soo low right now, and i don't know how to boost it up. I mean, it's crazy! Well, wednesday, i went to my g-mas's house...and i forgot how much i love it up there! I'm goin to start goin  up there more! It's soo awesome! I mean, i can't even begin to tell you, how much, i love it. I mean, i while back, i was all hatin to go up there and stuff, but, now, i mean, it's like, that's the perfect place to go, when i need my mind cleared! My g-parents don't ask questions..they just comfort!..and it's great! But, the ex-boyfriend that i mentioned a while back, is a HUGE jerk. And i can NOT stand likin him as much as i do, b/c he's soo cocky...and i dunno why! I mean, he just needs to get the snot beat out of him by a girl! OOO you know how he was talkin to a girl from another school?...alrighty, well, the reason he hasn't asked her out...is b/c she told him no, the first time he asked her out, and then, i guess not too long ago, she told him that she didn't want a boyfriend....but, they could still talk or whatever!..haha...i was like..ok, well, why would you lie to somebody about it?...that's just stupid to me! but, whatever floats your boat! Guys, i'm still havin a really hard time....dealin with the whole brandon and kasi thing. I mean, i know she says that they're just friends, but, i mean...he's an ex-boyfriend, and she's a "best friend"...and somebody brought it to my attention that if she knows how i feel about this...about it upsettin me and all....and she still hasn't told him that they can't...whatever....then, maybe...she's not the best friend i thought she was?!...but, i dunno...i just want it all to stop...i want everything to stop!....but, maybe she isn't the best friend i thought she was?...b/c, she did go to the movies with him...behind my back...with no intention on tellin me...and best friends would't do that! so, maybe this person was right, by tellin me that i might need a new best friend?..i dunno....pray for me!..bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! Ok, well, that person that i didn't want to read my blog, read it, and now, she thinks that if she were to choose brandon, then, she would lose our friendship, and to be honest, she wouldn't. I mean, i don't like him, well, not anymore. And i mean, she can't help she likes him, but, it aggrivates me, because, like i said, we swore up and down that we would never do anything like this, or whatever, with one of our ex-boyfriends. And i mean, if i were to talk to one of her ex-boyfriends on the phone all the time, or go somewhere with him, or even act like i like him, she would be upset, and maybe even mad. She might not tell me, but, she would tell other people. And the thing is, i've asked some people, how they would feel about this whole ordeal, and they said that they would be soo mad, but, i'm not mad, i'm just...i dunno...dyin! I mean, i can't stop them from going out, and i can't stop them from liking each other. Alot of people have told me that they don't agree with what she's doin, b/c we're best friends, and i dunno.  I just flat out don't know anymore. I've talked to a teacher about everything, and she told me to tell kasi how i feel, but, i just can't. I don't know why, but, i just can't. And i know i'm holding back, but, that's the only thing i know to do b/c i know she's hurtin too....b/c she likes him, and she reads what i'm sayin and everything, but, then again, you know, the teacher i talked to, said, but, what about you, you've got to be happy too. And that hit me, b/c i do need to be happy, but, i would rather her be happy, even if it makes me hurt this much. I dont' know why in the world, it's hurtin me to see them like this, but, it does. My only guess that i feel this way, is because she's my best friend, and he's my ex-boyfriend. I just hope, that she doesn't think that i like him, i mean, i do have some feelings for him, but, then again, i have liked him since the 6th grade. IT'S SOOO CRAZY!!  newayz, on to another subject! I'm thinkin that i still like my ex-boyfriend from last year, alot, b/c he really and truly was everything i've ever hoped to look for in a guy. he was the guy that what my first true love. And, honestly, i would do anything, for him to feel the same about me, but, he doesn't; he doesn't even know i like him. He is talkin to a girl from another school, and honestly, i don't think would ever date me again. It's just sooo unfair that i'll probbably always love him, until i find the guy that can give me everything this guy did, and more. And i did find a guy who gave me that, but, my actions, and his words, were hurtful, and it didnt work out, and i wish soo much, that we were still goin out, but, we aren't,and he's not even lookin twice at me, but, i'm workin on getting over that, and i've almost got that down. But, i've tried and tried to get over the ex-boyfriend from last year, and i just can't seem to do it. I dont' know what it is about him, but, i just can't! But, i'll let ya know how it goes with everything! Bye bye, Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey again guys! Listen, um, i just wanna know if all ya'll out there will pray for me, b/c right now, i'm goin through one of the hardest things in my life that i've ever had to go through, and it's literally killin me!, and i don't know how much more i can take of it! I REALLY REALLY REALLY hope that a person i know doesn't read this, b/c it'll come hard, but, i haven't said anything to anybody, except for one person, and i feel like i'm holdin it in, so, i have to do somethin! Ok, here goes: one of my best friends in the world, and i, have drifted apart, over a guy.  She knows it, and i know it, but, we just, do'nt talk about it.  It's over an ex-boyfriend, and that's what kills me. We've been best friends, for the past 3 years..this bein our 4th, and everyday, for those past 3 to 4 years, we've sworn up and down, how we would never do anything or go anywhere or whatever, with an ex boyfriend.  We swore how we wouldn't like them, how we could'nt like them, and that, we just, flat out, wouldn't do that.  Well, i went out with a guy last year, and my best friend, started likin him.  Well, that was fine, you know, i could handle that.  Well, then, i go out with a guy this year, and then we break up. Well, he comes over halloween night, with my two best friends and i, and then, later that night, he kisses me.  Well, honestly, i started to like him, again, and was goin to talk to him, about maybe gettin together again, but, that night, my best friend, starts text messagin him, and i know how she is.  Once she starts talkin to a guy for a lil while, she starts to like him, so, i was just like, well, nah, i dont' think i like him.  And honestly, we kissed, and i, do think, that, that should have told her that i liked him, and did have some PRETTY STRONG feelings for him, but, it didn't, i dont guess. And, we've talked about how i feel about him, and her and all, but, i just can't bring myself to tell her that i had, or may still have, these feelings for him.  I mean, now, it's like...neither one of them, have time for me anymore, and i know that sounds, conceited, but, one of them was my best girl friend, and the guy, well, we were workin on our friendship bein best friends, and now, it's like...BAM, it's gone. and, it hurts.  It hurts, to know that everysingle one of my other best girl friends, wouldn't dream of datin one of my ex-boyfriends, whom of which i've liked since 6th grade, but, yet, one does.  It hurts, to know that my best friend and i swore up and down to each other, that we wouldn't ever do anything like that, or like this, or anything with one of our ex-boyfriends, but yet, she does it. It seems like i'm always the one getting shorted, but, yet, i always hold up my end of the bargain.  And, i'm sick of it.  She did it with another ex-boyfriend of mine, and now, she's doin it again. I find it highly funny, how she just switches over from one of my ex-boyfriends, to the other one.  And, i guess, it just aggrivates me, but, i dunno. But, that's all i had to get off my chest for now, bye bye, Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys!  Gees, i'm sick..and it's horrible..i can barely talk, i cough every 5 seconds, and when i cough..i sound like i'm coughin up a lung! When i get up, i get dizzy, and one minute, i'm hot, the next, i'm cold! I HATE IT!! Well, as i said, i met daniel last night, and he's such a sweetie! he's cute too! We were holdin hands ...sortof... haha..can't really explain that one!  but, it's cool! Well, jonci and i went over to lindsey's last night, and we had the best time, except for the bein sick part of course! We're both sick, at the same time, but, her fever was goin away, and mine was stayin, so, i dunno! I need to go to the doctor, but, i'm scared it's goin to be somethin REALLY bad, because when i try to breathe, my tonsils and throat are badd...and my tonsils aren't in too good of shape! But, ima quit my belly-achin now! Newayz, guys, i've got a problem! ok, i think i might have feelins for this daniel guy, but, i haven't decided on it yet. But, there's this guy, who'se name is bubba, who'se i liked all last year, and all this year..just about...well, when i wasn't goin out with anybody! well, a coupla months ago, bubba and andrew come over to my house..and i was likin bubba...alot...and then, andrew kisses me, and i pull away, and tell him, that i can't kiss him....b/c i like bubba alot...well, i guess andrew tells bubba that i kiss him or whatever..and then bubba, just like...stopped likin me..and everything..well, bubba talks to me yesterday for the first time in i dont' know how long..and calls me, and honestly, it felt great! Bubba is actually a guy, who i can play around with, and have fun with, but, be madly in love with at the same time, and i've missed that, when we haven't been talkin! but, i mean, i think i might like bubba, but, then again, i've got daniel there too, and i don't know what to do! And, i've got this ex-boyfriend problem, you remember, with the ex-boyfriend that i might still have feelins for?! Well, the thing with the ex-boyfriend, is that he was my first "true love".  I know what you're sayin, i'm only in 9th grade, how can i know what love is!  Well, the truth is, i can't, and i honestly don't think anybody else can either, but, it's different with him! It's like, whenever i'm around him, if i have a boyfriend or not, or if he's got a girlfriend or not, i just..want him to hold me, and i feel like i wanna spend the rest of my life with this guy, and it drives me crazy, b/c i'm soo positive that he doesn't like me like that, nemore, and it kills me to know that i still feel soo strongly about this guy, but, there's nothing i can do to change it! And, i can't say anything, or do anything, b/c he's talkin to a girl, and i wouldn't be suprised if he was goin out with her now...and, i just, can't say anything! But, it makes me soo mad b/c, i know that i gave my heart away to this guy a long time ago, and i never really got it back! But, newayz..pray for me...bye bye...Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      When the road gets dark, And you can no longer see, Let my love throw a spark, Have a little faith in me, And when the tears you cry, Are all you can believe, Just give these loving arms a try baby, and Have a little faith, faith in me  Have a little faith in me Have a little faith in me, oh and Have a little faith in me Have a little faith, faith in me  When your secret heart, Cannot speak so easily, Come here baby, from a whisper start, To have a little faith in me, And when your back's against the wall, Just turn around and you, you will see I will catch your, I will catch your fall just, Have a little faith,faith in me  Have a little faith in me Have a little faith in me Have a little faith in me Have a little faith, faith in me  I've been loving you for such a long, long time, Expecting nothing in return, Just for you to have a little faith in me, You see time, time is our friend,  Caus the rest is the end, All you gotta do is have a little faith.  I will hold you up, I will hold you up and, Your love gives me strength enough to, Have a little faith in me, Oh faith, darlin'  Have a little faith in me Oh, faith  This song has really hit me hard, with everything that's gone on lately!  But, i mean, i just wanna have break through and tell people, to have a lil faith me, b/c ima be alright! I mean, i kind of...had my lil "breakdown" if that's what you want to call it, these past coupla days, but, i'm fine now, and i realized, that i'll be fine in the long run also! It feels great comin to this realization...b/c i know and god showed me last night...that i'll be alright, and, that sometimes, it's ok to cry, and it's ok to let everything out...because if you don't, you keep it in, and then, your emotions start to get mixed up, and you get confused.  So, it's ok, and I know i'm goin to be ok!  But, i gotta go now, bye bye, Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Today was a pretty good day!...but, i've had better...i was just a lil tired all day!  Ok guy, i've got this problem.  ya see, i like my ex boyfriend...and, honestly, he could care less about me!  Whenever i see him, or pass him goin somewhere..he looks straight through me, as if i'm not even there..and that hurts! I mean, i dunno why, but, i still like him alot..and he just, basically acts as if i'm not even there..but, it'll all work out..hopefully! Also, i think i may like a previous boyfriend of mine! I mean, i wanna tell him, or like, drop hints...but, i can't...b/c he's talkin to one of my friends...so, what's a girl to do? I'm goin to one of my *BeSt FrIeNd'S* lil birthday get-together things, and it's gonna be pimp..hah..sorry, i just really love that word!...jonci and i are gonna bust up in there with lindsey and be like....WWWWHHHHAAATTTT..haha..j/k..but, it's gonna be funn! but, newayz! gees, what do you do, when the guy you're head over heels with, acts like he doesn't even care?...i mean..it's killin me...b/c i wanna tell him soobad that i'm head over heels in love with hi..and that i want him back..but, i can't do that...but, i'm workin on movin on....and i think i've got it almost down...but that all i got for now..bye bye, Love, Lauren 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys!!...today, was the BEST...ooo it was soo good!...it's been the best day i've had in while! gees, i started to forget what they felt like!  Well, things are back to normal between kasi and i....well, almost, and with jonci and i, they're kind of shapin up, and well, kristen moses was all gettin into somethin that didn't involve her, but, it's cool, she let me know somethin i didn't know already, and uh, it turns out allison i think, is still upset at me...but, i honestly, dont' care b/c i'm sick and tired of goin down that road!...newayz...ok, i think jonci and i are goin to our friends lil party deal this friday, and that guy daniel...is supposedly goin to be there..and ima hafta bust up in there lookin good..WWWHHHAAATTT..haha..j/k..but, i do hafta look decent..which is goin to be rough....and ima hafta play hard to get..but, it'll be easy! haha...i hope he doesn't read this..but, o well!  Gah, josh fuller, ima get you!..he hit me in my head today..and i was gonna get him back..but, could'nt! He's crazy!  Newayz!..alrighty guys, i guess ima go now, but, i'll write ya lata...bye bye!...Love, LaUrEn
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      GUYS, lemme tell you!!...kasi and i talked..and we're good...gah..i can NOT tell you how much better i feel!!...gees...but, i still have to worry about jonci and allison..but, i'm not that worried about allison!..i just hope jonci and i get things worked out! but, i gotta go now, bye bye Love, LaUrEn
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, i've got more bad news!...today, wasn't any better than friday!..or thursday!...ok, well, it seems that kasi and i, are never going to be the same again!...it's like..i dunno...but, i've still got the same 'ol feelins for brandon, and no matter how hard i try, there's nothin i can do to change them! and i mean...i'm soo not goin to tell kasi..how i feel..although she somewhat has an idea..b/c she means the world to me...and i just honestly couldn't live with myself if i let her pass brandon up...and i heard that they were supposed to be doin somethin this weekend...gah, that's what killed me!...i duno..would you say i have feelins for brandon?..i guess so, but, we've tried over and over to make "us" work...and, it's just wasn't workin! so, i dunno! Allison is "upset" at me! her boyfriend and her broke up, and i was sittin with him talkin to him last night at church and while we were out to eat, and obviously, she didn't like that very much, but, i don't care..he was my friend while they were goin out, and he's still my friend, no matter if he broke up with her..or what..he's still goin to be my friend..and i'm not goin to play the 3rd grade game, and just not talk to him..b/c he broke up with her..i dont' do that..it's not my style! guys, i just don't know what to do anymore, it's like, my life's upside down, and i can't handle it anymore...i dont' know what it is...but, i can't...kasi, means the world to me..and she's gone..i've lost her...and i dont' know how to get her back!...allison's gone..and i don't know how to get her back..and jonci's just about gone..and i don't know how to get her back either!..jonci and i drifted back apart..and can't get back together...if i lose her and kasi...i'll..hafta move somewhere..b/c i can't take lookin at the everyday..and knowin that i lost em...they're two of the most important ppl in my life..and....they're gone...gees..i'm bawlin now!..i mean, when kasi didn't speak to me, or even look at me, last night, and today, it crushed me..and with jonci..i mean, she talked to me and everything..but, we just...are driftin apart...and we both know it..or we should!..i mean...it's the point...where i can't take it anymore...my life..is turning into hell...and it's to the point..where it seems like, i would be better off somewhere else...in another state...in another school, somewhere else...than here...and i do'nt know, if i'm supposed to be leavin..or if i 'm just..supposed to stick it out...but, i must admit..it's gotten me ALOT closer to God...and that's the only part about this whole ordeal that i like..hah..what a way to go...but, that's all i got for now guys, so i'll just talk to you later..i'll keep ya posted if somethin else happens!..bye bye!!...Love, LaUrEn
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, what's up? Yeh, nothin much here either..cept i've had this headache that's killin for last..oo i dunno....3 HOURS!!...i really wanna do somethin tonight...but, this heachache is not lettin me! I was like..talkin to this guy...not really talkin talkin like about to go out talkin...but, like talkin as in hey what's up talkin...to this guy from hillcrest..named Daniel..(not givin you his last name)...and i mean...first time we talked..he seemed pretty cool, but now, it just seems..like everything i say...is like...retarded...ok, for instance, i crack a joke or somethin....all he says is ok...and i'm like...yeh, that was a joke..and he's like..ok..and i'm like...GAH, NEWAYZ!....but, it's all cool, that just means..that i gotta get out there and find that goofy, retarded guy...like i had....before i broke up with him...gah, i miss him soo much...his name was....left side..haha...that was a joke between us...well, his left eye is bigger than his right eye..so, i pickED on him about it...but, i don't wanna say his name! I liked him so much, and we just...clicked..b/c we were both ReTaRdEd..prolly me more than him..but, that's all cool!....but, he said some stuff, about my best guy friend...and it just wasn't workin out then..and honestly, we broke up in anger..and i've always been told never to do anything while you're angry..and i guess, i got showed what happens when you do..huh? But, i found out the very next day, he apologized....so, it's all cool, but, we're still not together :(...but, i'm workin on completely gettin over that one!..i duno why it's takin me soo long to get over him...but, it is! OMG guys (girls too) i think i might have feelins for an x-boyfriend of mine...that i dated a LONG time ago! well, it wasn't that long ago...but, it was a good bit ago!...he's soo goofy...i guess that's what i'm attracted to, along with eyes...and he's got killer eyes! But, i'll keep ya posted on how it goes!  OMG..you remember kayla...the girl that was sayin stuff?..well, she calls my best friend jonci (good news!!...we're startin to drift back together!)....while jonci was at my house...she stayed the night with me last night...and then kayla calls today...to see if she can come get her!! i was like...how rude is that!!..but, it's all good...jonci had to go..so, i'm cool with it! OO..and kayla and brandon's lil brother are goin BACK out..and he was like..sayin crap to me..about "goin off" or whatever on kayla!..i was like..no, she prolly didn't even tell you the half of it..and all...but, whatever!  That's all i got for now guys, i'll talk to ya'll later...bye bye!!..Love, LaUrEn
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Guys, i'm Lauren.  Yesterday, and today, have been the worst! Ok, this guy named Brandon and I were goin out a lil while back, and we broke up..which is fine and all...b/c i'm cool with it! Well, i've liked him since like the 6th grade.and i still have feelings for him, and i mean, who wouldn't...likin somebody that long!..but, my feelings for him aren't like...be his girlfriend feelings, they're more like...ok, put it this way, the physical attraction is there...but, the chemistry isn't! Well, it turns out that my best friend..likes him.  And honestly, that's fine and all..but, it hurts....bad...b/c she's my best friend...and i have feelings for him! I don't want to feel like this, honestly, i don't, but, I do, and i can't do anything, but accept them. And it's like, ever since she started likin Brandon, she's got no more time for me, and it hurts. Guys, (that means girls too); you just don't understand how important she is to me, and if i lost her, i don't know what i would do, but, i don't wanna say anything to her...b/c i would much rather me suffer than her suffer...anytime! And i was talkin to brandon yesterday, and was like..yeh, im a lil upset with Kasi, and he's like, why and i was like..b/c it's like..she's got not more time for me and stuff, and then, he tells her...the one person, i thought i could trust...tells stuff..and that right there hurt me...b/c he promised me that he would never tell anything i told him..and he did, so now, i can't talk to him anymore about stuff.  And then, i've got another friend, jonci, who i love with all my heart!..she's like my other half!...well, it just seems lately, that we're drifting apart, and i do'nt know what to do to stop it!...i mean..i try talkin to her more.but, sometimes, she just turns the other way!..and corey...i love corey to death, but lately, we just haven't been clickin as good as we used to...and i don't know what to do to stop that one either! It's just crazy.  And it seems like everybody's turnin against me.  And, austin, my hot chocolate, yelled at me today, and i started cryin!...it was bad...b/c he's never yelled at me before...and i just..lost it..i went up to david and said ima cry..and he hugged me..and tears started flowin! i dunno what to do anymore..i mean..i guess i need to find new friends?..but, it's goin to be hard replacing the ppl that i love! But, on a happy note, i think i'm goin to go meet this guy from hillcrest this weekend....but, i'm not sure!...Maybe i could replace brandon with him...haha...i'm crackin up....sorry, that was mean....but, i could'nt resist....wow, that's one of the only times i've laughed today...thanks...but, i guess i better go now, bye bye....love, LaUrEn  Alrighty guys, i'm back, to tell you some more bad news! It turns out, that a girl named Kayla has been tellin ppl some stuff about me, behind my back, and it's really pissin me off....sorry to cuss, or whatever..but, it is! She's been sayin all this crap...about how i'm mad at kasi..and she's been sayin that one of my best friends is tellin her this..and everything..and then she's goin to get mad at me for somethin i said earlier today...ok, lemme tell you what happened:...ok, so, she went out with brandon's younger brother, Jordan, well she broke up with him and was like..i like brandon, and then...she goes up to brandon today, and was like...i don't like you nemore b/c i like jordan..and i heard about it..and i was like..haha...it crossed over on you..big deal..well, she goes behind my back tellin ppl that she's soo mad at me and everything..but, when i'm talkin to her..she seems like there's nothin wrong..and i'm sorry..but, if i'm mad at somebody..and they start talkin to me...then, ima let em know i'm mad at em..not necessarily by tellin...but, more than likely by my tone of voice..and it gets on my nerves..and let's hope that lauren doesn't get too carried away...but, i'm sure i'll be fine!...but, that's all the news i've got now..oo..and by the way..please don't think that all i think about is brandon..b/c it's not...honestly..it's just that he's the one causin soo much crap right now....hah.bye bye...Love, LaUrEn
     
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HEY GUYS! i'm back from Georgia!! I had the BeSt time ever!..gees, i has tons of funn!! But, i'm glad to be back! I went to movies, i went shoppin, i did a lil bit of everything i guess! but, it's really good to be back! Well, the whole stephen thing, is goin nowhere!...i mean, i don't think he likes me..and i mean, i know that should'nt stand in my way of likin somebody...but, why like somebody...who you don't even have a chance with? I know i tell everybody not to give up, and just go for it, but, stephen's known that i've liked him....forever...and he knows that i've liked him even after we broke up...and, he hasn't done anything..and i've flirted like crazy..so, i'm guessin this is it? I mean, one minute, i'm soo close to askin him out, but, the next, it's like...what am i doin? I like him soo much, but, it hurts...big time, to like somebody soo much, and know that you don't have a chance in the world..with them again! And now, it's like..i'm the one left thinkin of him, and he's not even lookin at me!:  I woke up early this morning around 4am With the moon shining bright as headlights on the interstate I pulled the covers over my head and tried to catch some sleep But thoughts of us kept keeping me awake Ever since you found yourself in someone else's arms I've been tryin' my best to get along But that's OK There's nothing left to say, but  Take your records, take your freedom Take your memories I don't need'em Take your space and take your reasons But you'll think of me And take your cat and leave my sweater 'Cause we have nothing left to weather In fact I'll feel a whole lot better But you'll think of me, you'll think of me  I went out driving trying to clear my head I tried to sweep out all the ruins that my emotions left I guess I'm feeling just a little tired of this And all the baggage that seems to still exist It seems the only blessing I have left to my name Is not knowing what we could have been What we should have been So  Take your records, take your freedom Take your memories I don't need'em Take your space and take your reasons But you'll think of me And take your cat and leave my sweater 'Cause we have nothing left to weather In fact I'll feel a whole lot better But you'll think of me  Someday I'm gonna run across your mind Don't worry, I'll be fine I'm gonna be alright While you're sleeping with your pride Wishing I could hold you tight I'll be over you  And on with my life  So take your records, take your freedom Take your memories I don't need'em And take your cat and leave my sweater 'Cause we have nothing left to weather In fact I'll feel a whole lot better But you'll think of me  So take your records, take your freedom Take your memories I don't need'em Take your space and all your reasons But you'll think of me And take your cat and leave my sweater 'Cause we got nothing left to weather In fact I'll feel a whole lot better But you'll think of me, you'll think of me, yeah  And you're gonna think of me Oh someday baby, someday  *You'll think of me* :::Keith Urban::: Well, this is it guys, i guess, i'll hafta, get over stephen, and get back out there in the game! It was great...but, there's no more "us"..and won't ever be! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Guys! how's it goin? Umm..it's goin ok here too! Gees, i'm dyin! I want stephen to get on the computer...sooo bad..so, i can ask him out! Haha...lauren T,and i, sound like i'm flippin askin him to marry me..hah..it's funny! But, what if he says no? Gees,i don't know how that would hit me...i know it'd hit me hard...but, i don't know how i would take it! I mean, I like him soo much...and i know there are other guys out there..that like me...but, i just..don't think of them the way i think of stephen! Like, i mean, i think of stephen, somebody who i would take, and introduce to my grandfather! And, i've never felt soo strongly enough about somebody to introduce to my grandfather! I hold my grandfather, very close to my heart, and if he doesn't aprove of a guy, i just...basically don't see him anymore...i would tell a guy, that i could date him, or whatever..if my grandfather didn't aprove! And i know ya'll are like..well, what if you really like him?..but, i'm sorry, if my grandfather doesn't like a boyfriend..then, i don't date em...and if my grandfater doesn't like somebody...then, i don't like em! If Stephen and i do go out, i honestly can sit here and tell you, that i would take him to my grandfater, and introduce him to my grandfather, which, is different for me, b/c i've NEVER introduced my grandfather to a boyfriend! NEVER! And i'm scared, b/c if i do introduce stephen to my grandfather, if he doesn't like him, i'll be heart-broken...and i don't know what i would do! But, newayz..i guess i better go now, but, i'll keep ya in the know...bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How's it goin? Yeh, it's goin ok here too! Ok, so, i was talkin to Lauren T. today, about guys and all, and i've been thinkin about askin stephen out for a while, and she threw this at me: it's better to live your life without a bunch of what if's then with them!...and i read it..and realized..that i need to be askin stephen out..whether or not he says no...doesn't matter...but, i'll have the satisfaction, in knowing that i made that leap..and did what i could do! So, i'm askin stephen out!...and then, she showed me this: ..I wanna be the girl that he goes to bed thinking about,the one thought that never leaves his mind.The girl hes never had these type of feelings for,and even if he marries someone else, I wanna be that girl that he tells his kids about, and be known as "the one that got away"I want to be THAT girl he can't get over..! Guys, i wanna be this girl...to stephen! I don't know why i'm likin him soo much, but,i am, and i'm not just gonna sit here and let him pass me by! I'm sorry, i'm that kind of girl, and thanks to Lauren T, i finally realized it!...thanks girl, i love you soo much! I'm always here for you!...but, i guess i'm gonna go now, i'll be sure to keep you in the know about everything! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How's it goin? yeh, it's just goin ok here too! Well, last night, my dad and i went to sonic, and to blockbuster, and then came home and watched Leage of Extraordinary Gentleman, and my dad fell asleep about in the middle of it, so, i finished watchin that by myself..and then, when that was over, i watched How to Deal, with Mandy Moore!..it was a cute lil o movie! But, i'm sittin there..and the things that happened in the movie...made me realize..that that's how stephen and i would be..if we were still goin out! And, i've realized, that i'm gonna go for stephen, even if it takes me askin him out :(..i'm scared to ask him out..i've never really asked a guy out before! Wow...but, newayz...i just...don't know how he feels..but, i guess i'll find out soon! I mean, all i can say about this whole this...is, i dont know....and maybe that's all i'm supposed to know right now?! It's just all crazy..but, one thing i can say i do know..is that i like stephen..alot! And i know ya'll are prolly thinkin that i go from guy to guy, but, i don't!...I know i said i liked bubba...ALOT...and i did...but, stephen never left the picture...he was just shoved into the corner! And it took me a while to get over bubba, b/c i've liked him since the 8th grade..and honestly, i think he'll always have a part of my heart...but, that's fine..b/c i don't like him...i like stephen..and always have..since the first day i met him...and laid eyes on him! I liked him when i was likin bubba....but, it took bubba tellin me that him and i could only be friends, to realize it!...and i'm soo glad that bubba and i didn't work out...b/c i would hate to be goin out with bubba, and then me realizin then instead of now, that i like stephen soo much...and breakin up with bubba...b/c of that!..that would just kill me! But, i dunno....i'm gonna go ahead and go...i'll keep ya in the know about everything!...bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys!..how's it goin? Yeh, nothin much here either! Last night..was soo much funn..haha..i stayed the night with Jonci last night! We went to the movies and saw Lord of the Rings,and there were some lil chicks behind us, that just would not shutup!..haha..i thought we were gonna roll up in that mug..haha..right jonci? hah, we crazy! And we were ridin in her car today, and we were at the end of this road, and then, she was gonna do a u-turn, and asked if there was a car comin, and there wasn't..so, i said no..well, she starts to go..and i was like...WOOOAAAHHHH..and she like, slams on brakes..and i go..there's a car comin now...hah..it scared the crap out of her..and me too!! Hah...i couldn't quit laughin! But, newayz! Yeh, i'm still likin stephen!...it's soo crazy, b/c..i mean, i dunno how he feels about me...and all!..i mean, sometimes, it's like.he's sendin these lil messages sayin that he likes me..and then, other times..it's like..what the heck are you thinkin likin me?..it's just crazy..and i haven't decided yet, if ima go after him!..i mean, i do like him...dont' get me wrong...but, i just..don't know how he feels! But, i think that i'm just gonna go after him neways! I think he might be playin hard to get (which he's doin a really good job of, by the way) and honey, if he wants to play hard to get..i'll come and get him...there's no problem there!...but, i gotta go now, i'll keep ya in the know about what happens!...bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Sorry i haven't written in two days..hah!...how's it goin?..um, it's goin on with me..but, could be better! Alrighty, i've decided that Stephen's the only guy i like,and the guy i wanna go out with!, but, the problem is...getting him...b/c i'm pretty sure that he doesn't wanna date me:(..which sucks a big one!!...But, on the other hand, i do think that jonathan and brentley are cute, but, i mean, who doesn't..and that's all i think, is that they're cute..I DON'T LIKE THEM...i just think that they're cuties! But, newayz...yeh, i think that jonci and some other ppl might come and stay the night tomorrow night..and we're gonna roll left side's house..haha..it's gonna be great..b/c he thinks that i'm not gonna do it..so, yeh, i'm excited! Guys, i can not tell ya'll, how much i like stephen..i mean, i've never stopped likin him, since we were goin out! I mean, i liked bubba alot there for a lil while..and it was killin me, b/c i liked stephen just as much too...and i just..never told nebody..but, chacha over there could always tell ;)..girl, i love you soo much!....and it's just crazy...b/c knowin that you like somebody soo much, and then, you knowin that they won't give you the time of day...it sucks..big time!! But, it's like..whenever i'm in a crowded room..i look over..and i always tend to look where he is!..i don't know why..but, everytime i look over at him...and i just...wish we were goin back out!...like, today, i looked over at him, and then, he looked at me..and we were standin there..for about 5 seconds..lookin at each other...and then somebody's stupid tail had to pull my backpack..and loose that *LiL mOmEnT*..but, it's all good..we have alot of em..nah, not really..haha but, newayz!! And, well, i think i might be thinkin this other guy is cute?..but, i duno bout him yet...so, i'll keep in the know..hehe..but,..i gotta go now, bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! how's it goin? umm..it's goin ok! I feel alot better..bout the whole bubba thing...and i think i'm basically over him...but, it's still a lil rough around the edges! And, i found out today, that the ex-boyfriend that i might like....said that he only went out with me..b/c of my "body"...which i soo totally do not have! And, it hurt...bbbaaadddd... so, i dunno what i'm gonna do!..i mean, i think i might really like stephen alot..and honestly, i never quit likin him...but, theren't not a chance in the world that stephen would wanna go back out with me! But, it's handlin itself...maybe it'll handle itself right! But, i dunno what to do about him yet...he's just soo..complicating!...it's crazy!..and, i think i have a lil *CrUsH* on Brently Prestwood!...but, i dunno bout that one either...b/c i mean, i could like..meet him, and he be a total jerk or somethin...which i'm sure's not the case...but, you never know!....but, i think i'm just gonna go up and introduce myself to him....b/c..WE AIN'T NEVA SCAAAED...right baker?..hah..i love you girl!...you mean the world to me!..but, newayz...yeh, ima just march myself right up to him..and be like..i'm lauren..and stick my hand out for him to shake..and hopefully he'll go, i'm brentley..and we'll shake hands..and then, i guess i'll just be like..i'll see ya later B...heh..isn't that cute?..but, newayz...i guess i'm out....i'll tell you about anything that's happened..if anything happens later on today...bye bye..Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! how's it goin? Yeh, it's goin pretty good, but, could always be better, and worse! Today was an alright day! Had a coupla hangups, but, nothin big! Well, the "mystery" guy waved to me today, so, i think ima go up to him and introduce myself...and give him my number..hehe..but, i dunno yet! I think i might like an ex-boyfriend..but, i dunno about that one either!...but, it's all good! Guys, i'm just..i duno..kind of depressed! It's like...i dunno how to explain it, like, last night, i was watchin cmt....and it was like 2 in the mornin, and there goes my life by Kenny Chesney came on, and it made me think of bubba, and i just started cryin...sooo much, and i dont know why! and then i'm sittin there cryin, and i thought, why doesn't bubba want me?...am i not good enough?...and then i thought..well, maybe no guy is ever gonna want me....maybe i'm like, the worst girlfriend or whatever in the world! And, i just, don't know what's wrong with me!...i mean, i don't wanna feel this way, but, i can't help it!...i mean, i sit there..and i talk to my best friend...and, i just wonder if we're really best friends!..i mean, i know we are..but, sometimes..it's like..i dunno...i just...can't really describe it..i just wonder if she really wants to be my friend?! I dunno..i just...need a good cry i guess!...wow..i bet everybody readin this is thinkin i'm a psycho..hah.i'm not..promise!..i'm just..havin alot to deal with right now!...and it's kind of..crazy! I promise i normally dont' cry like that! haha! Guys, i'm torn between two ppl..on decidin who i like...i'm havin a hard time decidin on the ex-boyfriend, or the "mystery" guy...but, it's all good, ima go up and introduce myself to the "mystery" guy..but, i better go now, bye bye, Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! did ya'll have a good weekend?...mine was sooo much funn! Well, friday, jonci came over, and then cristine came over, and then, we went ridin! We went to wal-mart to get some toilet paper, pads, and shavin cream, to go roll a friend of mine's house! Well, we get there..and christine is like..OMG..is soo lit up..so, she's like..lauren, go run out there, and lay on the ground..to see if anybody can see you from the road..well, i had my hand on the handle on the door, about to pull it, and then, a cop shows up, so, we like..left! Well, we turn into this other subdivision and when we were sittin there waitin to turn out..a cop comes by..and stared us up and down like crazy! We were like..OMG..b/c it was the same cop...well, we leave..and then, another cop shows up..and then, we see another one..so, then, we're on our way to my house..and then, a cop follows us...and it was just crazy..so, we're gonna hafta get my friend's house next weekend, or somethin..b/c he thinks i'm not gonna get it..and i couldn't this weekend..b/c the cops..and then saturday i stayed with a friend..but, it's all good!...but, i gotta go now, bye bye!...Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys...how was your day? Mine was ok...gettin better every day! Alrighty guys..i think i'm startin to show some progression on gettin over the whole bubba deal! It's just that..when i have absolutely nothing to do..he's on my mind..so, i tend to stay busy...b/c when i don't think about him...i don't miss him!..but, it's all good..i'm startin to get over him...which i'm really glad of! But, i think that i'm thinkin this other guy is cute..but, i haven't decided on that one yet..so, i dunno! Guys, it seems as if i'm losin all my friends! I dunno what it is..but like, all my friends are like..leavin me...but, yet, i'm gainin new friends left and right too!...so, i dunno...it's crazy! I dunno about the guy status right now..i think i might just lay low...but, yeh...that one guy is cute...and then, there's this other guy, who is cute..and who'se startin to talk to me more also...but, he's kind of talkin to somebody...so, i'll hafta see how that goes before anything happens! And, i think i might like an ex-boyfriend...AGAIN...gees..it's crazy! And i don't know that i wanna like him...i mean, i can't help it...it's just somethin that's like..attracting me to him...but, it's great....but yet, it's horrible...so, i dunno?! He's just soo..funny..and..i dunno..somethin about him gets me everytime....! Not too many people can get me..unless i've just come to like em...and bubba got me alot..and still does...and this guy does..sometimes..but, i haven't figured out how i feel about him, or anybody for that matter..yet! But, i guess i'm gone..bye bye...Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      *we may think that the one we love is the only one worth it for us, but, havin a broken heart is just a part of life; one that must be endured and overcomed. However, it's pointless to stay that way. Love doesn't mean holdin onto feelins and bein devoted to someone you can't have anyway. It's wanting what is best for the other person even if it means not getting what you want. That's not to say that the pain shouldn't exist or will fade away just like that, but true love desires the happiness of the one you love. Knowing before hand could have saved you that piece of your heart for someone else; someone who will share a life with you so beautiful that you'll cry tears of joy at the thought of it as opposed to the tears of pain that led you to where you're sittin right now.*    Guys, this was given to me, by one of my good friends, and i thank her soo much, for giving this to me. I know that i still like bubba..and care for him alot..but, with help from God, and my friends, i'm movin on..slowly, but surely..and i've realized..that i'll be ok...in the end.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I will remember you will you remember me? don't let your life pass you by weep not for the memories  remember the good times that we had  let them slip away from us when things got bad clearly i first saw you smiling in the sun wanna feel your warmth upon me i want to be the one  i will remember you will you remember me? don't let yoru life pass you by weep not for the memories  i'm so tired that i can't sleep standing on the edge of something much too deep it's funny how i feel so much, yet cannot say a word we are screaming inside oh we can't be heard  i will remember you will you remember me? don't let your life pass you by weep not for the memories  so afraid to love you, more afraid to lose clinging to a past that doesn't let me choose where once there was a darkness, a deep and endless night you gave me everything you had oh you gave me life  i will remember you will you remember me? don't let your life pass you by weep not for the memories *I Will Remember You: By: Sarah Mclachlan*  Guys, i found out, last night, that bubba and i were gonna be just friends. Yeh, it hurt...right in the heart....but, i'll be ok! I'm workin on movin on..and maybe when the next guy comes along..he'll be better?! I dunno..but, i guess i'm.."free game"..as somebody called me yesterday..yeh, thanks..you know who you are!...but, newayz...well, there's a guy i'm thinkin is cute...but, i dunno...he doesn't even know i exist..so, it's all cool..but, i'm gonna go now guys...bye bye!..love, Lauren      
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Guys! How are ya'll? yeh, i'm doin ok too! But, i think that...my heart's gonna wind up gettin broken! Well, see, bubba came over friday night, and i haven't talked to him since friday..so, i'm thinkin he just..doesn't like me...and the way he was actin..i just..don't know nemore guys! i used to could tell when a guy was just in it to get somethin..or not..but, now...they're stepped it up a notch...so, i guess ima have to also! Guys, i can not even tell you..how much i like him! I sure hope he doesn't read this...b/c it'll prolly drive him away..but i'm head over heels for bubba! But, everything will work out..in the end...HOPEFULLY :) But, it's cool! So0o...i don't guess i really have anything else to say..i'll keep ya posted on how things go with bubba!...bye bye! Love, Lauren!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Omg...bubba came over last night! He's soo cute...but... shhh..don't tell him i said that! Newayz, yeh, he came over last night..and i was like....soo happy all night...well, except when he got me upset..and i almost cried..but, that's a different story! And it was just great...b/c i really really like bubba..and i just..can not even tell you how much i like him..it's like when ever i see him..i get weak in the knees..and my heart beats slower and faster at the same time!...it's like my heart just melts!...but, that's another SHHHH! Newayz..ok, well, my best friend...cato...is suupppper pissed at me..b/c i didn't tell him that i've liked bubba since 8th grade...and i didn't tell him..b/c i was tryin to make it where i didnt like bubba...b/c i just..didn't think that he would ever like me...and it's crazy..b/c cato's pissed at me..and i can't stand it when he's mad at me!...and then there's pickett over there who'se laughin at me likin bubba..and won't tell me why that's soo funny, so, yeh, now i'm pissed at jason too! newayz!! Well, i guess i'm gonna go drownd my sorrows in a bottle of vodka..haha..j/k i don't drink!...bye bye!.....Love, Lauren!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How have ya'll been? I've been ok! Gettin better, and movin on...day by day! OMG...i'm in love!!..haha...umm...not really love love but, love!..haha..if that makes sense! I've liked this guy...bubba...for a while, and i was talkin to my youth minister wednesday, about my situation i thought i was in, and i got it showed to me, that there are many things that catch your eye....but, only few things that catch your heart....pursue that! And i realized that i REALLY REALLY REALLY like Bubba..and he's the guy i wanna be with (haha..maybe a senior though audrey) and i'm not gonna let that pass me up, so, i had decided that i was gonna ask him out, and then, i get on the computer, and he's on so, i was like yay! So, i'm talkin to him...and was like..so, who you likin..and he goes..i dunno..and i was like..oo..well, i was gonna ask you out.but, i dunno now...and he was like...why?..and i was like..well, i don't want you to say no to me...and he goes oo ok..and then, yesterday, i imed him and was like..hey bubba..and he goes hey, look, do you still wanna date? and i was like...umm..yeh...and he was like..ok, well, how about us doin somethin then seein where it goes from there..and i was like..ok...so, he called last night..and we were supposedly supposed to do somethin tonight..but, i dont' guess we are..b/c i haven't talked to him, today..so, i dunno? But, it's all good...i really hope everything works out with this one though! But, i gotta go now, bye bye! Love, Lauren!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Gees, the message tonight at church was AWESOME! I can NOT even begin to tell you how good it was! Guys, i can not even begin to tell you, how important it is that you know who christ is, and that you accept him, as your personal lord and savior! God created this earth, and the whole universe! He created everything, and i just don't see how people could sit there, and say that they don't believe in him, or they know he's real, but, just, choose not to accept it! I mean, why would you want to spend all eternity in Hell? It's just stupid! And for the people, who say, well, you can prove where hell is, and where Heaven is, well, lemme tell ya, Heaven is above Hell, and Hell is under Heaven! How do i know that God is real, you ask? Alrighty, you've got the bible, you've got personal testimonies, i mean, you've got all this stuff, around you, and you just sit there and act like it's a "coincidence" that it's there! I mean gees! C'mon now, if there was no God, then, there would be nothing! But, you know, if you wanna go to Hell, and ignore that you could go to Heaven, and live with God, himself, then, that's a decision that you get to make! But, i'm gone..bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! Alrighty, well, i guess kasi and i are just ok now..but, you can tell there's still tension, and as for brandon, i haven't talked to him in three weeks..and i do'nt guess i'll talk to him in a while!..but, i dunno! Newayz, umm, today was better than yesterday..thank goodness! But what gets me about this whole ordeal with kasi and everything, is that kasi and i will never be the same! You can sit there all you want and say it will...but, everybody knows that it won't! And as for us bein "upset" with each other...then, there's still that lil bit there...maybe alot for some ppl...but, who knows! Newayz, well, as for the guy status right now, I'm SiNgLe!!! haha..a guy told me that i was fair game today!..haha.i cracked up!...but, i dunno if ima get into another relationship just yet...i think i MIGHT like a coupla ppl..but, haven't decided on them yet! But, newayz..i guess ima go watch a movie now...bye bye! Love, Lauren!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys!..wow..i haven't written in like..forever..but, how's it goin? Umm..not so good here! Yeh, well, you know how cameron was all like..yeh,i like you alot..and stuff? Yeh, ok, well, he busted out that he had been thinkin about it..and he didn't think that we would work out..yeh, so, that's got me upset...b/c ever since brandon and i have broken up (except stephen)..it's like i'll like a guy..and i'll go for him..but,when i finally have him hooked..it's like..i don't like him anymore!..and with cameron..i was fully able to like him!..i dunno if any of this is makin sense..but, whatever! ..i mean..i know his feelins are his feelins..but, he could've told me from the get-go instead of bein all like, yeh, i like you..and gettin me into it..but, it's all good! I'll move on..hopefully...i always do! But, newayz..onto Justin! See, justin's a sweetie!...and i love talkin to him and all..but, he's just soo dagum stuck on this nicole chick!..i mean..gees! It's like..he says he wants to get over her..and all..and move on..but, he does NOTHING..to get over her! He still talks about her, he still thinks about her..he still text messages her..he still calls her!..i mean..c'mon...there's just some things that come with commen sense! And, it's like...when i call him sometimes..really needin to talk..before i cry..he doesn't answer..but, yet, when he calls me..to talk..i'm always there to talk!..and it's like..it's not a fair friendship! I mean, his ex-chick is like..crawlin back to him..and he's basically takin her back!...he says that he's tellin her that he doesn't want her back and all..but, i don't believe it! He's better off without her..honestly, but, i don't think he's strong enough, emotionally, to see that! He needs to get out there..and see that there are soo many girls out there.that would be so lucky as to have justin for a boyfriend! He's truly a great person!..and he deserves somebody better than his ex-chik!...but, who am i to tell him who he needs to date and who he doesn't need to date?..nobody!..But, newayz...alrighty..i'm gone..but, i'll keep you in the know..WAIT...OMG..ME AND CATO GOT THINGS WORKED OUT!!..i am soo glad! We're still friends! Omg..i can not tell you how glad i am that we got things worked out!..he was not talkin to me for a while..but, we're cool now!...so, i'm gone...but, i'll keep ya in the know about everything! bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! gees, i haven't written in like...4 days! But, what's goin on? Yeh, some stuff's goin on here too! Ok, well, friday, i stayed the night with abbey (hehe..i love ya gurl) and we went skatin!...and friday, at school, i gave justin a note..and it had my number in it and all...so, he called friday night, but, i wasn't here!..so, i called him back, and he wasn't home, so, he called me back saturday, so, i talked to him saturday, and saturday, abbey stayed the night over here! And sunday, i talked to justin too, and i talked to cameron too! See, i had talked to cameron on the computer, and he said somethin..don't remember what...and i said, well, i'd hate to come on too strong..and he was like..what..omg lauren..so, he called me..and we were talkin..and he goes yeh, bout the whole comin on too strong thing, i was just playin around, and i said, ok, and he goes, no, i'm bein serious..and i said, i am too..i said ok! So that was that..talked to him for a lil while after that..then, talked to justin! So, i dunno what i'm thinkin bout justin...b/c honestly, i think he's too caught up on an ex-girlfriend, and all her drama that she's got! So, i'm thinkin i minas well just leave that mess alone! I mean, they dated for 9 months, and i barely know him, so, i guess it'd be good to let him do his own thing..? But, whatever! I mean, i feel bad, to see justin like this..b/c..well, i guess b/c i've never seen him like this..seein as i barely know him..so, i mean..i dunno! But, i hope he does find strength to move on..and believe me, i know it's hard...but, sometimes, the best things for you to do in life...are the hardest things to do! But, i can't talk about that anymore!..it's makin me sad! So, on to another subject! Well, destin (cameron's brother) told me that cameron likes me! It took me by suprise..big time...b/c i just..didn't think that he liked me, but, i guess he does!? So, i dunno if i like him yet, i mean, i'm interested, but, i have to hang with him before i know if i like him yet or not! But, i'll keep ya in the know..on everything! bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How's it goin? Yeh, it's alright here...but, a lil bit of guy trouble..if you could call it that! well, the guy i was tellin you bout callin me a beotch..it's not about him..it's about the other guy..and it's gettin confusin so, the guy that called me a beotch...his name is justin...and the other guy, is cameron! Ok, well, see, i've known cameron for a lil while now..and we almost did this whole ordeal before..but, did'nt! And now, we're tryin it, i guess..i dunno how it's goin! Well, see, i do like cameron..i think...and, i mean..it's like..he won't talk to me! I mean, i put forth the effort to talk to him..and all he's got to say are one word answers, and oh or yeh, and it's makin me mad! B/c he barely talks to me..and usually, i can read most ppl like a book, and i can't him..i don't know if he's feelin me..or not..i don't know what's goin on! I mean, he KNOWS for a fact, that i'm interested in him, but, yet, he doesn't talk to me! The cameron i became interested in, was the cameron who made me laugh all night long, was cameron, that doesn't care what anybody thinks about him, and would talk to a brick wall, if nobody was lookin! But, obviously, i'm "comin on too strong", and he's changed..so, i guess that'll be that?! I hate it..with all my heart..but, it is the way it is!..so, yeh! But, i dunno how it's gonna turn out..prolly for the worse..like everything does..but, hey, it's all good!..but, newayz..o, yeh, i saw justin today..he gave me a hug!..hehe..but, newayz..i'm gone! bye bye! Love, Lauren..and by the way..thanks shortcake, for helpin me through this whole ordeal!..i appreciate it bunches!..and i'm always here for ya if you ever need me! =)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How was your day? Yeh, mine was pretty good too! oooo, you remember the guy guy i was tellin you about yesterday that said he was gonna hafta get my number?..well, he called one of my girlfriends, and asked for my number, and i was excited about that b/c he actually wanted it...=)..hehe..so, then, i asked him about it today, and he's like..yeh, i wanted it to call you, and tell you that you were a beotch! I was like woah!..i'm pissed now! So, i'm a lil upset at him now! But,i don't see the other guy i was tellin you about..at all during the day! It irritates me..b/c i mean, i wanna see him..i really do, but, i don't! And he has a twin brother..so, everytime i see his twin...he like..gives me these dirty looks!..makes me just wanna go up to him,and punch him in his face! But, newayz! I guess that's all i got for now..but, i'll keep ya in the know bout what happens with everything! Bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How's it goin? Yeh, it's goin pretty good here too! How was everybody's new years? Mine was pretty good! alrighty, well, Stephen and i are just friends now, well, we've always been just friends, but you know what i'm sayin! It'll take me a lil while to get over him, you know, but, i think i'll manage! And, in the mean-time, there's a guy, that i'm doin somethin with this weekend! He's such a sweetheart!..=) and, he makes me laugh!..which is great! Yeh, he's a sweetie! And i think that, there might be somethin there for us?..i mean, i dunno that it'll be anytime soon, or anything, but, i think there might be!..but, who knows..could be soon! And then, there's this other guy! He's a sophomore! (oh, and the first guy i was tellin you about, he's a junior) This guy, is a cutie, and sweet too! i was givin him a g'bye hug today, and he was like..you can't be rubbin me like that..and i was like..well, somebody better get used to it...and he goes, well, if you're gonna be rubbin on me like that..then, i better get your number..so, i was walkin off when he says this, so, i turn around..and i give him a lil ;)..wink!..hehe..it was great! but, yeh, that's bout all that happened today!..oo, and the first guy i was tellin you about, i was talkin to him on the computer..and he was like: so, who you likin these days?, and i was like..i dunno right now..but, i think i've got somebody in mind..and he goes o, who?..and i was like you..and he goes: wow..i'm suprised..and i was like..why?..and he goes..just am!..i was like.oo, alrighty!..haha..but, it's all good! But, ima go and take a lil nap now..bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! How's it goin? yeh, it's just ok here too! Well, i was at stephen's house last night...it was barbara, will, blake, vanessa, cameron, destin, stephen, and me! We just like...sat by a fire, watched movies, played games...and watched some ppl get mad at each other..yeh, i mean, it was pretty funn! Well, the whole stephen thing is  out! Like i've been tryin to tell ya'll all along..he doesn't like me...and i could have told ya'll that from the beginning, but, it just took me this long..to actually realize it! And when i found out, gees, i was like..soo upset...i almost started cryin..but, hey, that's life..right?..life's got it's ups and downs!..you just gotta learn to deal with em! So, it's over...i'll hafta quit thinkin about him, i'll hafta quit meltin when i see his face...and i'll hafta quit thinkin that maybe there's that lil chance that we could actually get back together! It's really over, i'll hafta quit thinkin that maybe he likes me...and i'll move on! It's gonna be hard, i'm not gonna lie to you, it is goin to be very hard, but, i'll manage..i always do! I don't know how long it'll take me...but, i'll hafta do it!...there's no way in gettin around this one!...Gees, the ONE guy i have to go after...i can't get...and it's killin me! I mean, it's like..my whole day gets better, when i see stephen, and now, it's like..i can't think of him like that anymore!? I dunno..but, i'm movin on..or tryin to!..i'll keep ya in the know with how that goes!...bye bye! Love, Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! What's goin on? Yeh, um, nothin really here either! Ok, so to keep ya'll informed here goes: Um, i am goin to introduce myself to this brentley kid, and i was goin to do it today, but, i got stuck between some guys that wouldn't let me go, until after he was gone =(..so, yeh, it'll hafta wait til tomorrow or friday! And, ok, you guys remember cameron? Ok, well, i dont' kow what the crap is goin on..but, it's like..i'm thinkin about him...and i have been for a while now, and i do need to stop..b/c i soo know that he doesn't think of me like that! I mean, i don't know that i like him, or anything, but, you could say that i'm interested! And it's like..since the whole him tellin me it wouldn't work, i just..keep thinkin about him; and i'm pretty sure it's the girls want what they can't have..but, dagum, this is a little too crazy, don't ya think? Yeh, i do too!..but, who knows?..not me!!  So, then, there's Bill!  Bill is a senior at clinton, and super hott! ok, well, he goes to my church, but, comes off as really shy, and doesn't really "interact" with the youth group..and i just..don't want our youth group to be like that!..i want everybody to be a part of it! And seein as i'm completely not shy, i'm goin to try to bring him out of his comfort zone some, but, it's just a try! Well, i was talkin to Bill one night on the computer, and was like well, what are you doin this weekend (this was before i knew that i was going to be gone until 12:30 saturday night) and he was like..nothin...ask john (his brother)..he'll tell you, i'm a loser! and i was like..well, i'm sure your not (got a lil bit of flirtin goin on) and then, he goes..yeh..i am!..so, i was like..well, if you're not doin anything..do you want to do somethin? and he goes..well, ms.gordon will probbably give us a term paper, but, if not..if not, and i'm free, we'll see!..so, i took that kind of both ways..one way, as i'm usin ms.gordon as an excuse...so, stop tryin..or that he really could have a term paper that could be assigned to him by friday!..but, i dunno!..so, i'll hafta keep ya'll informed and everything! But gees, lately, i've been havin the worst mood swings, and i don't know why! I mean, it's not that time of the month, or anything..but, my mood swings are bad!! I can go from super happy and smilin, to like..flat out rude within 5 minutes..and i hate that..b/c i really don't like to be rude to people, so, i try to control them the best i can...but, it's hard! But, anyways...i better go now, i'll talk to ya'll later! bye bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How's it goin? It's great here! Ok, so, this week, for spring break, i went to New Orleans with my youth group on a mission trip, and it was so amazing! Everyday for like 3 or 4 hours, we went to a park, and played with so called "less fortunate" kids, and they were soo amazing! I can not even begin to tell you, how many life lessons that i've learned, just from kids that are way younger than i am! And ther are people that sit there and say that they're less fortunate just because of what they have, or don't have, and what kind of places they live in, and it's not right...because those kids..were so amazing and this trip was one of the best experiences that i've ever had..and i will never, ever forget it! It was just so amazing..and brought alot of things into perspective! So, yeh, the guy status: still single! There's not really a guy i'm liking, or anything, so, i'm just..contempt! I mean..i think that i'm ready to find somebody that i can really relate to, and understand very well, but, you know, he hasn't come along yet, so, i'm just...patiently waiting! And, i haven't introduced myself to this person yet..because i don't know if i want to introduce myself to him anymore...i'm starting to think that it's not the right time for me to be dating right now..but, you know, if that somebody that i can relate to and understand comes along..i guess that'll be the time that it'll be right to date!...but, anyways!..i guess i'm gonna go now..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys!..gees, i haven't written in like....FOREVER! yeh, but, anyways! How's it goin? Yeh, it's goin great here too! Well, i'm leavin saturday to go on a mission trip with my church to new orleans, and it's gonna be GREAT! But, the guy status is still the same: single! And i'm thinkin it's for the best! I mean, if a guy comes along, that i have feelings for, then, that's great..but, if they don't..then, that's fine too! But, i've just...got alot of things on my mind right now..and i honestly don't think it would help that situation at all, if i had a boyfriend right now! But, i am going to introduce myself to this guy who i think is cute!, but, i dunno that he'll like me, or anything, but, it's all good! Ok, i'm about to lay out some stuff..that everybody thinks..but, just..don't say..and it's been botherin me for a while now..so, i've GOT to get it off my chest..so, here goes!: I think it's soo funny how one day, you can be friends with somebody, but, yet, when they start datin somebody, they just..completely change..and act like they don't even know you! I mean, it just kills me, with this one guy..b/c him and i used to be friends..and he used to be a great guy..and probbably still is..but, you know..he just..makes me feel so inferior..and i don't stand for that at all...nobody should feel the way that i feel when i try to talk to him..so, i just...don't talk to him! and i mean, i want to..i really do..but, i just..can't!...it's too hard!..but, whatever..that wasn't as bad as it could have been..i held back..but, NO REGRETS! I'm out..bye guys!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? Yeh, nothin much here either! OMG!! guys are sooo frustrating! ok, the guy i last wrote about....you know, about how i shouldn't like him?...ok, well, i talked to him the other night..i just dont' kno about him anymore! I mean...i've liked him for soo long..but, i just never really thought it was there..and i guess now i do...and it's like..he's changed! I mean, the guy i new before...wasn't the guy i know now! It's like he has this tone to his voice that says i don't care about you or your problems, and it kind of hurt my feelins yesterday because i would say somethin..and then he's just kind of act like he didn't care, and i dunno...maybe i'm just bein such a girl, but, i dunno! It seems as if i'm not knowin alot of things right now! And, maybe it's just that before...this person actually liked me, and i guess his voice showed it...but, now, it's like...i dunno....so hard, and not soft like it used to be!..gah, i'm gonna start cryin! hah..what a wuss! But, i think there's more to it than that! It's like there's somethin there..that's he's not tellin me..that's behind why he is the way that he is, and i don't guess he's a bad person..i just think...there's somethin behind the image..and into the soul, that he's just not lettin out..and i can't figure out, what it is..and it's killin me! maybe it's just me..but, it seems like, there's somethin there..that he's just not tellin! But, anyways!..i better go get ready now...so, i'm gone!..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! Yeh...today was great!! I had the best time! haha...and it's only school! But, yeh..um, i'm kind of going through a bunch of mess with myself because i'm getting feelings for somebody that i shouldn't be gettin feelins for..and it's horrible!!...i just feel soo....bad! But, the guy i wrote about yesterday, i've decided not to let anything happen between us, because it's just not cool for me to like him; but, this is a different guy! And, i hope that either nothing happens...or, if something does happen..it waits a while! But, anyways!! Ok, soo...nothin really interesting has happened today..except i went to the dentists office...and i have to get my wisdom teeth taken out..=(...i'm scared!! But, that's not until this summer..so, i'll be good! Anyways! Ok, yeh, so, now cato is mad at me..and for what?..i have nooo idea! So, this time..i honestly don't care..if he's goin to throw this crap up just about every other week..then screw him! He obviously wasn't the friend i thought he was!...but, other than that...everything's great..for now! I'm gone though!...bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys!..what's goin on? Yeh, sorry i haven't written in a while..i've been grounded because of grades =(..but, we're good now..=) Ok..well, alot of things have happened: Well, first off...jonci and i were in a bit of a rut..but, we're great now!..we talked..and everything's fine...thank goodness!....and then, there's cameron! See...i likeD cameron...but, i told him that i just wanted to be friends for this guy, and then the guy and i didn't work out...so, cameron and i were supposed to do somethin one weekend..but, i forgot..and now, he's datin emily!...so, that's cool! And the guy..his name is kevin...i did like him...and still think he has boyfriend potential..but, he'd hafta change for him and i to be somethin...because who he is now..just isn't what i want to be with! And now..there's not really anybody that's got my eye...except this on guy..but, i can't like him..because i've liked his brother..so, that's just not cool...at all!...so, there's really nobody! And that's fine with me..because if a guy comes along..that's fine..and if one doesn't..i'm cool with that too! but, that's really the only thing that's happened! But, i'm gone!..bye!!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mile marker 203, gas gage leanin on the edge of e.. i'll be dang if the rain ain't pourin down there's somethin smokin underneath the hood it's a bangin and a clangin and it's cain't be good it's another 50 miles to the nearest town everything i own is in the back in a hefty bag i'm out of cigarettes and i'm down to my last rag  i'd sure hate to break down here nothin off the header in the rear-view mirror out in the middle of nowhere, nowhere i'm in trouble if these wheels stop rolin god help me keep me movin somehow don't let me start wishin i was with him now made it this far without cryin a single tear i'd sure hate to break down here  under 50,000 miles ago before the bad blood and busted radio you said i was all you'd ever need but love is blind, and little did i know you were just another dead end road played with pretty lies and broken dreams  baby leavin you is easier than bein gone don't know what i'd do if one more thing goes wrong  i'd sure hate to break down here nothin off the header in the rear-view mirror out in the middle of nowhere, nowhere i'm in trouble if these wheels stop rollin god help me to keep movin somehow don't let me start wishin i was with him now made it this far without cryin a single tear i'd sure hate, to break down here  i'd sure hate to break down here  nothin off hte header in the rear-view mirror out in the middle of nowhere, nowhere i'm in trouble if these wheels stop rollin, rollin god help me to keep movin somehow don't let me start wishinin i was with him now made it this far without cryin a single tear i'd sure hate to break down...it's too late to turn around i'd sure hate to break down here   hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..pretty good here too! I love that song!! haha..anyways! don't know what i wrote about last..but, we're just gonna start from wherever! Well, the guy i was tellin ya'll about..said that he likes me too!..so, i'm excited about that! but, the whole self doubt thing is comin back..and i just..don't know how to get rid of it!! ok, i like this guy..i really do!..but,i'll sit here..and be like..ok, well, what if he's not "real"..(can't describe that one to ya)..and i'll be like..well, what if i don't really like him?..and i dont' wanna hurt him if i don't like him?!...so, i'm stuck! And i know i like him...but, i just..second gues myself..and i shouldn't do that! it's just...so complicated..and i do not like things to be complicated at all!! I' a laid back kind of person! But, you know..maybe it'll cool off a settle down..hopefully!..but, i'm gone..bye!  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..pretty good here too!..well, TOMORROW'S MY LAST DAY OF SCHOOL!! Gees, it's soo hard to believe..that my freshman year of high school is over! It flew by..which tells me that i need to start havin funn..because the other 3 years are just gonna fly by! But, anyways! This summer's gonna be awesome!...i'm goin into it with no boyfriend..so, that's a plus! Well, the guy that i've been writing about..still has on clue! And, i haven't told him..i really haven't talked to him..so, i mean..you know! well, today was a good day!..nothin special happened..except this soo amazingly great thing..but, can't talk about..because i'll get busted..haha! i mean..it wasn't bad..but, you know! Alrighty..well, i'm gone!..everybody be safe at graduation...bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..pretty good here too! well, i went to my g-ma's house this weekend..and i went shoppin, and to the movies! it was great..i've missed my grandma =)..ok, well, with this guy that i like..i think it might work out..but, he still doesn't know how i feel..i'm just a punk!..gees..can't even tell a guy i like him! Well, he's said that him & this chik are over..(so he says..but, doesn't mean it's gonna happen)..it makes me sad..but, yet..i'm kind of a lil bit happy...which is totally wrong..and i feel bad..but, that's the way i feel! Have you ever felt, that you needed to do somethin..but, you just couldn't? it's like..i need to do somethin about my friends..because we're driftin apart..but, there's nothin i can do! I mean..i'm sure they know it just as much as i do!..but, it hurts my heart..bad! Alrighty, well, i'm gone! i'll let ya know how it goes with this guy..we'll call him mac! ..i'll let ya know how it goes with mac! But, i'm gone..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..it's goin great here too! I've soo moved on with the crap that everybody's talkin about..because..it's just not worth it!! So, i'm through with that! But, i've got somebody in mind right now! =) but, the thing is..he's stuck on another girl..i think...=( i talk to him all the time..but, i still don't think he sees me like that! gees..if i could only tell him!..but, i just can't.. because it'd make him happy to be with this other girl..and i want him to be happy..no matter how much it makes my heart hurts!..but, it's cool..he'll realize it someday..hopefully...=/ But, anyways..bout to leave to go to my grandma's house...so, i'll talk to ya'll later..please be safe..and..i'm gone..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh, could be better here too! Ok, see, everybody's makin the biggest deal out of somethin that isn't a big deal! People are sayin completely different things than the actual truth..and i'm sick of it! people make the biggest deals out of the slightest things, and it's not right! I mean..here are people..sayin some of the most out there things..and it's soo not what it appears to be! I mean..i just wanna cry..and i'm soo glad that i'm goin to my g-mas house this weekend..because i won't have to deal with the crap that's goin on here! it's just stupid..and i don't wanna have to deal with it anymore..and i'm not! i'm just..gonna let it be..and not worry with it..because it's stupid..and i'm sick to death of all these stupid as crap stuff that i put up with from these high school people who act like freakin 5 & 6th graders! I mean gees..you should only have to put up with soo much..and my limit's wayy past full..so, im done with it..all of it..they can have it! But, i'm gone!..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? yeh, not too much here! Well, last night, i stayed the night at the smith's house..and went to magee for some scrimage games for terry..yeh...it was pretty funn..it was just mr.rusty, me & ms.smith that rode down there..we had a blast! haha! And jimmy (i love that kid) was bein crazy...as usual...and was tellin people that we were datin..i was like..uh, yeh..sure!..haha! But, there were some FIIINE guys there last night...there were soo many schools there..haha..yeh, it was great! But, anyways! Well, nothin new has really happened..just been hangin out with everybody..and everything!..so, it's been good! but, alrighty, i'm gone now..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? yeh, nothin much here either..bout to hop in bed! Well, nothin new's goin on..just same o' same o'! Oh, i think i might have two guys in the picture! Maybe..but, not sure! I'll hafta see how it goes with em..and see what all they're about first..and i'll get back to ya on that one! FINALLY..I HAVE NOOO DRAMA IN MY LIFE!! i love it to death!!! it's the greatest thing in the world! haha..i'm soo excited! Yeh..but, anyways! I guess i'm gone now guys..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? Yeh, nothin much here either! Guys, i'm soo distraught! two of my good friends are goin through an extremely tough time..and i just..feel soo helpless..and it kills me..because i want to do something to help them, but, i just can't! So, please pray for that! And, there's a guy who likes me...and asked me out..but, i don't want to ruin that friendship there is between him & i..so, i had to tell him no :(...but, it's good..because i think this is what i need to do! But, there's a guy in the picture..maybe! He goes to hillcrest..but, that's all i'm sayin..because i don't know how i feel about him yet..so, that's that! But, i went to the movies friday..and went to see mean girls..haha..it was good!..i saw a hott guy up there(no names mentioned)..right jonci?..haha! but, anyways! but, this guy from hillcrest...he's different...but, i think he might be me!? but, i think there's alot i don't know about him..like, he might have a whole nother side to him, so,i gotta figure that one out! But, i'll let ya know how it goes!..but, i'm gone now!..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! How's it goin?..yeh..goin pretty good here too! Well, nothin's really happened since i've last written..but, i did try out for flag!..i guess i did ok..but, anyways! Ok, well...time to update from the last write! Um, i don't think i like the guy...because..he's just...not me anymore! And that's that!..and the fact that he has a girlfriend..and doesn't like me! Haha..yeh..that's great! But, anyways! I don't really guess there's another guy out there right now! OMG..guys! my guy friend from florida (i love ya babe) scared the mess out of me! He was talkin about somethin..that i've never heard him talk about before..and i just..worry about him sometimes! But, i love him!!...yeh..dont wanna talk about him too long! So, that's all i gotta say..so, i'm gone!..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? Um, it's goin better here, than last time i wrote! i've let it go, and what's meant to happen, will happen, there's nothing i can do about it, so, why worry about it?..exactly..you shouldn't! Well, i have to say..i met this totally amazing guy! He's such a sweetie! I met him at the mall the other day! I saw him talkin to somebody, and it was like..he's the only one you notice, when you walk into a room; and, it's like..he's got this aura around when..that just draws you to him, and he's soo livin for god..it's awesome! i'm soo excited i got to meet him! haha..he was talkin to somebody..and i was with a girl named sarah from clinton, and i was like..oh, he's cute..and i guess he heard me..i duno..but, he came up and introduced himself, and got my number..and we talked for the longest..but, he's supposed to call me..so, i'll let ya know how it goes! But, anyways! Well, sunday's the 4th, and the smith's crew wants me to go with them, and claire & allie  
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..it's alright here too! haven't written in about a week! Well,nothin's really happened! Abbey came over..(love ya chik)...and then i went to her house...haha..we had a great time!   Guys..i don't know what to do! I had a friend say somethin about me, behind my back,and it hasn't been the same since! I haven't talked to him, since it happens, and it's hurtin. I want soo bad, for things to go back the way they were, but, i don't think things'll ever be the same between this person and i. My heart hurts, because i don't see how anyone, could clame to be your friend..and then talk about you, behind your back! They say they were kidding, but, it still hurts, and it doesn't make it right! I'm tryin the best i can, to not think about it, and just let it go..all of it...but, it's hard, and it's goin to take a while! And to be quite honest, i probbably won't ever get over it, but, i'm gonna try!   Well, there's one more thing! See, a while back, i went through a real hard time (for me) and, it was stupid..needless to say! And, i had a friend, (we'll call her sally) who would talk about this girl (we'll call her jackie)like she didn't even like her! I mean, sally would talk about jackie, and say stuff, like crazy! And, i'm not gonna lie, i said some stuff, but, it wasn't too bad, and it was mainly, more about the situation i was in..than jackie! Well, now, it seems as if sally & jackie are best friends, and also, sally is being so two-faced and is contradicting herself, on everything she says! She'll say something, and then turn right around, and talk to jackie and be like..oh, well, i doubt it'll happen! I just..had to get that off my chest, because it seems as if sally has changed, and we WERE best friends, but now it's like we don't even know each other and i just wanna say, who are you?    sorry guys, i had to talk about those two things, because it's real funny how things happen, when you honestly don't need them to, but, it's not a big deal! Things and people both change..sometimes for the better..sometimes not..it's life:you have to deal with it! But, i'm gone..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? yeh, i just got back from georgia yesterday. I went for atlantafest with my youth group...it was awesome! We had the best time! It's like i'm a whole new person..b/c i'm choosing to let go of everything..and just not worry about things anymore...because it's a waste of time!...when things happen, they happen..and you can't change it, so, move on! well, that's all i've got to say for now..so, i'm gone..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! what's goin on? yeh..nothin much here..haven't written in a while, so, i thought i would! Well, tomorrow i'm goin to atlanta, georgia for atlantafest with my church! It's gonna be soo much funn!..i'm excited! Well, i've got a lil problem! There's this guy, and we're talkin i guess, but, i'm at this time in my life..where i've just..decided that i don't need, nor do i want a boyfriend! And, i'm soo scared to tell him, because i don't want to hurt him! that's the last thing, i would ever want to do...because he's such a great guy! and what i hate..is i'm goin to have to do it by computer..because i'll start cryin...and i can't cry in front of him!..and i think that people should have better respect for people than to do it by e-mail, or im..but, i've got no other choice...so, that's that!  Guys, i'm really needin prayers right now! i don't know who reads this..if anybody at all..but, i'm having a really, really tough time right now..because i don't have somebody in my life anymore..who was a good friend of me..and it's hard. I just..don't see how anybody could talk about somebody, who'se supposed to be their best friend, the way i got talked about..even if they were just kidding. And what gets me the most..is that it's not just somethin stupid..it's something that could change my reputation..and i do understand that you're not supposed to care what people think..but, the thing is..it was done by a friend...someone whom you're supposed to be able to trust, and have secrets with..but, instead..they sell you out, like they never even cared, and i personally don't see how anybody could do that!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh, could be better here..but, tryin not to complain! But, what's been goin on? I haven't really been doin anything!..just hangin out & kickin it! But, anyways! There's nothin new really...except i think i might be likin this guy..but, not gonna say any names yet..because don't know how it's gonna go..but, i'll keep ya informed! but, i'm gone...bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! Yeh, well, i'm a lil better from the last time i wrote! My feelins are still hurt, but, i guess they'll always be, until i'm able to move on! But, anyways! What's goin on with ya'll? Nothin much here either!...just been hangin out! Talked to ashlynn the other day...and she seems to be doin good..so, that's good! I can't find my watch!..think i might know where it is..but, not sure! neways..i don't really have anything else to say..so, i' gone..bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      have your feelings ever so hurt, you didn't know what to do? See, i have a "friend" whom i trusted with my life; i mean, i had more trust and faith in him, almost more than anybody, and then i found out that he said somethin he shouldn't have! And, what he said, is something that could ruin everything, if it hasn't already! I understand, that you shouldn't care what people think, but, the thing is...when it comes down to it, you're going to care, if they think you're a slut or not! And, when i found out last night, that this person said these things..it crushed me!...absolutely crushed me...because it's the principal of the matter, that he would actually go behind my back, and say what he said, knowing good and well it's not true! I guess what i'm just tryin to say, is that my heart hurts, and i just wanna cry, because this person, is somebody i cherish very much, and would have done anything for, but, to hear, from a guy who you like, and would like to date...that somebody who's supposed to be your best friend, and your partner in crime...is talkin about you...the way that he did...was just..too much to take in all at once i guess because, i just...don't understand why he would say that...even if he was "just kidding"?! And, i found out some other stuff he said..and, it's down to the point now..where i just..need to stay away from him for a while...because i can't take his crap anymore!! My heart's hurting wayy too much, and, i can't take it! So, i'm through with it! I'm through with all the crap that i've had to put up with in the past, i'm through with all the laughs, i'm through with all the heartbreak, and tears, and crap!....i'm done!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? Yeh,&nbsp; goin great here too! Well, i'm still in georgia..but, comin home sunday (tomorrow)! yay..i'm excited! I talked to abbey today! gah, i miss her soo much! I won't get to see her until like, the 30th though....which really sucks! I hung out with rachel night before last..love ya chik!...that was funn! Went to stone mountain tuesday with a bunch of friends...and didn't get home til late! It was funn..we had a good time! Gah, these two weeks have flown by in georgia..but, yeh, i'm excited to be comin home and seein everybody! I GOT BANGS!! haha..i love em! Alot of people didn't notice em..which is good, so it isnt' too dramatic..but, it's cute..i think! Anyways!&nbsp; Have you ever just wondered why people can't mind their own freakin business? Yeh, its pissin me off..b/c my business is my business, and everybody else's business is their business..not anybody else's! Sometimes, i just don't see why people can't get that!? But, whatever...haha.no drama..and it's great! The people in georgia..are awesome! they're just like me,&nbsp; and hate drama! they just let whatever roll off, and don't say anything else about it..which is totally amazing!..i love georgia, and people from georgia! I guess i just needed a break from all the drama..a&nbsp;big one..but, i'm&nbsp;good now, and i'm&nbsp;ready to come home! haha..yeh, alrighty..well,&nbsp;i'm gone..bye!   -Lauren&nbsp;  &nbsp;(bye the way, this is on georgia time...not mississippi time) 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! I'm in georgia right now!! I'm here visitin family for two weeks, but, i'm comin back in one week! Gah, i miss everybody!..i'm gettin a lil home-sick! I've talked to a coupla people from home..but, not too many! Anyways, nothin much is goin on in georgia..except i've been shoppin a lil bit..and goin to &amp; doin things...and that's about it! ..i got invited to a party that's gonna be thrown on tuesday! haven't decided if i'm goin yet..don't know who all's gonna be there, and everything! but, i prolly will! anyways..just wanted to write and say hey..so, i'm gone!..bye &nbsp; -Lauren 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want someone to hold me in their arms, and tell me I'm beautiful...Just to make me feel good, because I know I'm not! I want to feel special, I want someone to give me hugs for no reason....Someone to hold my hand and make my heart go crazy, someone who won't get tired of me (because I seem to be doing that a lot lately)! I just want someone who wants to talk to me and who wants to always be with me....I just want to be with that someone!    so what's new? Yeh, alot here too! the friend i wrote about last..is doin ok, i guess! He says he's doin ok, but, i don't believe him..for some reason! I guess i can just see the way he is...compared to way he used to be,and it's different..but, not drastically! I really hope he realizes that he's such a great guy, and that he deserves somebody who sees how great he is!   I'm having soo many mixed emotions right now, it's stupid! I like this one guy..but, there's this other guy, whom when i'm around, drives me crazy! I love being around him, and always want to be around him, but, it gets a little twisted! I can't explain it, because i don't want people to know, but, i feel like such crap! It seems that whenever something good happens, something bad happens, but, is kind of good, if that made any sense! I'm between a rock and a hard place, because i don't know what to do! I don't want to hurt anybody, but, i have to do what feels right...but, right now, i don't know what that is! but, it'll all come together, so, i'm goin to try not to worry about it!   -Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! how's it goin? yeh..its goin ok here too!..but, my heart's hurtin! my friend's goin through a tough time..and i wanna be ther for him, and i hope he knows that i am..but, i just hope he pulls through this! I love him, and would do anything for him!..i just hope he knows that!  Well, me & blake: i don't exactly know what me & blake are, but, i'm gonna have a talk with him, because i wanna date him, but i don't want to be his girlfriend, because i don't think a boyfriend is best for me right now...and, i just wanna cry..b/c the last thing in the world i would ever want to do, is hurt somebody....especially blake! Blake's such a great guy, and soo much funn to be around..and i don't want to give that up, but, i don't want a boyfriend! I just hope blake realizes that i do like him, alot, i just..can't handle a boyfriend right now! I pray so much, that blake understands, because i don't know what i'm gonna do if he doesn't!                           -Lauren
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey guys! what's goin on? yeh, not too uch here either! well, i'm back home...and had flag camp til thursday this week...but, it's over, so i'm good! I stayed the night with lindsey last night..haha, we had a great time hangin with everybody! It was crazy! Well, i don't have a significant other...but, i think i'm likin this one guy! Not gonna say any names or anything..but, it's great! Then, there's this other guy...who i like...and i guess likes me?...we hang out all the time, but i don't think it's gonna go anywhere! He's a great guy, and soo funn to hang out with, but, i just don't think that it'll go anywhere..but, who knows?...anyways! Gah...school starts a week from tuesday! How bad does that suck? Yeh, it sucks a big one!! Anyways! Alrighty, i just thought i'd write and let you kind of know what's goin on...but, i'm gone..bye!      -Lauren  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>