<Blog>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I am in a rut right now. I haven't done any real work for a week, and my supervisor is back from a trip tomorrow.  I was *supposed* to be spending the week writing an article (or at least roughing it in), but I didn't.  At all.  Things came up.  And the subject matter is less than exciting... I just don't want to write it.  The thing is, I should have told him before he left, since it is now 3 weeks overdue to the publishers, and we are in trouble.  We will now have to write a 6000 word article in a week.  It takes me that long to write out all the references.  Yikes!  I am super-pissed at J today.  We had plans yesterday, and I was snubbed several times over.  It was raining, so our plans to go walk dogs at the SPCA fell through.  He called at 10:30am to tell me it was a no-go.  Understandable - who wants to walk dogs in the rain?  I suggested that I go over, and make some chinese food, to which J was amenable, but first he needed to do some things.  Call back in a few hours, he said.  Okidoki.  3 hours later, I am bored out of my tree, and I want to get out of my very small, very empty house.  So I call.  J hasn't done anything yet because a friend called.  He has now decided to take a nap.  Fine... when are we getting together? J: "I don't know.  I want to nap.  And maybe go for a run." M: "how long with that take?" J: "mmmm, I dunno." M: "You sound non-commital about the whole thing.  Do you want to spend the day by yourself?" J: "I didn't say that.  You know me, I hate being alone.  I just have some stuff to do." M: "Fine.  Go do your stuff." J: "I will call you later, and then you can come over, ok?" M: "OK, fine.  Call me later." J: "I will."  And then I don't hear from him.  I could have made other plans, but no, I am waiting for J.  Who never called.  It was so fucking rude, I want to smack him right now.  I know that I am not J's girlfriend, but I want to get all girlfriend on his ass.  I want to yell at him, and tell him that he can't treat me this way.  If a girl-friend of mine ditched me in the same way, I couldn't lose it on her, but a guy-girl friendship is different, and I feel that I do have some of those girlfriend privileges i.e. letting J know when I am really mad.  Which I am.  Fucker.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I heard something that I feel is fucking profound. Truly inspired.  It was a study that was reported last month in the Journal of Neuroscience (very prestigious journal in the field, for those of you who don't know) about brain activity during the male sexual orgasm.  I am still looking for the article, but basically, the study used neuroimaging to show that during and following orgasm, men's amygdalas show hypoactivity, or depression of activity.  What is the amygdala, you ask?  Well, basically it is the center of emotionality in the brain.  It is where feelings are processed, and connections made between things we experience and things we feel.  Fucking profound.  When I heard this bit of news, I actually paused for about 30 secs, and in that time, all of my past (sexual) relationships came flooding back to me, and it all made sense.  It all makes so much fucking sense right now, I can't even explain it.  You need to crawl into my brain and see how everything has just lined itself up...  BTW - similar study done in the 80s showed the opposite for women: increased activity during and following orgasm.  Of course.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So, for a few years, "Why Bother?" by Weezer has been my anthem.  How do I break the cycle?  I have given into it so often, I wonder if I can even give a person a chance?  In the last 3 years, I have not had a boyfriend.  I have been single for 3 years.  Holy crap, am I in a rut.  If you don't know the lyrics to my special anthem, I am sure you can guess.  Everyone always turns out to be shit, so masterbation seems like the best option, but with a melody that makes it more enjoyable.  I was just walking down the hall today, and I thought about Mr. Jake Candyman, and it occurred to me that he couldn't possibly be any good whatsoever.  He might be attractive, and know a fucking cool pair of shoes when he sees 'em, but he is probably stupid, or whiny, or clingy, or intimidated by a girl who fucking knows.  My friend M is a girl who knows.  She likes to analyze the quality of an orgasm when it's generated by fingers or vibrator.  She can read a horoscope, and make it fucking profound, instead of dumb and too general to mean anything at all.  She can talk to a guy for a minute, and know in an instant that they would be perfect together for so many bizarre yet prophetic reasons.  Although M is a bit more of a wild spirit than myself, I would like to think that I am molded in her image.  She is a bit older and a bit wiser, but she is my mentor, and I wouls like to think I have some of her spirit.  And I think it is amazing that she can just *know* about a guy, but I think most guys would think she is fucking nuts.  Most guys would think I am fucking nuts.  This is leading back to where I started with Mr. Jake Candyman.  I am imagining a meeting between me and Mr. JC.  How does it go? Starts out well, because there is chemistry, starting from the shoes up.  But I don't know how to play the game these days, it's been so long, so I am honest.  So mister, that was the coolest thing I have ever had anyone say to me.  If we were both cartoons, I would have blinked, and red hearts would have popped up in place of my pupils, and you would have instantly taken on a shiny quality.  I think it's honest and charming.  I might be eccentric, but I know that people are awful and judgmental, so I know he would think I was fucking crazy.  Back away slowly, and don't make any sudden movements.    Take it for what it is!  A sincerely expression of a moment in time that for me, was bliss.  It was a moment that I would like to keep all to myself, and yet share with everyone all at once.  It was sincerity itself, and I value sincerity above every quality I can think of.   A genuine comment about my shoes, followed by a genuine feeling of wow.  But it would be crazy to start off on this note.  It's all a game, and I don't know the rules, so I always lose.  Why bother?  And yes, I can say that I am eccentric.  My friend S says people who are eccentric don't know they are eccentric, but i disagree.  I know.  I know because I have these difficult-to-follow, winding thoughts that flow so easily, but are so convoluted.  And I also know that others cannot follow the connections that I find so logical in my brain.  I don't share alot of these thoughts, because people tend to blow me off when I share.  Sometimes, I am not trying to be funny, I am just being sincere. In my masters defense, one of my examiners commented that my writing was humorous and entertaining, and that I should never be afraid to express my personality in my writing despite the fact that scientific writing is supposed to be dry and cold, and devoid of personality.  Thanks, but I wasn't kidding in the least. This is why I know I am eccentric.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a great day in Halifax.  I met a person I desperately want to know... first time since I moved here, really.    I was fucking around yesterday afternoon with my friends A & M, taking the day off school to drink beer and play foozeball because A just defended her Master's Thesis yesterday morning.  After hitting Mexically Rosa's for a well deserved margeurita, we played some fooze at Dooley's downtown.  From there, A decided she wanted to visit Freak Lunchbox to buy some special treats for us all, and I almost bailed at this point to get some work done, but it was A's defense day, so she was princess for the day  Good decision, mac mommy, good decision.  So, Jake is working the counter, and he is attractive.  Just my type - very alternative, emo...love that.  First, while I was perusing the bulk candy at the back, Jake squeezes past me and touches my hip unneccessarily in the process... I am not averse.  Then, he turns to me, and takes my totally by surprise in the best sort of way... "Are those Royal Elastics?"  "Yeah, they are"...that is what came out of my mouth instead of, "Uh, yeah...do you want to have babies together?"  I was sooooo impressed.  If you don't know what Royal Elastics are, they are shoes that are so cool, only about 20 people on the planet know how cool they are.  The only reason that I own such shoes is because (a) I am a media hound, including all forms, even ads and (b) I just had to have them, so that I ate kraft dinner for a week in order to afford them.  2 years and $200 later, I am not sorry, because they have found me my future boyfriend.  Gawd, do I want to know this person.  And Jake is an aquaintance of A's, but she can't be the go between since she is leaving for UBC in about a week, so I will just have to deal with this on my own.  Any suggestions?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So I am cleansing my colon this week.  J and I are doing the master cleanse, the accelerated version.  So we are drinking plenty of the special lemonade concoction that is a legitimate part of the cleanse, plus laxative tea at night and a sea salt flush in the mornings.  Needless to say, our bowels are working overtime.  The juice that you get to drink with the cleanse is actually really effective at suppressing the appetite, but it can't stop you thinking about food.  And I have been thinking about all the food that I want to eat for a week.  I have been "cleansing" for 1 day.  This is not going well.  And J and D are doing as good as ever.  I am so fucked.  It really pisses me off, and makes me anxious, and I feel really awful about it all the time.  When we are hanging out together, I know that J is just thinking about if he has spent enough time with me, and when it is he can see D again.  We were watching movies on Saturday, and suggested we invite D over.  Yeah! Can we?  Then we had plans to go to the mall on Sunday, and again, suggests D comes along.  J: "D said he can give us a ride.  He isn't doing anything today." M: "Do you want him to come?" J: "Only if you do."  (Are you mad?  Why would I want to spend time with *your* new bf?  Are you mental?)  M: "I am not dying to spend time with D. But if you want him to come..." J: "-no!  That's fine."  And now I am the bad guy.  Thank you very much.  That was fun.  Whatever.   My situation would be helped out alot if I just had a bf.  At this point, I need a bf.  Just a quick fix for the short term, so that I can fixate on something else for a minute or two.  Christ!  I need to focus for a minute.  Perhaps I just need something to eat.  Ha!  My entry for the coast PSST: "Since I have arrived, I have met only humility and loneliness.  I thought Halifax had some excellent people, but I am lost.  Where have all the good people gone?  I know you are out there... but where are you?"    Do you think I will get any reply?  Me neither.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, I have cheered up a bit.  J has not forsaken me yet for D, so I am content.  I will deal with J leaving Halifax in at the end of December only when I have to.  That is, mid to late December. (I can't believe he is leaving me... I am so selfish).  We have decided too fast next week.  Actually, starting on Sunday, we will be fasting.  Actually, it is cleanse.  No solid food, laxative tea, and oral sea salt solution that encourages bowel movements.  I know, pleasant.  But a cleanse detoxs your colon, kidney and liver, and increases your metabolism.  There is also some anecdotal evidence that it improves mood by elevating "happy neurotransmitters".  I am looking forward to it.  Yesterday I wallowed in my hatred of Halifax, so I am waiting with baited breathe for the day that waking up in this city does not cause me a slight sharp pain in my heart.   I ruined J's most important accomplishment in life.  He has been waiting for three years for someone to write him a PSST in the coast magazine, and he finally got one this week.  At least he thinks it's for him.  And it is - I know it is.  I told D to do it for him.  But J doesn't know that.  And I stupidly joked that I wrote it - me, the person who sees J check the coast each week for his name in the PSSTs.  Before that, he was basking in the glory of some masked and anonymous white knight who was madly in love with him, admiring from afar.  Now, I have poisoned him with my silly comment, and he is convinced that I wrote it.  Particularly because the content of the message was so similar to the things I tell him all the time... i.e. you are pretty, and brilliant, and hot (apparently, D and I think alike).  So I have taken away J's fantasy.  I am a terrible person.  But I intend to fix it.  And I heard from the ex today.  This is more monumental for me that that sentence might imply.  Chris, who is not from Halifax, so I can use his name (besides, Chris is fairly ubiquitous, right?), emailed me today.  I admit, I was telling J all about my messy broken heart, courteous of Chris, and it occurred to me:  When you date someone for 5 years, from 15 - 20 years of age, not seeing or talking to that person for 4 years is mad.  Particularly when you can honestly say you have yet to meet someone as charming, sincere, attractive, and amazing since then.  That is me.  Apparently, Chris and I feel very similar about each other.  He has a gf, and has no intention of leaving her for me, which is fine - I am a different person, but it was good to know that he thinks I am as excellent as I think he is.  I have never had a bad word to say about Chris, and I never will.  I imagine one day I will be able to be the person I was when I was with him all on my own.  Cross my fingers. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, that is enough.  I fucking hate this city, and this is the letter that I plan to submit to the coast about it:  Dear Editor,  I am looking for an outlet for my anger, misery and disgust at the people that make up this city.  I can't believe it.  After a year and a half here, I have given up hope of every liking Halifax, and I can't imagine a single thing that I am going to miss about this city.  Especially the people.  Let me provide some examples.  Making friends here has not been difficult, it's been impossible.  In the last city that I lived in, I made most of my friends through several volunteer positions.  Volunteering is rewarding, and typically the people you meet doing are pleasant and empathetic.  So, I ventured out and dropped my name and number off at a few places around the Dalhousie University Campus.  Specifically, the Internation Student's Office, and the Gazette.  I thought that I might be a valuable volunteer for incoming foreign students because I am fluent in Mandarin.  For the Gazette, I thought I could put my travel skills to use by helping write an article about ins and outs of travelling abroad.  A month later, and still no call from either organization, although both were willing to take my number to begin with.  Next up, a social organization downtown.  I am not going to name names here, because I still think that they provide a valuable service to the community, and have branches in most cities in Canada, but when I offered my time there, I was once again denied.  How is it that organizations based on volunteers don't need more people to provide their time?  Next, I thought perhaps I would join a sports team to try to make friends.  It turns out that most teams are not looking for new members, and already have too many.  BUT!  Good ole' ultimate!  I don't actually like Ultimate Frisbee much, but I was looking and I found a team that was taking.  So I joined.  Unfortunately, my teammates all turned out to know each other before hand.  After 2 practices and 2 games, I realized that no, no one was going to introduce themselves, and no, they didn't care who I was.  forget that.  There are also those loitering downtown who feel the need to mock me.  I was walking on Spring Garden a few days ago, when some guy who thought he was so punk he was almost wearing his skateboard like an accessory, asked me in the most mocking tone, "excuse me miss, do you listen to Rod Stewart?"  Fuck you.  I may have been doing my best impression of a Gap ad, but don't you judge me.  I stopped buy Survival of the Phattest when you were still listening to Jesus Jones.   Finally, there is the random vulgarity that I have encountered while spending time with the few friends I do have here.  On several occasions, while walking home with friends at night, I have had guys mention something sexual explicit to me and my friends.  On four separate occassions, while walking with completely different guy-friends, I have had stranges say something along the lines of "Hey, need a third?  I like to do it doggy-style, and he can watch."  Or more simply "I fucked her yesterday."  What?  Who are these people, saying these things that are obviously designed only to make me feel bad and embarrassed?  And this is what I am left with: An unbridal hatred for this city.  It stinks, and the people stink, too.  And if this letter outrages you because you think it is unfair and doesn't apply to all, I beg you to proove me wrong.  In fact, you are probably the person that I have been looking for since I got here.  Where are you?  Where are all the good people in Halifax?  I must be looking in the wrong places, so if you are out there, show yourselves, because frankly, I am exhausted and I don't have the energy to keep looking.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I am obviously neurotic.  I know this.  And if anyone were ever to read this, I want you to know that in the real world, I am coherent, intelligent, witty, cute and interesting.  To look at me,  you would never know what a mess I am.  So, this blog is really an outlet for all those feelings that I never let anyone else see.  The self-analysis that goes with a quarter-life crisis that no one is allowed to know about.  Hence the anonimity.  I woke up again this morning early and experiencing a slight panic attack.  3:30am, and I am breathing like I just climb 3 flights of stairs - not a full blown panic attack, but there is no reason that my heart should be beating so fast.  I talked to the one person that I truly lean on in Halifax (and I suppose in life) yesterday, M. I hinted that I was feeling uneasy about some things, and M suggested that I buy some tryptophan from a health food store. I think everyone knows that tryptophan is the chemical in Turkey that makes you tired after thanksgiving dinner so that you want to unbutton your pants and dooze infront of some horrific parade on TV, but tryptophan is also a precursor for seretonin.  Seretonin is a neurotransmitter in the brain that is responsible for, among other things, positive emotion.  Seretonin makes you happy.  One class of antidepressants block the re-uptake of seretonin after it's release so that it can have more of an effect on the target neuron. The action of these antidepressants also encourage neurogenesis in the hippocampus in the long-run, relating back my first entry about my head possibly feeling a bit smaller.   FYI - The designer drug ecstasy also has an effect on seretonin, first causing all of the seretonin stored in cells to be released, then blocking the reuptake so that it can continue to have an effect on the target cells.  So it seems like a good idea to drop a few tabs of tryptophan now and then.   By the way, the experts seem to agree: depression and anxiety are simply different symptoms for the same pathology.  So even though I would describe myself as anxious, not depressed, there is a blurring between what treatments might work for me.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, hello world.  I was reading a study recently about neurogenesis.  Turns out the experts were wrong - people continue to 'grow' neurons (brain cells) even after they are born, and throughout their life.  In particular, neurogenesis in the hippocampus has been linked to the beneficial effects of antidepressants.  This has lead to the hypothesis that perhaps the cessation of adult neurogenesis may be responsible for feelings of anxiety and depression.  I think I need to tighten up my hat these days.  I got up this morning at 5:30am, turned on the TV, and doozed while watching a West Wing re-run.   I feel less anxiety when the TV is on while I sleep.  I have no idea where this anxiety is coming from, but it is very real, and I wanted to burst into tears when I woke up and it was so early.  A friend of mine sent me one of those terrible emails that gets forwarded out to her entire emailing list.  It was about being twenty-something, and I wasn't going to read it (I almost never read anything that Elena sends out anymore), but I did, and did it ever sum things up for me.  I will paraphrase: I have no idea what I am doing anymore.  I am lost.  I AM LOST.  I used to watch movies with people spouting cheesy lines that they didn't know who they were, or that they were confused about life, and I used to think, "Who are these retards who don't know who they are?  How can you NOT know who you are?"  It turns out I was being a tad judgmental.  I feel like I am in a pool, swimming in the middle, and the end is getting further away from me, but turning around isn't an option, because where I started is even further away.  How did I get here?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ok, so it's been a while, but what can I say?  I am lethargic sometimes.  Well, the holidays started off with a bang... actually, a fight with Joe.  I was being a dick at the bar, and he got so mad, I have never seen him like that before.  His reaction was scary, and I though we were going to lose our friendship.  He actually ran away from me, literally. It was 3 am, and we were walking home, and he just started running.  I couldn't keep  up... it was ridiculous, and I felt like a girlfriend, trying to chase down her boyfriend.  And it occurred to me, that is exactly what Joe is.  A boyfriend.  I was telling stories about Joey to a friend from high school, and he asked if Joe was my fuck buddy.  Then it struck me, we are the exact opposite of that.  Everything BUT the sex.  Even the high drama that comes along with being in a relationship.  I don't mean to make light of the fight that we had.  When I finally made it back to Joe's house that night (he is a runner, so I was left in the dust), he left me outside of his door for an hour, begging to come in.  Then he tried to lock himself in his bedroom, but I forced my way in. And we had it out.  I don't remember ever being that upset.  Not even when my relationship of 4 years broke up.  Read into that what you like, I am still trying to figure that one out.  I obviously love Joe, but it comes back around to the same old question: am I in love with Joe?  I thought I was pretty fucking smart, but I think I am losing my grip on reality.  Partially Joe's fault though... he told me a couple of weeks ago that he is bisexual.  Vanessa once asked me why I like hanging around with a gay guy.  Because he can never reject me.  I guess that one backfired.  So now that I know he *can* like me, I am rejected.  Why doesn't he?  And is that what I am feeling?  Perhaps it's not love, just confusion about why not love?  Fuck it, I love him, and I will live with it for as long as he lets me.  I am rambling.  I saw the ex boyfriend last night.  Crazy.  It's been 4 years, and I can't tell you what it was like.  Surreal to say the least.  I haven't seen him since we broke up, actually.  We've been apart almost as long as we were together.  Anyway, it was strange and wonderful.  Chris is a great person.  And I am a better person for having known him.  He is engaged to the girl he moved in with 3 months after we broke up, it you can believe that.  I almost choked, but it's good.  It became very apparent to me after 2 hours of chatting that we have nothing on common anymore.  It was crazy - I want to live in a big city, the biggest that I can find, and he wants a small town.  I want to get away from Canada, he never wants to leave.  He drives a big gas guzzling truck, and I take the bus.  We are different people now... the engagement still stung a bit, but I can move on now.  Although, he is still gorgeous.  So beautiful.  C'est la vie.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing today, just wanted to pop-in as a reminder to myself that this place exists.  Otherwise, I would be liable to call this the first day of my giving-up on blogging.  But I am not.  See you soon, mac mommy.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ummm, I don't know.  I don't want to write today.  Three things quick: I did manage to wander down to Freak Lunchbox, it turns out that no, Jake was not working today.  Alicia was even with me today, and she was going to force me to talk to him... but no luck.  At least I got to buy some boysenberries - which I probably would have been too embarassed to do if he was working.  I will use candy to console me.  And I apprear to be caught in some kind of alternate dimension or something, because the number of people who think Halifax is great far out number the people who think it is shit.  Namely me.  How can this be?  I don't understand.  No wonder I have no friends - I am a complete alien to these people (and they are aliens to me). I am starting to question whether I truly speak the local language... I appear to, but I am suspicious.  Finally, speaking of my lack of friends, I have lost Joe.  I mean, I set him down for one minute, and he is gone.  I don't know where his head is at, but he has dropped off the face of the planet, and I don't know what to do.  I am a fag-hag without her fag.  And I am really sad about it... I don't know what is going on.  I am going to try to remedy things tonight, but I think Joe thinks there is nothing that needs remedying, he is just tired and wants to nap.  Like he has been doing for two weeks.  What the fuck is going on?  I have no idea.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I am almost finished revising and formatting my thesis.  It has been a real bitch, but I am so happy I am almost done.  I am going to bid a fond farwell to that demon... perhaps with some lighter fluid and a match.  I have to admit, the formatting has been a bigger headache than I imagined.  I mean, each section needs to have the page number at a different location than all the remaining pages in that section.  Do you know how long it took me to figure out how to do this in Word?  Let's not talk about it... however, if you ever need to know, it is now firmly planted in my brain.  A is leaving on the weekend.  It is sort of weird...I have known that she was leaving since I got here, but I think I have really only recently become close with her (in the last semester), and I only very recently has it sunk in that she is leaving.  It's sort of sad... she has always been a really sweet girl, and now I am really going to miss her.    Of course, J won't miss her.  He thinks she hates him...and to be fair, A has been a bit judgemental about my friendship with J.  She obviously doesn't trust that I can be such close friends with a man without getting hurt, and of course, the potential is there.    And once again, I have missed hooking up with Brad.  I met Brad in September at a festival that I was volunteering at, and I thought to myself, "THAT is a person I should know."  And I wasn't even interested in him.  He is attractive enough (oh yeah), but it never seriously occurred to me that we would ever date...in fact, that is the reason that I could talk to him.  I have this thing where I can only talk to guys where there is no possiblity of dating (i.e. gay men, men with gfs, men I don't find attractive, men out of my league)  I will be honest, when I first met Brad, I thought he was gay.  Anyway, the feeling of comfortableness stuck, and so did not assumption that we would never date, so I can still talk to him.  Now, soon after the festival, Brad went to TO to look for a job, and after about 6 weeks of looking, he found one.  He was back in Halifax for the last week or so, I guess packing up.  I don't know, because we never hooked up.  That is the funny thing... I hate Halifax because I think the people in this city are fucking terrible.  One more time cuz it feels so good, FUCKING TERRIBLE.  They are the worst people ever.  So I volunteered at the festival to meet some people, because I was certain not *everyone* was terrible.  I met Brad and thought to myself, I should get to know him, because he is awesome, and then perhaps I can get access to a whole circle of wicked people (ie. Brad's friends).  Of course, my plan has failed miserably because he almost immediately moved away, and even on his visit home, we have not been able to get it together and hook up.  This is so typical of my life, it's almost funny.  Actually, it is funny.  And this would be more amusing if you could understand how adorable Brad is, and how often we have tried to get something going (coffee, movie, drinks, etc).  Anyway, today is a bit of a light-hearted mood, since I have decided not to take anything too seriously anymore.  I am giving up stress all together.  Good luck, Mac Mommy!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      oh my god.  I sent it in.  How is this going to work out????!!!  I *am* insane.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I now intend to "practice" my PSST note for the Coast.  I am sending it later today, so it probably won't show up for a week or so.  D'oh!  I think that is too late... it's too close to the holidays - what if he isn't from here?  Anyway, possible notes are:  "Jake @ FLB - I think you are ridiculously attractive.  Are you single?  I wish I could get my head out of the sand, cuz I think we'd make a good team.  Just come up to me and say hello!"  Very Weezer-esque...maybe too much so.  "Jake @ FLB - I haven't had a crush like this since high school.  You make me nervous and weird, and I want to give you my number, but I can't seem to get the words out.  I don't want to buy anymore candy, but I don't know how else to see you."  Too childish?  I think it's sincere, but I am not sure if people would understand where I am coming from.  "Jake @ FLB - Did we make serious eye-contact, or was that just wishful thinking?  Maybe so, but you should know I think you are attractive, and if I had the chance to get to know you, it would be amazing.  How much candy do I need to buy to get your attention?"  Ok, last one.  This time, how about a feel-good message?  This is what I would like to get from someone.  "Jake @ FLB - there is something about you and it makes me want to know you. I want to ask you out, and if I knew you were single, I would do it.  For now, I will admire you in secret, and keep coming back for boysenberries."  There we go.  That's the one.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So I talked to J yesterday, and told him I was upset about being ditched on Saturday. He was having a blah day.  And he did not listen to me at all - simply saying, "look I am sorry, I don't know what else to say" so that I looked like a fucking bitch for being mad at all.  I am less than satisfied with his explanation, and I think he has blown it off to me being on my period.  Whatever, I am still really hurt because I think I have been a fucking wicked friend to J and I am feeling a bit taken advantage of.  I am just so disatisfied with life right now.  J is the one person that I thought understood where I was coming from - depressed to be living in this shithole, and in need of a hand to hold, but his problems and moods always seem to take presidence.  I have put him on friend probation, which I think he has taken as a joke, and I guess it is because I am so desperately unhappy that I will take a crappy friend over no friends.  OK, J isn't a crappy friend... he has just been pretending to be a crappy friend for the last little bit.  The final draft of my masters thesis is due in a couple of days, and there are just so many holes in it.  I didn't realize, and of course a month and a bit away from it has left me with 20/20 vision that makes me cringe.  How did my committee let me pass?  Ridiculous!  I actually stayed in bed this morning because I didn't want to face the music.  Avoidance is my favorite coping mechanism - which of course really only serves to compound my anxiety because I now have precious little time to fix all my mistakes!  I know, I am a retard.  One more update:  I went back to the candy store.  My future bf was working, and I managed to squeak out a question about A's favorite candy... "My friend A and I were here last week, and she asked you for a specific candy - do you remember what it was?"  I know, lame.  That is me.  I am going to get a t-shirt made up, in fact.  "I am lame".  Anyway, he quickly found the nerds rope that I was seeking, and then bounced off to answer a phone call.  Not only did my pathetic excuse to talk to him not lead into the witty conversation that I had hoped for, but when I was paying for my goodies, I overheard him say to some unknown on the other end of the line, "yeah, I should be home in 25 minutes" and it sounded as if the unknown on the other end shared said home.  Although he could have been planning a night out with the boys, and was just referring to when he would be at home to change etc.  Whatever, I am over-analyzing the situation, I know, but my strategy for years has been to expect the worst, that way you are pleasantly suprised rather than bitterly disappointed when things don't work out the way you expect.  Although, my way always means it fucking sucks when you are right.    Anyway, I have decided to put a PSST in the Coast in order to try to get his attention.  Or at least to put some positive vibes out in the world, so that he can feel good about himself...that is always nice.  Perhaps his good mood, inspired by my note, will cause a chain reaction that will culminate in me meeting the man of my dreams, who is not in fact the candyman, but some completely unrelated stranger to both of us, removed by 6 degrees of separation.  (I thought I might give hope a try this time, since after reading the last paragraph bitter disappointment now seems more appealing that the smug, lonely self-satisfaction I have been feeling for the past 3 years.  Wish me luck!)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, about an hour ago I realized that the last post I contributed was half-assed.  It took me that long to get my shit together in order to make a better effort (that should tell you something), and in the mean time, I went to see if my blog had been posted on blogscanada.ca yet.  When I registered, I was gazillionth in line to be approved and posted, and I haven't checked back since.  That was only in December, so I figured I might still be in line... but apparently no! I am on there!  And.... they have the little thumb next to my site, to indicate "site favorite".  Are you crazy!  That's insane!  I am a retard!  What kind of responsible website would actually send people my way?  Anyway, after that, I was certain that a better effort was necessary.  So here it is.  So last week, I went out with my new friend Katherine.  We went to what I fear is the last Retro Night at the Marquee.  The Marquee has closed its doors for a month and a half to renovate, and the rumor is that the new look is meant to inspire rampant hooking-up.  Just what Halifax needs, another meat market.  Anyway, we were out with a bunch of her friends, which was fine.  Actually, they were all really nice, but I have a bit of social anxiety sometimes when I am afraid my outfit isn't cool enough.  I am shallow, and often judge people on what they wear, so I assume people are doing the same to me.  Katherine introduced me to Keith, who was fucking gorgeous.  He was also thin, attractive, and well-dressed.  Being in Halifax, this means that Keith was probably gay, and of course the fact that I found him attractive was the clincher.  However, finding people attractive, and being attracted to someone are different things, and I am a smarty (most of the time), so I was really scoping him for Joe.  They would make a wicked attractive couple.  Anyway, I asked Katherine if he was gay, and she said that he was but not out of the closet yet.  In fact, Keith has yet to admit that he is gay.  Now this brings something up.  Perhaps he's not actually gay.  I mean, he fits the profile.  In fact, Keith is a "hair designer", his roommate is gay, and he was casting some sidelong glances at Willis, Katherine's rather delicate-looking, adorable straight friend. So even to me, it's obvious that Keith likes boys.  However, if Keith still likes girls, "coming out" might be harder than it looks.  How do you admit to people that you like everyone?  I can understand straight, I can understand gay, but bisexuality is something more marginal than either of those sexual orientations.  In fact, the word orientation inplies that you are pointing in one direction or the other.  I think alot of people don't even believe in bisexuality, like it's a cop out for guys who don't want to own the gay lifestyle, or girls who are simply tired of guys' bullshit (HELLO!).  I think I was leaning in that direction until before Joe told me he was bi.  I mean, Joe *is* living the gay lifestyle, but has recently admitted liking girls.  How do you come out all over again?  "Hi guys.  Remember when I told you I didn't like girls?  I was wrong.  I like both boys and girls."  Particularly when a large proportion of your friends are gay, as in Joe's case.  I don't even think he has really told anyone.  I don't *know* how his gay friends would react, but I can imagine there are a few who would behave worse than Joe's straight friends when he told them he was gay.  Kudos to Keith for waiting until he has figured things out.  And I am now in a position to appreciate his apprehension.  I would like to take this opportunity to throw my support toward everyone who has declared their bisexuality, and apologize for my past prejuidice - love should not be constained by the likes of me.    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was highly annoyed on Monday.  Wholy unsatisfied with everything and everyone about covered it.  Perhaps it was hormonal.  Either way, my attitude about Halifax is starting to change.  I am no longer down about living in this city I hate, but I am frustrated and angry!  To add insult to the already injurous city I live in, three of my favorite hangouts have closed.  Are you kidding me?  Seriously, though.  I don't understand it!  How do people live like this!  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmmm... I have been neglecting you, my dear blog.  Sorry baby, but I have been busy, and these days, so rarely motivated.  That point can actually get things started.  I was reading The Coast last week, and there was an article about SAD - Seasonal Affect Disorder.  I think I have a mild case, since the only thing that I have been motivated to do this week is get out of bed in order to plant my ass on the couch.  Good times.    But, I have a new friend (yeah for me!) and she is super-fun.  I feel like a winkie in a home who needs to count the number of friends I have.  Pathetic.  But whatebs, Katherine (and friends!) is great.  A bit young, but still awesome.  That is more pointed at her friends anyway.  They are all still so much cooler than I am, but since I am older and in graduate school (oooOOOooo) I get extra points.  I have developed an infatuation with Muchmusic's new VJ, Devon.  Holy crap so beautiful.  I love him to death.  He will be mine... I have a three part plan.  Muhahahahaha!  www.muchmusic.com/vjsearch.  Look, but don't touch.  Finally, anyone want to make out?  I had a discussion with my friend Nick about my new attitude this year.  My attitude is that I know I am a great person, and I know that at some point I am going to meet somebody perfect, but right now, I just want to have fun.  Nick suggested I was looking for Mr. Right Now, as oppose to Mr. Right - which is a fair and accurate statement, but I was still insult.  Fuck him.  I'm out.  In a while, alligator.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, I want to say that this post is a tad political; however, this blog in general is not meant to indulge in political ramblings or critiques of mass media.  It is meant to indulge in any thought that enters my head and that I deem interesting.  I just wanted to warn amyone reading that although this post might sound political, I do not mean to turn into one of those ultra-boring political/media blogs that seem so popular.  Read the damn newspaper yourself!  Anyhoo.  I was reading Time Magazine's article "Who killed Jesus?", and I will admit that although I didn't read all of it, there was one part in particular that bothered me.  It's something that the media has brought up before, but the fevered pitch seems to be at a high right now with the release of Mel Gibson's film "Passion"  just around the corner.  Specifically, the article mentioned the film is worrying Jewish and other religious groups because of it's possible anti-semetic sentiments.  I would like to take issue with this.  For the record, I am an aetheist, and I am vehemently opposed to organized religion, and in particular Catholicism.  You can call me an anti-christ. Tee hee.  Anyway, the idea that this film might destroy all the inroads that have been built between Christianity and Judaism since the Second Vatican is ridiculous!  For those of you who don't know, the Second Vatican (in the 1960s) said that although there were Jewish people involved in Jesus' death, there people in no way represented all of the Jews alive at the time of his crucifixion, nor all of the Jews of today.  I agree.  Why would Gibson's film undo this?  From what I understand, he makes the effort to stress that those pressing for the "messiah's" death are elite members of a Jewish Temple, and do not represent the Jewish population of Jeruseleum as a whole.  I think that Gibson is really trying here to explore the emotion of Jesus' last hours, and not to explore the extra-religious or political motivations that may have brought about his death.  But don't make him sugar-coat it.  If it was a Jewish high priest who was the most influential person in ensure Jesus' crucifixion, then show it that way.  No one with half a brain will translate that into = all Jews, now and forever.  That's stupid.   And as a side note, in the event that a movie is ever made about the rampant sexual abuse perpetrated by priests in the Catholic Church, I hope that no one will feel uncomfortable about protraying them as CATHOLIC PRIESTS.  Since they were, in fact, CATHOLIC PRIESTS!  On that same note, I hope that no Catholic who is NOT responsible for the perpetration of abuse or subsequent cover-ups is judged for these crimes, simply for being Catholic.  There are a lot of reasons to judge Catholics, but that isn't one of them.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nick called me last night at around 9pm, which is weird.  Nick is one of those friends who calls for a specific reason..."I am going to this movie, thought you might like to come..." or  "the museum is have a special exhibit, do you want to go..." etc.  So it was about a minute into chatting when I asked him, "What do you want?"  He kind of giggled, and said he was down at Rogue's having some beers with a couple of the guys, and wanted me to come down. He also added that he was "working on my problem".  Ok, can I just say yuuuuccchhhh!    This whole thing started a few weeks ago with me complaining about guys.  I thought I might try relaxing my strict criteria for a while, and see how that goes.  I even wrote about Nick's response that pissed me off so much, but so accurately described what I was talking about ("you're looking for Mr. Right Now, not Mr. Right").  I think Mr.  Right Now belongs to his group of drinking buddies.  This wouldn't irk me so much if I didn't know for a fact that Nick routinely warns girls at the bar away from his friends, because they are all such jerks.  And I can just imagine the situation:  Friend:  I wish I had a girl to fool around with. Nick:  Hey, I know a girl who is looking for Mr. Right Now.  Maybe that's you!  And!  She has huge tits! Friend:  Really?  Can you call her right now?  The whole thing leaves me rather disgusted with Nick for trying to pimp me out to his friends.  Very disgusted.  I suppose it has also made me re-think the "looking for Mr. Right Now".  It's all a matter of who knows what, and when.  Did anyone see that episode of "Friends" where Rachel tells Chandler that she is looking for a fuck-buddy, and he tells one of his workmates, who asks Rachel out?  Rachel's goals really haven't changed, but it was bothersome to find out that her date knew her intentions.  I suppose at this point, you really get into the ethics of dating - intentions, actions, who needs to know what when, etc - which I don't want to touch.   Bottomline, Nick is an asshole.  I think I already knew that.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, can I just say that the phrase "This one time..." was, in fact,  used by people before American Pie came out and totally destroyed legitimate use of it!  Now, I have to be all specific about when and where my stories take place in order to avoid the ridicule that naturally follows when you start a sentence with "This one time...".    Joe wants a party.  He is coming back to Halifax in a couple of weeks in order to write the DAT for application into dentistry.  He told me that I should throw him a party for after the test.  Are you kidding me?  The worst part is that after I mocking him for such an expectation, I then thought twice and started planning a super-secret surprise party for Joe after the DAT.  I am such a sucker.  I swear to god, Joe has the entire universe wrapped around his little finger!  I need to take lessons...  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, so I have a propensity to exaggerate a bit, and I indulged myself yesterday.  I was walking home, thinking about my singlehood.  I will admit, I am a complete commitment-phobe, but my dry spell had gotten a bit ridiculous.  This is where the exaggeration comes in.  I was having a running dialogue between me and myself in my head (don't even pretend you don't know what I am talking about), when I thought, "wouldn't it suck if I never dated again".  Holy crap.  I know it's remote, but it's possible.  I mean, it's basically been... a really long time as it is (and it is none of your business how long) - what if I have lost the ability to date??  I know, I know, stupid.  It has inspired me to try harder, though.  And that brings me to the question, how can I possibly know how attractive I am?  This is the low-down: 130lbs 5'4" short-ish, brown curly hair round face (freckles)  Now, I think I am relatively cute.  I know that at 5'4", with curly brown hair and freckles, sexy is not on the list of adjectives most people would use to describe me.  But my point in that I look in the mirror, and I don't hate what I see.  When I am wearing make-up and having a good hair day, I think I am alright.  Do I have an over-inflated sense of my own attractiveness?  Because literally, nobody hits on me.  I haven't had anyone show interest in quite some time.  What is that?  Is that me?  I suppose either I am uglier than I think, or else I am using body language to tell guys "back off, get your own sandwich!".  Hmmm... I will opt for the latter, because *technically* that is something I can change.  Speaking of self-evaluation, I have to pass on this little note about my friend Nick.  We were hanging out on the weekend - we went to the market, then the Art Gallery of Nova Scotia, and then for coffee - and I was lamenting over the complete lack of available, *viable* men in Halifax.  I specifically mentioned that anyone who was well-dressed and good-looking was gay, to which Nick cleverly replied, "I didn't *think* I was gay?"  Predictable.  My answer was, "I will give you one or the other, but you can't have both, sweetie".  Let me pause for a moment and describe the outfit that Nick was wearing for our outing: ratty cargos, sneakers, plain, faded navy hoodie, colorless t-shirt.  I will continue.  Nick unwisely chose well-dressed.  No! No! No!  Nick, I gave you this one!  In light of your terrible choice of clothing that day, and the fact that clothes can change, but (for the most part) your looks can't, I thought this would be easy!  Apparently, I was wrong.  A note to those out there who might be reading this: and a note to those who aren't: what you wear is important!  There is a guy that I work with that has some very questionable grooming habits.  He will come in with clean clothes, all tucked in and neat, washed hair, and shaved face.  let's call this day 1.  On day 2, he will come in with the same clothes, slightly touseled, hair slightly greasy, and a bit of stumble.  On day 3, he is a mess, and it is apparent that he has simply rolled out of bed (or more likely, off of some couch) and strolled into the lab.  Then the process starts all over again.  It's gross, and I judge him for it.  And it's true: I judge you, too.  Throw away those shirts with holes in them!  Wash and iron your clothes!  Yes!  Iron your clothes!  I discovered starch last year, and I think it was my favorite discovery of 2003.  BTW - John, if you are wondering if I am talking about you in the previous paragraph, wonder no more.  And stop reading my blog!  If I wanted people I knew to read it, I would have sent out the link!  FYI for anyone else, John is a member of my lab, and recently, when I was asking for help trying to figure out some code, his accidentally/intentionally switched the browser to my blog, which I had open.  From there, he has done a search for "Fear and Loathing in Halifax" and found this little piece of my brain.  My blog address also includes my avatar, mac mommy, which I have printed on my bank card, so there is no doubt that this is the place.  Ergo, fuck off, John.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!  I have figured it out!  The comments function is back!  Yeah me!  OK, so now I am inspired to learn how to write my own code - especially since my template looks pretty ass, and I am starting to hate orange.  Anyway, just a quick note to say that comments can be made.  And John, stop reading this.  It's not for you.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello again, dear blog.  Ok, I can't remember what went into the last post I wrote, but let's assume that not all of what I am about to write has already been written (although, surely some has).  So, here goes.  Last week, I went out with Katherine, who is an undergrad we has doing some very menial tasks around the lab during the summer.  I think katherine is great!  She is everything that I wanted to be when I was 20.  I would still like to be some of those things, but I feel like I am too old for some of those traits to be effective and endearing.  Anyway, I went to the Marquee's last retro night before a very extended closure for renovations.  Katherine rounded up some of her friends, and invite me along.  She has done the same in the past, and I never go because I am so social phobic these days, and any effort is too much effort, but since the Marquee was closing, off I go.  It was loads of fun, actually, but I was a bit pervie.  All of Katherine's friends are 19-20 years old, and Willis, the youngest looking of the bunch, caused me some anxiety (read: I thought he was attractive).  I know, I am only 24, but still. At this point in my life, I feel like that is a huge difference.  I think I have picked up alot of indifference in the years between 20 and 24, and I don't see it in Willis' tiny little face, so I am probably pervie.  BUT!  I need to make another confession in order to highlight a very disturbing trend.  I have also previously mentioned my infatuation with the new muchmusic vj, Devon Soltedieck.  Ahhh, Devon.  Those pouty lips... the slight figure... the whispy, baby-fine hair hanging into his eyes.  Beautiful.  If you would like a closer look, go to www.muchmusic.com/vjsearch , and have a look for yourself.  I must admit, the resemblence between Devon and Willis is pretty striking.  I was horrified when an aquaintance of mine saw a picture of Devon, and suggested I just have a baby if I wanted someone to take care of and coo over.  Holy crap!  How did this person, who I barely know, so accurately describe the reality of my dating preferences??!  It was in the moment after her comment when all became clear.  I like my boys looking young.  What is that about??!  I am not as pervie as that sounds, but I like Devon's sveltness, and babyface.  How do I get rid of this?  OK, maybe I am sick.  What do I do??!  I actually an soliciting an anwser here.  Once I figure out how to repost my comments function, you can all let me know what you think...er, be kind. The idea of having random strangers judge me harshly is still stewing in me.  Also, I wanted to share a bit of my inner self.  One of my strangest anxieties...  I have a fear of my last breath.  Ok, I am not afraid of dying, but of literally taking that last breath.  I have no reason to think so, but I feel like everyone knows when they are taking their last breath.  I honestly think I would know, and it scares the fuck out of me.   If you don't know what I am talking aboout, then picture it.  You are old, you've had a happy life or whatever, and you are dying.  Lying in bed, here it comes.  You are ready.  In....out.  Done.  Yikes!  What is going to happen?! Even if you are sure, do you really know?  I mean, if you knew a gun was empty, would you really test things by putting it to your head and squeezing the trigger?  And the anxiety of not knowing is excrutiating!  The worst part is that now that I am a conscious, living being, I can't get out of experiencing that last moment.  It really scares me sometimes.  Other times, I agree with you... I just sound like a space-cadet.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ha ha ha!  I was just telling my friend Kerry about my encounter with Mr. Redneck.  I also told her about Andrew-the-super-crush, and how it appears that I have missed out on my soulmate (oh! the melodrama!).  She made a really good point: Had I asked out Andrew a year ago, it would have turned out that he was an English major, failing every course, completely without direction, and a total asshole.  By virtue of the fact that I *didn't* ask him out, he is a genetics genius who has several top schools foaming at the mouth (of course, there is still no indication of whether he is an asshole or not, but in keeping with the theme of my life, let's assume is amazingly nice and thoughtful and lovely in every way).  I think the fact that Mr. Redneck was the first guy I was *thinking* about kissing in...uhem, quite some time, proves her logic.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here by my side, an angel Here by my side, a devil Never turn your back on me Never turn your back on me again.  I love Matthew Good.  I went to his show on Saturday night at the marquee, and it was amazing.  Goosebumps, I tell you.  I wish that my parents has forced me to play an instrument.  I was watching some news channel, and there was a piece on how children who learn to read and play music at a young age are smarter than their non-musical peers.  It's all got to do with how the brain is organizing itself during our formative years. It turns out that during early childhood, about half of the neurons we were born with die off.  The brain produces neurons in over-abundance as a fail safe, to ensure that everything that needs wiring gets the resources, but when everything is set neurons are programmed for death as a sort of "house-keeping".  An organized brain is an efficient brain.  Anyway, if you play music, you get to keep more neurons.  In addition, those neurons have influence over how other populations of neurons function.  Matt Good is a genius... but hhe didn't even pick up a guitar until 20... even more impressive.  So, I tried really hard this weekend to "search my soul".  My horoscope in The Coast was pushing me to find some treasure I have been pining for.  So I tried.  First, at the show, I looked around for Andrew the super-crush.  No luck, but I kept my eyes open all night while I flirted with a friend of a friend - Scott.  Upon leaving, Scott offered to walk me home, and I thought "I suppose this is someone I could make out with".  It's been my view for some time that if I only got back on the horse, then approaching people wouldn't seem nearly so daunting.  Anyway, so Scott and I stop at pizza corner, and he is chatting with some guy and I overhear him say "You should see this place at 4am - it's full of niggers and lebs". I just about fell over.  Ok, so maybe I can't make out with this guy.  But we are close to my house, so we keep walking, although at this point I am obviously keeping my distance for mr. redneck.  As we walk up to my building, he says "Is this where we go in?"  I reply "No, this is where I go in.  Thanks for walking me home"  when he says "Are you serious? But I walked you home."  Now I know why I am in the position I am in.  I would rather be sad and lonely, and wishing I had asked out Andrew than trying to figure out how to dissect guys like Scott from my life once I realize what pigs they are.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why am I always so stupid?  I am insecure, and awful, and sabotaging my own life!  I went to convocation on Tuesday, and saw my prince.  Actually, he is just a remarkably lovely man that I see around my academic building occassionally.  I used to also see him in my apt building, last year when I was still living in the dump called Fenwick.  Anyway, turns out he was graduating as well, but from undergrad.  With a university award, no less.  I noted his name, and googled him today... first off, he is brilliant.  Nominated for a Rhodes Scholarship, among others.  Offered a 6-figure scholarship to go to University of Chicago (unheard of!).  Leaving in the fall for England.  Depression setting in...   I noticed him a year ago!  Or more!  Why didn't I ask him out!?  I am complete shit.  And he is just so lovely.  If anyone knows a brilliant man named Andrew, please tell him I am sorry I never asked him out.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, it's been a long time.  There was a crash and burn, and I decided I didn't want to write for a while.  It's like when your train of thought leads to the MOST embarassing thing that you've ever done - completely by chance - and you quickly try to think of something else.  Writing in this blog was too painful, since it dealt with the instigation of my crash and burn... but we won't talk about that.  So, Kathy is dating a new guy named mark, who I have met a couple of times.  He is very attractive, but in a slightly nervous and weird sort of way.  I am so jealous.  But not really, because Kathy is amazing and deserves an attractive guy who has the capacity to blush is a really genuine way.  Anyway, I know he worked at the library, since that is where Kathy picked him up.  I went yesterday to get some journal articles, and I was making a conscious effort to look for him, but I have misplaced my glasses, so if a person is further than 4 feet from me, there face is a blurr.  In general, I don't wear my glasses out and about, though, so I have become rather adept at recognizing people from their gait and their hair sillhouette.  I am standing in line at the counter, and I think I see mark, so I am staring at him trying desperately to figure out if it's him, but his hair is off, and he is not walking, so gait is out, when he waves in my direction.  But I am still far enough away that the wave is ambiguous.  Is he waving at me, or the guy behind me?  Or is he not mark at all, and is waving *because* I am staring?  So I don't wave, and stop staring.  Eventually, mark comes over and we chat for a bit, and it becomes very obvious that he has cut his hair... Mark is on dangerous ground, I tell you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Love is the cognitive hormone that regulates reproduction, and hence survival of the species.  Think about it. :|
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, what do you think of my new template?  I like it, but I am missing the links I had set up, and the page counter, which took me *hours* to figure out.  C'est la vie.  It occurred to me after the post about paying people to write in the comments section so that I could "connect", that it would make no sense for me not to write the people who were taking the time to write me.  Perhaps this is added incentive - write in my comments section and you will get a chance at the $5 in my pocket AND an email from me.  Perhaps not.  Anyway, I imagine I have reached my limit of commenters, so I will have to choose who to send the money to from the three people from the first day (and I just realized that time is up).    Well, catching the fruits of my labor might be easier than I thought.  Or more difficult.  Commenter Ken, who mocked Ultimate Frisbee players and suggested I take the $5 and go for a drink, has also suggested coffee.  Yikes!  I mean, I made the call for comments, he commented, I emailed my thanks, and he suggested coffee.  Together.  Is that crazy?  I should watch what I say, because he is probably going to read this, sooner or later.  On the other hand, I haven't watched what I said before, and he *says* he's read all that, too.  I have been relatively open on this, my little piece of the internet, and yet he still wants to meet.  Perhaps that's reason enough not to.  This was supposed to be an outlet for my neurotic anxiety that I try to hide in my real life (I am more and more convinced I that I am not doing a terribly good job at it).  So, the question is, should I do it?  Any thoughts?  I mean, I am not desperate for a relationship, but I think it's become clear that I am desperate to make a connection with people in this city.  And Commenter Ken is in this city.  He said he's not disfigured or fat or anything, only short.  I am bordering on freakshow short myself, so I don't judge (yes I do, but I try not to). But what if he's a geek?  Not like in high school, since it turns out that most of those people were cooler than the "in" crowd anyway, but like those people who stand too close to you, or like someone who doesn't get the hint, and keeps calling, even though you never call him, and you cell phone seems to be on the blink, because he always finds himself leaving you voicemail, which makes you cringe.  (BTW - when did "phone messages" become voicemail?  Is there a difference?)  But there is the fact that I have been soooo honest.  It might be a great place to start a friendship.  I have a hard time voicing my lunacy because I think my friends think I am holding it together (like I said, I might be a tad delusional on this point, but I am not ready to let go of the fantasy yet).  If he already knows, no point in hiding it, right?  I guess the real question is whether there is any harm in meeting Commenter Ken.  Right now, I can think of none.  Meeting a stanger in a public place for a chat and a coffee.  He *could* follow me home and start stalking me.  Yikes.  But that is true of the guys I actually give my number to, and I haven't even given him that much rope to hang me with. However!  I am not blind to the fact that I am infallible - if you have a suggestion about some other way Ken might be creepy, something that I just haven't seem, let me know.  In fact, let's put it to a vote - should I make the leap of faith?  Or should I save myself the trouble because people are basically shitty and are more trouble than they are worth?  Vote by Monday, June 28th, and I will let you all know the results and my plan.  I just re-read the question on the ballot.  Fuck it - I am going to do it.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The incoming comments, which seemed to be on a roll, have ceased since I posted my picture and profile - am I ugly?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow.  I am stunned.  I have had 3 different people send me wonderful comments, and none of them want the $5!  I am truly touched.  I am also guilt-ridden.  I went out with Kathy Friday night to seem some *formly* local calypso band called Piggy. They were awesome. Kathy made a good point that night - I thought that by being honest about how people here make me feel like such an outsider, I was daring them to let me in.  Literally, my response to the question "Oh, you're from away.  How do you like Halifax?" was always "It's small and the people are insular.  I hate it."    Kathy took my hand, and with a wise tender face, said "no, no, no, sweetie.  You aren't daring them to let you, you are daring them to keep you out. And alienating them in the process."  So I have resolved to stop pouting.  I wouldn't say my feelings have changed - I still feel slighted and alone and awkward, but there are some things I truly like about Halifax (Freak Lunchbox...Hello!), and some wonderful friends (Kathy, Kathy, Kathy, and Vanessa, and Mandy when she is around), so I am far better off than quite a few out there.  And I get paid to go to school!  Yeah me!    And of course, the guilt comes from the fact that though perhaps not everyone who commented or will comment is from Halifax, obvious, there are some good people out there.  In addition, by expressing myself so freely, I am slighting those people that *do* make an effort to be my friend, as laborious as that sometimes is.  I didn't mean it.  I am an ass.   But the contest continues.  Since lovely Brandi, Ken and Bruce don't want my $5, I am going to leave it up for offer.  I am going to have a gin and seven-up for Ken, and I am going to Freaklunch Box tomorrow to by $5 worth of candy, and think of Bruce.  And for Brandi, I am going to buy myself a button from Biscuit, since she didn't have a suggestion about what to do with my $5, and I love buttons.  So if you want to compete, leave me a comment following this post (the first set of comments were erased when I changed my template! oops!).  Again, contest is over June 23, 5pm local time (that means, "you figure it out, since I am too lazy to find out the time zone").  Thanks guys.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it seems this blog is not serving it's purpose.  I want to connect.  if this is your first visit, have a look at the last few entries, and perhaps you will understand what I mean.  I fear my existential crisis is reaching a breaking point.  I feel I am about to jump ship on my life... no, no, no.  Not suicide.  I don't want to kill myself, but I want something else.  What else?  What else... I want to go for cocktails with my girlfriends, and flirt with boys, and wake up happy to be where I am.  Unfortunately, I live in a city full of insular locals (read: shitty, close-minded ass-wipes who only chill with the friends they were borning knowing), my close friends are all from "away" (yes, Haligonians have a word for those of us not born here... we're "from away"... gives me chills) and in relationships.  I love my job dearly, and marvel at the fact I get paid to go to do what I do (currently doing my PhD in neuroscience) but I can't take it.  I need to connect to someone.  Anyone.  I fear I am about to give up my dream, so that I can run-away from this god-forsaken place and find a job as a waitress in Vancouver, or Hawaii, or Italy... or anywhere the people don't fucking lick goats.  So, I have a proposition.  I have $5 in my pocket.  I will send this special $5 to the person who leaves a comment that makes me smile.  I am running on a tight budget, so I am only going to send this $5 to the best smile-inducing comment. Obviously, I will be the judge of who left the best message for me, and I am making a deadline of June 23, 2004, 5pm local time.  Make sure you leave your email address, so I can get a mailing address from the luck winner to send the special $5.  Now, let's all be realistic.  I don't get more than 1 or 2 hits a day, and the average time that someone spends on my blog is about 43 secs, so I am not expecting more than one or two comments. If you do comment, chances are pretty good that you will win.  It's an easy $5... connect with me.  Make me smile.  UPDATE:  If you read the story about Scott the wonder-asshole who expected sex for walking me home, there is an update to the story.  If you remember, Scott is a friend of a friend, Amber.  Of course I told Amber the story; I thought she would think it was funny (which it was, and she did) and I was hoping she might be able to provide an explanation (which she couldn't).  Anyway, I was talking to Amber last night, and it turns out that she has shared the story with her and Scott's circle of friends, and Scott's new nicname is "Dirty".  I love it.  I imagine if Amber ever has another party, or if there is another show we all want to go see, things are going to get ugly between me and Scott.  In fact, I have already heard he is bitter about the story getting out...  The truth hurts, Dirty.  One more thing:  At one point, Kaylee had linked to me from her own blog.  I don't know Kaylee, but how nice is it that she things I am worth sharing?  Anyone, I have lost her!  I think she changed her blog address, and I have found it on blogscanada.com, but the link is broken.  Kaylee, if you are reading this blog still (again?), give me a heads-up about where you're at, and make an attempt for the $5.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here is the root:  I cannot seem to connect with anyone. I just want to meet someone who understands my jokes.  I hate explaining my jokes.  And do people use metaphores anymore??!!  If you blush on a regular basis, and you know when something is ironic, email me: ironyismylife@hotmail.com.    There was a PSSST in the Coast a couple of weeks ago, posted by two girls.  It was something like: "Two nice female roommates want to find some un-sucky friends", or something, plus an email address.  Good luck ladies.  Good luck.  And now I am off to humiliate myself at ultimate frisbee.  Not because I can't play, but because I have to associate with the immature assholes who play ultimate.  Yeah, that's you buddy.  (BTW - if you missed it, the irony of that email address is that no one is actually going to contact me there.  Get it?  Get it?  Oh, fuck it.)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Do you ever feel the need to fuck with people? I am fucking with two people right now, and I am deriving a sick sort of pleasure from it.   Dr. D is a faculty member in my department - he has only been here 8 months, and he is young (let's say 29ish).  He has recently been beating around the bush about asking me out.  Convenient group outings, and a common interest in film has made it possible for him to imply that he would like to go out on a date, but he has been subtle enough that I can ignore it and no one feels awkward.  Why am I fucking with this poor man?    Let's take a look at victim number 2, since the reasons that I am fucking with them are related.  The other person I am fucking with is an undergrad - Bonnie - who volunteers in a lab that is linked to ours.  I don't like Bonnie.  She is such a phony, sychophantic wanker.  I also don't like her because she hangs out with some friends of mine - the boys.  One of the boys, Dan, liked her but she was engaged to some 30 year old guy (she's 21).  She ended up making out with Dan, and then ignoring him the next day at church.  Hand-in-hand with her fiancee.  So she is also a hypocrit.  I heard a couple of weeks ago, from a very reliable source, that in the first 3 months that Dr. D was here, they hooked up.  Although Bonnie is no longer engaged right now, whether she was when she was with Dr. D is a little shady (I think yes).  The worse part is that this could have dire consequences for both of them.  Dr. D just got here, and this is a serious breach of ethics.  Not a good first impression.  And Bonnie has appllied to be a grad student at Dal, so she should also have some concern about sleeping with a faculty member!!!  They are just both so... and it makes me want to fuck with them.  I'm not doing anything really mean.  I am still reasonably nice to Bonnie, and I just happen to mention, on occassion, Dr. D's name.  Inviting her to these group outings, and so on (she always has an excuse).  You have to understand that she implies that she has nothing to do with him.  They don't know each other... but I know different.  I have managed to make Dr. D think that I might be interested, by inviting him to group outings and keeping him appraised of any new art films in town.  He manages to avoid the get-togethers where Bonnie is going to be present.    I take a wicked pleasure in watching both of them squirm.  I have no explanation for my abominable behavior.   BTW - crisis is still ongoing, but after smoking a fatty with my friend Mandy last night, and trying to figure out the hidden messages in some wacked out commercials, the crisis has subsided.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am having an existential crisis.  I thought writing in my blog might help, but I can't even imagine where to begin.  Be back soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       While I am in Toronto, I am hopefully going to see my long-lost-almost-friend, Brad.  He moved away from Halifax shortly after I met him, and we never actually got together for the drink or film we had discussed.  And then we've missed each other the three times that Brad has returned to Hali since moving, for one reason or another. I haven't gotten an email in ages, and I wasn't actually expecting to get a reply, seeing as our friendship never really got off the ground, but I emailed him a heads-up anyway, and then there was his email in my in box.  Lovely.  I love Brad - I wish he was still here so that we could hang out.  And being the wickedly cool, charming, and lovely person that he is, I would also hangout with all of his awesome friends, because guys like Brad only have awesome friends.  *sigh*  Anyway, he invited me to go to an "artsy/queer/indie" place called Vazaleen, which is actually at Lee's Palace.  It's a once-a-month party that's held there.  Even though it's not really my scene, (although I am good at "queer") I though it was really nice that Brad extended the offer.  The world needs more people like Brad.       
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I am going to Toronto for a few days, and I am so excited about it.  I am staying with some friends I met while living in Taiwan - Martha and Chris.  They were both a bit older than me, and I felt like they were my big sister & brother.  It was nice that they were so protective of me.    Of course, it wasn't all about protecting me - it was also about taking care of me while we were partying.  Chris and Martha were much more experienced with the international party scene, and were good about taking care of me when we went out to clubs or parties.  I was naive, but Martha was always making sure I got home safe, or would pull me away if she knew I was talking to trouble, and with them I had some of the best times of my life.  There was this one party in Kaohsiung at a foreigner's house for Halloween... that was a really good time.  We should have all been deported for what went on.  *Sigh*  Good times... and more to come by week's end.     
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      that's all I have to say today.    Wait - you are, too, otherwise you might say hello.  Step outside the box, sister, and write me something nice.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       In the last two days, I have become very bleak. It leads me to believe that I have cyclothymia. I have been trying for ages to like this city, and I don't hate it. I don't hate Halifax... I hate being here. There are some things that I like about this city, but living here isn't one.    I NEED CULTURE FOR CHRIST SAKE!  I am just too goddamn bohemian for this city.      Ok, so I made myself smile a bit.  That was a little funny.    Anyway, I am not feeling myself. I just found out that a guy I have had a crush on for ages knows I have had a crush on him for ages, and my reaction has  not  been typical. This is a guy I have never really spoken to in my life, but he's gorgeous, and I imagine he is an amazing person (the Halo Effect). Sure, I am probably imagining it - looks  and  wonderful personality - but it's fun, goddammit! And I would never do anything about it. It just keeps me busy, goddammit! But it turns out he knows. And it turns out he's known for ages! And I like it that he knows. I am happy he knows, and that we will  still  never talk. The typical me would cringe every time I though of *Gorgeous* knowing that looking at him is something of an addiction for me because he is so beautiful, as if it is my worst possible fault or the most embarrassing thing about me. But what the fuck? I have nothing the lose... Fuck it. Fuck. It.      BA!   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ok, since making the committment not to rag on Halifax anymore, I have come to realize that it is not the worst place I can be. I am getting used to it, and I have found my niche. I can't say that I am really happy, though.    My horoscope for the coming week:            The astrological omens suggest that I should urge you to be far bolder than usual. They even seem to be saying that the more brazen you are, the bigger your rewards will be. In fact, Scorpio, if I'm reading the signs accurately, you might want to draw your inspiration from the 40 starving artists in Paris who broke into an abandoned building near the Louvre a few years back. They built studios inside and have been squatting rent-free ever since. Now the city of Paris has bought the building and is paying $3.5 million to renovate it so that the artists can continue to thrive there. Be like them.   *sigh* How to be bold... what boldness can I undertake, and for what purpose? I just want to be happy here, and right now I have a smile on my face but it's fading. I will grin and bear it for a few more weeks, and then... and then... and then. I should stop writing in my blog, for one.    So, part of my unhappiness comes from a cancelled trip I was about to take. I was going to go to a university in Ontario for a month to complete an fMRI research experiment, but the magnet at the Robart's Institute is fubared, so the trip has been postponed indefinitely. I was really looking forward to this being the highlight of my summer - getting out of this city, and getting some perspective, plus seeing some friends in Toronto.     Darren, the witty new addition to our lab, tried to cheer me up with my  favorite ,    fuzzy grapefruit slices this morning. How very thoughtful... Darren, am I detecting a crush?    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I deleted this post because I suspect people I know are reading it, and I don't want to get anyone in trouble.    It's all downhill from here.    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I was going to write about how fucking upset I am right now, but the only thing that would come out was swear words, so I am going to write about a cool fact I heard the other day.  I will write about my frustration later when I have had some time to deal with it.    I was talking to Kerry the other night about how I think science makes things more interesting and beautiful, not less so.  There is an illusion with the moon that gives me goosebumps - when the moon is low, it appears to be really large, but if you hold up a dime or your thumb to it, you would find that it is the same size as when it is above you and looks small.  It's because people assume that the sky above them is closer than the sky at the horizon.  The brain reasons that if the sky at the horizon is further away, but the moon is the same physical size, then the moon at the horizon must be huge, and just translates that directly into the perception of a really large harvest moon.  I love that fact.  And whenever I see a harvest moon, I always point it out to people.  But my friends think I am ruining the beauty when I share these little facts.  I disagree.    Anyway, I heard a better one the other day:  When people are in love, looking into the eyes of their partner causes the pupils to dilate.  The dilation acts as re-inforcement for looking into each others eyes - it's like a physical manifestation of "I love you", which is why it is so rewarding to look at a person you are in love with.  I love that fact, too.  And I don't think it makes gazing into your lover's eyes less romantic - just the opposite.    Is anybody reading this?      I am going to watch The Notebook again sometime this week.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I had so much fun, it was retarded.  Friday, I went with Kerry to see The Notebook, which was amazing.  It was the most romantic movie I have ever seen, and it made me want to fall in love.  Then we went to the Economy Shoe Shop for drinks and tapas, and met up with a group of friends.  It was a  lovely evening.    Saturday, I went with Kerry to the Gay Pride Parade.  It was so good!  I am always amazed at the vibrant gay seen in Hali.  At one point, we were looking at a gorgeous man with a wicked body having water poured over him while he danced on a float.  I told Kerry it was a guy I knew, and she asked if he was gay (of course) and then said, "Oh!  That's so wrong!".  Three people turned around to glare at us.  Wrong thing to say at a gay pride parade, Ker.   Although it raised the interesting question, why are all the good ones gay?  We decided it was something like having a specialized job.  If your job is specialized, and there aren't a whole lot of positions available, you have to be the best in your field.  If you have some run-of-the-mill job that you can find anywhere, what's the motivation to be the best?  In short, all the good ones are gay, because women have yet to demand better.  I am putting my foot down.  It is not sooo hard to have a bit of style, take some time with the hair, and make an effort at person grooming.  This is all I ask, and I am tired of the answering being, "sorry, I'm gay".  Not good enough, boys.    Saturday evening was the best time I have ever had in Halifax.  I went to a joint stagette with a small group of girls, and it was so great.  We kept running into a stag party full of rowdies at several of the bars on our pubcrawl.  Kerry thought I wasn't talking to them because I was shy, but it was really because I was not willing to yield the lowest common demoninator.  Is it just me, or do men you meet in bars always demand the stupid bimbo?  Kerry is an amazing girl, and I am so happy we are such good friends these days, but that girl delivered.  As it was, I allowed some guy to hold my hand for about a minute (it was one of those, "come'on.  Just hold my hand for a minute?  Why are you so reserved?" - yuch.  I can't believe I caved) and kissed a guy on the lips.  I offered my cheek, and was pressured into using my lips.  This is how I was turned into a Bimbo, and I was even  resisting  the pressures.  I was called "the uptight one" and still, they managed to turn me into someone other than me.  This is the dance we do - the guys act like macho assholes in an effort to bend us, and make us small, and we oblige.  Not good enough, boys.  And girls.  But, not all my time was wasted by men in togas, so it was still a really great time.  I even saw one of the multitude of eye-contact crushes, and managed to make loads more eye-contact with him (just talk to him!  I will next time.  I promise).    Still, the whole thing was fun, and when we ended up at the Marquee, I met Justin, who has style, and is a great dancer (not even gay, ladies!) and even gave him my number.  I am looking forward to the call, but he is no Ryan Gosling, and I am no Rachel McAdams... I want to be Rachel McAdams.  Oh well, you've got to start somewhere, right?   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      a  urlLink photo gallery  from a very recent Manitoba show, and a link to an  urlLink interview  with Manitoba that is wicked.  This guy is probably the coolest guy on the whole planet.  Fuck Rivers Cuomo.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow.  I went to see Manitoba at the Marquee last night, and it was so. fucking. intense.  I was speechless.  First off, Manitoba is a "DJ".  Sort of.  He samples, and there are beats, but there was so much going on, it is almost indescribable.  I will try.  Even though Manitoba is just one guy (I assume he is in charge of the arrangements...?), there were two other guys on stage with him.  They all came out wearing these bunny masks... which was alot cooler than it sounds.  Behind them, they got a video feed of random shots and video that was streaming, while turning into paintings.  It was awesome.  So Manitoba is on one set of drums, with two synthesizers beside him.  And then there is  another  drummer on the opposite side of the stage!  I now feel that two drummers are not option - they are mandatory.  Christ!  It was so good!  The third guy in the center played guitars of all sorts (one at a time) plus some crazy instruments that were I assume homemade (maybe not).  The music was so intense, it was like nothing else I have ever seen.  Loved it.  Loved.  It.  I now want to have Manitoba's babies.  They would be geniuses.  Did I mention that Manitoba is doing his PhD in pure mathematics over in England?  Holy crap.  Side note:  I saw this guy Jeff at the show.  Jeff is from Edmonton, but I met him ages ago at a friend's birthday party here in Hali.  We had a good chat, and Mandy, being the socially retarded friend that she is, asked him if he has a girlfriend, and when he answered in the affirmative, she actually said "sorry" to me.  I have got to get rid of that girl (just kidding, Middy, you know I love your quirky ways!).  Anyhoo, it's been ages since I have seen Jeff, but he still said hello, and commented on the awesomeness of the show.  I met loads of people at that birthday party, and had goog chats with quite a few, and so far, Jeff has been the only one nice enough to not pretend he doesn't remember be.  I love Edmontonians (and I wish Jeff didn't have a girlfriend).
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love to read my weekly horoscope from Rob Brezsny's  urlLink Free Will Astrology .  That man has had some insights into my soul like no one else.  On the day before I defended my master's thesis, I was compelled to go get the Coast in order to read my horoscope.  I figured that I needed the guidance, since I was so nervous, my anxiety was nearly overwhelming me.  It was raining out, and I still made the pilgrimmage.  And when I finally read it, it was like the clouds opened up (they didn't really - it was still raining).  My horoscope for that week was all about how I was a genius, with the potential to do amazing things.  It was my time to shine, and follow my soul's code.  I was about to do something great.  From then on, I have been religious about reading Rob's guidance (I wouldn't really call then predictions).  Anyway, this is my horoscope this week:  Each day many of your cells expire and are replaced by others. As long as you live, this relentless process of death and rebirth never abates. Periodically, then, you have a completely new set of flesh and bones that retains none of the same atoms you were composed of earlier. Think back, for example, to the physical body you inhabited in July of 1999. There is nothing left of that old thing! In a sense, you have reincarnated without having to endure the inconvenience of dying. Do you realize how free this makes you? In the coming week, Scorpio, take full advantage of this gift. Show how much you appreciate it.    What the fuck does that mean? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Someone asked about the mac mommy moniker, so I thought I'd take a minute to explain.  I am a  urlLink Mac -convert of the worst kind.  I am like one of those ex-smokers who feels holier-than-thou, and complains bitterly about public smokers, but with PCs.  When I got to my current lab, everyone was on Mac.  I made the switch, and never looked back.  Macs are the greatest creation in history, and if you aren't on a mac now, you will be in 10 years.  That's how long I predict it is going to take stubborn PC users to realize that better media, no viruses, superior programs, and a more intelligent, intuitive operating system are worth the growing pains of having to make a change.  It took me 2 months to fall in love.  And of course, there is the take-off of "mack daddy" (see definition  urlLink here ).  BTW - I tend to post on the same day because I am saving up.  I don't have a connection at home, so I write on weekends, or in the evening on my MAC ibook, and post all at once.  I don't write continuously (well, I do sort of, but it's scientific crap, so I don't post it).
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If anyone is down with film, you need to check out  urlLink The AlFresco FilmFesto  down at the Halifax Waterfront.  Saturday was the screening for Best in Show, and it was so much funnier watching it outside with a bunch of strangers.  But cold, so if you go to any of the other films, bundle up.  Anyone who has been reading might be wondering what is up with Commenter Ken.  Nothing, so far.  I was going to forget about it, because that is my special gift.  Seeing into the future, and knowing that nothing will come of it so why bother with the intervening nightmare date, and skip right to the "no-contact" phase? But Mandy talked me out of that plan of attack.  Apparently,  she  thinks it hasn't been working lately.  But what about this:  I haven't had a single (bad) date in ages.  So there.  Let's not get sticky about the details.  So I am going to send an email and suggest coffee... I just need to put it on the record:  I think meeting someone off the internet is a really bad idea, the worst I/mandy have had in ages.  And not because of Commenter Ken - if I had met him at a party or something equally normal, he would have my number.  But this is more like a scary blind date (which I also think is a bad idea).  Wish me luck.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got my hair cut, and I think it looks like ass.  But it will grow, I guess.  Still, it makes me want to grow it out again.  I was having a discussion with Mandy, and together, we had an apiphany about Hali.  Haligonians aren't assholes (although I am reluctant to let that one go), they are just improperly socialized.  Halifax is so small, that when a person says "Hey we should get together sometime and chill" they really mean "the next time we run into each other, which will obviously be very soon because halifax is the size of a dime, let's not pretend we don't know each other".  I am used to Edmonton, which is an *actual* city, and if you want to see someone again, you'd better get a number, and you'd better call it.  This is why I have been getting so down - I hand my number out to people all the time (read: girls - cuz guys here are ass), and I expect to hear from them, say, the next time they go out, because that's what people do in Edmonton.  But I don't, and I sit at home, and curse the bitch who said we should chill.  Mandy is the bitch.  Not really, since we are obviously friends, but she say the other point.  There was a girl she met through friends who said "We should chill" and Mandy agreed.  And then she called.  Mandy thought it was weird and awkward, but invited her out with friends for a night out.  She said it was like a date, and didn't really understand what this girl wanted from her, becuase really, they were bound to see each other again.  My point: IF YOU DON'T MEAN SOMETHING, DON'T FUCKING SAY IT!  Sometimes I think I have a touch of Asperger's Syndrome (a mild form of autism) because I can't read between the lines. And I have no time for games or innuendo.  I think it makes me scary sometimes, particularly in halifax.  "Oh my gawd, isn't that the girl who actually says what she means?" 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We have a new lab member.  I wasn't really looking forward to my supervisor getting his new grad students, and I was shocked to come back from Alberta to find one was already here!  How dare he show up before September!  I feel cheated out of my extra time with our prof. I was nearly petulant yesterday.   But!  There is an up-side.  Darren is basically the male version of me, so he is great!  We share a sense of humor, taste in politics, television and I suspect movies.  He spent some time teaching English in Asia, just like me!  And seeing as he is here in this lab, we obviously share a similar interest in research.  No crushes yet, but I think I have become asexual.  I *do* think we will become good friends, if he doesn't start to annoy me.  Knowing me (X2!), he will.  Shortly.  But I will try to be optomistic... he probably won't annoy me as much as John.  FYI - I am writing this about 2 feet from where Darren is sitting.  It only goes to show that people around you might be thinking nice things about you.  Or mean things.  Whatever.  I suggest you make the assumption that the person in the next room is thinking something really nice about you, and are making a note to tell a friend that nice think later.  Or their blog. :D  Finally,  I set up audioblogger, and I'm goin' out tonight!  Perhaps if things get rowdy, I will call in a message to say hello, and have Vanessa say somethin' funny.  Or Amber.  Yeah! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you liked  urlLink  Donnie Darko  , you will love the website.  Holy crap, I need to smoke a joint right now.  That was fucked.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I never liked poetry when I was younger. Until I was in my twenties, I thought it was useless - people should just say what they mean. I still believe that, but out of no where, it occurred to me that poetry has it's place. Well, not exactly out of no where. Gradually, I have become aware of how much I enjoy words. Like kiddiecorner. My new friend Dustin recently reminded me of that one, and although I am unlikely to see Dustin ever again, I will call him a friend and think of him as kiddiecorner to my life. And metaphores. There is something so delicious about metaphores, I could just eat them. Sometimes, you hear something that moves you, or there is a phrase that you just can't help but repeat to yourself. That is where I started to love poetry. And I still like to collect phrases that I will roll around in my mouth, and try to use in conversation, or just let roll around in my head for a while because it somehow makes sense, despite the semanticlessness of it.   Here are some of my favorites...  "not vicious or malicious, just de-lovely and delicious"                                        -Deee-Lite,  Groove is in the Heart   "There is just no smooth or sophisticated way to do this"                                        -Robin Wright-Penn in  A Home at the                                                     End of the World   "Catching the fruits of our labor,  Holding our hearts in our hands, Waiting for you to sounds a prayer in the form of an anchor"                                        -Further Seems Forever,  How to                                          Start a Fire   "Holy sweet gawddamn!"                                        -Weezer  "Fear not, MacBeth!     No man that's born of woman shall e'er have power upon thee"                                        -Shakespeare,  MacBeth    I will share others with you when I find them. And please - PUUL-LEEEZ! - share them with me if you have some. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since I am always talking about being single, I thought I might tell a story about not being single.  This is obviously from waaaay back in the day.  When I was 15, I started dating a guy named Chris.  Chris was - and is - a truly wonderful human being, and I love him still.  We were together for 5 years, and shared some really great times, and I can't deny that he is part of who I am today.  We broke up about 3X for pragmatic reasons.  Once it was because he moved to Edmonton to finish high school at a private school.  Once it was because after coming back to Slave Lake, I moved to Edmonton to go to University.  After he moved to Edmonton to go to college, we broke up because he decided to apprentice for electrician, and moved to Grand Prairie for a job. Each time, we got back together because we just couldn't resist each other.  Seriously.  We just had to be together, when we could.   The fourth break up stuck.  Oh gawd, was that awful.  But I'm getting off topic.  I want to tell the story of Chris and I getting back together the second time. I was moving to Edmonton, so we broke up.  Shortly afterward, Chris decided to join his friends in moving to Edmonton for work, and we were going to meet up there - but I was resistant this time.  I was graduating HS in a small town, and I wanted to see what it was like to be in the big city.  I told him I would talk about it only after I had beeen in Edmonton two weeks.  We spent to whole summer apart.  Once I moved, I got into the groove very quickly, and Chris helped.  We actually hung out a fair bit without getting back together.  Exactly two weeks after I moved to Edmonton, we were going to go to a dorm party with our friend, Nicole.  We didn't buy tickets because Nicole assured us that we could buy them at the door.  After a few hour of drinking on Nicole's floor, we went to the party room. It turned out that there were no tickets left, but that Nicole's roommate, who had come down earlier, already bought her one.  Chris and I were SOL.  We decided to head back to my place, and rent a movie.  By the time we got home, I was only slightly buzzed, and we started to watch the movie in the dark.  I started to fall asleep on the couch that was adjacent to where Chris was sleeping, and when he  noticed, he came down beside me, and whispered, "Christy, I need to know.  It's been two weeks, and all I want to do is kiss you and hug you, and be with you."  It was so sweet, and honest, and wonderful to hear.  And I really did love him, I just wanted to see what was out there.  But all of the sudden, that didn't matter.  I sat up, and could barely see his face, but knowing it so well, kissed him slow, and then we hugged and I whispered, "how can I say no to you?"  We cuddled on the couch for a while, and it was the most lovely half-hour of my life.  Just being so in love with someone, and having them be so in love with you back.  I wish I could really describe it.  Well, we broke up a couple of years later, and didn't talk for a few years because I was stubborn and wanted to hurt him.  Last year we started emailing, and met each other for the first time in 4 years (OMG!) at Christmas.  He told me he was engaged, and I was really happy for him.  It was clear to both of us that we weren't right for each other anymore - Chris loves small towns and the Conservatives, and doesn't think gays should have the right to marry or that women have the right to choose (did I mention he went to a private CATHOLIC school?), which is the complete opposite from what I am all about.  But I love him still, and I hope that the feeling we shared is the same thing he feels with his fiance everyday, because that was the sweetest moment of my life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend held some good times.  I went into Edmonton to visit my best good friend from undergrad, and it was lovely.  Although I am short, Lori is *actually* freak-show short.  She's 4'10".  Yikes!  She's the only person in  the world I can mock because she's short.  We went for a nice dinner, watched Farenheit 9/11, and then went to my favorite pub in Edmonton, Black Dog.  God, I love BD.  Everyone these is exactly my style.  Evidenced by the fact that I ran into a guy I met two days earlier in Slave Lake, Dustin.  I think I mentioned Dustin in my last log - he is Matthew's friend, who smoked weed with us while we looked at the fullmoon through the sun-roof of Matt's car.  He was there with friends, and we all hung out.  It was really lovely.  And this is what I am talking about.  I meet a guy one day, and two days later, I see him at a bar and he *actually* talks to me.  I mean, he invited me and Lori (who he'd NEVER met) to have drinks with him.  I know I wasn't going to rag on Hali anymore, but in Hali, I have never seen that.  Were we in Halifax, I would have expected him to pretend he didn't know who I was.  Happy accidents and nice people.  And on my way back to Slave Lake this morning, I had three experiences in one hour that made me feel really good about the world.    1.  After taking care in checking my oil, and adding a litre to my mom's jeep *while* being very polite, I tipped a boy working at a gas station.  He was giddy, and so grateful, it made my heart smile.  2.  At a fast-food restaurant, I was a mess, and accidentally dropped my tray into the garbage with my garbage.  When it began to clear my drink and keys would shortly follow, a nice girl who worked their insisted that she would fish it out for me.  3.  I was speeding a little - which I HONESTLY rarely do, and coming over a hill a guy flashed me his brights.  I thought to slow down, but I also thought there might be something wrong with the jeep (it *was* down to it's last inch of oil, so who knows if my mother actually cares for it at all), when I saw a cop just pulling someone over for speed.  It was a good-natured warning.  Thank you Will at the Esso in Westlock, and the brown girl who works at the KFC, and the guy who was driving the slightly beat up old-school orange truck on highway 44, just north of Edmonton.  You all made me happy to be alive today.  When I get back to Hali, I am having Seamus Murphy Byrne make me a shirt that says "I love nice people."  Cuz I do.    (although I would hate to lose the reputation for being kinda insane and a little mean myself, but I digress).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am back in Alberta right now, visiting my family who is dangerously close to pushing me off the edge.  I am also bored out of my tree. Last night, I went to the local lounge with my two remaining high school friends, and some of the people they are spending their time with.  Jamie is amazing - I think the reason that we are still friends is that she didn't put up with the bullshit from the mean girls we were friends with in HS, and I was weird, but still accepted because the most popular girl in school was my best friend back in the day.  In sum, we were both outsiders.    It turns out that me more than her these days.  I get alot of stares when I go back to my hometown.  I think that everyone thinks I am better than them - which I don't in the least. Well, when it comes to their inappropriate use of the word ironic, I do.  But really, how can I judge when the youth were educated by Alanis, who wrote a song about it and still doesn't know what irony is?  Anyway, the local was alright - alot of gossip about people I don't know, or don't know *anymore*.  Then Matthew came by.  I had an after-school job with Matt when we were in high school, and I love him to death still.  We would be a couple if I still lived here, he's so lovely.  We didn't have the same social circle in high school, but Jamie is our link now.  When we were moving from the local lounge to the local pub, Matt was driving his new VW Gulf, and Jamie had some bud and a pipe.  Matt and his friend, Dustin, joined in, and it was a blissful moment.  When everyone around is someone you like, and they don't care who you were in HS, and they understand that things are the way they are - Going to grad school was not a rejection of them, just as getting married or working construction was not a rejection of me.  Letting the roof of the car open up, there was a nice waft of smoke out, and for the first time in ages, I didn't feel like an alien in my home town.  Stare all you like - I am almost the person I want to be.  And closer than I ever dared while living in Slave Lake.  Matt and I once had a conversation about sex at the Deli we worked in.  We were 16 or 17, and his sister's best friend has just told him how she had slept with this guy who came 4 minutes after he penetrated, and Matt was telling this as a funny story.  We were both virgins, and I warned him that he shouldn't judge, because I wasn't convinced he could do better.  He countered that he would be able to last way longer, and when we were adults, and no longer virgins, we would have sex and he would show me.  I tell this story, not because we had sex, or I want to have sex with him now, but because it is so quintessentially Matt. Vulgar, yet charming and lovely.  I wish Matt and Jamie would move to Halifax. Then it would be a great city.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The content of this entry was too infamitory, and might be construed as malicious - which it was not. But after re-reading it, I thought better of publishing the whole thing, and decided to simply publish the following thesis statement at the core of the entry:  I am sooo right all the time.  Seriously.  NOW... I just wish I wasn't so cynical; otherwise, I might have a really great life.  Also,  urlLink Jonny Rocket , your picture is gorgeous (who is your photographer??! Lovely), and I have just added a link to your blog (on the side, too). Everyone should go read it, and leave a comment (or just send out good vibes to make sure he gets his trip).  Ciao darlinks.  And it wouldn't kill you to leave a comment here, too.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ok, I had a fucking rockin' weekend in Toronto.  The t-dot is my new favorite.  First, seeing Martha and Chris was great.  They are some really fun people, and it was so good to see friends from Taiwan (the last time I remember being happy and having loads of fun).  Also, I managed to get some flirting in.  Talking to Martha and Chris's friend, Chris Reynolds, about music, I found out that Reynolds actually knows Manitoba (see previous post "Manitoba" for details).  How cool is that?  Plus, Reynolds admitted that I made him nervous, which I took  alot  of pleasure in.  Finally, I got to see Brad.  *sigh*  Alright, I need to explore something for a minute.  Let's ask the direct question, shall we: Is Brad gay?  So, he is well-dressed, attractive, fit, and does his hair... that would suggest yes.  But he is not actually from Halifax, so attractive and well-dressed doesn't neccessarily satisfy the criteria of gay in Halifax (even though criterion 3 has been met - I have a huge crush on him!  But I am trying to be unbiased).  Also, he  did  move to Toronto, which indicates some kind of underlying coolness about him that might be something other than gay).  There is also AS.  AS is a gay hottie in Halifax, who after the Closing Night party for the Atlantic Film Festival asked Brad if he was gay, and Brad ambiguously answered: "Let's have some drinks and see what happens."  BUT!  Continued to pay attention to AS's female roommate all night.  Hmmm... tough call. When I emailed Brad that I had run into his friend AS, he wrote me back that AS had "asked me if I batted for his team. ha ha ha"  What is so funny there?!  That he asked, or that the question was so ridiculuously phrased?!!  Stop being so ambiguous!  Then, when I am Toronto, Brad asks me to go to Vazaleen (see last post) - which might be "artsy/queer/indie", but is mostly just queer.  So, what do I make of an invite to gay night?  Well, I suppose I might swing back the other way.  But maybe not - Brad has a friend from Germany staying with him, and his friend Flo is trendy (and a guy).  Maybe Brad just wanted Flo to see the trendy aspects of Toronto?  Also, Flo has met a girl that day, and was expecting her to show up later...  So obviously, Flo's not gay.  Right?? Anyway, Martha and Chris live really far from downtown, so we had to leave early (2am) to catch the last train.  When I was riding home, I texted Brad: "That was fun.  Let's do it again [when you come back to Halifax for a visit in September] @ AFF opening night.  We should've hung out more in Hali... ciao.", and he replied: "I miss you already".  What does that mean?  WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?!   Brad is either the most ambiguous man on the whole planet, or the most  unambiguously bisexual  man on the whole planet.  Or else he's a flamer, and I am the biggest retard on the whole planet.  Any way you look at it, we are setting records.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>