<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Particle systems have long been recognized as an essential building block for detail-rich and lively visual environments. Current implementations can handle up to 10,000 particles in realtime simulations and are mostly limited by the transfer of particle data from the main processor to the graphics hardware (GPU) for rendering.  This article introduces a full GPU implementation of both the simulation and rendering of a dynamically-growing particle system. Such an implementation can render up to 1 million particles in real-time on recent hardware. It helps you to dramatically increase the level of detail and allows you to simulate much smaller particles. Thus it goes back again towards the original idea of a particle being a minimal geometry element.  The massively parallel simulation of particle physics on a GPU can be a flexible combination of a multitude of motion and position operations, e.g. gravity, local forces and collision with primitive geometry shapes or texture-based height fields. Additionally, a parallel sorting algorithm is introduced that can be used to perform a distance-based sorting of the particles for correct alpha-blended rendering.    urlLink Gamasutra - Features - "Building a Million-Particle System" 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      July 28, 2004   Sony Profits Soar Despite PlayStation 2  Sony officials have surprised the market by posting an unexpectedly large profit for its first quarter, as the weakness of the yen boosts the value of overseas sales.  The company announced a group profit of ¥23.3 billion ($208.4m) in the three months ended June 30 – a huge increase on last year’s figure of ¥1.1 billion ($9.8m) and well above market expectations of around ¥4 billion ($35.8m).  However, the company’s game division slipped into the red with a recorded loss of ¥2.9 billion ($25.9m) for the quarter – hit by high research and development costs for the PlayStation 3 and PlayStation Portable. This result is likely to be a one off though, with software shipments actually increasing to 38 million world-wide, compared to 31 million at the same time last year.  Hardware shipments are well down to 0.71 million, from 2.65 million at the same time last year, but this is put down to a peculiarity in shipment timings and inventory shortages.  Officials have not altered the company’s full year estimates, which are expected to see an overall operating profit of ¥160 billion ($1.4bn), after discounting ¥130 billion ($1.2bn) in restructuring costs.  Source: Forbes  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More Microsoft news then necessary, every day! How could anyone resist?   urlLink Watching Microsoft Like A Hawk - Microsoft News Watch Site 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An expanding set of tutorials are now available for the free and powerful Tokamak physics engine. The fifth tutorial has just been added, detailing custom terrain callbacks. All tutorials are available from http://www.adamdawes.com/....  http://www.tokamakphysics.com/
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a good glossery for lighting terms you come across in papers.  urlLink Reflectance | Albedo | Diffuse Reflectance 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Radiant intensity - is the radiant flux radiated from a point on a light source into a unit solid angle in a particular direction.   Radiance - Radiance is the radiant intensity per unit projected surface area, where projected surface area is the real surface area multiplied with the cosinus of the angle between the direction of the radiation and the surface normal. &nbsp;Standard unit of radiance is watts per steradian and square meter (W/sr&nbsp;m2)   Radiant exitance - is the total amount of radiative flux leaving a point on a surface into all directions above the surface.  Irradiance (usually Ei in formulas) is the total amount of radiative flux incident upon a point on a surface from all directions above the surface.  Reflectance / Albedo – the ratio of incident luminous flux upon a surface which is reradiated in the visual spectrum  Luminous - Emitting light, especially, emitting self-generated light (as opposed to reflected light). 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HDR Summary Normal texture maps pre-scale and quantize the color of a surface. This in effect bakes in the amount of light the surface is reflecting, at some give time. Once lighting information is scaled and quantized, detail surface information can get lost, especially if the scale value used in the process is very small or large relative to the quantize range. All of this is bad because the amount of visible light that can be viewed reflecting off a surface can vary widely due to camera aperture settings and dynamic lighting. HDR textures solve this problem by storing the un-quantized reflectance attributes of a surface. The reflectance values stored in an HDR texture can be viewed as the ratio of incident light on the surface that will get reflected back. These values will range from very small to very large positive floating point values. The samples stored in an HDR/radiance map are typically relative to the average radiance in the scene.   Benefit summary Large range of light intensities can be reflected from a surface, and the surface will change appearance as it would in nature. &nbsp;An object can go from being dimly lit where not much detail is noticeable, to brightly lit where once hidden details will appear. For example, chiseled details would gradually appear on a dimly lit stone, as a player walked up to the stone carrying a torch.   Camera exposure lengths can easily be simulated, by using a simple function to scale the overall light intensities up or down. When reducing the aperture, and making everything darker, brightly lit areas will stay bright, and contrast in the scene will persist.   Dynamic Day / Night effects could be made easier with a system like this.  Blurring, blooming, reflection mapping all can benefit from HDR, as contrast between pixels is maintained during blend operations.  Texture Costs / Encoding Formats We will need 32 to 24 bits per pixel, not counting an alpha channel.   LogLuv24 The 24 bit LogLuv24 format requires extra processing to transform in to RGB space and may not be practical. &nbsp;It uses 10 bits for luminance, and 2, 7 bit indices for indexing color along with a 16K lookup table. The look up table would be the same for all LogLuv24 textures I believe.  RGBE The RGBE format is a 32 bit floating point format that uses 8 bits for a common exponent, and 8 bits for each color component. This offers about 6 times more range then is needed. We could possibly use a few bits for alpha from the 8, if need be.  References  urlLink http://www.anyhere.com/gward/hdrenc/hdr_encodings.html   urlLink http://www.ict.usc.edu/~jcohen/hdrtm.html   urlLink http://www.anyhere.com/gward/papers/cic98.pdf  p:\papers\bloom and HDR\GDC2004_PIoHDRR_EN.ppt  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Polynomial textures (PTM’s) can encode how light reflects off points on a surface from all directions on a hemisphere. Each sampled point corresponds to a texel in a texture map. The hemisphere of luminance values is represented by a polynomial with six coefficients and parameterized by the light transformed in to tangent space and projected into the texture plane. (lu, lv).&nbsp;   In order to create a PTM texture, you’d have to render a scene or object multiple times with a single light source coming from a different direction each time. You’d need about 30 (!) of these render samplings, in order to achieve decent results.   They claim polynomial textures can encode shading, shadowing, interreflections, & sub-surface scattering. Combined with standard phong lighting they also claim anistropic, fresnel effects can be modeled. They can not encode view dependent lighting information, such as specular.   L(u,v; lu, lv) =&nbsp; a0 lu^2&nbsp; + a1 lv^2 + a2 lu lv + a3 lu + a4 lv + a5 = Luminance   R = R’ * L, G = G’ * L, B = B’* L.  a0..a5 are the PTM coefficients, normally stored per texel.  lu, lv are calculated from the tangent space light projected in to the texture’s UV plane.   Basic Vertex Shader processing  For every vertex, lights are transformed in to tangent space, (from object space?) and then projected in to the texture’s UV texture plane. The 2D lighting parameters are scan-converted and passed along to a pixel shader.   Basic Pixel Shader Processing  Using standard texture coordinates three texture loads are needed, 2 loads for the 6 coefficients and 1 for the standard RGB texture. The polynomial is then evaluated with the lighting parameters from the vertex shader, and the 6 polynomials from the 2 PTMs. This value is then used to scale the texture’s RGB value.   Polynomial Luminance Per Vertex Instead?   I’d think it possible to store PTM coefficients per vertex, instead of per pixel and just do the PTM calculations for better vertex lighting.   PTM coefficients can be linearly interpolated, so possibly these can be scan converted and the PTM calculation could still be done per pixel, with a whole lot lot less data.   Paletted PTM’s?  Yes they can be.   Bump Mapping  There are two methods. Either the surface normal can be calculated from the PTM coefficients, or a LUT can be used to convert a normal to a PTM. The LUT encodes N dot V. Calculating the normal from the coefficients looks expensive.&nbsp; &nbsp;   
    
</post>


<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink DVD Shrink: Shrink your DVDs to fit DVDR! 
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GameDev  urlLink GameDev.net -- Math and Physics 
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3D Math reference  urlLink Game Programming 99 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ALLOFMP3. The Best MP3 Downloads. Full Albums. Music, Soundtracks, Singles, Games. AAC,M4A,WMA,MPC,LOSSLESS,FLAC,MP4,OGG.   This site is AMAZING. Download entire CD's for .01 per MB. Huge audio collection, lots of formats and download options. This well put together site is located in Russia, and I doubt it's RIAA endorsed. I'm guessing the only reason the RIAA has not gone after this site is that it would be hard to shut down, it being in Russia, and they do not want to give them any publicity.   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NewsIsFree is a news portal with an advanced aggregator which lets you browse several thousand news sources and weblog on your own customized pages.   urlLink NewsIsFree: Syndication of 'Tom's Hardware Guide: News' 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Tech Report - NASA nabs 10k-node Itanium 2 cluster   Just think about the amount of heat 10,240 Intel Itanium processors put off....  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jinx - Gamer Geek Hacker Computer Nerd T-Shirts TShirts T-Shirt TShirt Shirts Shirt Hats Sweatshirts Clothes Clothing Gaming Hacking   Cool T-Shirts
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I think Google is just trying to be different. It mistrusts wall street and is trying to distinguish itself. Look at gmail, compared to yahoo mail or hot mail and you get a good sense of the company's philosophy. They are obviously trying to carry this philosophy over in to their financial dealings. I can see this playing out either way: The IPO deal will backfire and they'll end up looking like idiots, or the IPO will be a big success despite their screw ups, and they'll be considered genius. They are a great company and if I had to bet, I'd bet on the later.   How to screw up an IPO:    Do it Dutch! Dutch auction that is.&nbsp;   $100 stock price.   Issue 2 classes of stock.   IPO during the summer when everyone is on vacation   Show contempt of institutional buyers. (Doesn't mention how)    The Full article:  urlLink How Google Has Ruined Its IPO Deal   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Slim Browser - Reviews and free downloads at Download.com   Nice IE based browser that lets you do tabbed browsing.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following is a darkly amusing newsgroups discussion I came across reguarding an adult dating site.   From: natplas@swbell.net (natplas@swbell.net)  Subject: Re: [ASP] ADULT FRIEND FINDER BIG RIPOFF   After 7 months I had no luck. Only one woman wanted to meat me and she was almost 2,000 miles away. The other resonses wante to sell something, mostly their web site or their panties. I think it is a rip off. I had only one local woman respond and she was 100 miles away. turned out she weighed 400 lbs. and wante me to come do her and let her husband watch. She was listed as single.   From: Venture 0 (venture0@aol.com)  Subject: Re: [ASP] ADULT FRIEND FINDER BIG RIPOFF   I have been a member for almost a year. I have never had a single response and all the women I wrote to have rejected me. I signed up back in the days when I was brain washed by the media into believing that no men want large women. I thought to myself, hey even though I am not attractive I do not mind large women so I should have my pick of them. Then I found reality is all women have their pick of men and I do not make it past the first cut of their lists.   If you are attractive you should do fine in any of the services just like in real life. If you are not attractive you just have to pay for a woman's company or find some way to trick them. I am not very tricky.    Just a thought from, Venture0   From: blue_manx@hotmail.com (blue_manx@hotmail.com)  Subject: Re: [ASP] ADULT FRIEND FINDER BIG RIPOFF   I have never used them but I know how you feel. I signed up to a couple places that offered the same thing. Once this girl emailed me her website URL when I got there it said I had to buy one of those adult pass ids in order to see more. So I did. I saw more nude of pics of her. I emailed her to setup an appointment.. well guess what.. I never heard from her again   From: HotHotCoCo (hothotcoco@aol.com)  Subject: Re: [ASP] ADULT FRIEND FINDER BIG RIPOFF   Okay, I'm gonna put my 2 cents in about these posts about adult friend finder. I have an ad on there (and it isn't misleading) and I don't answer about 80% of the responses I get from there... why because they are either vulgar and there some married guy who is looking for a freebie who then gets mad when he finds out i'm an escort... when someone can explain to me why a single woman would want to get involved with a married guy just for the hell of it, please do so,  k? (and don't tell me for nooky... she can find that with someone who is SINGLE!) I have alot of respect for guys who use professionals and would even if I weren't involved in the business.   So my advice to those who are bagging on adultfriend finder; If you are looking for someone to snuggle up with during the holidays, find another site! If you are just looking for some "relaxation" stop trying to dupe the women, it's really cruel to just tell a woman what you think she wants to hear just to get her in bed. You wouldn't someone pretending to like you just to get your money or whatever would you?   And for you guys out there who are complaining about being unattractive, I'll let you in on something.... Alot of women are more interested in who the person is on the inside. I know that I am one of them! So work on who you are on the inside and don't worry about the looks! Spend some time allowing the person to get to know you!   Okay, I'm getting off my soapbox...Happy Holidays to all   From: Bustygirl of Houston (bustygirl@pdq.net)  Subject: Re: [ASP] ADULT FRIEND FINDER BIG RIPOFF   CoCo...thanks so much for saying that!!! I agree wholeheartedly, and am glad someone else finally said it!!! The men in my life have been of varying physical types, but I can honestly say that some of the best relationships I have had (and some of the best sex I have had) was with men who were not the most physically attractive..... a point to ponder for you guys :)  If you are plain looking that does not make you unattractive, and even if you are gorgeous....I would not want someone who did not have a good personality :)   Amber     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink flipCode - Game Development News & Resources 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying to get the blog stuff integrated with my own site.... 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Test 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		  		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Tanabata 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink misawa .			 		 	  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 These would easily mask out some un wanted oders.... 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink DSCN9248 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink pjbeardsley .			 		 	  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 Ripped from the flickr.com site:  "Tak showed me an old issue of Egg Magazine which he brought back from Japan. The theme is "ganguro" fashion (meaning "black face," the girls go for a tanned California look) which was quite amusing. Near the end of the issue was this, info on how to make your boobs look bigger -- I just love her pose." 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Egg Magazine 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink robotgirl .			 		 	  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well after a lengthy an often childish (on both sides) battle over the name Lindows, Microsoft has finally realized that every time they try to beat Michael Robertson in court, they're just giving him more free publicity. This is, of course, exactly what he wanted. So, to just settle the damn thing once and for all, Microsoft has bought out the Lindows name for $20 million. Of course, this works out great for Lindows... er... Linspire, as well. They basically get a $20 million investment with no dilution or strings attached -- plus a bit more publicity due to this deal.   urlLink Techdirt:Microsoft Now Owns Lindows 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apple makes me want to sell my ipod sometimes....  CUPERTINO, Calif. (AP) - Apple Computer Inc. said the company is "stunned" at a move by RealNetworks Inc. to distribute software that lets customers play music from Real's song download store on Apple's iPod.  Apple said it is investigating the implications of RealNetworks' actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other laws.   The company said it was "stunned that RealNetworks has adopted the tactics and ethics of a hacker to break into the iPod."   Apple said it is highly likely that Real's Harmony technology will cease to work with current and future iPods when the company updates the music player's software.    urlLink InformationWeek > Intellectual Property > Apple 'Stunned' By RealNetworks' 'Hacker' Ethics > July 29, 2004 
    
</post>


<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a test post from  urlLink   , a fancy photo sharing thing.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going to give flickr a whirl to automatically post pics to this blog via email. Should be especially cool for mobile phone pictures. 
    
</post>


</Blog>