<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Last year in FL a couple of the awesome kids there showed me this website. I just think it's hysterical... check it out. Buy a T-shirt. Watch the Fluffy Puff Commerical in the Shorts section.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When I was a baby Christian, I thought I had life completely figured out. God was not a complex being - just a loving Lord. God's will was simple, easy to know and figure out. More recently, I've struggled with almost every decision I've made. I constantly question - Is this God saying what He wants? Or is this Satan trying to get me to do something against His will? Or is it just me wanting to satisfy my own desires?   And so in the next few weeks, I have to make another decision - where is God taking me to do ministry with Young Life? Arlington Heights in Chicago or West Plano in Dallas? Or should I stay right where I am in Colorado Springs at the Service Center? I know that God speaks in a gentle whisper - but sometimes I pray that He would just write it in the sky or send me an email.   I suppose too that if we are willing to listen and pray that He will reveal His will - that in fact He let ya know. That also takes trust and faith that He knows better than me. Sometimes, you just don't want to accept that.  Someone once told me that as long as I am seeking Him in my walk and faithfully drawing closer to Him, no matter where I end up, God will bless it. But doesn't He has a certain path for our lives?  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I live at home and while it's probably not the greatest thing in the world to live with your parents, it does have some advantages. For example, my 'rents just got Wi-Fi in our house. Thus, hopefully I will be able to keep up with this silly blog. In the meantime, I'm still figuring it out. I haven't even visited this site since I opened it last December! :) Fun stuff.   If you stumble upon this blog... check out another one.  urlLink Adam Griffin  rocks my face off. :)  
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There have been a few times in my life when I've done some pretty spontaneous and silly things, but this one was a lot of fun. I left work at 5:00p on Friday and drove straight through to El Paso that night from Colorado Springs. Yeah, that was interesting. The first leg of the trip was beautiful - the sun was setting over the Rocky Mountains, weather was perfect. Good day for a road trip. Then it started getting dark - and darker. My eyes started getting tired. But the Mountain Dew and caramel Apple Pops help get me through the night. I pulled into El Paso at 3:00a and parked in a church parking lot. I was so nervous that a cop was going to pull up and think I was a Mexican hopping border so something that it took a while to fall asleep. But I woke up at 5:22a and crossed the border.   Driving into Mexico by yourself at 5:30 on a Friday morning is quite different than it normally has been. I've been to Juarez at least 10 times now. But my one day excursion was by far the best trip I've had. By the time I got there that morning - everyone was still asleep. Juan wasn't awake to open the gate - so I had to hop the fence. Thanks to Tim Kuenker, I didn't rip a hole in my jeans. Seeing everyone there was awesome. I remember some of these friends from when they were still in junior high (like 6 - 8 years ago). Now seeing them all in college, thinking about careers, walking with Christ - it was kick butt awesome. And totally worth the 10 hour drive.   They had already worked on the house the day before and by the time we got to the site - I saw a solid foundation, all four walls up, the roof on, blackboard covering the whole house and partly chicken wired! UNBELIEVABLE that they finished all that in one day. Of course, they had lunch delivered, it wasn't hot at all and siesta wasn't necessary - but come on, none of the houses we've worked on have ever been done so quickly. On Saturday I worked the whole day after only two hours of sleep. Granted I did chicken wire and electricity all day - but it was fun. The entire house was finished by Saturday afternoon at 4:00. Craziness. So, we did the dedication, watched the family and everyone else cry and then headed for Peter Piper's where I proceeded to then pass out on the table.   All in all, it was an awesome trip and will probably be my last with all of those people. Thus, it's bittersweet. Hopefully where I'm going in Dallas I'll find people like those I miss in St. Louis. They are good people.   More later... taking a nap now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I always thought it was quite humorous to think of those people who are running for the border. And of course, we all like to joke of the border towns where all you see is people hopping the fence or swimming the creek to get to freedom.   Well, I'm headed for the border - but not with that attitude. Yeah, I'm going to get in my car after work tomorrow at 5:00 and drive from Colorado Springs to El Paso to meet some friends who are working with Casas por Cristo to build a house this weekend. It's going to be a long day tomorrow, but I'm pumped. I can't wait to get out of this town. So, hopefully I won't run into any crazy Mexicans, but will find my way around fine and that my car won't get stolen. :)   Pray for me! :) I love having the freedom to just get away. I'll be back Monday. Which unfortunately means that I'm not going to get to work on this blog this weekend! Oh well...  Hasta luego! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
              
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is Radar, my little chico de Mexico. He's a lot of fun. But he tends to bring sticks and pine cones into the house instead of chewing on his sticks... mom doesn't appreciate that much. He's a cutie though!  urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
              
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So today I told the guys in Plano, TX that I would love to do an internship with WyldLife... but thoughts keep going through my head ... AM I NUTS? Plano, TX? Why so far away? Why with middle school kids? Why in Plano - where Young Life has really struggled to get off the ground??!?!? So many questions and yet, I have no answers. I also interviewed in Chicago, where - to be honest - I felt completely comfortable. The people were so awesome. It's high school Young Life ministry with kids just like those I went to school with. The Area Director and his wife were kick butt awesome people. But it was almost too comfortable. Knowing me, I need large challenges that will cause me to stretch and grow. Which I'm sure could have also happened in Chicago, especially seeing that I was only 15 minutes from IKEA. What am I thinking?  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I failed to mention that on  Saturday  I spent the whole day with a good friend  Brian Burns  (who is closing on a house tomorrow... whoo hoo). The  zoo  was fun... but not as such fun as the rest of the day. I dropped by his house just kinda to hang out, maybe have a sandwich for lunch and I guilted him into spending the day with me. (Sad, I know). But we then went to  Panda Express  and on the way I convinced him that the zoo would be so much fun. So, then we went to the zoo, had a blast with the giraffes and hippos. Then we went to  Target  because he's going to see John Mayer at Red Rocks next week (so jealous) and wanted to pick up the new CD before the concert. (Actually before Target we went to  Borders , but it was like $19.) So after Borders we got some awesome Mint and Cookies ice cream from  Coldstone  (but were jipped on the serving size). grrrr. Then to Target, where Brian noticed that I was wearing and red jacket and khaki pants and then proceeded to make fun of me the whole time we were there.   From Target you can see  Guitar Center  across the highway. Neither of us had been in a guitar store in probably 18 months, so we went in, indulged a little. Fun times. Then we drove by the  $1 theatre  to see if there was anything we wanted to see... nothing really. I had already seen  Hidalgo . So, we decided to go get food. Then our friend Jena calls and they are going to see Hildalgo in 15 minutes. So, we drop by the  gas station  for cash, get tickets, go inside and I see the movie... again. (It's a good movie, I don't mind.) But Jena and the others never showed up! So then we went to  Macaroni Grill  (where I used to work) for a late night dinner and hashed out some good topics and floorplans for his new unfinished basement. So, the zoo was fun, but hanging out with a good friend all day was better.   Companionship was one thing I was greatly reminded of this past weekend. While I spent most of my time in Florida last year very, very lonely, God has certainly blessed me overabundantly with some awesome friends and people whom I love. The speaker at Pierced on Sunday (young adult worship) talked about the  Oneness of the Body of Christ . When you are separated from each other - there is ache, a longing to be with one another. I'm already feeling that ache about leaving my brothers and sisters here. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My good friend Brian and I went to the zoo on Saturday and I had a blast. I'd been wanting all week to go to the zoo. I'm not sure why except that I could. I thought the weather was going to be horrible, but it wasn't. We had a great time. It started raining pretty bad, but we foudn shelter and then walked around again. It was a good day. The giraffes are my favorite I guess. Probably because they are so tall. :) And I'm not.   urlLink Check out all the zoo pictures.   Their tongues are pretty gross.   urlLink     My new friend.   urlLink     Look at his legs! That is crazy. :)   urlLink     It's Timon!   urlLink     That was my day at the zoo... 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not sure what is up with this town sometimes, but they live in Colorado Springs and just never see the HUGE mountain in their backyard. There is rarely a day that I do not look outside and admire this visible glimpse of God's majesty. But I guess if you live here all the time, you might just get used to it. Lately it's been kinda drab to look at - no snow, almost completely brown and dry. Not the greatest snapshot, but still majestic.   It was so amazing though... Last week you couldn't even see Pike's Peak. The weather was awful. Thunderstorms (which I love), lots of rain (which we need), gray skies (which reminds me of Wisconsin), and lots of fog (always fun). Plus it was COLD... like February, "what the heck is going on?" cold. But the mountains were surrounded by clouds -- just covered in dark clouds. Almost since I came back from camp it's been this way. But then, we got a little break in the weather and as I drove to work on Monday or Tuesday, I glanced over toward the mountain on the beautiful sunny morning...  The whole top of Pike's Peak was wrapped in a blanket of snow. I mean completely covered. It was probably more snow than in the winter (seemed to me anyway). It was so beautiful and gently reminded me of God's grace.   Often times we are going through some pretty tough storms in life. There are things just downpouring on us - career, family, friends, our spiritual walk. During those times we just ache, yearn for a little bit of sunshine. Seems like you can't even see ten feet in front of ya because the fog is so thick. Let alone can you see God in such times. It seems like He's abandoned you or doesn't care about what you are going through. It's like He's not there.   But then, the rains stop, and the clouds begin to roll away. A beam of sunlight peaks through and suddenly it's blue skies again. And then you see that God has been there whole time and He's been working during the tough times. Even when we thought He had left us bone dry - but instead covered us white as snow. I was blessed by that glimpse of grace a few mornings ago and felt I needed to share it here.   The last couple of years have been quite difficult for me. I felt at times that Jesus had abandoned me in my walk with Him. I realized more and more lately that He was there, blessing me the whole time. For that I'm grateful. I'm grateful for the place He's brought me to so far in this journey. And I know that even when the clouds are blocking my view - God is still there.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So tomorrow I'm supposed to be making another car payment, due the 24th of each month. grrrr... BUT ... guess what...  I ALREADY PAID IT OFF!!! Last month. So exciting. No more car payments. Whoo hoo. Anyway, I thought I'd share my excitement with you.   So, when do you pay off your car lease? Leave a comment. Winner gets a prize. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not sure if I know what I'm doing... but I moving away from Colorado Springs... away from the mountains... away from awesome days like Saturday when the clouds just kinda settled on the hills of Pike's Peak. It's going to be hard to look outside every day and not see a HUGE example of God's majesty in my backyard. :*(    urlLink     Just some random pictures I took while driving around... It's been raining and starting to green up around here... awesome.   urlLink     Yeah... ran in to this guy... weirded me out--he wouldn't stop taking pictures of himself. Wacko. There are some strange people in Colorado too... maybe it's a good thing I am leaving. :)  urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When you start to really complain about gas prices or insurance or bad drivers. But you know that it's getting worse when you start to get super tired at 9:00 p.m. and tell your friends it's your bed time or that you don't feel like going out. What's up,  pathetic?! :)   But to top it all off, when the ladies in the office start to set you up with guys you've only met for 30 seconds - YOU HAVE ARRIVED! Don't get me wrong, I love the ladies in my department (good ol' Mission Assistance at the YL Service Center). But when you start to feel like the only way you are going to meet that special someone is by your older lady friends setting you up - well, it's just heartbreaking.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
              
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Do you ever wish that you could harness the small of the rain in a bottle and market it? I'm sure some people have tried - but I know it's not like the real stuff. Especially when it's been hot for a while and the rain hits the pavement. Reminds me of when I was a kid... It doesn't rain much here in Colorado. I guess it's good that I'm moving to Texas then. um... yeah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Camp Eagle was a blast. I am very excited about working with these kids in Plano. God certainly affirmed that for me last week. Below are just a few of the pictures I took. If you want to check out the whole lot of them, check out this link  urlLink Kimi's Photo Albums . Then click on Camp Eagle.     Beautiful Princesses outside of their palace  Caroline, Emily, Kimi, Amanda and Megan  urlLink     Amanda and Caroline  urlLink     Goofy Dan  urlLink     Don't mess with Scott the kick butt dancer  urlLink     Casey  urlLink     Emily the Princess  urlLink     This is Megan... isn't she cute?  urlLink     Don't mess with dese guns  urlLink      Fighting Ninjas  This is all of the West Plano group last week. They are awesome kids. Yes, I'm the one that looks like Shrek.  urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If I ever had doubts that I'm supposed to go to Plano West WyldLife for my Young Life internship... those doubts are gone! :) We had such an awesome week at Camp Eagle in Rock Springs, TX last week. Thanks for all of the prayers - God certainly answered them because all four of my girls accepted Christ (a couple were more recommitments) on June 10 or 11th. The Holy Spirit was certainly working and some truly awesome things happened, even in my own heart. It was amazing. And as soon as I get my computer back, I will post some pictures and some stories. I am so excited about Plano West WyldLife - I can't even begin to tell you! :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm at New Staff Training for Young Life in Portland, OR. We're staying at Multnomah Bible College in the city. It's beautiful out here. When I was flying in, there were clear skies and you could see the huge (random, but huge) peaks of Mt St Helen's I think it is and some other stinkin huge mountain. They were so beautiful and just the mountainous area out here. Amazing. My mom said that I wouldn't want to move to Texas. But that plane ride in was just amazing.   So far, everything with training has been great. I'm meeting a lot of people who are just wonderful. I volunteered for the Chapel committee which has been fun to plan a worship time with other brothers and sisters.   Unfortunately, I was here not even two minutes stepping off the bus and I went to pick up my suitcase (right around 50 pounds). When I lifted it up, I stubbed my toe and ripped part of my toe nail off. Yeah. Total gross, it was bleeding everywhere. And now I've had a bandage on my toe (which just throbs most of the day) and so everyone asks me, "What did you do to your toe?" So, I'm the toe girl. And since there isn't some great story with that - it's not a good thing. Now, every time people see me, they are like, "How's the toe?" Sweet.   I am having a great time being around other Young Lifers. I'll definitely keep you all updated on my toe adventure. God is ministering my heart by these people and by our classes already. I feel at times as though I've gotten myself in over my head, considering I haven't led a club ever in my life and really haven't been around Young Life but the last five months. So, pray that God would provide protection over my heart and help me to guard my heart from those times when I know Satan is just trying to bring me down. It's been a struggle and a slight discouragement.   My roommate, Cayla, is great. She's also going to be doing wYLdlife accept with urban kids. She's a lot of fun and we already have a good time together. I'm excited to be in the same training class with her (only two girls) and to experience these next two years with her as we learn and are stretched by God in wYLdlife.   Well, it's late. And I need to get some sleep. Back to college dorm set up - community bathrooms, echoing hallways. It's a good time.   Sincerely,  The Toe Girl 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm in Colorado for just a day before I take off for Young Life's New Staff Training in Portland, Oregon. I am so excited, but it's 12:30 and I haven't posted an entry about my week in St. Louis, I've just finished packing and I still have a paper to write for class - I might be pulling an all nighter. Grrrr. My own fault I suppose.   I do have some pictures I want to share with you. My week in St. Louis was great. Prolonged because there are so many people there I love and also because I had to get the window tinting on my car fixed. So... I only had one day at home before I take off again.   Today we got a new puppy. I think my mom and I decided that her name is going to be "Leta" (pronounced "lee-ta"). We have no idea if it means anything, but it was the name of the street the people we bought her from lived on (awkward sentence). Here she is... (this is a close-up... you can just barely see her eyes closed and her little nose. She was sleeping in my mom's purse when I took this.)    Leta   urlLink       Here are some pictures from my week in St. Louis. I went to see a friend, Jed Maschke, marry the beautiful Anna Hasty. Hung out with some friends from high school and my church, St. John Lutheran in Ellisville. I also went to lunch with my brother, Kevin. It was a good week.   My friend in St. Louis I've known since high school... me, Jake, Jenny, Erin and Ben.   urlLink     Ryan Peterson... what else can you say??   urlLink     This is Olivia Klemm... a good friend of mine from college that I haven't seen in a while. It was really good to catch up and talk with her at the wedding.    urlLink     This is my twin brother Kevin. He still lives in St. Louis and just got a new place near Clayton. He's a kitchen manager at CJ Muggs. He's a lot of fun.    urlLink     This is my good friend Erin... I miss her terribly, but it was really awesome to hang out and be goofy with her this week. She and Ben are getting married this October and I have the privilege of being one of her bridemaids. :) I'm very excited. Isn't she so good looking?!   urlLink     This is Jake. He's 6'4"-6'5". We discussed the idea that if we got married and had kids - that all the boys would turn out to be really short and the girls would be 6'. It was an amusing conversation.   urlLink     I did also get to spend some time with my friends, Tim & Tim. They are good guys - Laura Mueller and I watched  Top Gun  at their new house in St. Charles for the fourth of July. It was a good fourth. Although, I think my ears might still be ringing from surround sound.    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       St. Louis is a fun town. But the people actually make the city for me. Outside of the horrible drivers and road rage... they are good people. I'll post more when I get home. I have lots of pictures and good times.   I also figured out a new name for my website... more on that later though. :)  Hope all is well. Sorry I'm slacking.    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's kinda scary if you ask me, but I'm moving to Dallas in about 9 hours. Right now, I'm still packing up my car. I'm going to make one pit stop at the Service Center in the morning and then head out for the two lane roads between here and the Big D. I'm excited, but also a little bummed. Tonight was hard, even though I really didn't let anyone show it. I've been so blessed to be here and a part of a community at Pierced Chapel. I'm overwhelmed right now. I think tomorrow, as soon as I leave those Service Center doors, I'm pretty much going to lose it.  A friend of mine is taking a nap right now, waiting for me to get done packing to see me off. :) It's the little things that I'm going to miss.  I'll check up on blogging as soon as I get settled. This last month has been so incredibly awesome. It's great. God is great.  So I'll see ya in Texas.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>