<Blog>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        "Chalo line mein khade ho jao, madar**** tu kya hero hai, ja line mein khade ho ja   Chapra was at his voiceferous best, trying to come to terms with the new found image of a MIP(most imp. person...... as far as the second years go), I guess even that was not enough to overlook the tensions and headaches he "acquired" tackling the acco issues of the new second years in the hall.   Chapra:   abey tu isko jaanta hai kya?   Me: Nahi   I am stared ... it slowly turned into an emotion that could represent a hybrid of intolerance and anger. Although a bit delayed, I pick up the cue.  Me: No ....No SIR.....   Thankfully so, or so I believed. Unfortunately, the sling was already in motion and the late re-address of sir, well, could do nothing to prevent the first slap.   Chapra:   "Good .... aab se tum dono roommates, C-101"     Giddu T, hence became my first roomie, though only for about 6 hours. We exchanged our roomies, and dips replaced T. Slowly, I shifted my baggage into C-101, attired in formals and shoes and helped a few seniors to shift to their wings, was already inviting a few stares.  Some Senior:  abey tere ko main force toh nahi kar raha hoon na ... mere samaan carry karne ke liye....   Me: No sir Senior:   Dekh tere ko koi problem hai toh bol, mere ko apni zindagi barbaad nahi karni hai, samaan carry karwake   The attitude was set, what you want is what you get or being computationally corrrect...WYWIWYG. We were supposed to set our limits for OP, which in a way was good but I guess it did dilute the whole process.   Senior:   Chalo beta log, thanks ... aab neeche jaake line mein khade ho jao    All us second years, who helped the seniors to move are not horizontally aligned. Splash! Two bucket full of water completely drenched up ... not a pleasing feeling ...  Dips: abey bagal ka room khali hai .... chal apan log lock kar lete hai    After a lot of deliberation, we thought that it might be right to approach chapra and take his permission to "occupy" C-102.  Chapra:   Khali hai kya?    I and dips nod obdiently.   Theek hai, le lo ... lekin sala agar koi naya student aayega toh adjust karna padega...    Yes Sir.... and C-102 is officially MY first room in Patel Hall now. After shifting into my room, finding a cot in B block ground floor, I am now totally equipped - a bed, a table, a chair and a cabinet:).   It is 4:10 PM, Kattu, would begin his address in about 10 minutes, we quickly ruch to the ground between B and C blocks, facing the ground floor catwalk and having mukhops look over us from the first floor one...    
     
    
</post>


<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Mama, Mama! The show has started!" screamed A from his lawn, unable to contain the excitement of his debut as a i-day firecrackers viewer. The noise of commotion: Mom.A, Dad.A, ElderBro.A and ElderSis.A rushing out to join A, fired the alarm for the neighbors, Neighbors.A.   The whole block is together, cakes and pies included, watching the sky on fire. Jokes - that caused constipation till now, were flowing free. Pizza and pop complimented the aroma of camarderie.   The air smelt Davidoff. The air smelt Dior. The air smelt CK. The air smelt green.   Every event complimented the other in manner that it begged to be called picture perfect......       Picture perfect till   ...       "Mama, Mama! The show has started!" screamed A from his lawn, unable to contain the excitement of his debut as a i-day firecrackers viewer. The noise of commotion:  Mom.A, Dad.A, ElderBro.A and ElderSis.A rushing out to FETCH A, fired the alarm for the neighbors, Neighbors.A.   The whole block is together, cakes and pies included, KNOWING that the sky is on fire. Jokes - that constipated the carrier till now, DIGESTED. Pizza and pop added to the STRANGE SMELL of suspicion.   The air smelt SWEAT. The air smelt SWEAT-ER. The air smelt SWEAT-EST. The air smelt CELLAR.   Every event complimented the other in manner that it begged to be called picture perfect..    Only nobody hopes to be a part of it.    Crazy that a few fanatics,Q, can change so many things in so little time, whereas the a subset of the complimentary set, F', still hope that India would beat Australia at least in the ICC tournament. It would not be long though for F' to dissociate themselves from the men in blue if they abuse the Aussies physically. Me hopes the same would happen to Q. Quoting Louisville cardinals: "Dare to play fair" may i add "and we would show who has the balls"!!!         

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Seems to be VHP and Bajrang Dal's famous phrase. Fine, hypothetically let us assume we will "force" them out of India. I hope these dumb fucks - the Bajrang dals and VHPs, will agree that the security of our country should not be sacrificed. So, if all the muslims leave will these nitwits join our army . Will the coward-on-throne Thackarey join the army? Will he allow any of his kin to join the army?? I guess not, after all someone has to look after his empire. will the dastard Modi have the courage to face the bullet or at least the difficulties of the army? Nope, he has a state to rule and yet dear brothers and sisters of india, these are the people who "rule" the country, what an irony.   A person who has no atrributed record of patriotism is preaching it ?? Am i missing something? Hello, who is this media obsessed " I am the saviour of hinduism" thackarey? would someone please tell him to shut the f*$% up and mind his own business and let me live my life. Who is this Modi to tell me whom to include in the society and whom not to?   It's high time for the desi crowd to give these i-am-good-for-nothing-so-i-would-preach idiots the finger and lemme hope I don't have to wait for ages for this to happen.    Another blog that happenned about an year ago. Althought this blog expresses pretty strong emotions, I have let it stay unaltered to represent my feelings at that time.    

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was quite perturbed when I heard this from sales woman at the video rental shop, Christina. A reference to the two recent hindi movies - Paap and LOC, got me to think - how true. Echelons ago, at least that is the time I would like to believe, when I was all of five or six, when there were no computers, no cell phones, i heard India and pak were at war ... and still we are at war. Uncomfortable, as it was already, she fired an instantaneous query, "why". As if that was not enough, the final nail was drilled in soon " Were you not the same a few years ago?" Yes Ma'am, true we were, with all disdain to the nationalist and jingoistic politicians, we were, but thanks to the wilful, if not, evil politicians - it is the brothers in arms - albeit arms of the other kind.  Three and half hours later, with LOC uncontrolled, wonder why there was such a disparagement for life. I don't know much about the way a soldier feels, but I would still wonder - is a piece of land worth the multitudes of sacrifices. Maybe it hurts a soldier's ego more than anyone else to let go, but methinks, with greater conviction, that it is time that we say- do we need to carry it on only for the politicians? Have they allowed our soldiers to go on operate as they wish? Have the politicians given them the independence? Are the forces pleased? If I understand my two good friends from school days, it reads a big NO. So, why do our friends, our brothers need to sacrifice for politicians.... are THEY worth it ??    This was blogged ages ago, when I was more fresh with the GRE funda. Easily visible by the generous use of terms that evade my comprehension now!   

						
</post>


<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah! Parag is getting married, 't was fun talking to him and neha. The date is June 20th and I would be there, hoping every wingie makes it. After the indian team reverted to its form of losing test matches, this was a welcome end to a decent year.  (around 42 minutes left for the year ;) ) The marriage is in Ranchi, also dada (Swaraj Mukherjee) is also getting married on Aug 20th. I would refrain from talking about the probability of me attending this marriage though.    Back to Parag's marriage, I am happy to see at least one relationship from KGP is working out and I would say that the three days prior and three days post are booked for the celebrations.   Probability treated me well today, understood what I was reading. I think I would be a probabilist some day according to my sixth sense. Amen ;) One the qual blues are over, I am gonna paint the city red. Did i mention, red is my favorite color and my fave mobile the ferrari spider that I would own (hopefully before my grandchildren are born)! mark my words mate, this would happen someday!  U know what I think I deserve a ferrari, now that it has steadied itself as my wallpaper for 2 months, I think I and ferrari are kind of made for each other. Let's say Amen to this as well!!   Ha ha ha .. ho ho ho .. whatever, driving me nuts thinking what a probabilist would look like in a ferrari, I don't want to imagine it, it would decrease my sixth sense of being a probabilist to to fifth or maybe even a fourth ... shuck I am writing gibberish ... lemme quit!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After being privy to hazaar plannig for marroing G and after listening to numerous late night ads about finding the G(spot), I finally have the G-Factor in my life. Thanks to blogger, I now have access to Gmail (karumanchi.remove.this@gmail.com). Yes! Yes! Yes!   It was something real unexpected, I wanted to blog and lo behold! I find myself filling in the username that I want to use to access the G-mail! What a shock maaan!!  1 GB of pure, unadultrated space to store all my mails!   I guess there is some about the letter G - they say you get high on G, you bet I am. They say you are satisfied "at" G, do I dare to differ? 1 GB (another G), I mean 1 whole GB, or as tanks might put it 1 fucking GB of webspace - how do I celebrate thee. Back at kgp, it would have meant an instant daru party with dhoom pichak dhoom/prodgy/metallica blaring off to glory in the background, but here at Purdue - there is no loud music, no wing parties, no  eggies/cheddis even ..   WTF, let me continue on my movie marathon, reservoir dogs to celebrate my G-bond!!!   Jaane kahan gaye woh din .... 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        originally blogged on 12/03/2004    This day i am totally screwed up... have a project on security analysis and a take home exam of time series,.    Actually econometric time series sucks and sucks big time... people do all sorts of useless things to get to useless conclusion that will never ever be explored by anyone else except desperate students who are forced to look into them. Actually an econometrician is a either a very paranoid person or a person who wants to show that he knows every test for a unit root under the sun. How else can one explain every theory going to 10001 tests before it is approved ... and even it is approved .. someone else would come up with a slight modification and satisfying +1 tests and lo behold ur theory is antiquated. i mean if people are so underconfident of their own theories, I don't know how they will ever convince other to work on it... whatever this course has been the worst course in my life .. will make sure no one else is made a sacrificial goat to this utterly depressing subject!  let's talk security analysis... great stuff .. had fun coding altho' was up all night but then really enjoyed it ..   might look nerd-ish talking gibberish a out some time series and security analysis ... but then there comes a time where every one has to be a nerd .. and this is the time for me ..
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Future Rear-viewed&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two things that have never happened and two things that will never happen are the sun rising in the west and indo-pak truce. It's politics time time of the decade and all the parties have almost readiedtheir platform. With the virtue of being in power, BJP is one up - the indo-pak peace talks.   The logic of the leaders across the borders beats me - We have identified the problem area, but we will not talk about it. Gosh! it is like knowing that a school kid is weak in maths, but since he is not understanding math, let me teach him history and geography and make him a mathematician. Like, we know that the boat has a hole at the bottom, but as we cannot plug it, we will try to plug the holes in the side - *WOW*. I would hate to term it as some form of logic- it defies its meaning even in the weakest sense of the word. And still we have the world applauding the "trendsetting" trip of one Mr. Vajpayee to Pak. Give me a break will you, these gimmicks have been a part of indo-pak peace talk folklore since I remember and they have not been one bit useful for the common man, although it has ensured a lot of political gains.   I hate to appear like a punchline-lifter, but I have to quote Wipro: "Apply thought"? What is the point in killing the water snakes in the pond and proclaiming it is as safe when you know there is a king cobra lurking down under? We need to understand that as long as the kashmir issue exists, we can never have peace with pak. If the leaders have the guts and the balls, let them start the peace talks by starting with kashmir. Resolve kashmir first an then everything will fall into place. If we don't resolve the kashmir issue, then it will draw your attention through another kargil.  High time you stop misleading the common man of india and pak with these peace talk and holding hands antics.  Better still leave the kashmir issue to us - the citizens of india and pak. I have many pak friends and I guess they are few of the nicest ppl I have come across. There is no hatred between us, except for the cliched "breaking of ice". We could never comprehend why ppl fight over a small piece of land. As some one rightly said in telugu "desam ante matti kaduoye, desham ante manushuloye" - Country is not about the land encompassed but the people who inhabit it.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK am done with studying Stats + CF at Purdue. Graduated with a Master's degree in Statistics with emphasis on Computational Finance and completed my mini-MBA as well. Dude, the mini-MBA was an experience! I never knew that I had so much motivation to class for 5 hours and then complete the homework for 4 hours, all for 10 long days, just a week after my finals! KV tussi GOD ho yaar...  I am going to louisville for my internship at RQSI (a small hedge fund) and plan to be there till august ... hopefully kentucky will treat me well. One thing I always knew walking into KGP was that it would change my life, now I realize how. I don't have to search for an apartment at louisville thanks to Subhashis Satpathy, a senior from IIT KGP who has kindly agreed to take care of the makaan part of the need trio "roti, kapda aur makaan".  Presently, I am in a marathon of movie watching. Since yesterday I have watched blues brothers, gone with the wind, the 39 steps, A beautiful mind, Shrek 2 and scary movie 3. Ideally I would finish with reservoir dogs / yuva. Let me hope for the best. I truly deserve this after the marathon sem crediting 6 masters courses.   Talked to bapu yesterday and made plans for a cali trip, knowing bapu a bit too well, I think it would be in my interest to consider this trip a volatile one. I hope D and Parag also come over, so that we can pull in tanks and muthu uncle and have a semi reunion.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        shock : abash, agitate, anger, antagonize, appall, astound, awe, bowl over, daze, disgust, dismay, displease, disquiet, disturb, electrify, flabbergast, flood, floor, gork, horrify, insult, jar, jolt, knock out, nauseate, numb, offend, outrage, overcome, overwhelm, paralyze, revolt, rock, scandalize, shake, shake up, sicken, stagger, startle, stun, stupefy, traumatize, unsettle!  G-shocks: G-abashs, G-agitates, G-angers, G-antagonizes, G-appalls, G-astounds, G-awes, G-bowl overs ..... G-traumatizes, G-unsettles!     Shravan got married!   Abu Saleh got married and is in Venezuela.   Siri is "engaged".  Pratyush is committed and posts a "kiss" on orkut.  Vivek mails after 2 yrs.  Portugal beats england in Euro 2004. (7-days delayed telecast by FSWLD, Tue 8PM). Someone do something about decreasing the lag time ;)!   WTF? 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      kudos to moore! might try to meet him tomorrow .. if my time permits;)  working in the weekend sucks bigtime.   Kashmir rocks! Awesome chicken chilli.   Ranjana di's party was fun, Sesame's food - 4*'s!  Ignorance by Milan Kundera  The excerpt of the week:   Those who were unlucky in life in spite of their skills would eventually rise. The lucky fool might have benifited from some luck in life; over the longer run he would converge to the tate of a less-lucky idiot.    Nassim Nicholas Taleb in "Fooled by Randomness" 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ends two days later ... mid week blues, yellows and greens!!   Hate Subhasis da for changing my style. Unable to shrug off the brevity punches.   The 3 Mays: May weekend come sooner. May the weekend camping be blessed by my presence. May you see portugal lift Euro 2004. The Brazil factor!  and the ole Miss: Miss getting up at noon on wednesdays.  and btw, Kobi sucks! He is useless without Shaq! GO Kings!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      if(Today != Weekend){   Get up at 8 AM;   Rush to Work;   have Coffee;   Code till Lunch;   Lunch @ Jersey Mike's;   have Coffee;   have Coffee;   Code till 6;   back from work;   if(today!=Friday){             Prepare dinner;             Eat Dinner;             Read a Novel;             Sleep at midnight;                   }   else PARTY;  }  Systematic or Monotonous? Did someone yell Subodh -   "theek paanch baje"  yoga and all ?    Paapi pet ke liye sau avataar.     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "And Chantal revises her old metaphor: it is not an immaterial, poetic rose fragrance that passes through men but material, prosaic salivas, which move with their army of microbes from the mistress' mouth to her lover's, from the lover to his wifem from the wifeto her baby, from the baby to its aunt - a waitress- to the customer whose sop she spat in, from the customer to his wife, from the wife to her lover, and from there to other mouths and to others still, so that everyone of us is immersed in a sea of salivas that blend and make us into one single community of salivas, one humankind wet and bound together."  excerpts from Identity - Milan Kundera  This is a must read it now book!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "When he did that, I understood the sole meaning of friendship as it's practiced today. Friendship is indispensible to a man for proper function of his memory. Remembering our past, carrying it with us always, may be the necessary requirement for maintaining, as they say, the wholeness of the self. To ensure that self doesn't shrink, to see that it holds to its volume, memories have to be watered like potted flowers, and the watering calls for regular contact with the witness of the past, that is to say, with friends. They are our mirror; our memory; we ask nothing of them but that they polish the morror from time to time so we can look at ourselves in it."  excerpt from Identity - Milan Kundera  Adapting the same thought process, friends, I feel, are more like milestones, they announce the emotions that you had exhibited, they share the past to intricate details in lengthy conversations, they show the same passion they did ages ago, but, in fact But, they have no clue on the voyage thereafter. The acknowledgement of the "distance" between seperate paths, is however, resisted with billions of lucid details of the diurnal activities, as if the conversations were a past-reverting process. Processes that can transport you into the past and fortunately or unfortunately, terminating usually, with the hang-up tone.   May I Hypothesize, The "anthology" of one's life is quantified by the packets of friends that he gathers in his journey.     Now wonder they say, count your life with friends...   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There was a time when alankar used to be the confluence of the best lit talent of KGP and if you could get your article published in it for an arm or a leg, you would have viewed the crutches in the green light. Now, we don't have enough enthu in people to host all the editions of alankar online, what a pity. I hope the plan with percy and suppandi works are we are able to have the publication online. It would be shameful if those contributions find no place to call home, especially when their quality could, on any given day, compete for the best awards around the globe.   I am getting hooked to Kundera, on the "Identity" track now - long distance relationship and "the works". This weekend, I would be done with this and the Da Vinci stuff.   News of Modi ouster again. They would "discuss" and decide that Modi, was actually not responsible for anything that spells Godhra.  Dude, either the BJP politicians have no balls or I have been taught a wrong definition of the word -"secular". By the power invested in me by myself, I would clear all the allegation towards, Ishaque Ma'am, my english teacher.     May Modi be ousted, do some social work, get blessed and go to heaven! I don't want to live with him in hell!        One more weekend, One more GP, One more win for Schumi :) QED.  Going out to check out 4th street Live today! My first visit to the "Hard Rock Cafe". After being hit by the snobbish value of the infinitely many tees and mugs, it's hight time I get into the club. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Slowness" - this title is so imposing that you'd feel Kundera wants you to read it slowly, but actually he forces you to do that. A real neat read! The juxtaposition of two centuries in the very end, kind of makes you realize that even after major innovations in science, tech and punishments for DCs in kgp, the basic needs will remain unaltered.  Re-run of sex and the city this week I am informed. WHAT? I was never a follower of the series, but hey! I could take a quiz on TV programmes and schedules any day, any time even in my sleep. and now someone tells me that ads have been flooding the idiot box since a month, and I have not a clue?? I say hey! what's going on ? There was a time I believed that live without TV might be close to a modern algebra class at 7:30 in the morning, but I guess the hazaar time I am spending on books is priceless.    And then, Lakers lost!  Thank "god" I was not there to witness this triump of the good over evil:). I mean how much good can you pack in a series. All things sweet, victory of hardwork over talent, team spirit over studs, yada yada yada ... give me a f**king break, infact gimme two. This series was fixed, everyone was bought over, malone - payton were much more richer than they'd have been after winning the ring, and hence, in the end, it was money that came out victorious:). I hope this goody-goody angelic feeling doesn't creep into F1 and have the minardis and the BMWs taking over.   Had hyderabadi biryani at louisville yesterday at a newly opened place called Taj India. Was good, nto as good a "the" biryani at bawarchi or paradise, but it was much much better than the ones I had in the past one and a half years. Hyderabadi and a biryani are truly made for each other.    I Hypothesize  :   if a hyderabadi really really like a gal, he would call her biryani.      OK! now either I am missing hyd big time or I am getting into talking trash again. So, either ways, I better quit! 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just about three hours and a successful attempt to clear the 100 mph threshold is all it takes to go from Lafayette from Louisville. I was convinced that I really missed lafayette, turns out that I "missed" only the people, not the place. I know, I know, fifteen days and me already ranting about missing factors in life, but giving its due credit, this has been that period of time when self-sufficiency forced itself into existence and hence, I hypothesized that this place might be "more" special to me. I guess nothing beats good ol' kgp, Louisville would be a close second though.   Back to the drive, half way into it, I realized that I kind of missed the after-work fun at Louisville,so then, could I be attached to a place so soon or on a higher plateau, could I be attached to a city in the first place? Is the attachment to a place totally independent of the friends there? Certainly kgp seems to contradict these claims blatantly. I would not miss cheddis or for that matter eggies or vegies, if it were not for the people there or would I? A decent topic to reflect upon, however back to Louisville after work fun.   Officially debuted wine tasting and live Jazz on wed. night with Rajarshi da and Subhashis. Raj da is CS, NH 1992, Inter IIT and TDS member,  and hence, if I may,  a great "experience". With Euro 2004 and F1 tomorrow, guess it is the time for "kick" in the fast lane. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Warning : This blog might be a bit too technical for the uninitiated.  After about four days forced haitus, I guess I just could not resist my temptation to blog. I think I am kind of forcing myself to blog now, but then now that I have started enjoying it, might as well go ahead. I have started learning C#, all by myself. Now, this is not a great achievement if you were Madda*, but forcing oneself to ponder why a certain "Hello! World" program would not run (after meaningless modications), is not my definition of fun.    Paapi pet ka sawal hai, toh karna hi padega... aur agar kar hi raha hoon toh  might as well enjoy it, and as they** say, if getting rape is inevitable, lie down and enjoy**!!    On a tangential and unrelated plain, I am kind of thinking of learning to play golf soon. My short cricket has been standstill after I migrated to Louisville, I have been hearing hazzar stuff about Kentucky Cricket Club and the Asha Cricket Tournament, have to check 'em out.     Long time no gultness, http://www.bullithera.com, is hosting info to download new gult movies (and also some hindi movies, I believe). Pirates of the Arabians, check it out but make sure that you pay royalty to the movies that you liked by going to the theatre near you to watch the movie :).  Yeh unke pet ka sawaal hai   !     * Madda: KV's dictionary states that madda is a "fictitious" person who knows (or has the ability to know within a week's time) all universally available software/programming languages.   ** An old saying that I would comfortably, without any guilt, attibute to the seniors (generic term) of Patel hall.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I guess, as I have guessed infinitely many times before that there is something strangely mysterious about this letter G. For, one G also be forced to represent Guru. Now, that I have unofficially accepted my post of GoGA - Guru of Gmail Aspirants, I am planning to start a society, AoG, abbrevating the "Art of G-ing". Also, to stay up with the spirit, I would be called KV baba. Bolo KV baba ki ........Jai ....   I have already given enough G-yan to hazaar people (ok make it 15), on how to get a G-mail account, now I think I should charge for it. For kgpians and boilers, I guess I will not charge anything, se se senti and all! As rajat kapur would say ... Yaar phatichar! tu itna sentimental kyon hai yaar ... seesh, I loved the TV shows of yester-years, phatichar, mungerilal, tehikikaat et al. I wish they would come out on DVDs too, Phatichar - Season 1, types.  Weekend's almost over! Recharged my batteries decently, have slept for 20 hours in these two days *WOW*! Gotta go ... sona hai ....    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wish it were true! Desperately coming terms to the great welcome provided by the "industry". Created a website as vast as my own in a day!! This is a real demanding world. Learnt dreamweaver as FrontPage was not available and I guess with facts that before I "graduate" from this internship, I would learn all the software that is used in the finance industry.  Have to rush home now, going with Subhashis to play soccer and have also mega plans of reading "Da Vinci Code". Now that I have heard so much about it, I guess I would give it a try. I don't have the patel hall's green number 10 jersey or for that matter the blood-red #7. I am sure that I would have lived upto the reputation of ronaldo/romario wearing them;) chalo then.... gooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaallllllllllllllll.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Tune mujhe C sikhaya maine kuch nahi kaha, Tune mujhe C++ seekne pe majboor kiya, phir bhi main chup raha,   lekin aab, aab jab tu, MFC, ATL aur .NET seekhane ki baat karta hai toh bhagwan, meri bhi yeh baat sun le  "pehle se lagi padi hai, itna toh mat mar yaar"   - KV's antaratma  Thanks to my, never pronounced but duly practiced, sepertation or for the lack of a better term, divorce from the latest in software lingo, I now have the daunting task of learning C++. VC++, .NET, MFC, ATL and C# all in a week's time, okay maybe if I beg with a senti face, I might get two. And I have to confess,  meri buri tareh se phati hui hai...   My great expectations of a peaceful sailing have crash landed, but then, I had to face the world some day or the other, had to learn all the C and dots somethings some day or other, let it be today!  If I have any sense of estimation, I would require two months at the least, but then you never know ... wtf, I have madda's inspiration and being his deptmate I have to live upto the expectations. Anyone reading this post and wanting to offer any kind of advice on how to go about in this process, would be truly appreciated.   For the past two days I have gone to sleep at 1 AM and woke up by 6 and in the process getting more convinced that this internship might just bring about the much needed discipline in my life.   Bolo bapu maharaj ki ... jai ..    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wasn't me who said it. These were the words that followed the famous "I am the best boxer in the world" quote by Ali. Now that Louisville is my home for the better part of two months, I am kind of liking this place and might add, been treated well by Louisville in the past 22 odd hours. Subhashis is one of the best hosts I have met, we went down to Kashmir for dinner yesterday. The masala chai was AWESOME... so the tip for the day goes   Louisville > Kashmir > Masala Chai   Started "work" today and thank god, no deadlines to meet as of now. The environ is excellent, mega helpful people esp. Sean (who is my immediate senior) and Chris & Tom, whom i report to. Now for the reason why they receive these accolades ;) flexi hours and no monitoring of internet usage. I hope I would not be the reason they start it. Have cut down myu pace at orkut and am checking my mail with one-tenth frequency.  Started to read this book by Sandipan De on IITians, for an alumni of kgp it is hazaar nostalgic. Good thing about Subhashis' place is that there is no TV, I can catch up on all the reading I want. And yeah Lakers won yesterday, I always knew that I had it in me to pick the champions. Guess I should try my luck in the Kentucky derby next ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Change of origin from (110E.Columbia #202, 47906) to (1848 Frankfort Av #3, 40206) with infinitely improved aesthetic appeal. No more gastronomical appeal - would beat everyone for fastest delivery tho'.   Work working on me. NoLunch++ thanks to C# and ADO. The # of TLA's I have learned in the past couple of days > my old list. How about AFKFAFM due Tofer: away from keyboard for a few minutes, an SLA classified as TLA under some complex classification theory.     The next statement from Natwar Singh " We regret the killing of the three indian hostages". That statement should absolve him for taking a decision of not to take a decision.  Gult Blues 2 happenned. Hyderabadi => a decent laugh!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Radio-Head prefers Bong's call Papa Romeo Alpha Sierra Hotel to Kilo Victor, but only on the waves.  Skipped lunch. Annadata Namo(m)Namah.  Kentucky temple and Sambhar. Radha Rocks.  15000 people in KY, IN still without e'city. thanks to thunderstorm.13July2004.  Is it the # 13 or is India more cool? Power restoration time: two days.  Miami Heat supporter ++. Shaq Rules.    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Neruda week and as Bong says, TISA Pablo.  Pablo Neruda.  Pablo Picasso.  Juan Pablo Montoya. Oops my bad.   The world converges, with removable divergence, below as the best by Neruda, may he RIP.     Saddest Poem  		 I can write the saddest poem of all tonight.   Write, for instance: "The night is full of stars, and the stars, blue, shiver in the distance."  The night wind whirls in the sky and sings.   I can write the saddest poem of all tonight. I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.  On nights like this, I held her in my arms. I kissed her so many times under the infinite sky.   She loved me, sometimes I loved her. How could I not have loved her large, still eyes?   I can write the saddest poem of all tonight. To think I don't have her. To feel that I've lost her.  To hear the immense night, more immense without her. And the poem falls to the soul as dew to grass.   What does it matter that my love couldn't keep her. The night is full of stars and she is not with me.  That's all. Far away, someone sings. Far away. My soul is lost without her.   As if to bring her near, my eyes search for her. My heart searches for her and she is not with me.  The same night that whitens the same trees. We, we who were, we are the same no longer.   I no longer love her, true, but how much I loved her. My voice searched the wind to touch her ear.  Someone else's. She will be someone else's. As she once belonged to my kisses. Her voice, her light body. Her infinite eyes.   I no longer love her, true, but perhaps I love her. Love is so short and oblivion so long.  Because on nights like this I held her in my arms, my soul is lost without her.   Although this may be the last pain she causes me, and this may be the last poem I write for her.   - Pablo Neruda  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Dosa  Thank god it ain't kgp. The name doesn't instill panic, and after BNS, doesn't demand respect.    The blog title though is dedicated to the plain and the masala kinds.   4 plain, 2 masala and a cup of coffee. Dinner.com. Radha is a real good cook.  Bong, still on indian lag and dubai dreams, woke up at the right time to hog. Me wondereth: would the olfactory work when we are asleep?    Tuesday dinner woes! Dial K for Kashmir ;)!     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One universe. And the UFOs. One world.And Mars. One life. And the Near-Death-Experiences. One Career. And paradigm shifts.  One heart. And bypass surgeries. One relationship. And "the" ONE RELATIONSHIP ......  .......that haunts you. Day after day, Month after month, Year after year, Relationship after relationship.  Diamonds are forever. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      New blog: http://teblind.blogspot.com.   Roti's published stories ++. http://www.jackmagazine.com/fictionrgupta.html  kerry + edwards => Richie Rich, a [poor little]/[rich] guy. methinks its a winning combo. All jokers of the world unite.  Chida-Mohan: sexy budget (everyone is aying that). grrr : tax on stock transactions, grrr++: reduced interest on NRE accounts.  More books this weekend. Sleep. Sleep. Sleep. Sleep. Kashmir.     
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Frida:  Mal and Kiran pickup at Indy. One more acci on I-65 : Driveway to hell (or heaven for me-hates!). Delay factor - 2 hours. Missed great lunch by half an hour. Screw 65.   Lafayette: Bball. Chutan arrives. Hum Tum and Madeera :). No! Not a Bagpiper ad!  Sat: Good Morning at 2 PM. Chalo Chicago. Hey there - Santosh, Sriram and Madan. Madeera ++. Chicken 65. Butter chicken. Biryani. Amar clearing Cathy's misconceptions.  Sun:  Aurora Temple, Downtown Chicago, Gharib Nawaz. The only thing worser than boddu behid the wheel might be muthu behind the wheel. :)  Mon: Dev. Back to Louisville.   Total Lack of sleep: 12 hours. Total Driving: 20 hours. Remembering moments of kgp: Timeless.    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>