<Blog>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Helloz 2D-ians...esp. Sze Jin...Adeline's b-day (8/3/04) is coming horz...so,yah...=)  By: Amanda
      
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hElloz...muahaha..missing all those from 1D - 2D peepz...all e bezt for e upcoming E and A Math paper...muackz...  By: Amanda
      
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      thanks for irving nices word hope u all come back here to see if there is a furture gathering when all are adult and can see porn   By: Glenn
      
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To all 1D-2Dnians... We have re-done this website as this is a new year... Hopefully we have more people coming to visit this website now ;-) This is a place where all you guys can come together and leave a message at the tag board at the bottom right hand corner... If you're interested in joining our blog team, u can leave a message in the tag board in the bottom right hand corner and address it to us (gan, glenn and me)... So do hope u guys will enjoy ur stay here as we have now loaded a song into this site for listening... Do hope u guys will come in often and not let our time spent here creating this site be wasted...   Thanks for visiting our site and pls leave a msg...  Also thanks my blog team-mates (Gan and Glenn) for contributing together this site...   Enjoy Ur Stay!! :-)  By: Irving
      
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      SONG CHANGE!!!!!!!  VOTE FOR YOUR FAV SONG ON THE TAG BOARD!
      
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Glenn mrs solastri is droping to 3e3 so i pity the fools....no lah she was a great teacher and she just wanted a class that could give her a better result let hope 3e4 can passs the test without her....Glenn will be feeling the pain
      
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Attention!!   There are rumours that our Miss Solastri is going to drop either 3E3(my class) or 3E4(last year 2D) ... Any1 wif info pls tag the board!!! It would be pretty sad if she would drop 3E4 as she won't be able to see her own form class.  Cyrus
      
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Congratulations!!!!  We have our 100th visitor for this blog and it is ... ME!!!  Tomoyo "100th" Mayuki (Az)
      
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey ya... I heard there is going to be transfers between Hammers & Slackers!!! ...DETAILS PLZ!!!  Cyrus
      
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DEAR MR CHEE YONG  as u are not  part of  our 2d wonder full class i suggest u not ppost here and find some other blog to show  and forget this blog URL THANK U for your time taken for this  Glenn 
      
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      TOmorrow school open sad i was lazying artound today i rushing with home work any wone is the same as me
      
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hElloz...gUeSS wHo'z biRthdAy is cOminG up neXt??....Salihin's birthday...it's oN tHe 19th March...whiCh is yesterday....HAHA!!!...okie..sorry 4 not keeping u guys informed ah...pai seh...anyway...hE is hAvInG a chAleT as East Coast 2day...so, yah...can join if u guys want...for Ganesh's info...Salihin lykes this gal called Seow Hui n bOTh of tHem hAve tHe samE birthDatE leHz...hEEhEE...okie...take cAre u Guyz...Happy hoLidays..2 days more...*sob sob*
      
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      O-kay...solved the counter thing...  -gan-
      
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1xolevel 1xmath paper 1xnews paper aticles  do 5 unknow word go to www.dictionary for that 1xjournal refelct review replan 1xlit things 1xpshycia 1xchec 1xperimer english all of chapter 1 1xbook review  dear 3e4 this is our home work list thank me if u like it by glenn
      
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The day has come the march holidays.......we must use this time wisely and i wish u all good luck rememder the hreat of 2d cannot be broken   By: Glenn
      
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok....changed song...it's "where is the love" by black eyed peas original version...it is different and it does not feature justin timberlake as he's gay....lol...so,enjoy and have a good march holiday people...   ps:If you want the version with justin timberlake,let us know by tagging the board...  By: 3!!|m|5t
      
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      how was the run nu guys at funny thing happen can repot?peace out
      
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      me too glenn.. i also feel like walking.. but it ends at 5pm and i want to leave at 5pm.. so hopefully will be in time.. anyway good luck to those who r taking part in the competition.. ;-) the mass runners have fun lor..  By: [NCC](CPL)Irving KW
      
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i cant run i wish i could go to x country race i remember how me and ganesh used to walk to gather........maths dun worry is not the end........i belive that u guys are smart people so can make it some thing big in furture.....i am furture lazy bum.....wednesday got basic test how the hell do u test for basic mad.....bty big fish is not wroth watching2/10 stupiud story line ....next moive butterfly effect mauch thanks for reading..  By: Glenn
      
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      maths paper alright lor.. graph qn quite ez.. nvr do 2 qns minus 7 marks!! :|... otherwise alright lor.. shud passed.. yea got x country and make up lessons.. bz week up ahead.. mon common test for physics.. no tham to study ;-).. take care + study hard..   [NCC](CPL) Irving
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hElloz people...how was e Math paper??...freaked out anot???....relax alrighty??...heeheee...next friday got Cross country at Macritchie in the afternoon...and next Saturday there will be schooL to replace e lessons we lost during LOTR day...take care...*hugz*  -Amanda Lee
      
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      GOod luck to all of you guys who are writing your math test today...  GAN
      
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok.. got that..   Irv
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To irving:I've sent sze jin the invite...if there is no error,then he'd be joining us...  also,i see no error in the tagboard....so,start chatting again....  ps:glenn,put ur name after u post and dont 4get 2 update us on new movies...  Gan
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      gan.. wats wrong wif the chatterbox?  to everybody.. sorry for any inconvenice caused, the chatterbox will be up again in a while.. thank you/  By: Irving
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      in the class of 3e4 i vey happy to say that 2d people are dam togather.....i hope this blog can make our relationship as long as your part of 2d u have every right to post here.....bty all the boys were to gather right did we hate any one in 2d last time please post your memories
      
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      sorry was at tution can some one tell me my job   By: Glenn 
      
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmm.. glenn somethings u can decide but something u cant... haha.. ok gtg eat my dinner liao.. gan see the chatterbox and ur email inbox.. sended some msgs to u... take care folks... byez for now... :-|  By: Irving
      
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yeah we must get sze jin and adeline togather so that sze jin can finally be a man post your plans or idea i will decide who the best one.  By: Glenn
      
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Epl Weekend    Scores for top 5 sides:   Arsenal                                 5-0                                     Leeds Utd  (henry 4 goals, pires 1)  Chelsea                                0-0                                     Everton FC   Portsmouth 1 - 0 Man Utd  Steve Stone (36)     Liverpool 0 - 0 Fulham   
      
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hEy...seems lyke no one updated pple lyke Ganesh abt e soccer thingy...aniwae...for everyone's info...the Hammers played wif 3E2(my class) guys...on Good Friday...n they won with a score of 7-5...fantastic playing guyz...although e score difference shld be even bigger lahz...  There will be another game coming up...unsure of e dates...but will keep u guys updated...btw...Hammers are making a new jersey...Nike 90...Blue colour...so yahz...  take care people...=) -amanda lee
      
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thursday 22/4, Sec 3 camp at near lim chu kang.. be there by 7.45am.. other details will be informed later..  by: [NCC](CPL)Irving
      
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Soccer Update.  Hammers(7) 7   :   5 Ex-2C AllStars(11+-) Salihin 3,Brice 1,Lip Tiong 1...Cant remember whu scored for them...
      
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      AManda updates us on the upcoming birthdaes,irving tells us any events coming,glenn rates movies 
      
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Ya!!!  On the 9th of April(Good Friday).There will be a friendly between Hammers Vs Ex-2C.Can our manager please give more details on it and also, whats with "Birthday Calender" and "Event List" ???? Whats those??  Tomoyo "Az" Mayuki
      
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY YA!!!  There are rumours that Hammers and Slackers are merging!!!!Can someone pleaze tell me wats happenin wif Slackerz!!!?!?!  Tomoyo"Az"Mayuki
      
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The New Song Is Heyya By Outkast......Enjoy.....  PS:Admin,Please Update The Birthday Calender And Events List
      
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DERS A NEW GAME AND ADVERTISEMENT(OLE!) IN NIKEFOOTBALL.com!check it!ITS COOL...e game si lyk pinball..!v fun...haha...thrashin' henry's house!  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      anyone hu hates man utd and has a friendster account...plz add a "friend" called man utd sux!hahaha...aniwae arsenal linked 2 kaka(can tt b possible?)man utd sign alan smith and set to sign heinze(sux)...liverpool linked 2 signin' valencia coach benitez since houllier has been sacked...liverpool set 2 sign cisse n alotta players since e thai pm is goin' 2 take over liverpool...chelsea linked 2 drogba after shevchenko signed a new deal wif milan instead of movin' 2 e roman empire...newcastle and boro linked 2 kluivert,man city linked with reiziger...barca linked 2 benjamin...hope arsenal will sign kaka and sneijder/joaquin(:P:P:P)!
      
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        HAMMERS VS 3E2(dUnno wHat nAme)  well well well...2day was a holiday for many of us...we didn't have papers so we didn't haf to gO to scHooL...tHey hAd a gAme at tHe Bukit Batok field...although a lil lousy...11 VS 11...4 spectatorz...it was called a Barbie Doll match cuz many of 'em got injured...n e game was v dramatic...maybe got Mediacorp contract...keke...joking lahz...  anyway...Hammers won e game...yes...again!!...tHis tiMe they played only 45 minutez...2nd half was a walk over...3E2 didn't wanna play mahz...  score: 4-1 ->Irving, Shawn, Nizam, Farhan(penalty),and Fazlan  injuries: ->Johnathan, Jian Wei, Daniel(finger), Nigel(ankle), Joel(ankle), Brice(kenna studs at the ankle) and Salihin(crampz)...     spectators: ->Aqilah, Maimunah,Azliah n Amanda...
      
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OH MY GOD MAN!!! IVE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS DAY FOR SO LONG!!!! FINALLY EXAMS ARE OVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! time to have my month break man! ive work very hard and hopefully the results will show! too bad 3e3 has a dnt paper tml! ;-p haha.. take care everyone ! have fun
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Ya'll!!!  Juz here to wish best of lauck for anybody takin E X-ams and to tell ya'll that I'm am officially(lyk president's aproval...) in the National Day Parade 2004... WoooHooo!!! so most prob i won't be free on Sat's & Sun....SO dats all and i wont be online for the next week and so..and Gan, CHILL!!  Peace! Cyrus
      
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      har...aft months of hardwork i finally came here..:P...UrCh!n!ok...arsenal jus 1 match away frm immortality...man utd shd lose 2 millwall in e fa cup final...i tink arsenal's title presentation on martin keown's testimonial match...ranieri expected 2 b out and mourinho in...arsenal linked 2 frey,niemi and etc....inter and newcastle r faves 2 land alan smith...boro 2 land viduka...paul robinson 2 go spurs...arsenal expected 2 offload kanu and wiltord...mexes to liverpool/arsenal?cisse 90% chance 2 go 2 liverpool...alryt tts all 4 e footy update!
      
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At this time,i would like to welcome sze jin to our blog team..YEA!!!
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WAD HAPPENED 2 SWEDEN?!feel lyk whackin' up e dutch!wah liew!so tyco....sweden shd progress n win e euros...but becoz of e dutch...haizz...make dis tournament end so early 4 e swedes...nvm...holland will lose to portugal aniwae!haha...but realli i believe the czechs will win it....when dey losin',dey will fight back...such a quality team shd win it...2 bad dey haf 2 face greece in e semis...my 2nd fave team...haizz...y not meet at e final...:'(....nvm...nw is "Go CZECHS Go!"  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      helloz...anybody moaning cuz England losing to Portugal??sob sob...i m...i woke up at 3am n saw tt e score was 1-0...Michael Owen...keke...yah yah...but they had to draw at 2-2 even after extra time was given...  Then there was e penalty shoot out...i dun blame Beckham for missing...cuz i think he was feeling pressurised...so i dun blame him for missing e shot...  He-he...i think Ashley Cole n C.Ronaldo so funny...they kept following each other...looking 4 Ronaldo??...juz look out 4 Ashley Cole...everywhere he go...Ashley wanna follow...keke...  anyway...since England is out...who do u hope to win this yr's Euro Cup...i hope Holland/France...  take care people...school is about to start liaoz...=)
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey Folks  I bet you all are watching the  euro 2004 ...So,we would like your thoughts....Who do you think will win the EURO 2004? Post it in the Chatbox....   PS:Sze Jin,dont write until so much -___- 
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      sorry...ydae my bro use e com e whole dae...i din get 2 touch e com at all.... Switzerland(Out) 0-3 England France 2-2 Croatia Denmark 2-0 Bulgaria(Out)
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- PORTUGAL   1-0   RUSSIA '7 Maniche ::The Portugese played SLIGHTLY better than the Russians. ::Maniche did well to score on the first touch after a pass by one of the Portugese players. ::The Russians were later invaded by a raid of attacks but after that they had a few chances too. ::The Russians,before half-time,can count themseles unlucky for their goalkeeper was sent off for handling the ball outside the box but the referee' decision was harsh as it was an unintentional handball.  Full-time report:- PORTUGAL       2-0       RUSSIA '7 Mancihe '89? Rui Costa ::Nothing much to say...Portugal dominated the match. ::The Russians are struggling maybe because of them playing with 1 man less. ::The Portugese kept on attacking until the 89th minute where their efforst paid off.A fine move by Rui Costa and Ronaldo,Rui Cista passed to Ronaldo when reaching the box and Ronaldo ran towards the byline and cross to Rui Costa who only need 2 tap it in.  Conclusion:Well,what more can i say?The Russians are out of the tournament.The Portugese...well,they've gotta perform better than today to beat the Spanairds.They've gotta win that match so they have to create more chacnes for the strikers.Sad case for the Russians,a glimmer of hope for the Portugese.Let's see whether Spain or Portugal will qualify with Greece...  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- SPAIN         1-0      GREECE '30+ Morientes ::The Greeks didn't deserve to go down. ::Both of them played equally well.Both had a few chances too. ::Morientes capped a fine move when Raul capitalised on a poor pass by the Greeks.he back-flicked the ball for Morientes to shoot past the keeper a curling shot. ::The Greeks later had a chance which was well-blocked by Marchena.  Full-time report:- SPAIN         1-1         GREECE '30+ Morientes            '68 Charisteas(or smth) ::The Greeks fought hard for this draw. ::They did really well,resisting Spain's attack and a good performance by Dellas and the goalkeeper again. ::The goal came out of nothing.It just suddenly went to the striker's feet and he did well to shoot it past Casillas' legs. ::The Spanish attack after the goal and came close to scoring at the period. ::At the last few minutes,the Greeks did really well to keep the scoreline 1-1.  Conclusion:The Greeks can congratulate themselves for this hard-fought draw.The Spanish now have to win Portugal as the Portugese would be expected to win against the Russians at the next match showing later.The Greeks will have easier opponents,Russia while Spain and Portugal has to fight it out in the next match.Congrats to the Greeks as they really deserve to qualify for the quarter-finals after two good perfromances.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- GERMANY   1-0   NETHERLANDS '34 Frings ::It was an agressive and competitive match where both sides didn't deserve to lose. ::For the first 10 minutes,the Dutch dominated and controlled the match. ::At the next 10 minutes,the Germans began to have equal possesion with the Dutch. ::At the 30s,the Germans began to have more control over the match and broke the deadlock in the middle 30s when Germany got a free-kick from outside the box at the right side.Frings swing the free-kick and reach an unintended target..the goalmouth!The ball went in and it can be blamed on either van der Saar or the defence for not covering the far post.Generally, think it should be the defence at fault. ::After that goal,the Germans defended well to keep it free until the half-time whistle.  Full-time report:- GERMANY    1-1    NETHERLANDS '34 Frings        '81 van Nistelrooy ::Netherlands played a lot better but kept on trying but the German defence kept on frustrating them. :: Sneijder and Overmars were the sparks after being brought on in the 2nd half. ::Germany played really defensive and it was really hard for the Dutch to break their defence as it was very organised. ::Although the Dutch dominated much possesion in the second half,Germany had a few chances missed by Kuranyi and Ballack etc. ::When it was the last 10 minutes of the game,the Ditch suddenly showed the urgency of need to win the game. ::van der Meyde ran down the right flank and crossed inside the box and i have to admit van Nistelrooy's striker instinct showed as he was under pressure from Nowotny/Worns but managed to hit the ball into the net. ::The Dutch kept on pressurising the Germans until the final whistle was blown but they fail to hit the target.  Conclusion:This is a fair result.It was expected,wasn't it?This will boost the both sides' chances of qualifying although the Czechs & the Latvians should not be underestimated.Their next two games is against the Czechs & the Latvians.I believe that the Germans & the Dutch can beat them both and pregress to the quarter-finals.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_ 
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      New template....also,thanks to sze jin for giving us an uninterrupted,excellent coverage of the EURO 2004
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- LATVIA          1-0          CZECH REPUBLIC '45 Verpakovskis ::Surprise,surprise.Czech dominated the boring match but are at half-time tralining 1-0!!! ::The Czechs dominated the match but couldn't score against the plucky Latvians. ::Latvia only needed 1 break into the Czech defence.Stepanovs put a beautiful pass forward and the Latvian left-midfielder put in a cross which Cech should have dived for it and Verpakovskis ran to it and slot it in. ::The Czechs leave the field at half-time shocked.  Full-time report:- LATVIA         1-2         CZECH REPUBLIC '45 Verpakovskis           '74 Baros                            '85 Heinz ::The Czechs were lucky. ::The Latvians defended well until Baros scored at the 74th min.They were kind of demoralized by the goal. ::Baros scored from a goal scramble.The corner came into the box and was poorly cleared and Baros took advantage by chesting it and ramming it into the goal. ::Then came the decisive moment.At the 85th minute came a corner then it was another goalmouth scramble.Then there was another poor clearance and when the goalkeeper ran back to his goalposts,Heniz blasted a shot near the top corner and that sealed the Latvians' fate.  Conclusion:Well,the scoreline isn't surprising so the Czechs have a headstart to their Euro campaign but they have to finish their chances when given as they had 26 shots but only 2 goals.The Germans' and the Dutch's defence is tighter and the Czechs will have lesser shots so the Czechs have to be wary of that.The Latvians,well i thought they came here as extras but they showed that they're not that easy to beat after all as the Czechs have to fight hard to get the well-earned three points.Congratulations to the plucky Latvians who at least put up a good fight.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- SWEDEN       1-0       BULGARIA '32 Ljungberg ::It was a fair contest as both sides had almost equal possession. ::But Bulgaria started their game faster and nearly scored in two occasions. ::The Swedish didn't had more chances than the Bulgarians. ::But the Bulgarians had three yellow cards compared to Sweden's one. ::But when the chance came,when Lucic launched a ball across the Bulgairan defence to Ibrahimovic,he sprint to the box and crossed a low ball only for Ljungberg to tap in as he trailed Ibrahimovic's sprint.  Full-time report:- SWEDEN       5-0       BULGARIA '32 Ljungberg '57,58 Larsson '78 Ibrahimovic pen '91 Allback ::WOOHOO!!MY FAVE TEAM!!! ::Sweden outclessed Bulgaria in the second half. ::THE LARSSON SHOW. ::Larsson was superb and showed his world-class striking when Edman put an inswinging cross right in front of Larsson and he put in a goal by a diving header.Beautiful. ::Wilhemsson charge into the Bulgarian penalty box and put in a middle-height cross from the right and Larsson scored with a fine volley. ::Then,in the 78th minute,Ljungberg ran past the Bulgarian defence and at just inside the penalty box,a Bulgarian defender slid in and Ljungberg fell,causing a penalty.Ibrahimovic ram it past the keeper although he dived to the right side. ::In the final few minutes,Larsson passed a through pass through the Bulgarian defence and made Allback free.Allback ran to just outside the box where the keeper ran out and he ram a high shot.Although the keeper managed to fingertipped it,the bal went in and sealed a miserable day for the Bulgarians.  Conclusion:Of course i am damn happy.My favourite team won!lol...ok...serious.The Swedish now top the group with an 'a lot better' goal advantage than the others.This made me confident that they can qualify for the quarter-finals.They showed what they can make the grade as they showed great teamwork and great individuality by some players.With Larsson in top form,Sweden have a good outside chance of winning the Euro.Take my words,man.Bulgaria is in deep trouble.They better find a way past the Danish because after the Danish would be the Italians who are the favourites in the group so i think Bulgaria can be counted as hopeless case.
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- ITALY 0-0 DENMARK ::It was a boring match as the Italians always do. ::The Danes played better than the Italians and I was surprised by the sublime skills of their wingers,Rommedahl & Jorgensen.(too bad Gronkjaer wasn't there) ::But the Italian defence,as they are known(water-tight),just will not let Denmark have their break. ::Italians played their usual game of "making their opponents think they are playing well and score 1 against them" but so far Denamrk has defended pretty well especially Sorensen,Helveg & Laursen. ::Helveg had 2 beautiful shots just skimming the bar.  Full-time report:- ITALY 0-0 DENMARK ::A good performance from the Danes as the Italians fail to break Denmark apart as what pundits expected. ::The whole Danish team did well while the Italian strikers(Vieri,Cassano,Del Piero & Totti) kept on missing and could not break the deadlock. ::A very normal match where this is Italy's most famous scoreline.  Conclusion:Italy must be the more disappointed lot as it is a match where they are expected to win.The Danes must be happy with the scoreline since Italy is the toughest in the group.Congrats to Denamrk who did really well while Italy must win against Bulgaria or Sweden in the next match to fufill their full potential.Adding on,i will say that Vieri should be dropped.He is old,slow and kept on wrong-timing his runs.Cassano mustn't be too rough or he will only get cards but hes one to look out for the future.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_ 
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- FRANCE   0-1   ENGLAND                '38 Lampard ::France stunned by England. ::Lampard scored by heading an inswinging free-kick from Beckham. ::The French played well but not better than the English.The Englishmen's play were superb.The French could not play their usual game of quick passing as Lampard and Gerrard did well to cover the midfield. ::Some of the French players disappoint(e.g.Henry,Zidane) although the whole team is to blame. ::The English who played brilliantly were Lampard,Gerrard,Scholes and Cole.They attacked as a foursome and did well. ::The French better wake up or else prepare for a disappointing start to their Uro 2004 campaign.  Full-time report:- FRANCE   2-1   ENGLAND '91 Zidane     '38 Lampard '93 Zidane pen ::France in the second-half did better but still not good enough to beat the stubborn English defence. ::The English defence played well for the 90 minutes. ::Zidane and Henry played better in the 2nd half. ::In the 1st min of extra time,Heskey fouled Makelele just outside the box and Zidane took it superbly with a curling shot past James,who was staring at it. ::Then at the last minute of extra time,the shock came when Cole wanted to clear the ball but Gerrard hit it back for James when Henry was there walking around and he sprint past James and James had to foul him and caused a penalty. ::Zidane slot the penalty in and the whole crowd was stunned by the 'crazy 2 minutes'.  Conclusion:The French were really lucky but it was also England's fault as they didn't score after scoring just 1 and leading only by 1-0.They defended well but thye should have tried to score at least 1 more goal as they should know the French attack is one of the best in Europe.The French took advantage of the two set pieces rewarded at the dying minutes and it was really the Zidane show.Beckham should also be blamed for MISSING A PENALTY so he also should be partially blamed for the defeat.Now France get off to a winning start while England grieve over the deafeat after leading for such a long time.Now England must buck up get points from the Switzerland & Croatia game to at least qualify fir the quarter-finals.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- CROATIA 0-0 SWITZERLAND ::Very quiet match. ::The Croats had more possession and chances but didn't score. ::Had 1 chance where it hit the post.The Swiss can count themselves lucky.  Full-time report:- CROATIA 0-0 SWITZERLAND ::Not much highlights can be given. ::Swiss did better in the second half but also,as the Croats had done,didn't take their chances.  Conclusion:This result is not favourable for both Croatia and Switzerland since they are both the underdogs in Group B which contains the two other big teams,England & France.They both get only 1 point each and a win might help 1 of them to have better chances of qualifying from the group.Fromt this,I can infer that France and England look set to qualify from the group unless their match later also ends up a tie.But even if it ends up as a tie,they still have the upper hand as they have much better squads than Croatia and Switzerland and both England & France will face both Croatia & Switzerland after this match.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_ EXCLUSIVE EURO 2004 COVERAGE BY URCH!N:)
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      LATE REPORT:- SPAIN        1-0       RUSSIA '70+? Valeron ::Didn't watch the match.Was tired after the Portugal VS Greece match.
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Half-time report:- PORTUGAL  0-1  GREECE                '7 Karagounis ::Portugal stunned by Greece. ::Greece showed more hunger than the Portugese. ::Good performance shown by Greece especially Dellas,Karagounis & the goalkeeper(Nikopolidis?) ::Bad performance from the Portugese especially Figo who shown that he is already passes his prime.  Full-time report:- PORTUGAL   1-2   GREECE '90+'Sissy' Ron  '7 Karagounis                  '50+ Basinas pen ::'Sissy' Ronaldo pushed a Greek player and caused more trouble than help.(S)he should go home. ::Basinas finished the penalty coolly with a near top-coner shot. ::Portugese fans must be cryin' and cursin' at the sissy. ::Sissy managed to get back his pride after causing the penalty by scoring a header from an inswinging corner.  Conclusion: A shock result to me as i thought it would be a draw.Greeks look good to qualify for the quater-finals.Portugal has to pull their socks up.Their old players(e.g.Figo) are passed their prime and the younger players look hungrier(e.g.Ronaldo,Deco).If they still don't win against Russia,they would be in deep trouble.They have home advantage and if they still don't win.They shouldn't even host the tounament.  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hw were ur holidaes so far?haha...4 me it was goin' out n doin' hw...sigh..such borin' holidaes as owaes...mayb w/o e hw i might feel betta!:P:P:P...aniwae hw r all of ur holidae hw cumin' so far?haha...surely der r alotta ppl hu r still in a holidae mood(me included)!!!hehe...i m oso here 2 inform ur tt i wld b ur EURO 2004 reporter!half tym reports n full tym reports!hehe...oso add sum1 called "Wadeva Tanglin" in friendster.com coz tt is our class in friendster!its 2 reunite 2d 2003 as a class...so plz join n oso when ur join...drop by a testy alryt?  _::signin' off:UrCh!n::_
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of my best hols in my life!!... Juz came back from Bali.. over there juzt enjoyed e sun, sand, & SURF!!!... went surfin 4 2 days straight... now whole body sunburned..HAHA!!!...Olso had 1 of the best on-flight meal of my life .. lol .. didn't noe aeroplane food tasted sooo nice.. e beaches at Bali are awesome and the waves are giant compare to S'pore... waves there can go as high as 5metres while S'pore waves only until knee level...  Cyrus aka SurferDude !PEACE!
      
</post>


</Blog>