<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This entry breaks the "Uganda-only" rule, because I've quickly come to realise that this journal inadvertantly also deals with questions of free will, moral choice and breaking out of the so-called 'box'. Many friends and passers-by have written to me about these issues just in response to these first two Uganda entries.  In the spirit of national day in Singapore, political changeovers and time for national and personal self-reflection, I've decided to take a quote from a good friend of mine's favourite novel. Phil, if you're reading this, you probably know it by heart already.   "Winston, sitting in a blissful dream, paid no attention as his glass was filled up. He was not running or cheering any longer. He was back in the Ministry of Love, with everything forgiven, his soul white as snow. He was in the public dock, confessing everything, implicating everybody. He was walking down the white-tiled corridor, with the feeling of walking in sunlight, and an armed guard at this back. The long-hoped-for bullet was entering his brain...      He gazed up at the enormous face. Forty years it had taken him to learn what kind of smile was hidden beneath the dark moustache. O cruel, needless misunderstanding! O stubborn, self-willed exile from the loving breast! Two gin-scented tears trickled down the side of his nose. But it was all right, everything was all right, the struggle was over. He had won the victory over himself. He loved Big Brother."     The totalitarian communist state may not be such a clear and present threat in our lives any longer, but other similar man-made cages encircle us and threaten to suffocate our beliefs and integrity (intended or otherwise).  In any case, Happy National Day to everyone in Singapore, and I really would like to see this place grow and mature into a state I can truly be proud of and want to live in one day, in the not-too-distant future. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whenever the subject of Africa (here I mean sub-Saharan Africa, excluding states like Egypt, Morocco, etc) is broached in conversations, the responses I get from people I talk to tend to fall into one of several categories.  1. The total-ignorance response - “Africa? Oh okay. Wow.” (Awkward silence) 2. The Afro-pessimistic response - “Africa? That’s really brave of you. But why the hell would you want to go there and meet lots of black people? There’s nothing to be gained from there - you think you’re some kind of hero? You might get a disease or even die a horrible painful death.” 3. The pseudo-Africanist response - “Africa? Yeah I was there a couple of summers ago. Amazing place. Visited seven countries in six weeks. (Starts rattling off the whole Lonely Planet Guide on the spot as proof of having ‘gone native’.) 4. The genuine-curiosity response - “Africa? Which country? Uganda? Will you be working up in the north? Is most of the country safe?”  The responses I got the most often tended to fall into the first three categories, both here and in the UK. The fourth is much rarer. And it really shouldn’t be the case. The reasons for why Africa is a dark hole (in all sense of the phrase) in the middle of the world are too many to go into detail. The lack of knowledge and even interest about the continent is simply appalling. I can’t go into it without getting overly technical and boring after awhile. Maybe that’s just me.  But let’s try looking at the issue from a few different angles anyway. a) Africa doesn’t matter because economically it sucks and contributes virtually nothing to global commerce. - this is blatantly wrong. Let’s just look at oil. Africa has always been a major producer of crude oil and is poised to play an even greater role in the years to come. Think Shell in Nigeria, oil in Chad, Sudan, etc. Many of our raw materials, include those used to make computer parts, are believed to originate from African soil. - From a cynical point of view, Africa plays an extremely important economic role in terms of the ‘informal sectors’. This includes illegal/illicit trade in drug trafficking, money laundering, diamonds, and a whole gamut of raw minerals without which most of our major industries would have been crippled decades ago. Heroin grown in Myanmar makes its way through Africa as a stopover entrepot point enroute to Europe and North America. Where Africa lags in production, it excels in trade and barter. And let’s face it - informal and illegal economies are just as important to the running of most states as are the credible, more celebrated ones. - The dependency argument, as commonly voiced at the WTO and other trade summits - Africa isn’t contributing enough in terms of agricultural produce simply because it is being shut out by the so-called developed nations and their agricultural subsidies. Remove these, say the free trade pundits, and not just Africa, but most of the developing world would stand to gain incredible amounts of credit at a relatively low economic cost to the developed nations. This in turn would create a situation for these less developed countries to grow and diversify their economies and move into secondary and tertiary industries.  b) Africa doesn’t matter because we are too far away geographically to be affected by its misfortunes and vagaries. - this is not only a dreadfully apathetic and heartless response - it also severely underestimates the extent to which Africa is part of the so-called ‘globalisation’ process. So many of aspects of its various cultures, the arts and music have become a staple diet of consumers brought up on Western pop music, whether they know it or not. - Terrorism. Tanzania, Sudan and some other states are known to have been staging grounds for ‘terrorist’ organisations including Al-Queda. Hence increasing US diplomatic involvement in the region. An insecure Africa provides a breeding ground for global insecurity, and this is something which has been realised a long time ago by many policymakers, even during the Cold War.  If we accept that Africa is so important in all these aspects then why is it given so little credit and importance as a continent? That will be something for everyone to think about. And it is an extremely difficult and complicated question to satisfactorily answer, because it leads to the query ‘What is wrong with this damn continent’ and subsequently ‘What makes you think there IS anything wrong with what is going on in Africa?” The old Afro-pessimism stance versus the newer, rationalised ‘Africa works but in ways we don’t fully understand’ relativist position.  I apologise for the rambling and inaccuracies you may find in the stuff written above. It’s all obviously come off the top of my head, and some serious research is needed before I would be confident enough to make any further arguments in this line of thought.  What I really wanted to say at the start was my own personal reason for why Africa should matter.  The whole continent fascinates me. The sheer diversity of its people, its cultures, their stories of oppression and history bathed in blood and beauty at the same time. Ugandans are renowned for their friendliness to visitors and each other, their passion for dance and fiery rhetoric. I want to be first-hand witness to that. I want to see how a people who can be capable of celebrating life in its fullest can also be responsible for some of the most horrifying acts of brutality against their own flesh and blood. In other words, I want to be witness to the double-sidedness of human nature. A researcher and friend of mine once said, “At the end of the day, we are all human beings.” At this point of time I don’t believe that there are insurmountable barriers between understanding ‘us’ and ‘them’.  I actually have much more trouble understanding the way many of the people I see around me in my own country live. I think we’ve lost touch of what it means to be truly alive in many parts of the developed world, and to hide it we simply coat it with layer after layer of material success or cultural reinvention (or brazen cultural theft). It’s funny how a recent dengue outbreak in Singapore is blown up by the local papers as a war against a national threat. But at the end of the day, if we’ve apparently solved almost all our major human requirements in life (food, shelter, healthcare, employment), where does that leave us? How much money do we actually need to make in order to live? A serious reassessment of priorities is needed soon. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I’ve spent most of my time back in Singapore (two weeks so far) resting and making preparations for the trip to Uganda. For just today these preparations amounted to the sum of 400 Singapore dollars - that’s about 130 pounds, or 230 US dollars. Four long-sleeved cotton shirts, two t-shirts, a pair of new outdoor shoes, mosquito repellent and net, a blazer, two books on post-colonial African politics and some other miscellaneous stuff. When condensed into a single sentence it seems almost ridiculous how much money went into buying these items, even though at the time of their individual purchase they seemed to make absolute common sense.  Given the nature and purpose of this trip, I think it becomes really important to ask myself whether the items I’m spending all this money on are absolutely essential. That same amount of money could have sent four kids in South Africa to school for a whole year. It doesn’t take a great stretch of imagination to believe that many Ugandans would be able to get by for the same period with far less money.  There is always in my mind this anxiety that I am going to stick out like a sore thumb there, having been brought up in a wealthy, sheltered environment where I’ve never had to worry about real money matters. Perhaps it will be written all over my face when I come face-to-face with the poverty and suffering I expect to encounter. I was talking with an old friend tonight about these issues, and she said to take things one step at a time, that you can only work out what you actually need in life when you are in the midst of the Ugandans you work with and have tried to live their ways long enough. I think those are really wise words - they make obvious sense, but to hear them from someone else is always a reassuring feeling.  The truth is, I feel awfully unprepared in many ways for this one year abroad. I don’t really know what to expect when I get there. I have never been to Africa before, not even Morocco or Egypt. I don’t even have any good African friends at this point in time. Should it matter? In my head I know it doesn’t. I know roughly what I will be doing for at least the first 8 months there, and many months ago I knowingly chose Uganda to be my future country of exploration because of the extremely friendly reputation its people have. So I’ve done as much preparation and planning as I can comfortably fit in, and the rest…well that’s when all the interesting stories start happening!  So to try and answer the dilemma of needs vs. wants - I don’t pretend that the main purpose of this trip is an altruistic one. I am an ambitious person, and I would like to gain as much as I give whilst I’m out there. I don’t wish to be a Gandhi. The thought of doing something different from most of my contemporaries is a source of great pride and motivation. Some would disagree with this and say that this is totally contrary to what the spirit of voluntarism should be about. I think my decision to go abroad is a mixture of the idealistic and pragmatic, and that you have to be sensitive to your own needs first if you are going to be able to help others effectively. The 400 SGD I’ve spent today on personal items will go a long way to satisfy both important psychological and physical needs for the year ahead, and I intend to make full use of these items in the work I will do over there.  It’s for this same reason that I’ve decided to not to have my own website at the moment (this one is being hosted under the umbrella of a large webjournal company). It looked like it would cost at least 50 Singapore dollars a year to have my own domain name and server space, and I haven’t successfully managed to get anyone to host me on their site, for now anyway. If someone is willing to host me, and can spend a few hours teaching me how to use the web interface to construct the site before I leave on August 19, I would be really grateful. Otherwise the journal will remain here. 50 dollars on a 'personal' website could be much better spent elsewhere, especially within Uganda. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>