<Blog>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay- so today is the last day of 2003...   It seemed to go by so quickly.  I think that all in all it was a pretty good year.    The past few weeks have been a little out there, but in a good way.  I am so smart- I have a perfect 4.0 GPA this semester (now, if only I could get money for that!) and I love that all of my grades are A for Annie!!!  I guess that all those hours spent NOT sleeping paid off!!!  Christmas was wonderful!  I actually got a talking Eeyore- one who others can hear, not just me hearing the voices in my head.  His brothers are so excited!  I LOVE that thing!  I even got a little bling-bling from the boy (who is being wonderfuller and wonderfuller, even if he is too practical sometimes).  I think this Christmas was one of the best I've had so far.  When I came to NYC (and Queens-for those of you who are keeping track) I got a letter in the mail saying that I was invited on an educational expedition in AUSTRALIA!!!  It's some place called International Mission on Education and they select like 80 college students from the U.S. (or so they say) to go to Australia and check out all the cool stuff they do in the educational field there.  Totally a once in a lifetime opportunity- but it costs way more than this future educator can afford.    If anyone knows if this company is legit please, please let me know.  I wanna go so bad!!!  Unfortunately, short of selling my soul on eBay or doing some other morally reprehensible act, I'm not sure if this trip is feasible.  I really can't think of many ways to raise $4000 in two months that don't involve run-ins with the law!  Now that that's off my mind, I can rest a little easier.  I just want 2004 to be an awesome year for me (I secretly think it will be).  The new Harry Potter comes out in June- how bad can it be?!  :oD  Okay- I will talk to you all next year (I know that was corny, but it had to be done).    Peace All, and Happy New Year!!!   Don't get too drunk (or at least don't puke- yuck)!!!    ttfn,  *me*  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Still sick.  This cough will not go away!!! UGH!!!  Thank God for strong drugs- hopefully it will be gone by the end of the week.  Just got back from work.  The time went by so fast- 5 hours, that's an easy extra $60 bucks in my paycheck.    I've got two finals tomorrow... The first at 8am... That is way too early for my brain to function!!!  Gotta finish up the studying and then hit the sack.  Eh, who am I kidding... Watching the Nanny and then passing out.    Wish me luck!!!  ttfn,   *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am.  I am FINALLY done with all my stupid school work.  Now I have finals to look forward to.    Is it Christmas yet??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am still sitting here trying to finish work that should NOT have taken this long to begin with.    The codeine is kicking in and I am soooooo  sleepy .  My bed looks so inviting right now.  Just a little longer...    I am having so much trouble forming a coherent thought, let alone stringing several together in the form of a thoughtful reflection.  Whatever happened to writing a few sentences to convey your thoughts.  Now they want pages and pages of introspection and analysis- which I'm sure will never get read anyway.    I am starting to get a little anxious... I wonder if I would make a good flight attendant... Celia's idea has me thinking now... If only being a groupie would pay the bills!  I guess I really should be typing up something meaningful and thought-provoking for my paper, but it doesn't seem to be working that way.    Somebody, ANYBODY- please tell me why I always wait until the last minute... Is it really human nature, or am I the only fool who does things like this?!  Today, of all the days, I decide to go to the doctor about my cough... God bless medicine, but it is not exactly helping my cause here.    Alas, I must endure- only two more days of class, then it's all downhill- HOPEFULLY!!!  Now, I am seriously going to finish these portfolio entries.  Personally, I think literacy is overrated!!!  ttfn,   *annie*
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      WHY, OH WHY CAN'T I DO MY WORK?!?!?!?!?!  I have (unfortunately) found a new distraction... and I think I will be using it as a method of procrastination.  The drugs are kicking in and I am getting really sleepy- but I have miles to go before I rest...  DAMN THESE PORTFOLIOS!!!  Just wanted to vent a little.  If you love me then show it!  Oh, well.  I always have Eeyore.  Eeyore would brave the elements... He's the best!  OK- Back to work.  I mean it this time.      ttfn,  *annie*
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To love one's self is the beginning of a lifelong romance... That or chronic wrist pain.  That's all for today.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, my mommy is gone, but we had lots of fun last night!!!  Is it normal to take your mom to a strip club?  Is it normal for your mom to actually go with you?  Who cares.  All that matters is that I got to hang out with uber-hot guys with nothing but a banana sling on.  The way they stuffed those things, they must be keeping the tube sock industry alive.    Had fun at the club afterwards, too- but why is it that only the guys who can't dance try feeling you up in the club??? Only the freaks and weirdos who look like they're doing some bizarre activity from gym class who come up behind you like they're Tony Manero or something.    Anywho, today is just for chilling and drooling over my pics of the guys.  *SIGH*  Later.  ttfn,  *me* 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a wonderful day!  Went to the Bruins vs. Rangers game today at 1.  It was pretty awesome- even though my New York boys totally disrespected me (they lost 5-2).  Went with Vinnie and Vanessa (who of course made sure to get totally decked out in B's gear) and we had a great time.  The nosebleed seats were just not cutting it, so we used the penguin connection to move ourselves down to some comfy chairs- with padding!!!  Got on the Jumbotron- ok, so just my head and Vanessa's hat- but it still counts!!!  I'm on the STAR 93.7 website, at least that's what they told me when they took the picture... And I even got a free shirt.    But that's not all...  TONS AND TONS of awesome pictures with the Bruins (the Rangers were not in very good moods after the game- they all booked it out of the locker room).  The B's are not only awesome on the ice, but there are lotsa hotties on that team.  I got to take pictures and shake their hands.  SWEET!!!  Topped it all off with some yummy food delivered straight to my room.  Now I have something besides Reduced Fat Triscuits... HOORAY!!!  Life is good... If only I didn't have homework to do, it would be perfect.  *sigh*  Damn my procrastination...   *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Forgot all about signing up for the MTEL.  I broke down and called my mom to ask for money.  I can't afford the test and my textbooks- at least not by 5pm today (the deadline to register).    Who makes a freaking test cost $120- especially a test designed for college students???  Probably the same people who charge a hundred bucks a pop for a text book.  It's beyond me.    Anywho- looks like I am going to have to resort to selling some organs to afford going to school from now until I graduate.  Hopefully I won't need to give up anything vital, but if it's for cash then who knows...   My mommy rules... I'm so glad that I'm her favorite!!! Too bad the rest of her kids suck!    Okay- Off to sell my soul for textbooks.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First day of class...  Gotta start saving money for books.  UGH.  Anywho.  My checking account needs to get beefed up.  Being a penguin is harder than it looks.  If only there were another way to rake in the dough (that isn't illegal).  Oh, well.  Okay.  Off to do my own thing.  ttfn,  *me*  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I decided not to go to Australia.  Not that I will never go, but I can probably figure out a way to visit down under without dropping four grand...  Onto bigger and better things.  I decided to stop penny pinching and spend some of that Christmas cash (since I won't be using it to visit little kangaroos and dingos anytime soon).  I joined the digital revolution- or something like it- and invested in an mp3 player.  It's sooooo shiny!!!  Plus it works awesome.  That was a little something-something for myself.  It is fun to play with and I'm sure that once I figure out how to use all of the functions it will be even funner!  I've been keeping busy in NYC for the past few days.  Making sure my Mommy gets her daily hug quota filled.  I wandered around Queens today to check out her new hood.  It's pretty cool- I managed to find a tattoo parlor on my adventure today and decided to get something pierced.    I LOVE MY SPARKLY BOOGER!!!  Needless to say, I went out and got a hole in my nose.  But on the brightside- one can never have too many piercings (at least in my opinion).  The best ones are the ones you have to look for.  *wink wink*  Anywho, trying to stay out of too much trouble before school starts.  Also trying not to spend all my money, but that's inevitable.    More later.  Peace.  ttfn,  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MTEL tomorrow...   Did I study???    NOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!  Wish me luck- it might be the only way I pass this test.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       WHAT A SURPRISE!!!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And now a little something for all my friends who speak spanish... ENJOY!!!    Carta de una ex-novia a su ex-novio...   Recibi tu carta y me sorprendi, que pen- sandolo bien eres muy tonto y por eso te dejo, te imaginaste que me ibas a co- nocer mas; yo valgo mucho como mu- jer, espero que tu comprendas que for- malizar estas relaciones, nunca se podrian comu- nicar, asi por asi no se puede.  Asi mismo te hago saber que no soy pu- ritana pero tampoco una gran ton- ta, mis hermanas me dijeron que tu ver- dadera intencion hacia nosotras, no nos ala- ga, es deplorable y que no sirve para for- mar un hogar, esto te lo quiero comu- nicar las veces que yo desee.  Yo quiero un hombre fuerte, que pueda cu- brir mis sentimientos y que posea amor fami- liar todos los dias y en varias posi- bilidades, y triunfar en la vida en situa- ciones por dificiles que sean. Creo que co- nocer la dicha conyugal que deseamos toda mu- jer es lo mas importante de la vida.   AHORA VUELVELA A LEER, SALTANDOTE UN RENGLON 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       Just hanging around my room tonight.  Eeyore and I need some quality time.  Wine and no sleep will make you pretty cuddly with any ass...  Words of wisdom spoken by yours truly.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I learned how awful school cafeteria food can actually be today.  There's nothing better than walking out of a class to barf.  C'est la vie.  Anywho, getting better with a little help from my sister and the boy.  Soup helps take the yuckies away.  Hopefully I will be good for a full day tomorrow.  Hopefully...  In other news- trying to get over my addiction to Trivial Pursuit Pop Culture Edition.  It's the one with the DVD.  How can you not love this game?!  So much for studying tonight.    Trying to get plenty of rest and put the whole RA selection process behind me (I'm all done, it's best not to think about it at this point).  Time for a nice long veg out session in front of the TV.  I love adult swim.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just moping around my room.  Feeling yucky.    Being a girl can sometimes suck.  That time usually comes once a month.  Getting ready to go to New York tomorrow.  Hopefully the cat makes it and I won't be stranded at the side of the road.  Wish me luck- and NO traffic!!!  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an overall wonderful day- minus the permanent fixture of stomach pains.  I actually got an 87 on my History mid-term- which is a great grade for me (for History)!!!  I thought for sure that I had bombed that one. God works in mysterious ways...  In other news, I am finding it harder and harder to type with these damn nails!  Next time they are getting cut way short- I am going to have a freaking fit if I make another type because of these stupid things!  Oh, well- it's my own fault I suppose.  I will learn to get over it.  Sitting here, wasting some time online checking out cool new Internet Explorer skins.  I am totally addicted to personalizing my computer... It's my baby!If anyone else gets this bored, feel free to email me- BabyFatChance@hotmail.com   Okay.  Just wanted to check in before I hit the sack.   Time for bed- minus the cute little bedtime buddy I left behind in NYC... :*(  Miss you Eeyore!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today has been one of the hardest days of my life.  I never thought it would be so difficult to deal with losing someone.  It seems like a person can be here one minute and then gone the next- you never know when or where will be the last time you see them.  It could be at an all you can eat sushi restaurant where you share what you both have been up to for the past few years since high school.  It could be walking through the west village looking for a place that sells nose piercing retainers.  It could be in the Astor Place K-Mart looking for a cheap Rangers t-shirt.    The last time I saw Oscar was as he stepped off the W onto the Times Square platform to go home.  He gave me snacks to take for the long bus ride back to Boston.  He gave me inspiration in his courage.  He brought a smile to my face every time I  talked to him.  Now he is gone.    He's not hurting anymore.    RIP Oscar Orlando Acosta, Jr.  You are missed more than you know.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So much to talk about, and yet so little...  Well, I can start off by mentioning that school has once again resumed- much to my chagrin!  I have never felt less like doing school work.  Why can't you just go to classes when you feel like it?  I would do so much more work if I actually felt interested in the course content.  Alas, such is the life of a college student- it is a hard path to hoe, but I'm doing the best I can...  In other news, this Spring Break was not all for naught.  I went to the  urlLink Foxy Lady  in Brockton (for those of you who don't know what that is, use your imaginations- or click on the link, DUH!) on Saturday night.  It's amazing what you can see pierced there, and I am somewhat inspired.  We can just leave it at that.  Again, you may use your imaginations.  Just looking for a way to kill time between classes that is more interesting than doing actual assignments.  It's not easy being a world-class slacker, but someone's gotta do it!  I guess that nothing else of interest has happened lately, besides my eventful trip on Saturday.  So I suppose that I will leave it at that.  ttfn,  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This little bundle of joy is courtesy of Rita (who still finds a way to spread smiles through emails and share heartaches through phone calls).  That's what Bestest Friends are for!!!   This guy was lonely and so he decided life would be more fun if he had a pet. So he went to the pet store and told the owner that he wanted to buy an unusual pet.  After some discussion, he finally bought a centipede, which came in a little white box to use for his house.   He took the box back home, found a good location for the box, and decided he would start off by taking his new pet to the bar to have a drink.  So he asked the centipede in the box, "Would you like to go to Frank's with me and have a beer?"  But there was no answer from his new pet.  This bothered him a bit, but he waited a few minutes and then asked him again, "How about going to the bar and having a drink with me?"  But again, there was no answer from his new friend and pet. So he waited a few minutes more, thinking about the situation.  He decided to ask him one more time; this time putting his face up against the centipede's house and shouting, "Hey, in there! Would you like to go to Frank's place and have a drink with me?"      A little voice came out of the box:   "I heard you the first time! I'm putting on my fucking shoes!!!"     For all of you who know Rita and I, it is so obvious right now why we are Best Friends!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My history test is over and done with.  We can just leave it at that.  Although I don't think I did exceptionally well (it has never taken me the full exam time to complete a test before this one), I am fairly certain that I at least passed.  In other news, I began to unwind from this horrible week by going to tonight's Bruins and Rangers game.  It was, as usual, a lot of fun!   urlLink Gonchar  scored his first goal as a Bruin, and good old Joe got the other two red lights tonight.  The people watching was at its prime- there are so many entertaining imbeciles there to pass the time (and the nachos aren't terrible, either).  Hockey seems to make me feel better- Vinnie's proposal includes one hockey game a week to relieve stress.  If he finances this method of treatment, I won't be too opposed!  I can begin collecting the souvenir cups- you can never have too many!  Hopefully spring break will make me feel better.  I got approval to stay in my dorm for the week.  I figured the office of residence life and housing might as well approve something, since I didn't get the RA position.  No big deal, I can have more time to myself and less time detracted from my studies and other such ventures.  Spring break has commenced and I am, once again, free!  The man can't hold me down anymore!!!  Okay, gotta go to bed- work tomorrow morning at 8!  Later.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's confirmed- I am having a nervous breakdown.  I've got a history midterm tomorrow morning which I am dreading.     I am incredibly stressed out, but that's okay- only 2 more days until Spring Break.  Wonderful- Spring Break, or another reason to mope because I have no money to do something fun (or someone fun who is willing to spend time and money with me).  Life is so sucky right now... Just when you think things can't get any crappier... SURPRISE!!!    If I don't figure out what the cause of all of my stomach aches are, even if it isn't good news, I am seriously going to freak out!!!  I would rather know something bad than not know anything at all.  I can't say that I would be shocked if it was stress related...   Only a few more days until I can just take it easy.  I will be counting down the hours.  Maybe I'll even do something fun (if I can scrounge up the cash) to celebrate my successful completion of half of this semester.  Or I will just sleep, that's equally as good at this point.  Well, wish me luck on my history test.  Lord knows that I am incapable of doing well without luck and plenty of prayers!   *me*   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pretty wasted...  GOD BLESS JUNIOR-SENIOR TOAST!!!  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, now I am a   real   Catholic.  I was officially confirmed on Saturday at the Easter Vigil Mass at the Emmanuel Chapel.  It was pretty awesome.  And, as an added bonus, I am absolved of ALL my sins (which is a pretty good deal)!  Just reflecting on the importance the Catholic faith has had on all of my life's journeys.  Went to a discussion tonight on the  urlLink Voice of the Faithful , and was moved by the recognition that the church hierarchy needs to change, not the church community and that really resonated within me.    Just wanted to get that out there in the open.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my GOD!!!  I HATE MICE!!!  Not only do I detest these vermin with a passion, but I am even more repulsed when they make my room their sanctuary.  I am so freaked out right now, I don't even know what to do.  I know that they're here, and they aren't even scared of me!  How is it that this stupid little creature is smarter than me, so much so that it makes me afraid to live in my own room.  I don't know what to do.  Please God, don't let them get to my shoes!!!  HELP!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like a new Annie...  Since my little excursion to the Emergency Room last week, I have decided to take my health a little more seriously.  I also decided to participate in the Self Challenge.    I began the challenge on Monday and have been doing pretty well so far.  The only temptation I keep having is for chocolate, but I have some will power (albeit not enough to say no to a fun-size Reese's FastBreak.....mmmmm.....But it was tiny!)  Other than that my diet consists of pretty much all vegan, earthy-crunchy, hippie food.  Not so tasty, but I feel much, MUCH better- and no stomach pains!!!  I'm definitely feeling sore, but in a good way!  Once this icky Boston weather clears up I am resuscitating my baby and we are going out for a ride!!!  (For those of you who are confused right now, you obviously don't understand the relationship I have with my bicycle)    The only TV I've been watching is Cartoon Network (I'm only human!)- other than that my DVD player is in overdrive with The Joy of Yoga!!!  Today I discovered FitTV (great for motivation!) and put my sticky mat to work.  It has never felt so good to be so sore.  At least I know it's not from something lame, like falling down a flight of stairs, which has also been known to happen.  I feel like I am making really positive changes in my life, and I also know that that sounds corny, but it's true!  I love yoga, and it feels awesome to get back into it.  If only I had a yoga partner... But I'm barking up the wrong tree on that one.    Well, I guess that's enough of me raving about the joys of healthy living... Don't get me wrong, I love the bad stuff as much as the next person- but I have to get back into shape so I can enjoy the bad stuff to its full capacity- he he he!  I shall write more later.  Have a blessed day!  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just found something amazing:  an online  urlLink Etch-A-Sketch !!!   SO AWESOME!!!  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Get to know the REAL you by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your Name           You Are A:    Prep      Your Favorite Band/Song    Marilyn Manson - Dope Show      You Like To Read:    Religious literature      You Firmly Believe In:    God      Everyone Thinks You Are:    A sleazy prostitute      You Were Conceived:    In a cheap motel      You Will Marry:    Ghandi             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       *HEE HEE* 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today was interesting...  The appointment I had at the Temp Agency was sooooo much longer than I expected.  Those tests are such a pain in the ass!  I use so many short cuts for things but the tests don't accept these as proper responses.  I was hardly thrilled with my evaluation- it was marginal at best.  Oh well, despite the hindrance, at least I have an appointment to start training in like a week.  Don't know if I'll be getting paid for that time (a whole 8 hours, blechhh!), but I DO know that the rate of pay after that is $18 an hour... Can we say new car for Annie!!!  In other news, I am still completely bored here.  New York is not nearly as much when you're broke.  There's plenty of things that I would like to do in the city, however my dwindling bank account forces me to opt for spending more time playing Lingo online.   urlLink The Game Show Network  is a pretty good way to pass the time, though.  I must admit that Lingo is quite addictive!  That and  urlLink [adult swim]  keep me sane... Or is it insane?!  Who knows!  More later...   *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sooo addicted to  urlLink Aqua Teen Hunger Force ! (Now I know what Lamont was talking about, Rita!!!)  Adult Swim is the new highlight of my life.  How sad is that?!  Later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am doing everything within my power to avoid doing my damn Catholic Social Teaching paper.  I just want to be done- why do all of these extra papers and assignments keep popping up at the last minute?!  When am I just going to be able to go to bed and sleep late and be a total slacker?!  In other news, I finally got to meet Lamont- Rita's boyfriend.  Yes Rita, I do hereby give my approval!  But I must say, he reminds me a little of  urlLink Dave Chappelle  urlLink  .  Just thought you'd like to know.  Anywho, right now I'm listening to the boy snore... A LOT!!!  Trying to resist the temptation of holding a pillow over his face until the snoring stops.  No, no- that would be bad!  Only a few days left and then I get to go back to New York.  Missing the city bigtime!  Missing my Yankees!  Missing real subways!  You know the deal.  Countdown to my birthday... Only 8 more days to go!!!  WHOO HOO!!!  Hitting the big 2-3!  Damn, I'm old (but wise)!  Better get back to that paper, before I get too sidetracked.  Oops, too late.  Maybe just a little longer on eBay!  *me*  P.S.  Why is it that a guy and a girl can never just be friends?!  Someone fill me in on that one- I am so confused.  I'd love an answer at some point, but I won't be holding my breath.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EVERYONE SHOULD GO SEE FAHRENHEIT 9/11!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am back in New York.  I am sooo sick.  This sucks.  My weekend started out pretty good.  The Aerosmith concert on Thursday was  wicked awesome , they put on such a great show!  Cheap Trick was good, too (though I know not many people showed up for them).  Friday was full of Rita and Annie bonding- we always have the best time, even if we don't do anything.  I can't wait until she comes to the city- whoo hoo!!!  Rita and I back in the Big Apple- that means trouble, he he he!  Saturday was great, too- Vinnie and I hung out with Katie and Tim.  We had a wonderful Texas-style dinner, followed by ICE CREAM and miniature golf!!!  The weekend was an uber-delight... Until Saturday night.  Saturday night my sniffles turned into mega-congestion with a hacking cough, and I couldn't sleep at all.  I finally ended up going to the drug store at 4am, when I couldn't handle it anymore.  I must've gone through half a box of tissues and the coughing kept triggering my gag reflex and making me barf.  It was not a good night, to say the least.  Then I had to drive back to New York.  Not a fun trip.  Needless to say, I am getting plenty of rest today.  It's just me, Eeyore, Vicks 44, and lots of Spongebob episodes.  I hope this doesn't last more than a few days, I hate being sick.   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WTF?!?!?!  I don't even know what to say about  urlLink this .  In other news... I am sitting here at my desk waiting for something to do.  I just came back from lunch (yummy McDonald's salad and Starbucks coffee), and there's still not much to do around here.  I found that interesting website and that killed a few minutes (although I have no idea where he came up with some of these grades).  Mostly I'm just enjoying getting paid for doing nothing- besides looking up cute doggy names for my future puppy.  So far Lola and Pepper are in the lead, but I still like Phoebe and Zoe (maybe for my future daughter, WAY future!).  I'm also pretty excited about Thursday.  It's not everyday one gets the opportunity to watch aging rockers strut their stuff on stage.  I am really stoked to see Cheap Trick perform live- and Aerosmith are in a league all their own!  I know that Vinnie is excited too, although I don't know if it's the concert or the fact that we will be driving in a car from this decade... Maybe a little of both!  So I am trying to find ways to make the day go by faster which wouldn't get me fired immediately.  If anyone has any ideas, please let me know.  There are only so many quizzes one can take before getting tired of them.  Some day I will reach that point.  Until then, I enjoy hearing that I am Meatwad.  Despite what Vinnie says, I am  not  that gullible or dumb- but the rest is pretty on the money.  For what it's worth, I think he's Carl!!!  I'll write more later when I get bored again.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it was an eventful weekend!  Friday night I went to the ballet to get my culture on with my momma!!!  We actually had a lot of fun hanging out around Lincoln Center during Midsummer Night Swing after work and watching people make fools of themselves trying to dance.  It was pretty cool, and the ballet itself was beautiful.  Swan Lake by the American Ballet Theater- the sets were amazing and the music was incredible.  I should go to more cultural events like that- as long as someone else is paying!  In other news, Saturday afternoon I dragged my mom out to the  urlLink K-Rock Dysfunctional Family Picnic 8 .  It was  really  cool!!!  There were a lot of punk bands at the festival stage-  urlLink Taking Back Sunday ,  urlLink Story of the Year ,  urlLink New Found Glory  and a couple other local bands.  I saw Winnie the Pooh crowd surfing and he even got on stage!  Mad props to that kid- it was really hot out for that costume (trust me, I know)!    After the festival stage acts were done, the main stage acts came on and they were pretty awesome!!!  The Beastie Boys were by far the best act of the night, but The Darkness, The Strokes, and even Cypress Hill were unbelievable, as well.  My only complaints were how many fourteen and fifteen year old kids were roaming around and being annoying (thank God  I  was never like that!), AND the fact that beer was nowhere to be found!!!  OH, THE HUMANITY!!!  I'm totally going to go to the Warped Tour and Lollapalooza now.  Having fun is addictive, lol!  I am also super excited about Aerosmith and Cheap Trick on Thursday... Must find some "concert enhancers" by then.  Anyways, here's another cool quiz.  Leave your results!!!    Peace out, Homies!!!    YOU ARE MEATWAD -- A little ball of raw hamburger meat, Meatwad is a friendly, optimistic, happy little fellow.  He is extremely dumb, however, and often very gullible.  He loves dancing, playing with his homemade dolls, and is often chased and injured by Master Shake.  Does very little for the Aqua Teens, but he has a good heart.    urlLink   What 'Aqua Teen Hunger Force' character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am here at work.  I am supposed to be working, however there is nothing to do.  The phones are not ringing.  There is nothing to be faxed.  Nothing needs to be copied.  I am sitting here watching the little clock in the corner switch numbers- ever so slowly- until 5:30, when I can leave.  Fridays are so incredibly dull.  No one is here, and no one cares about anything whether they're here or not.  My sole consolation is my access to the internet- God bless email (and Katie, for keeping me amused)!!!  I have looked up prices for cars, checked my account balances, read about what happened on this date in history (nothing that exciting), and worked out my fingers by typing infinite emails to my mom.  If only there were a fire, or some other entertaining catastrophe.  I suppose I could flood the bathroom, but then my soggy shoes would undoubtedly give me away.  Oh, cruel fate!  Why must I have the attention span of a newt?!    I guess I'll just keep myself occupied with random stuff I find online.   urlLink The Dumb Network  is a good place to start.  I wonder how much money one makes by coming up with creative (and stupid) bumper stickers... Perhaps a career change is in order!    On that note, I will write more later.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another quiz based on my television addiction... Life is good!    You are Philip J. Fry    urlLink   What Futurama Character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Here's another  urlLink Futurama Character  quiz- Let me know which one is better, and which character you got.   urlLink        urlLink I'm Leela, who are you?  by  urlLink Lexi  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't even know where to begin the explanation for this... In all honesty, I don't think there is one that would remotely make sense.  Oh, well.  The things you so when you are bored.  *sigh*    Barbie Got Back!  Go you!  You're the closest thing ever to a true black Barbie.  Shake that fat ass of yours.    urlLink   If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      urlLink Which Family Guy character are you?    I do NOT agree with this one, but whatever... Maybe if I was a guy... MAYBE!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Self Portrait!!!  I am so darned CUTE!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Anyone surprised?  I didn't think so!!!  Just lounging around the house, trying to avoid getting out of bed for as long as possible.  Gotta do the laundry today (yay) and run a few errands.  Gonna pick up my check in the city this afternoon and then go to the dentist for a cleaning- getting those teeth so fresh and so clean.  Nothing else exciting going on.  The brother and sister are both home today, so that's a motivating factor to get out of the house.  Been so busy being a working girl that I have nothing else going on right now.  I got sick of my claws and gnawed them all of last night.  Now I have little stubs for nails- but at least it won't cost me $15 every two weeks, that gets pretty old pretty fast.  Just hanging out in my pajamas with the TV on in the background.    I am still kinda sleepy and not really in the mood to do anything today.  Better take advantage of my day off, because it's back to work tomorrow and Friday.  At least I'm getting paid.  Still trying to figure out what to do for Father's Day and all that stuff.  I still have bills to pay, so we'll see...  Anywho, I guess there's nothing else exciting going on right now.  I'll add more later if something good happens- but I doubt I'll be abducted by aliens before dinner.  *me*  P.S. Some good sites to pass the time:  urlLink Disturbing Auctions   urlLink Awful Plastic Surgery   urlLink The Payback  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Playful    urlLink   What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Playful me wants to throw a party Saturday night... Anyone interested???
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're My Little Pony!!  Sweet and innocent and happy, you make people want to spew burrito chunks.  Even a Care Bear could kick your ass.     urlLink   What childhood toy from the 80s are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SOOOOOO much fun tonight!!!  Words can't even begin to describe it, but alcohol might...  CONGRATULATIONS MOE!!!  See you all soon, hopefully.  *me*
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            The  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am on my 6th can of Coke for the day.&nbsp;   Needless to say I am counting down the minutes until I can go home... &nbsp;Also, until I can take a bathroom break.&nbsp;   What a fucked up day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Long live the curse of The Bambino!!!  Yankees win it 8-7!  WHOO HOO!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you call a dog wearing ear muffs?   Anything you want, he can't hear you.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here I am.&nbsp; Another day at work- only today I actually had work to do, a TON of it!&nbsp; This is the first time that I've had any time to myself since I came in at 9:30.&nbsp; I'm not sure I like having to run around for all of these incompetent people (one in particular, but we won't get into names).&nbsp; Time to go to lunch, I will write more later.  &nbsp;  Okay, I am back from lunch.&nbsp; It was uber-yummy.&nbsp; Mmmmmmmmmm.&nbsp; I am just sitting at the desk now, relishing my down-time.&nbsp; Not much is going on now, and I think I like it this way.&nbsp; It gives me plenty of time to update my blog and listen to the radio.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Nothing much has been going on in the life of Annie.&nbsp; This week is going to be full of boring entries, since I am actually doing work and not having typical Annie-ish adventures.&nbsp; At least I'm working and making that money, *bling* *bling*!!!&nbsp; Now I'm not the only one who's gainfully employed- there's a certain penguin out there who's playing with wires- WATCH OUT!!!&nbsp; I am really happy and proud of you, babe- keep up the good work and don't get electrocuted (without at least having me be there to laugh, lol)!  &nbsp;  I guess I'm just going to keep myself busy by going online and continuously drinking Coke.&nbsp; Ahem- I said  drinking  not  snorting  for those of you with your minds in the gutter... Like all of you!&nbsp; Besides, I can't afford it.&nbsp; LOL!!!&nbsp; At least the soda's free!  &nbsp;  I suppose that on that note I will leave you.&nbsp; Peace out to all my homies in the 'hood!&nbsp; Stay real!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I have been at work for 20 minutes now, and I am already totally bored out of my mind. &nbsp; Just thought I'd let you know.&nbsp; I'm sure there will be more later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   all about your sex life...         Full Name         Age          your sex personality colour is...      orange - wild and crazy.        you'll probaby fuck....      anyone who accepts your offer        your favourite sex toy is...      a rusty coathanger. And you wonder why you have no friends?        you will get __# std's.      12              This   fun quiz   by  urlLink  cowboysbecamefolkheros   - Taken 70980 Times.          New -  Dating Advice  written by YOU! 
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, so much has happened in the past few days.  Okay, not really, but I did do some stuff.  Monday was the Teacher Empowerment lecture at Sarah Lawrence College with Sheila, a teacher/professor who lives in my dad's building.  I met Jane Andrias and heard her keynote speech about her life as a young teacher and as director of Central Park East 1.  I met so many cool teachers and people in charge of all kinds of different masters programs in New York.  We'll see where that goes, but for now, I will totally stay in touch with Sheila.  Tuesday I went to see the taping of Late Night with Conan O'Brien with my sister and her friends.  It was SOOO funny!!!  Conan is freakishly tall in real life, but oh, so hilarious!  We got front row seats and one of Laura's friends was actually on TV.  This kid was only 18, but he still managed to try and hit on me.  I will leave him to Laura, though- He is actually old enough to vote, so it's a step up.  After the taping we all headed over to Ellen's Stardust Diner, the one with the singing wait staff.  They are always really entertaining.  I had a total blast and it was cool to watch Late Night afterwards and know what was going to happen.    Today was an adventure also.  I picked up my paycheck, which was pretty sizable considering I worked twenty-eight and a half hours last week.  I took out some cash and headed to my mom's office.  We met my sister downtown and went to this totally cool little Indian restaurant where they served us a ton of yummy food and free wine and dessert with dinner.  There were like a million strings of lights, including Christmas lights and those pepper lights that you hang out in the yard, and if I had epilepsy it would have induced a seizure.  After that we walked back up St. Mark's Place to the take the train home... Only I convinced my mom to make a pit-stop into Andromeda (the tattoo and piercing studio) to look around.  I love that place, it's where I got my tattoo!  Well, long story short, I have a new hole in my body.  Don't worry, it's above the waist!  I am definitely going to make my way back there before the summer is over.   I guess that's all for now, but I will let you know how much it hurts tomorrow.  I cannot believe that it takes 6-8 months to heal.  *sigh*  We'll see after a few weeks how worth it this was.   And now for something completely different...          urlLink   What will God say to you when you die?         Name         Age         Religion          You will say:      What is the meaning of life?        He will say:      I am whole-heartedly disappointed in you.       How much do you deserve to be in heaven? -  88%                                                                                   This   fun quiz   by  urlLink  megalomein   - Taken 27394 Times.          New! Get Free  urlLink Daily Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am just sitting here feeling really depressed.  I am completely, totally, utterly broke.  I can't get approved for a loan for school, even with a co-signer.  I don't even know someone who's credit worthy enough to co-sign for me.  Life stinks right now.  Let's just hope that this week things will turn around.  Until then, I am still poor.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check  urlLink this  out...   Now you too can label your deepest fear in a scientific fashion so as to appear intelligent and impress your peers...   But to me you are still a freak.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No offense to any of my blonde friends, but this is one of the funniest blonde jokes I've heard in a while.  As a matter of fact, it's so funny that I made a complete ass out of myself laughing out loud at the office!  BWAAA HA HA!!!   A blonde calls her boyfriend and says, "Please come over here and help me. I have a killer jigsaw puzzle, and I can't figure out how to get it started. Her boyfriend asks, "What is it supposed to be when it's finished?"  The blonde says, "According to the picture on the box, it's a tiger." Her boyfriend decides to go over and help with the puzzle. She lets him in and shows him where she has the puzzle spread all over the table. He studies the pieces for a moment, then looks at the box, then turns to her and says, "First of all, no matter what we do, we are not going to be able to assemble these pieces into anything resembling a tiger."  He takes her hand and says, "Second, I want you to relax. Let's have a nice cup of tea, and then," he sighed, "we'll put all the Frosted Flakes back in the box."    Go ahead and laugh, you know you want to!!!  ;o)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Bowling Shoes- fun, unique, and vintage, you don't care a lot about what other people think. You do your own thing and are your own person. You have fun no matter what you're doing and enjoy being surrounded by friends. You still need your down time though!   Why am I not surprised?!   urlLink What Kind of Shoe Are You? 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How trippy is  urlLink this ?!  AND  urlLink this one , too!!!  Will I ever get any work done today?  I think not.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Your future President and Vice President... Note the fabulous hair! DONKEYS RULE!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am all set to go to my first Kerry/Edwards campaing fundraising event on Friday.  I am really excited.  Eeyore is so proud of me!  Just thought I'd share my do-goodingness with the rest of you.  If anyone is in the city (New York City, that is) on Friday night feel free to come with me.  Email, call or IM me.    urlLink John Kerry for President    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay- So I am a bleeding-heart liberal, do-gooder type... Oh, well.  Supporting ethics, human dignity and the civil rights and liberties of all people (except Red Sox fans) has always been my downfall.  I just signed up to  urlLink volunteer  to help the Kerry campaign.  We all know what a big fan of politics I am.  I actually read his stance on the issues (especially Education- ahem) and I have to say that I approve.  We'll see where this goes.  I'm sure as it gets closer to November I will have a lot more to say.  I definitely like John Edwards- another do-gooder- and like the fact that there is attention being paid to the marginalization of poor Americans in this country.    I think that this will be a very eventful year.  You had all better  urlLink register to vote - I MEAN ALL OF YOU!!!  P.S.  I should have realized my destiny sooner- I  do  have a deeply rooted love of Donkeys!!!  (Hi, Eeyore!!!)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Fourth of July!!!  Just feeling a little hung-over (and A LOT queasy).  Tequila is my arch-enemy, disguised as my best friend.    Anywho- I hope everyone's Independence Day was wonderful.  Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm, wonderful!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay- so let's see... I am a little happy right now.  Drinking makes everything so much more significant.  Nothing much has happened in the past few days.    I got lost in Maspeth/Ridgewood last night on a wild goose chase for the UPS warehouse.    I finally got my Dell Digital Jukebox (a full 20GB of music for my personal enjoyment), lots of cool tunes for fun and profit.  Ah, the miracles of modern technology.  I have  IMAGINATION , now all I need is a box...  I have been feeling better lately- but there are still many boogies to go.  I hate being sick, especially when I'm congested and I sound like a weirdo.  I am just glad that it's July (I keep getting closer and closer to September and classes).  Getting back to what I was talking about- what was I talking about?- ummmmmm, Rita is coming down next week (YAY!!!) and we are planning some fun adventures.  We are too cool for school!  Okay, well I will post more later (maybe) and right now I am going to go play with some doggies and refill my drink!    WHOO HOO for alcohol!!!  P.S.  Here is the  urlLink Holy Grail  of yummy drinks online.  And check out my  urlLink live journal  (although I don't know why).  Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH MY GOD!!!!!!!!!!  I read the words "hot sex" in my sister's live journal and I am infinitely more disturbed than I thought possible!  Not even another monkey friend could make this better... GET OUT OF MY HEAD!!!  Please say it isn't so- It is such a gross thought!!!  Okay- will write more later from Beantown (which still sucks since the last time I was here, but in a better car!!!)  Peace out, stay cool my babies.  P.S. Nomah may be better- but he's still cursed!!! HE HE HE!!! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>