<Blog>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  Derby Champ Smarty Jones Wins Preakness   I bet on him to win the Derby, and I made about $40 on it.  Since his  urlLink odds  on the Preakness were so ridiculously good, he returned $3.40, $3, and $2.60.  So if I had placed my usual $10 on ol' Smarty to win, I would've made a profit of $7.  Shoulda done it.    Guess I'll have to wait for the Belmont. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Wolfgang Petersen 's summer blockbuster  urlLink Troy , which opened in theaters nationwide yesterday, is a full-blown, old-fashioned "epic" movie, a tiresome two and three-quarters hours in length, which features at least four scenes at funeral pyres, and leaden lines of dialogue like "Before my time is done I will look down upon your corpse and smile."   urlLink Brad Pitt  does a good job flexing his muscles, both artistically and, ahem, literally.  Seriously, the guy is huge.  He's so big, his muscles have muscles, and those sub-muscles must have a better workout regimen than I am.   urlLink Eric Bana  never manages to quite shake his Aussie accent.  He was better in  urlLink Hulk , and that's not saying much -- in Hulk he was upstaged by a ridiculously unrealistic CGI monster.   urlLink Orlando Bloom  channels  urlLink Legolas  for the climactic moment of the film (trust me, I'm not spoiling anything).  I'll give you a hint.  Someone gets shot in the heel.  His one weakness, you could say.  The one scene I wish they had shown:   Odysseus:   So... I'm gonna make my way home now.  Random Greek:   OK, you need a map?  Odysseus:   Nah.   urlLink I'm good . 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The  urlLink New York Yankees  begin a two-week road trip with a three-game series against the Anaheim Angels starting tonight at Edison Field.  Javy Vasquez (3-4, 4.10), one of the two bright spots of the Yankee rotation, matches us against Aaron Sele (2-0, 3.62) in the first game of the rematch between the two teams who met in the Bronx last week, with the Yankees taking two out of three.  The Yanks have been plagued by injuries of late -- Posada took a baseball in the schnozz while trying to break-up a double-play last week, and tonight should be his first start since then.  Giambi has been troubled by back spasms, which would explain his 0-for-6 performance in the Yankees' 13-inning loss to Seattle on Saturday.  It would be nice to see Vasquez straighten himself out.  After pitching absolutely lights-out for his first few starts -- including a gem at opening day at The Stadium, witnessed by my brother Patrick and myself -- he's been shaky for the past two starts.  He says it himself -- he likes to throw strikes, and when he can get ahead in the count and make his pitches, he's at his best.  The bats still haven't really woken up.  A-Rod, Sheff, Giambi, and Bernie are all batting well below .300.  Jeter, after bringing his average into the mid-200s, ran it back down to about the .190 level with a 1-for-19 slide.  It's getting a little too late for the "small sample size" arguments to hold true, and if these numbers continue to June, my arched eyebrow will likely turn into a full-fledged furrowed brow.  Still, the Bombers are in first place, with a half-game lead over the Sox.  You gotta feel good about that, but Boston's only going to get stronger with the imminent return of Nomar and Trot in early June.  I'd still love to see the Yankees pick up Beltran in July, but I don't think they have the major-league caliber prospects to offer in such a deal.  Of course, I have this fantasy, where I close my eyes and I see Barry Bonds and Pedro Martinez in pinstripes next year... it's crazy enough to happen. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Shigeki Maruyama's caddie is SMOKING a cigarette during the Open.  What is this, a burned out public course in Alabama?  Who smokes during a major golf tournament?  I know, I know, he's Japanese and it's a cultural difference and all... but come on.  You're playing in OUR national golf championship.  At a private club.  Put that cigarette away.  Call me a traditionalist.  I just saw Tiger Woods hit a bump-and-run on 10 that rolled onto the green and then fell almost 30 yards back down to where he was standing.  And then, he did it AGAIN.  Tiger Woods, standing there, watching his shot roll back down to his feet.  He'll probably have to take a triple bogey on the hole.  OK, Tiger just made it up on the dance floor.  He's lying five and hasn't putted once on a par four.  TIGER WOODS.  This is mini-golf stuff, and why the U.S. Open is the absolute best golf tournament in the world.  I'm sick and tired of these Wal-Mart Opens, where the winner shoots 24-under and the Saturday cut is at 10-under.  Give me a tournament where these guys have to work, have to earn their keep, and have to contend with greens like bowling alleys.  That's what major golf is supposed to be.  That, combined with the fact that Tim McCarver is doing the color commentary for the Yankees-Dodgers game on FOX, means that I'll be sitting in front of golf all afternoon, and only intermittently checking in on the Yanks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Boy, is it hot in New York today.  My  urlLink Weatherbug  says it's only about 79 right now, but with about 50% humidity it is not a nice day to be outside.  The Olympic torch came through my neighborhood at about 10:30 this morning.  That was the last thing we needed around here -- people running a giant open flame through the streets.  I wouldn't be surprised if there was a trail of scorched pavement  urlLink where the torch ran .  My neighborhood, Astoria, boasts the largest Greek population outside of Athens, Greece.  Astoria features such Greek wonders as Cafe Omonia, a wonderful place to get some baklava and espresso late at night (and the bakery which made the wedding cake for My Big Fat Greek Wedding).  There's also the Athens Cafe, a place that continually gets busted for violating the NYC smoking ban, and Uncle George's, which according to Zagat's, has the best gyros and souvlaki in the city.  I'm partial to Aliada, which makes a mean tahini (a meany tahini?), and for a full sampling of the ethnic palate, you can simply cross the street to Sac's for a mean baked ziti and merlot.  And forget about Bavarian Hall, the best and largest beer garden in New York City.  I am not sure that there is anything better in the world than sitting at Bohemian Hall, enjoying a tall, cold, Pilsener Urquel, and tucking into a plate of keilbasa, sauerkrat, and pierogies.  So while Astoria is certainly an ethnic melting pot (or, as my 12th-grade history teacher would say, an ethnic "tossed salad" -- no joke), the Greeks far outnumber all other nationalities.  So I guess that's why we got the Olympic torch.  I'll have to admit, though, it was hard for me to get excited about seeing the torch pass through my 'hood.  In fact, the Olympic torch ran about 50 yards away from my apartment this morning.  Sure, I guess it's a big deal and all, and I appreciate the fact that's the  very  torch that will light the flame in Athens this summer, but I guess I view the "Olympic torch relay" as little more than a big, long, international publicity stunt that nobody really cares about.  Instead, I helped a friend move a bed about 10 blocks.  When we discovered that it wouldn't fit into his car (The Dodge Intrepid -- a decently sized American sedan), we realized that we'd have to carry it.  It wasn't heavy, but with each step, it dug more and more deeply into the flesh of my palms, leaving my hands reddened and sore after the 15-minute hike.  So I felt I deserved the "Extra Large" iced coffee I got from Dunkin' Donuts, and I really deserved the everything bagel, toasted with cream cheese, and I  really  deserved the Boston Creme that completed my breakfast of champions.  My feet are up, my two air conditioners are blasting, I've already made it through the Times and the Post, and I'm watching Phil Mickelson try to win the U.S. Open.  I can't complain. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm afraid this isn't the last time we're going to see  urlLink this .  I don't really even know what to say, I'm far too disgusted to compose any rational thoughts right now.  My prayers go out to his family.  We are really up against a heinous enemy that seems determined to break our spirit and our will in the most barbaric way possible.  The only way they win is if we back down. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Was offered tickets to Madonna today at work.  Turned them down.  Wait a second, are we supposed to call her Madonna or  urlLink Esther  now?    In any case, maybe I'm the only person in the world that has absolutely no interest in seeing Madonna anymore (OK, fine,  urlLink I know that's not the case ).  But I can't think of anything I'd less rather do than go to a concert in which I have absolutely no interest in the artist performing.  I've fallen into that trap before...  Cue dream sequence...  The year was 2003.  Bruce "The Boss" Springsteen was performing about 12 consecutive shows at Continental Arena at the Meadowlands.  I've never been a big fan of The Boss.  In fact, one time when I was about 12 or 13, I was stuck in a car coming home from summer camp and my friend's sister played Springsteen tapes NON-STOP.  We're talking New Hampshire to New Jersey here --seven straight hours of "Tenth Avenue Freeze-Out" at top volume from the speakers of a soft-top Jeep Wrangler.  We could barely hear each other talk.  It was my own private version of hell.  But I digress.  One day at work last summer, I was surfing the internet and came across an article about how absurdly fast Springsteen tickets in Jersey had sold out.  I can't seem to find the article now, but it was probably in the Times or the Post or something.  I think they put 600,000 tickets on sale and they sold out in eight seconds.  Something like that.  I guess it falls under the category of: "You don't know that you want something until you realize you can't get it."  Or, more accurately, "You don't know that you want something until you realize that you  can  get it and millions of other people  can't ."  I work in an industry with a lot of connections for tickets, so all it took was a few well-placed phone calls, and I had a pair of prime Springsteen tickets.  I had to pay for them, but I got them.  And they were good.  It was gonna be on an August Saturday night, The Boss at Continental Arena.  Definitely legendary.  The stuff that you're supposed to tell your grandchildren about, right?  Only one problem -- I don't like Springsteen.  I know maybe four Springsteen songs.  I'm maybe the only person in the history of the world that has been born and bred in the state of New Jersey whose skin crawls when the opening chords of "Glory Days" come on the radio.  Allow me to explain.   "Glory Days" was my Ridgewood High School Class of 1998 prom song.  How precociously ironic of us, right?  Well we were 18 -- we didn't get irony.  Of course, "Glory Days" is quite possibly the worst prom song of all time:   Yeah, just sitting back trying to recapture a little of the glory of, well time slips away and leaves you with nothing mister but boring stories of glory days.     By the way, Bruce... why the second "of"?  "Trying to recapture a little of the glory of"... what?  A little of the glory of [insert glory here]?  Is that what you mean?  I guess I always thought he was saying "A little of the glory uh" or even "gloria."  But I guess it's "a little of the glory of" according to  urlLink his official-looking website .  I think "Born to Run" is his best.  Even before  urlLink Christopher Moltisanti  memorably quoted a line from the last verse in "Long Term Parking" ("The highway's jammed with broken heroes on a last chance power drive"), my college's marching band used to play it at hockey games and I always thought it sounded cool, especially played by a marching band, reverberating inside a hockey arena.   So we get to the concert, and it's a mob scene.  They've taken the parking lot of Continental Arena and turned it into the Asbury Park Boardwalk.  Or at least a reasonable facsimile thereof.  There was a "Springsteen Karaoke" stand, where drunken buffoons got up, one at a time, to perform their rendition of "Rosalita" and "Born in the U.S.A."  I remember one version of "Blinded by the Light" that sounded startlingly like my own personal version of the lyrics: "Blinded by the light... revved up like a douche, another runner in the night" (Again, Bruce, what?).  Cotton candy.  Dunk tanks.  Fried dough.  Cold beer.  It was just like the Jersey shore.  Except in a parking lot.  At The Meadowlands.  Wonderful.  As we walked past a group of Jersey-ans sitting around their hibachi, I remarked "This is like  urlLink Tanglewood  to these people."  Someone had the brilliant idea of selling a different t-shirt at each concert.  So 12 dates in New Jersey, 12 different t-shirts.  They were all a different color and included the number of the concert on the back.  Ours was green and had a big "7" on the back.  All that was missing was "Make 7-Up Yours" on the front for the effect to be complete.  There were people there with t-shirts from every single concert.  Entire families, each wearing a different t-shirt.  I guess it's supposed to be a badge of honor -- in a "I pulled two graveyard shirts so I could bring my family to 12 consecutive Springsteen concerts" sort of way.  The concert itself, of course, was eh.  I spent most of the time watching the only two people on stage that I was interested in -- Little Stevie and Max Weinberg.  Sorry, Bruce.  But for a guy whose two favorite TV shows in the history of time are "Sopranos" and Conan, it was far more important for me to see Silvio Dante and Max Weinberg.  And I admired Bruce.  Dancing around the stage -- jumping, kicking, screaming.  He really impressed me, considering he's what, 80 years old?  Seriously.  But everyone around us was singing along with every song.  I was just standing there waiting for them to do "Born to Run."  And he didn't.  He did "The Rising," and I did know some of those words:   "Come on up for the Rising... come on up, put your hand in mine..."   As much as I hate to admit this publicly, but we left.  That's right.  We left a Springsteen concert right in the middle.  I grew up in New Jersey, and I left a Bruce Springsteen concert right in the middle.  It was maybe halfway through.  We beat the traffic.  We were the ONLY ones leaving.  The parking lot was empty.  So was the Turnpike.  On the way home, all of the classic rock stations were playing Springsteen.  We listened to NPR, or Z100 or something.  So when the Madonna tickets came across my desk, it took me about three minutes to pass them along.  Besides, I'd be standing there the whole time waiting for her to play "Like a Prayer."  And there wouldn't even be a dunk tank.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For now, dear reader (i.e. myself), the blog stays where it is.  It's probably too much money to get it on kevinmeyers dot com.  I've been bad at writing this week, I'm dealing with the hassle of moving.  As soon as I get settled in my new apartment, I'll start writing again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am trying to figure out how to get this onto www.kevinmeyers.com.  I don't know if that involves FTP or something... but it'll be my homework for the week.  That AND moving. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK, I'm feeling a little bit better now.  I had a nice, hearty, protein-rich lunch from  urlLink The Pump on 55th St. , I can't say enough how I love their meals.  I'm sure you can get something just as healthy somewhere else, but I don't know if you can do it as easily.  I think my general malaise this morning can be attributed to my slovenly lifestyle this weekend -- high sugar, high carbs, no exercise, and poor sleep.  Note to self: be healthier. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just imagine, for a second, that you're a professional golfer.  You spend your entire life with a golf glove on your hand, you drive from tournament to tournament, often sleeping in a trailer or sleazy motel, and you spend almost every waking moment thinking about your next shot.  You spend hours and hours on the practice tee, refining every shot in your arsenal.  You can hit drives more than 300 yards.  You can hit an approach shot that will land three feet past the hole, then turn on a dime, spin back and come to rest inches from the pin.  You are an artist with a putter, knowing exactly where to strike surface of the ball and with the precise force so it rolls precisely where you want it, up a break on the green, or down the other side, and finally, with its final breath, the ball stops spinning just as it drops into the cup.  Now imagine that you're this golfer, and you have the chance to play in the U.S. Open at Shinnecock Hills this past weekend.  Your drives jump off your club, then get lost in the swirling winds fifty yards above the ground, and come to rest amidst knee-high fescue that hasn't been trimmed or tended since 1978.  From this lie, you have to hit an approach shot onto a green that's harder than a linoleum floor.  Your ball lands three feet away from the pin, then either bounces right past the flag, or picks up speed and rolls another 25 yards into the bunker on the far side of the green.  And when you finally do get on to the green, you still have to putt into the hole -- hit it a shade too hard, and your ball not only slides right past the cup, but continues to steam its way off the green, through the first cut of fringe, and comes to rest in the rough, where you're forced to chip on again.  This is what you faced if you were a golfer at Shinnecock Hills this weekend.  And that would be for 17 of the 18 holes.  For number 7, the par-3 monster that was so bad that the USGA decided to WATER the green between groups on Sunday, you just hit your drive and held on for dear life.  Some golfers even said that your best bet on 7 was to aim your drive for the sand -- at least that way, you can blast it out onto the green, instead of driving for the pin and hoping that it holds.  Lots of golfers had some choice comments about the course.  Tiger was pissed (that's because his swing is messed up).  So was Mickelson (who choked with a three-put on 17 and blew his chance to win his second consecutive major).  The only golfer that didn't go on the record as critical of Shinnecock was Retief Goosen, who hoisted the Open's claret jug yesterday for the second time in his career.  And I'll go with the pros on this one.  If you have a field of the best golfers in the world, even on a reasonably difficult course, it stands to reason that SOME of them would shoot below par.  Not one of them broke par yesterday.  Only one shot even par.  Goosen and Mickelson both shot one-over.  It would be like a World Series in which the pitchers used golf balls instead of baseballs.  Like a Super Bowl with a field that is 200 yards long, instead of 100.  Like the NBA finals with hoops that are 15 feet from the ground.  When a sport's rule-making body resorts to something as patently unfair as watering the greens in the middle of a major tournament, perhaps it's a sign that the USGA must step back from it's stated goal of making the U.S. Open the most difficult 72 holes of golf in the world, and perhaps just focus on making them REASONABLY PLAYABLE.  Of course, we all would have liked to see a tournament where the average score hovers around par.  But with the average score of this weekend's Open hovering around 78, it's clear that the USGA made things a little too tough on the world's best golfers this weekend. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am such a slob.  Didn't get to the gym all weekend.  Also ate like a moron.  For breakfast on Saturday, had a bagel with cream cheese and an iced coffee from Dunkin' Donuts, capped off by a dinner of take-out Mexican.  Had a steak burrito and some nachos.  Then, yesterday, I started my day with another iced coffee-bagel combo (the breakfast of champions), and for dinner pigged out on meat lasagne at Sac's.  Couldn't get to sleep last night, either... maybe it has to do with my lack of exercise, or the two Cokes I had at dinner.  Maybe this unhealthy lifestyle has something to do with the recurring headache I've had since yesterday afternoon.  Isn't a sharp pain, really, more of a numbing throb right behind my eyeballs that occassionally spreads into my brain.  It feels better if I close my eyes and roll my eyeballs around.  Maybe I should get a vision check-up one of these days.  Will blog more later.  Need to get started on work. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Where's Kirsten Dunst?&nbsp; urlLink    &nbsp; Spotted this dude in Times Square yesterday on my way home from work.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Give generously," along with some other comments at Dave Barry's  urlLink blog . 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Martha was sentenced to five months in prison today, and took the opportunity to read a prepared statement from the courthouse steps, promising "I'll be back" and urging listeners to buy her books.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Sports Guy answers his mail.  These are always the BEST Bill Simmons columns.  He basically lets himself lose, and jumps from talking about Clemens to Jeter to Shaq to Seageal all in the span of the first two paragraphs.  I wish I could get a gig like his some day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I stand corrected.&nbsp; Just two days ago, I  urlLink wrote : "If you're not watching  urlLink The Casino  yet, you should definitely start. It rates high on the Bill Simmons unintentional humor scale. And, if for no other reason, watch it so you can read  urlLink TWoP ." &nbsp; The Casino is no longer being re-capped on TWoP.&nbsp; It's been put on "permanent hiatus."&nbsp; Which means it sucked so bad they didn't want to deal with it anymore.&nbsp; For their part, they explain:  "It is a truth universally acknowledged, that a single man in possession of a good fortune," some girl once said, "must be in want of a wife." We don't know which girl that was, because girls are just silly and we don't need them: we have shiny cars. But it turns out she was right, because when you don't marry those rich guys off, you never know what can happen. Two particularly terrible examples are Tim Poster and Tom Breitling, of the "Tim and Tom Connection," who randomly bought a historic hotel and casino in downtown Las Vegas with their dot-com bubble-illions. And then filled it with crap like transsexual hookers, regular hookers, roofie parties with hookers, creepy swingers, hillbillies that dressed like pimps, actual pimps, psychics, child welfare cases, and a host of other crap we never got to see, because we proved once and for all that TWoP is smarter than FOX by canceling it straight to hell.  While there may no longer be a reason to watch The Casino, there are still plenty of reasons to read TWoP, mainly  urlLink The Amazing Race .  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    crappy pic from my cell phone&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Larry Mahnken cements his status as a must-read on a daily basis with well-written, insightful, and absurdly knowledgeable posts about the Yankees on his  urlLink blog .    Today's post offers a great response to the millions of baseball fans who will undoubtedly immediately scream bloody murder if Big Unit does, in fact, come to the Bronx.  If you're the type to call in to a radio sports show, here are your talking points, courtesy of Larry:   I've said many times before that the point of assembling a baseball team isn't to have "enough" talent, it's to win the World Series.  It doesn't matter how many you've won in the past, the point is to win going forward.   To win the World Series, you have to try and field the best team within your means (and if you really think this is the year, perhaps a bit beyond your means).  If the Yankees have the opportunity to acquire Randy Johnson, why shouldn't they?  Because other teams are more worthy of having a great player than the Yankees?   Amen. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This camp just went from being the best camp ever to the worst camp ever.   Before this ruling: a teenage naked camp. After this ruling: teenage naked camp  with Mom and Dad .   And you really wanna play darts? &nbsp; &nbsp;   urlLink    Good thing this isn't a picture from the nudist camp.&nbsp; urlLink     
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Hideki Matsui powered the Yanks to a 5-1 victory over the surprising Detroit Tigers.&nbsp; urlLink    &nbsp; For the first time in his career, Jose Contreras pitched into the ninth inning.&nbsp; This in his second consecutive quality start.&nbsp; Possible that he's off the schnide?&nbsp; Perhaps.&nbsp; Contreras tonight:&nbsp; 8 IP, 4 H, 1 ER, 1 BB, 7 K, 0 HR.&nbsp; Threw 112 pitches, 68 of them for strikes.&nbsp; Not bad.&nbsp; In fact, just by the line score, that's gotta be one of the best starts by a Yankee pitcher all year.&nbsp; Now, will he keep it up?&nbsp; Or will his next start be another Contreras oddity, where the poor guy can't get out of the second inning?&nbsp; Who knows. &nbsp; On the offensive front, all five of the Yankees' hits were home runs.&nbsp; A-Rod, Jeet, Hideki, and Lofton went yard for the Bombers.&nbsp; Smallball it ain't, but it puts&nbsp;a W in the win column, and it works. &nbsp;  Giambi Update : 0-3 with a walk.&nbsp; During his second at-bat, he managed to work the count to 3-1, and just when Ken Singleton surmised that "he might see a good pitch here," he grounded weakly to second.&nbsp; Sure, that walk will increase your OBP, but that's not why you're batting fifth, behind A-Rod and in front of Posada. &nbsp;  Kevin Brown Update :&nbsp; He was supposed to pitch three innings in a Double-A game in Trenton, but only lasted two.&nbsp; Suffice it to say, it'll be a few more weeks before we see Kevin Brown in pinstripes. &nbsp; Paging Mr. Johnson?&nbsp; Mr. Randy Johnson?  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jesse McKinley weighs in on the nearly-averted strike that almost shut down Broadway earlier this week.  The producers finally made a deal with Equity at the 11th hour, ensuring that Broadway would not endure its second strike in 16 months.  McKinley writes:   The issue at the heart of the dispute between actors and producers, who averted a work stoppage with a tentative new contract brokered on Monday afternoon, was not the state of the theatrical economy in New York or the treatment of actors or their pay. Those issues were relatively cut and dried: actors would get annual raises through 2008, when even the lowliest spear carrier will make more than $1,500 a week for being on Broadway (not to mention pension and health care).   I know.  Ridiculous, isn't it, Jesse?  Especially when you consider there is a line of chorus boys stretching from Sardi's to Studio 54 that would take a part --  any  part -- for a quarter of that.  Also, what show has spear carriers?  Aida?  They work for Disney, they definitely make minimum.  And what's this about actor's getting profit sharing?  Max Bialystock is spinning in his grave. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I got a haircut yesterday.&nbsp; Tried out a new barber here in Astoria.&nbsp; That's always a big risk for me.&nbsp; You see, for my whole life, I've been going to the exact same barber.&nbsp; Ernie.&nbsp; I swear, the man's a genius.&nbsp; Started cutting my hair when I was seven years old, and hasn't stopped since.&nbsp;&nbsp; Ernie's Barber Shop in Ho-Ho-Kus, NJ.&nbsp; I swear, if you're ever in Ho-Ho-Kus, even if you don't need a haircut, go to Ernie's.&nbsp; It's "tucked" (some would say "hidden") behind a Sunoco station.&nbsp; But, like all good things, it's worth the extra effort to seek out. &nbsp;  Even when I was in college, I would strategically time my haircuts to coincide with my visits home.&nbsp; I'd get a haircut on the day before I left for school in September, the day I got home for Thanksgiving (if not before, since I was home occasionally during the fall), the day I got home for Christmas, winter break, Easter, spring break, and then the summer.&nbsp; I was in his chair so regularly, I'm not sure Ernie even knew that I went to college.&nbsp; For all he knew, I could have spent four years bagging groceries at the local A&amp;P.&nbsp; Come to think of it, he always used to ask me how things were up in  urlLink Hartford .&nbsp; I guess I never bothered to explain to him that I actually went to school in  urlLink Cambridge .  &nbsp;  You see, my hair is fiendishly devious.&nbsp; Cut it straight, and it's good to go.&nbsp; Maybe throw a little gel into it.&nbsp;&nbsp;With a good haircut, it's no muss, no fuss.&nbsp; Cut it wrong, though, and it's a bloody disaster.&nbsp; One time in seventh grade, I went to a new barber and was stuck with most penis-looking hair you've ever seen on&nbsp;an Irish&nbsp;Catholic child.&nbsp; The hair on 95% of my scalp looked normal, but my bangs were about one inch long, and they hung straight off the front of my scalp like a bridge that was in the midst of construction.&nbsp; It left me with an expanse of uncovered forehead that was an absolute monstrosity.&nbsp; There were Eskimos chasing down mammoths on the big, white, frozen tundra of my forehead.&nbsp; It was terrifying.&nbsp;  &nbsp; But back to Ernie I would go.&nbsp; I would say, conservatively, that 90% of the haircuts I've ever gotten in my life have been with Ernesto.&nbsp; The man's a genius.&nbsp; An artist.&nbsp; A Picasso.&nbsp; Like Adolfo  urlLink Pirelli , "The king of the barbers, the barber of kings." &nbsp;  But recently,&nbsp;I had a problem.&nbsp; My hair was too long.&nbsp; It's been hot in New York the last few weeks, and I'd find myself randomly sweating.&nbsp; Not sweating because I was running to catch a train, or sweating because I had just come from the gym, but sweating because I was standing outside waiting to cross the street.&nbsp; Sweating because I was sitting on the couch watching the Yankees game with the window open and the air conditioner off.&nbsp; Sweating because I had crossed my legs.&nbsp; It was gross.&nbsp; The hair had to go.  &nbsp;  On my way home from work every night I pass a barber shop on the corner of Broadway and 31st St. here in Astoria.&nbsp; It's right next to a restaurant called Gables, whose proprietor looks like a cross between the  urlLink Gorton's Fisherman  and the  urlLink Greek Kenny Rogers .&nbsp; But I digress.&nbsp; But while I'm on this digression... I've been to Gloucester, Mass., home of the Gorton's fishery, and they actually have a  urlLink statue  that looks surprisingly like the Gorton's fisherman.  Anywhoo, on my way home from work every night I pass this barber shop.&nbsp; Here's what I like about this barber shop -- it's no  urlLink namby-pamby  salon.&nbsp; It's a good, old fashioned, barber shop.&nbsp; It has one of those candy-cane stripe  urlLink signs &nbsp;out front, and three big ol' chairs, manned by three big ol' barbers.&nbsp; I'm talking old school.&nbsp; Italian flag hanging in the corner.&nbsp; Pictures of the Rat Pack on the walls.&nbsp; Sports on the TV.&nbsp; Ten bucks for a cut.&nbsp; So far, so good.  &nbsp;  The place definitely had the feel of an old-time tonsorial parlor.&nbsp; A bunch of 20-something men sat about, passionately discussing the proposed trade of Roger Clemens to the  urlLink Mets .&nbsp; I half-expected  urlLink Cedric the Entertainer  to  urlLink walk  out from the back room.&nbsp;&nbsp; An older gentleman took care of me, and as I watched in the mirror, I admired his skill with the clippers as much as his economy with words.&nbsp; "Live around here?"&nbsp; "Some weather, huh?"&nbsp; "How long since your last haircut?"&nbsp; At the end of the haircut,&nbsp;I&nbsp;was so impressed,&nbsp;I introduced myself.&nbsp; "Great haircut, thanks so much.&nbsp; I'm Kevin."&nbsp; His name was Dominic.&nbsp; And, tell the truth, now that I think about it, he did look a little bit like  urlLink Dominic Chianese .&nbsp; He seemed happy to meet me, I tipped him two bucks, and I walked out of there a new man. &nbsp; It's a great haircut.&nbsp; I like it a lot.&nbsp; I don't get nearly as hot and sweaty, and it's much easier to shampoo in the morning.&nbsp; Yesterday I put a little dab of gel in it, and it looked a touch greasy.&nbsp; Today, however, I did no product at all, and my hair flatly clung to my scalp like a kindergartner.&nbsp; So, I'll have to experiment.&nbsp; Maybe a little wax, a dab of gel, or a healthy smear of Ye Olde Gentlemanly Pomade.&nbsp; No matter.&nbsp; In two or three weeks it'll look the same as every haircut I've ever gotten in my life.&nbsp; And if it doesn't?&nbsp; It's only a quick train ride out to Ernie.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Jose Contreras starts for the Yankees tonight as they begin the second half of the season against the Tigers.&nbsp; urlLink     The Yanks dropped two out of three to  urlLink Detroit  last week, before going on to sweep Tampa in a four-game series.  They looked pretty sharp in those last games against the D-Rays, especially last Sunday's  urlLink 10-3  blowout, which featured a strong five-inning outing from El Duque.  Captain Jeter continues his roll.  After going 3-for-3 in the All-Star game, raising his career ASG average to .700 (7-for-10), Jeter returns to the regular season still riding the high of his July 1 dive into the stands to snatch a victory from the jaws of defeat -- against  urlLink Boston , no less.     urlLink Giambi  (.241/.377/.439), however, has been totally useless.  Lucky for the Yanks, A-Rod (.270/.361/.510) and Posada (.275/.419/.508), continue to produce.  And in Giambi's absense, Tony Clark has been a pleasant surprise.  At the All-Star Break, so-called "journeyman" Tony Clark's numbers are comparable to our big All-Star Jason Giambi's?   Tony Clark  AB - 154 R - 27 HR - 10 RBI - 31 SO - 50   Jason Giambi  AB - 212 R - 30 HR - 11 RBI - 35 SO - 46 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Interesting, though not entirely surprising results of an exit poll of people viewing  Fahrenheit 9/11 . See the complete poll results  urlLink here . Posted on  urlLink BoiFrom Troy .  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The caption writer's dry sense of humor appeals to me.  Courtesy of  urlLink NewYorkish .&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Her record collection is awesome," Jenna tells Vogue. "She's got Jimmy Cliff and Bob Marley. When we have parties at the ranch, we play them and all our friends love it."    No comment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tony Pierce  urlLink offers  an LA perspective.  If he had come to the Knicks, I would have started to follow the NBA.  Alas, nope. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is my parents' dog Toby.  I am posting this picture of him to see how pictures look on KevinMeyers.blog.  Enjoy.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As my increased volume and pace of posts indicates, I am quickly becoming addicted to this blogging thing.  Hopefully soon I'll be able to publicize it a bit, get a little bit of a readership.  I'd also like to have some more time to write a little bit more of my own stuff, rather than constantly linking to news stories.  But still... I'd like to make this the kind of blog where if you're at work, you have some time to kill, this is a good place to come check out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As Bill Simmons would say, I wish I could have bought stock in this.  The SI cover jinx strikes again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Realizing that a constitutional amendment banning gay marriage faces little chance of passing soon, if ever, House Republicans yesterday discussed alternative approaches, including stripping federal courts of jurisdiction over the issue, passing a federal law to define marriage and using the appropriations process to ban gay marriage in Washington.   As Josh Marshall  urlLink writes , "If at first you don't succeed..." 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I left my cell phone at home today.  Who does that?  I guess I had it on the dresser to charge it.  I usually set the alarm on my cell phone to wake me up in the morning, which requires me to walk over, pick up the phone, and unplug it, but today I didn't do that.  I used my alarm clock.  So that's probably why.  Hm.  I guess I'm going to go a day without a cell phone.  I'm quite the Luddite. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh yeah, it's definitely cocaine. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The Sopranos  got 20 Emmy nominations this morning.  I hope they win them all.  In fact, it doesn't even seem fair to call The Sopranos television.  It's like an epic film, an opera, a masterpiece.  To compare Edie Falco to Allison Janney seems, to me, like comparing Derek Jeter and the shortstop on my 14-year old sister's softball team.  Check out the  urlLink Bada-Bing Blog  for more Sopranos blogging.  And from a boy that grew up in Tony's backyard along Route 17 and Route 4, I gotta give a plug to a site with the web address www.nj.com. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       God knows there are enough fat Republicans in the world...   (CNN) -- Weight loss product manufacturer Slim-Fast announced Wednesday it had dropped Whoopi Goldberg as its spokeswoman, following a controversy over sexually explicit comments she made last week at a fund-raiser in New York for presumptive Democratic nominee Sen. John Kerry.  "We at Slim-Fast trust the public understands that the way in which Whoopi Goldberg chose to express her own personal beliefs at the recent fund-raiser at Radio City Music Hall does not reflect the views and values of Slim-Fast," said a statement from Terry Olson, general manager and vice president of marketing.  "We are disappointed by the manner in which Ms. Goldberg chose to express herself and sincerely regret that her recent remarks offended some of our consumers. Ads featuring Ms. Goldberg will no longer be on the air," the statement added.   Does this mean that Blockbuster will pull  Ghost  off the shelves, too? 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        More than half of all U.S. consumers that have tried following diets that eschew carbs such as bread and sugar have given up, a survey released on Wednesday found, and interest in the popular regimens appears to have plateaued.    Of course.  Because pizza, bagels, and ice cream are just so damn good.  Mark July 14, 2004 in the annals of history as the day when America finally came to its senses.  Who am I to talk.  I've tried the damn thing three times... can never seem to get past three or four days. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We'll never have such an amendment.  I maintain that this whole thing is an election-year ruckus created by the Republicans to drive super-conservative Christian voters to the polls in November. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From today's  urlLink LA Times :   In the months and years leading up to the U.S.-led invasion of Iraq, they marched together in the vanguard of those who advocated war.  As lobbyists, public relations counselors and confidential advisors to senior federal officials, they warned against Iraqi weapons of mass destruction, praised exiled leader Ahmad Chalabi, and argued that toppling Saddam Hussein was a matter of national security and moral duty.  Now, as fighting continues in Iraq, they are collecting tens of thousands of dollars in fees for helping business clients pursue federal contracts and other financial opportunities in Iraq. For instance, a former Senate aide who helped get U.S. funds for anti-Hussein exiles who are now active in Iraqi affairs has a $175,000 deal to advise Romania on winning business in Iraq and other matters.  And the ease with which they have moved from advocating policies and advising high government officials to making money in activities linked to their policies and advice reflects the blurred lines that often exist between public and private interests in Washington. In most cases, federal conflict-of-interest laws do not apply to former officials or to people serving only as advisors.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Two pieces today caught my eye about George W. Bush's efforts (or lack thereof) to "get out the vote" in this November's presidential election.  First, Harold Meyerson  urlLink writes  in the Washington Post that today's Senate vote on the gay marriage amendment was scheduled solely to "frighten the religious right to the polls in November."  Further:   The Senate, as all its members know full well, is no more likely to come up with 67 votes for this bit of campaign-year demagoguery than it is to enact workers' and peasants' soviets. It's not just liberals but also centrists and conservatives (Lynne Cheney among them) who oppose placing a ban on gay marriage and possibly civil unions in the Constitution. But then, the amendment is being offered today simply because it will help the scare campaign hasten more right-wing evangelicals to the polls this fall.   The New York Times offers  urlLink this  piece, which posits that Bush's decision to skip the NAACP convention this week will further erode his support among black voters.  Buried deep is this:  What is more important for Mr. Bush is to avoid having huge black turnouts in crucial states like Ohio, Pennsylvania, Missouri and Arkansas.   Wait, George W. Bush  hoping  that black voters don't make it to the polls?  Well,  urlLink it's worked for him before . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know what I find scarier:   urlLink this , or  urlLink this . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How do you screw up a reality show that takes place in Vegas?  Apparently Mark Burnett has figured out a way to do so.  If you're not watching  urlLink The Casino  yet, you should definitely start.  It rates high on the Bill Simmons unintentional humor scale.  And, if for no other reason, watch it so you can read  urlLink TWOP . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last week I was again offered free tickets to a concert in New York.  This time, however, it was no simple Madonna concert.  It was the CONCERT FOR CHANGE, a fund-raiser for the newly-minted Kerry-Edwards campaign.   urlLink The concert raised $7.5 Million , Whoopi Goldberg caused a ruckus, blah blah blah we all know this.  In any case, Bush's folks got so angry that  urlLink they demanded the tape .  Now comes the response from the Kerry camp, which I think should be required reading.  Highlights include:  Considering that the President has failed to even come close to keeping his promise to change the tone in Washington, we find your outrage over and paparazzi-like obsession with a fund-raising event to be misplaced.    Check out the whole thing  urlLink here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Continuing my march into the 21st century, my blog now offers TrackBack.  Maybe people will start to read it.  Who knows.  Until now, I'm going to be able to TrackBack other people's blogs, and become a good citizen of the Blog community. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Those crazy kids at  urlLink Google  are at it again.  Apparently  urlLink this  is a recruiting tool.  Seems pretty ingenious to me.  I'm just not smart enough to get it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been moving.  As it turns out, moving is like a month-long ordeal.  The move started on Tuesday June 22 and still isn't over.  In the meantime, I've been across the country and back (Sacramento... not so good), attended the funeral of a family member (RIP Grandma Meyers), and purchased a 10,000 BTU air conditioner.  I still don't know how I am going to promote this blog... if at all... or if I'm just writing for the sake of writing.  Who knows.  But hopefully I'll blog more soon.  Very soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I made this audio post while sitting at a picnic table upstate this weekend.&nbsp; So if you've ever wondered what I sound like, here's your chance.  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Attack of the killer teeth.&nbsp; urlLink     I just ordered this flick from  urlLink Amazon .&nbsp; Apparently it's the #1 selling DVD on the site.&nbsp; They say it will take four or five days to ship, and then three to seven business days to arrive in New York, so I'm guessing that John Kerry will accept the Democratic nomination before I get my hands on this DVD.&nbsp; But once I do, I'll be sure to post my thoughts here.  Whether or not you've had a chance to see the movie, be sure to click  urlLink here  to sign a petition demanding that the FCC and Congress bar Fox from using the slogan "Fair and Balanced."&nbsp; And if you want to buy a copy of the movie and support an organization that is working towards independent media, click  urlLink here .  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     It is high, it is far, it is... GONE!&nbsp; Ballgame over!&nbsp; Yankees win! Yankees win! Thuuuuuuuuh Yankees win!&nbsp; urlLink      It's official.&nbsp; El Duque is back.&nbsp; I realized this last night as I sat at The Stadium and they re-played that stupid "El Duque Dance" music video that was first popularized two years ago, when El Duque was in his prime.&nbsp; And any doubts were further vanquished by his stellar outing this afternoon.   It was a true pitching duel in the Bronx today, as the Jays hoped to salvage a split of this shortened two-game series against the Yanks.&nbsp; Orlando "El Duque" Hernandez&nbsp;pitched a gem&nbsp;for New York&nbsp;-- striking out ten, walking only one, and allowing four hits scattered over seven innings.&nbsp; Toronto starter Ted Lilly (a Yankee castaway, as you may recall) similarly stymied the Bombers for six and two-thirds, allowing only&nbsp;three hits (two to the final two batters he faced) and walking only two while striking out six.   As we reached the bottom of the ninth, still with no score, I prayed that the Yankees would finish it off without heading into extra innings and avoid the prospect of losing bullpen arms in advance of a three-game set in Fenway.&nbsp; Thankfully, big Ruben Sierra finished Toronto off by blasting a moonshot to straightaway center.&nbsp; Game over, cue Sinatra, Yankees win, Thuuuuuuh Yankees win.   One of my co-workers said it best, as we were watching Sierra's game-winning blast play out on Gamecast: "Wouldn't it just suck to be a fan of any team other than the Yankees?"&nbsp; Why, yes.&nbsp; Yes it would.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My family is planning a trip to Cape Cod for a week in August, and although I can't really take an entire week off from work, I'm hoping to take Monday off and join them for a long weekend.&nbsp; I could get up there easy -- just hitch a ride with Mom and Dad in the family SUV.&nbsp; The problem is, then, getting back to New York on Monday. &nbsp;I don't have a car, which means I'm limited to mass transit, and the mass transit options between Cape Cod and New York are severely limited.&nbsp; To wit, my options are:     Take a bus from Hyannis to New York.&nbsp; This would take over six hours and require switching buses in Providence.&nbsp; I hate buses.&nbsp; Absolutely cannot stand riding a bus.&nbsp; Total cost = $70.&nbsp; I consider this a last resort.&nbsp; Right behind slitting my wrists.  Fly from Hyannis to New York.&nbsp; Obviously the most ideal option.&nbsp; US Air flies nonstop to LGA.&nbsp; Only problem?&nbsp; Last time I checked  urlLink Travelocity , the price for a one-way ticket was around $350.&nbsp; Yeah, you're looking at a guy that couldn't pick up his dry cleaning for two weeks because he couldn't afford it.&nbsp; I'm not going to be able to swing three-hundred-plus bucks for a one-way flight that will be maybe 30 minutes in a JFK Jr.-esque twin-prop.  Rent a car.&nbsp; Now here's the doozie.&nbsp; Because I am 24 years old, the car rental companies do not want me anywhere NEAR their vehicles.&nbsp; The top two -- Hertz and Avis -- won't even let me in the front door.&nbsp; They don't even want to hear about it.&nbsp; Most of the others, though, will rent to a 24-year old, provided they jack up the rental price with a $25/day surcharge.&nbsp; I don't understand this at all.&nbsp; The state of New York has no problem with me driving anywhere I want, any time I want, in any vehicle I want, solely because I am&nbsp;16 years old or older&nbsp;(provided it's not a commercial vehicle, and even then, U-Haul rents to 18-year olds).&nbsp; I actually have a New Jersey license, but because we have this wonderful thing called Federalism, I'm allowed to cross state borders all I want.&nbsp; Thank you,&nbsp;founding fathers.&nbsp; But the rental car companies, of course much wiser than our elected officials, have chosen to deny me the privilige of paying them a lot of money, only because I am 24 years old and, presumably, drive like a bat out of Hades.&nbsp; Total cost of a rental car: about $125 plus tax.&nbsp; And that's for a one-way rental for a single day from Hyannis airport to LaGuardia.&nbsp; Forget about renting a car for the entire weekend.&nbsp; I'd probably have to sell my unborn children for that.  Some sort of ridiculous combination of ferry to Boston and then train to New York.&nbsp; This is the option that seems most promising to me, but I haven't been able to figure out the Provincetown-to-Boston ferry situation yet.&nbsp; With all the rigamarole, this might be just as long door-to-door as the bus.   Ridiculous, I tell you.&nbsp; Absolutely absurd.&nbsp; But mark my words.&nbsp; I will get to Cape Cod.&nbsp; Some way, somehow, somewhere... I will figure out a way.&nbsp; And I'm sure you, dear reader(s), will be among the first to know.&nbsp; The bottom line is this -- why the heck don't I have a car????   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So excited to head up to Yankee Stadium for the... umm... I think fifth time this year.  So far I've been:  1.  Opening Day.  Vasquez hurls a gem and Yanks beat Chicago White Sox. 2.  Final game of Boston's April sweep.  Had amazing seats, right behind the Yankees dugout, but the game was just depressing.  Couldn't muster any offense off Pedro.  Everyone was slumping. 3.  My birthday -- April 28 -- against Oakland.  Contreras with his best pre-family-reunion start of the year, gets the win. 4.  Friday June 4 against Texas.  Soriano's triumphant return to Yankee Stadium.  Standing O for his first at-bat.  He steps out of the box and tips his cap.  Gives me goose bumps. 5.  Last night.    There might be some more games in there, and I definitely had tickets to two more games, which I didn't go to because: a.  I gave the first pair of tickets to my sister as a graduation gift. b.  The second game (July 6 vs. Detroit) was on the day of my grandmother's funeral.  Those tickets went unused, mostly because we had just moved, and I had forgotten where I put the tickets, and my mind was kind of scattered that weekend anyway, what with me taking a red-eye back to NY from Sacramento, celebrating the Fourth of July holiday, and preparing for a family's funeral all at the same time.  So last night was a fun night.  We took the D train up there after work, and it wasn't too obnoxiously crowded.  It looks as though the Yankee Stadium security forces are finally figuring out an efficient way to get everyone into the stadium in a timely fashion.  Earlier this season, it would literally take you an  hour  to make it through that security check.  I guess everyone is finally learning that no, you can't bring bags to Yankee Stadium, and yes, they're serious, they'll take them away from you.  Seriously.  They have giant dumpsters right at every gate, and if you show up with a bag, a backpack, or anything else that's on the "not allowed" list, they will look you in the face and throw it away.  I've seen people cry.  It's awful.  But I guess everyone has figured it out by now, so the line moves a little bit more briskly.  Last night was also Canon Photo Frame night, so we got a great little blue photo frame with a Yankees logo on the top.  I'm definitely using it -- I just need to find a photo that is deserving of such a great frame.  We sat in the upper deck.  For those of your familiar with The Stadium, we were in Tier Section 15, which is the upper deck section just beyond first base.  It's also -- importantly -- right next to the alcohol-free Section 13.  So all that means is there were a lot of  NERDS  in the section one over from us.  Especially three tools who kept cheering for the Blue Jays, even when the Yankees opened up a 9-2 lead at one point.  As you probably know if you follow the Yankees, they were ON last night.  The offense was clicking on all cylinders.  Vasquez was solid (6 IP, 9 H, 3 ER, 2 BB, 4 K), and he got a well-deserved win with enough run support for TWO wins.  The scariest line about the box score is perhaps that the Yanks left  ten  baserunners stranded last night, so the final score could have been a LOT worse.  We left after the seventh inning, not before I could polish off two dogs, two beers, and some nachos.  Hey, when in Rome.  I'll go for a run after work today, or do some spinning.  All in all, a good night at the ballgame.  I consider myself lucky to live in a city like New York, where world-class baseball is just a short (crowded, sweaty, smelly) subway ride away.  During the Republican Convention, however, that might change. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In clicking through my referral pages, I noticed that someone had recently visited this site by doing a search on  urlLink Yahoo! &nbsp;for "Randy Johnson Unit Penis."&nbsp; I did the  urlLink search  myself.&nbsp; And I'm apparently result number ten on the page.   So I guess that means I'll be getting a lot more traffic from weirdos interested in seeing naked pictures of the  urlLink ugliest man in baseball .&nbsp; And it is to these people that I address these next words:&nbsp; EW.&nbsp; GROSS.&nbsp;   I guess after this post, I'll probably move to number one on that search, right?    urlLink    I heard he turned down an offer from Playgirl to pose nude.&nbsp; urlLink       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ... here I come!  Shutting down my computer and on my way to The House that Ruth Built right this second.&nbsp; Vasquez pitches against the Toronto Blue Jays... hopefully he'll come off the schnide, the Yankees bats will wake up, and we'll have a lovely evening at the ballpark.&nbsp;   Full report to come...  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       William Rhoden with a good piece in the Times about Carlos Delgado's refusal to stand for the national anthem  urlLink here .  Delgado refuses to stand because he protests the United States' invasion of Iraq, as well as the Navy bombing of the island of Vieques.  Like Rhoden, I applaud Delgado for taking a stand, and only fear that this article's publication, prior to Toronto's season debut at Yankee Stadium, will lead to some nasty incidents for Carlos over the next two days.    When will the powers that be realize that Steinbrenner's insistence on playing God Bless America in the middle of the seventh inning is equal parts patriotism and gamesmanship?  Played, as it is, as the visiting team's pitcher stands on the mound, it serves to knock the opponent's defense out of sync while the Yankees bats enjoy a few extra moments of rest in the dugout.  During the playoffs, Steinbrenner's continued reliance on the Irish tenor Ronan Tynan is even more exasperating for opponents and fans alike, as Tynan always sings the  extra-long  version of the song, including the first verse.  I applaud Carlos Delgado for having the courage to stick to his convictions, and I was surprised that his teammates quoted in the article stood behind him so strongly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you've stumbled upon this blog, enjoy it, and don't know what to do with, oh, I don't know, let's say $379 or so, just click this link.   urlLink Weber 2004 Model 6211001 Genesis Silver A Propane Gas Grill  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So George King in today's  urlLink Post  surmises that the D-Backs won't trade the Unit until they can move Steve Finley, probably to San Diego.  This dashes my hopes of seeing Randy Johnson make his pinstripes debut in Fenway this weekend, but it sounds like he'll definitely be part of our rotation come August.  Last night's 9-7 defeat at the hands of the Devil Rays was softened only by the fact that the Red Sox just got their asses handed to them by Seattle in  urlLink stunning  fashion, a game that surely made Yankees fans around the world chortle with glee.  Is something wrong with Keith Foulke?  He has now blown his fourth save in his last six chances since June 12.  Still, Boston's loss was great, but it would have been better if the Yanks could have made it an  eight  game lead in the AL East, especially headed into Boston -- Unit-less -- this weekend. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Awesome.  "The guiding principle of the game is elegantly simple: The worse Ken does, the drunker you get." 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Awww, damn. New  urlLink iPods  have arrived, and they look a hell of a lot cooler than the one I have now. As  urlLink Gothamist  speculates, "the new ones won't be hitting downtown for a couple of weeks and will never make it to the rest of the world." So they'll hit New York just in time for all the Republicans to get them?   Someone outside my window is cooking some sort of meaty bouillabaisse sauce and it smells damn good. I wanna get me a loaf of Italian bread and go down there and dip it right into their pot, like they do in  Goodfellas .  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got sick of  urlLink Yahoo! Mail .  So I signed up for Gmail, the fancy-schmancy new e-mail service from  urlLink Google , the makers of  urlLink Blogger , and, incidentally,  urlLink KevinMeyers.blog .  So I'll let you know how it goes.  For now, if you want to e-mail me, do so at kevinmeyers at gmail dot com. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmmmm...    urlLink Barry Sonnenfeld , the director of  urlLink Men in Black  and  urlLink Wild Wild West , writes  urlLink this  in the June 2004 issue of Esquire, extolling the virtues of the  urlLink Tucks Medicated Pads  for non-hemorrhoidal issues.  "Tucks are like a romp through a field of daisies for your butt." 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I take back what I said about  urlLink Larry Mahnken  last week. He's not the only great  urlLink Yankee  blogger out there.  urlLink This  guy Alex is, too.   In today's post, he links a  urlLink few   urlLink interesting   urlLink articles  about the potential Randy Johnson trade. I still don't think we'll ever see The Unit in pinstripes, but God knows the Yankees have done crazier things. I'll be at the Stadium on Wednesday to see Vasquez throw against Toronto, so I'll post a full report then.  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am very tempted. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     The "M" stands for malarkey.&nbsp; urlLink     &nbsp;  &nbsp;  So last week there was all this buzz in the press about this Sci-Fi Channel biography of M. Night Shyamalan.&nbsp; The story goes a little something like  urlLink this :  &nbsp;  The Sci-Fi channel was all set to do an "authorized documentary" about the making of  urlLink The Village , the new Shyamalan flick coming out on July 30.&nbsp; But, when the documentarians began to dig too deep for&nbsp;comfort (oooh that sounds dirty), Night refused to cooperate with them any more.&nbsp; The press reported that he even walked out during an interview and threatened legal action if Sci-Fi aired the piece.&nbsp; This story was picked up by the wire services, and reported by the  urlLink New York Post &nbsp;(not on the same day, incidentally, that they ran their Gephardt-as-veep  urlLink "scoop" ),  urlLink CNN ,  urlLink The Boston Herald , and tons of other media outlets.&nbsp; So I did what any rational person in this situation would do -- I TiVo'd it.  &nbsp;  It took me about five minutes to have serious doubts about the authenticity of this "documentary," and about fifteen minutes to feel fairly confident that it was complete and utter bullsh*t.&nbsp; If you, like me,&nbsp;were gullible enough to be intrigued by the press "hype," you already watched it and know ridiculous the whole thing was.&nbsp; But if you watched  Six Feet Under  or Ali G instead ( urlLink remember , I don't get HBO), allow me to give you a little recap of the most absurd moments.    The documentarian, Nathaniel Kahn, goes to the gates of "Night's" house (everyone calls him Night, for some reason), where he finds about five or six disaffected youths, straight out of central casting.&nbsp; This is the first moment of the film where I blurted out "they're totally actors."&nbsp; Kahn asks them why they're hanging out in front of Night's house, and Angst-Ridden Teen A makes an big, exaggerated, over-acted "don't tell him anything!" face at Angst-Ridden Teen&nbsp;B , who blurts out that Night is "connected to the other side."&nbsp; We then follow Kahn and ARTB into his parent's basement, where the dude actually pulls out a Ouija board and instructs Kahn to ask "if there are any spirits that are familiar with Manoj" (which I guess is what the M. stands for in M. Night Shyamalan).&nbsp; At which, the Ouija board "eye" literally  jumps  clear across the board towards the "Yes."&nbsp; Right.&nbsp; Because Ouija boards totally work.&nbsp;   The interview "subjects" that Kahn meets are the worst actors of all time.&nbsp; There's the one guy that "accidentally" blurts out that there was another actor considered for Mel Gibson's role in  Signs , then jumps onto an incoming SEPTA train (of course, the interview was conducted on a train platform).&nbsp; There was the other "childhood friend" of Night, who happened to let slip that Night had fallen through the ice of a pond on his family's property, and had been clinically dead for about 35 minutes.&nbsp; You see, Night has actually died, so he  urlLink sees dead people , I guess.  There's this ridiculous scene where they go to visit the house that Night supposedly lived in when he was between the ages of 10 and 12, and it's apparently been on the market for 20 years, or so the actress playing the real estate agent informs us.&nbsp; First of all, none of the floors are warped, none of the paint on the walls is peeling, and it looks like a house that has been recently renovated for the sake of a bogus film crew filming a bogus documentary.&nbsp; AND IT'S THE EXACT SAME HOUSE FROM SIGNS!&nbsp; I smack my forehead at this point.  A billion other little things.&nbsp; When the show went to the first commercial break, it was revealed that the entire special was sponsored by The Village.&nbsp; Of course, I'm sure Touchstone Pictures would support a documentary that is the subject of pending litigation.&nbsp; The internet "chat room" that the documentarian visits to converse with other Angst-Ridden Teens who know Night's secret that looks like no internet chat room I've ever seen.&nbsp; And The fact that the pizza guy just happens to know a lot about the occult.&nbsp; Ugh.   So, I feel like I've been duped, and it was a total waste of three hours of my time.&nbsp;  urlLink Apparently , NBC, which owns Sci-Fi Channel,&nbsp;is pissed off that they duped the media.&nbsp; A spokesman for Sci-Fi even went so far as to give an interview to AP, in which he blatantly  urlLink lied  about the origin of the film.&nbsp; I guess I'm kind of a moron for believing everything I read on  urlLink Page Six , but there you have it.&nbsp; I watched all three hours of it.  And really, memo to all future "schlockumentary"-makers: if you're going to do a spoof documentary, please don't make it three hours long.&nbsp; You don't think I&nbsp;have better things to do with three hours of my life than watch a protracted ad for your new movie?  That being said, I can't wait to see  urlLink The Village .      
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Am I the only one who thought it was much more exciting when Tiger won all the time?&nbsp; This is Todd&nbsp;Hamilton.&nbsp; I've never heard of him, either.  &nbsp; urlLink     The claret jug just won a date with Todd Hamilton.&nbsp; urlLink     
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In  Runaway Jury , one of the most engaging John Grishman novel-turned-films released thus far, Gene Hackman plays Rankin Fitch, a crotchety old bastard who makes his living traveling around the country and profiling juror pools for attorneys.  This juror is too fat.  That juror is too Christian.  Using the most gadgets and gizmos since  Mission Impossible , Fitch's team (which includes  urlLink Marguerite Moreau , who I couldn't place throughout the entire movie until I finally realized that she was in  urlLink Wet Hot American Summer , which is an  awesome  movie, seriously, watch it some time) sorts through the potential jurors, determining which ones will benefit their client.  Dustin Hoffman's also in it, he plays the "good lawyer" fighting against the big gun industry.  He also has a jury consultant, but that character's played by the weenie  urlLink Jeremy Piven  who, incidentally, is on this new HBO show  Entourage , that I will not be able to watch, mostly because I let my HBO subscription lapse after  The Sopranos  season ended.  Anywho, the point of this all is that at one point Hoffman and Hackman meet up in the bathroom of the courthouse.  Or, more accurately, Hoffman follows Hackman in there, and they have this weird moment where Gene shakes Dustin's hand right after he pees, which is kind of gross.  I half expected Gene to say "it's just water," the way people do when they shake hands after they pee, but he didn't.  So I guess in John Grisham-world, you shake hands after urinating regularly.  Hm.  So they're in they're arguing with each other, Dustin's all "how dare you manipulate our legal system," Hackman's all "I am cool and rich and wearing a much more expensive suit than you are."  Hoffman gets all high and mighty, and Hackman retorts:   You think your average juror is King Solomon? No, he's a roofer with a mortgage. He wants to go home and sit in his Barcalounger and let the cable TV wash over him. And this man doesn't give a single, solitary droplet of shit about truth, justice or your American way.   Which I actually thought was a pretty good quote.  For a John Grisham movie.  Oh yeah, John Cusack and Rachel Weisz are in it, too.  Cusack plays a juror that claims to be able to "swing" the jury to decide in favor of whichever side pays him $10 million.  So, yeah, I thought it was an all-right movie.  You know what you're getting with Grisham.  For some reason, the guy always manages to write a lawyer story that involves people getting their asses kicked and their shit blown up.  I don't know how many lawyers have actually chased a speeding car down a New Orleans road in an effort to save their iPod, which contains precious details about their secret contacts, but in Grisham world, it all somehow makes sense. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wait, whaaaaaat?  Rock on with your bad self, A.O. Scott.  "Harold and Kumar"...is [one] of the few recent comedies that persuasively, and intelligently, engage the social realities of contemporary multicultural America."  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I prefer to use the term "bump," because "bounce," as  urlLink ABC News  pointed out, carries all kinds of gravitational implications.   I thought his speech was pretty good. Delivered at a very brisk pace, and very Presidential in tone and rhetoric. I liked his emphasis on his own national security credentials, particularly his war experience, and his non-too-subtle attacks on Bush, Cheney, and Ashcroft were well in line with what he'll need to do in the next month or so to counteract Bush's endless stream of negativity.   I happened to be watching CNN with a bunch of friends, and we heard the entire  urlLink balloon fiasco  firsthand. What were they thinking?&nbsp; Just&nbsp;cut the audio!&nbsp; Cut the audio!&nbsp; It's clear that we shouldn't be hearing this! &nbsp;Just wait, though, Republicans will blame Kerry for the F-bomb on CNN.&nbsp;&nbsp; Jon Stewart, wherever you are, I hope you have ten writers working on this.   Even John's saying, "Where the f@#k are those damn balloons?"&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink      I caught a little bit of Kerry's speech in the North End to begin the "bus tour" while I was on the elliptical this morning at about 7:30 (yes, I wimped out, I didn't do the treadmill, even after my excursion into the world of bad carbs last night). Man, does Theresa just look absurdly bored or what? Someone give that woman an image consultant! Would it kill ya to hire  urlLink Naomi Wolf , maybe make Theresa more of an "alpha female?"        
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Had some friends over tonight for a barbecue... The meal itself was pretty good.&nbsp; Chicken on the grill.&nbsp; Great, right?&nbsp; Unfortunately, my buddy brought over some beers... and I had a few.&nbsp; And then my other buddy brought over some cake.&nbsp; And I had a slice.  So I start officially on the South Beach tomorrow.&nbsp; Damn it.  Thought Kerry's speech was great, though.&nbsp; Too bad I was listening to it with a guilt-wracked conscience.&nbsp; I'll be back on the treadmill tomorrow at&nbsp;7 a.m.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This can't be true, can it?  I mean we're talking about the same publication that ran  urlLink this  gem.   urlLink Wonkette  expresses the appropriate amount of  urlLink skepticism  on this one, and I won't believe it until I see it on  urlLink Drudge . 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Eh, why not?&nbsp; I'm going to the beach for Labor Day weekend and want to look my studliest.&nbsp; So I'm going to give this here  urlLink South Beach Diet  a shot for a few weeks.&nbsp; We'll see how it works.&nbsp; Maybe the thought of posting what I eat up here for all of you to see (i.e. the three people who consistently visit  urlLink KevinMeyers.blog , which is fine by me) will inspire me to stick to it.&nbsp; And if (when) I bail on it, it'll provide endless amusement and humor for my readers.   "Foolproof plan," eh? We'll see about that.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink      So, this morning I decided to sleep through the gym.&nbsp; An auspicious start to a day on the Silent But Deadly diet (that's what I'm going to call it, because it's initials are  urlLink SBD ).&nbsp; My legs are pretty sore from Tuesday, when I had the awesome idea of getting back on the treadmill for the first time since May 2003.&nbsp; I mean, I've been going to the gym fairly regularly since then (I use the term "fairly" very loosely here, folks).&nbsp; But I haven't exactly been back on that wicked treadmill in quite some time.&nbsp; I always chicken out and do the elliptical instead.&nbsp; Or the bike.&nbsp; If I'm on the bike, I can read  urlLink The New York Times , and if I'm on the elliptical I can watch  urlLink Sportscenter .&nbsp; But if I'm on the treadmill, I'm in pain.&nbsp; Lots of pain.&nbsp;   I'm not exactly a runner.&nbsp; If you know what I look like, this doesn't come as a surprise to you.&nbsp; My body was not built for running.&nbsp; If there was a spectrum of body types, I would put myself directly at the opposite end of those  urlLink skinny Kenyans  that keep winning the Boston Marathon.&nbsp; I mean, I'm not exactly fat.&nbsp; I'm just big-boned.   Running to lose weight actually runs in the family, though.&nbsp; My pops did a pretty good job of it, actually running the  urlLink New York City Marathon  twice, in 1990 and 1991.&nbsp; And I am built sort of the same way as my Dad.&nbsp; So if I really got serious about running, I could probably get into some pretty good shape.&nbsp; My problem with running, however, is that it just hurts so damn much.&nbsp; I mean, why torture yourself?&nbsp; You can sit on a bike and get the exact same cardiovascular benefits, and you'll feel the burn in your hamstrings and your thighs, but you won't be unable to climb stairs for the next two weeks, which is the condition I'm in currently.   I ran for 30 minutes on that nasty treadmill, and I finished.&nbsp; That was the most important thing for me -- I finished.&nbsp; I usually quit.&nbsp; But I stuck it out, gritted my teeth, made unholy grunting noises, and frightened every small child within a three-block radius.&nbsp; It was pretty awesome.   So yesterday, because I had run on Tuesday, I decided to bike for 40 minutes.&nbsp; No problem.&nbsp; I like biking so much more than the hell they call running.&nbsp; I read the entire special section of the paper devoted to the DNC, I even had time to peruse the editorial page, and rocked out to my iPod.&nbsp; It was very civilized, I dare say.&nbsp; And I definitely broke a sweat, and definitely felt it in my legs.   So why does everyone hold up running as the be-all and end-all of aerobic exercise?&nbsp; Why not, say, rowing?&nbsp; Or elliptical...ling?&nbsp; Or Stairclimber-ing?&nbsp; I had a trainer once who told me the only aerobic machine that a man should ever think about using was the treadmill.&nbsp; While this macho chutzpah may sound nice to a trainer that spends all his time in a fancypants gym in midtown Manhattan, it was the equivalent of saying to me, "Yeah, the only effective way to cut your toenails is to attach them to the ceiling,&nbsp;hang upside down, and sway back and forth until your toenails rip off and you are a bloody, sweaty, screaming mess."&nbsp; This, to me, is about comparable to running on the treadmill.   The benefits of cardiovascular exercise are apparent.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink      So hopefully if I'm good at this SBD thing, I can take it easy on the treadmill and not kill myself.&nbsp; I had four scrambled eggs with water this morning for breakfast, and some tuna salad for lunch.&nbsp; Tonight we're having some friends over for dinner and I'll be grilling chicken... so I'll just peel the skin off and eat the chicken with some mixed greens. For dessert, maybe a sugar-free Fudgsicle or two.&nbsp; Those are allowed on the diet.   Eh, who knows.&nbsp; Knowing me, I'll probably have three beers, a bowl of ice cream for dessert, and tomorrow morning at 7 a.m. I'll be pounding away on the treadmill.    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm trying to post a picture to the blog, and it ain't working.&nbsp; Ah, well.&nbsp; I should be doing something more productive anyhow... like working!  The Daily Show's coverage of the DNC has been laugh-out-loud funny several times this week.&nbsp; I especially enjoyed Jon Stewart's comments on  urlLink Barak Obama 's Tuesday night  urlLink speech  (which, incidentally, was one of the best speeches I've ever heard in my life... Obama has set a high bar for Kerry).&nbsp; Stewart replayed Obama's famous line: "We coach Little League in the blue states, and yes, we have some gay friends in the red states."&nbsp; Then Stewart added: "To which, the gay friends in the red states replied, 'Ix-nay on the ay-gay'," while making the "cut it out" gesture with his hand across his neck.  I always shudder a little bit, however, when The Daily Show's so-called "correspondents" start into one of their feaux-serious commentaries.&nbsp; It's just a little too much.&nbsp; Besides, Stewart himself is such a great comedian that I often feel as though the Steven Colberts and Rob Corddrey's of the world are just bush league compared to the all-star sitting at the desk.&nbsp; I happened to catch Stewart being interviewed by Ted Koppel last night on Nightline, but was falling asleep as I watched, and didn't catch much of it.&nbsp; Ted Koppel has the tendency to do that to me.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I find myself refreshing  urlLink Wonkette  almost as often as  urlLink CNN  these days...  Where else can you  urlLink learn  about kinky sex available on Craig's List in Boston? 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm going to be the captain of a team in a fall touch football league here in Manhattan.&nbsp; It's run by  urlLink Zogsports , a company that donates shares of its revenues to charity.&nbsp; If you want to join, shoot me an e-mail.&nbsp; We especially need girls.&nbsp; For football.&nbsp; Seriously.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ryan McGee, one of my friends from college, has a pretty great blog that I'd like someday this little modest effort to look a little bit like.  In any case, the dude lives in Boston, and it sucks to be him this week because of the convention.  He's posting daily recaps, which are great.  Hopefully my life won't suck at the end of August, when the Republicans descend upon our fair city.  As in, hopefully I won't get anthrax on the subway or something... 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I haven't had much time in the past few days, what with being at Bear Mountain for a wedding from Friday through Sunday, and dealing with mountains of paperwork when I returned to my desk yesterday.&nbsp; I'm back, though, and am going to worry about publishing at  urlLink www.kevinmeyers.com  as soon as I can.&nbsp; Until then, though, I'm going to keep it here at  urlLink Blogspot , just so I don't have to worry about any issues that might crop up (like the photos not linking correctly, as was evidenced yesterday).  If I have some time this afternoon I'll post my thoughts on last night's speeches at the DNC.&nbsp; In short, I thought Gore was great.&nbsp; Self-deprecating humor always works well with politicians, especially Gore (since I've never seen Gore be  funny  at all), and I thought his speech was a great warm-up for the crowd to get them revved up for the Clintons.&nbsp; I didn't see much of Carter, since I was cleaning up from dinner while he was speaking, but I thought Hillary and Bill were fine.&nbsp; And as one of the commentators on CNN observed this morning, this may be the last convention at which Hillary introduces Bill, not the other way around.  I am looking forward to tonight's debut of convention coverage from  The Daily Show .&nbsp; That's always a treat.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As you can see, I am having problems getting my pictures to link properly, especially now since I am publishing on  urlLink www.kevinmeyers.com .  I hope to get it fixed soon, as well as provide a full report of my weekend.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       CNN reports that the first three seasons of  Seinfeld  are  finally  coming to DVD on November 23 "just in time for Festivus."  I don't know much about the cast contracts, but I do remember reading that there was some hullaballo when Michael Richards agreed to participate in this DVD.  Apprently he broke ranks.  But whichever way you slice it, these DVDs are going to be a gold mine for Larry David.  Lucky son of a... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey all. Sorry I didn't write much today. In fact, sorry, I didn't write much of anything today. Not that there wasn't a lot to write about. A wealthy Republican in Houston is financing television commercials that purport that John Kerry did some pretty awful things while in Vietnam, and Bush hasn't distanced himself from it... it's getting ugly, and we're not even a week into August, folks. The economy continues to tank, and New York continutes to be on edge... if not because of terror warnings, because of monkeys that might attack us in our local supermarkets. Seriously, folks, that really happened. Recently.  I'm on my way up to Cape Cod tomorrow morning for an all-too-brief respite with my family. I haven't taken a family vacation since... well, I don't remember when. But we're driving up tomorrow morning, and my sister and I are driving back on Monday afternoon. So I'll probably only really have one full day at the Cape (Sunday). It's likely that Dad will want me to come golfing with him and Patrick, so I won't really even have quality time at the beach. But I suck at golf, and I rock at sitting on the beach and relaxing. So I think I'm going to opt for the latter. Maybe I'll pick up a good paperback (the 9/11 Commission Report just isn't doing it in the "beach reading" category) and try to plow my way through it on Sunday at the beach. We'll see.  My buddies came over for a barbecue last week and accidentally left some chicken legs in the garbage can on our back deck that we never use. We didn't realize this until this morning, when we walked out on to the deck and confronted the vilest, most heinous stench ever known to mankind. So I spent about 45 minutes this morning hosing down our back deck. Except we don't have a hose. So I repeatedly ran into the kitchen sink, filled a bucket, and dumped it all over the spot on the deck where the chicken was sitting. The true test comes tonight when we have some friends over. Will they notice? Well, even if they do, we'll just blame it on the neighbors.  Or we'll just drink enough beer that hopefully our senses will be dulled.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Fantastic.  Chest and back.  Well, a little bit of back, at least.  And then 30 minutes on the ol' elliptical.  Damn, I'm proud of myself.  Don't mind if I toot my own horn for a bit, do ya?  Toot toot.  There I go.  Tomorrow I'm  really  going to try to do the 6 a.m. thing.  We'll see how that pans out.  Somehow the pillow has a habit of calling out to me when that alarm first goes off...  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So  urlLink here's  that article everyone's talking about, you know, the one about Flight 327, where the Syrian dudes kept doing weird things.  It's definitely a chilling read, especially if you are prone to dreaming about things you read about, which I am, which means that the other night I had a dream that I was on this flight, only in my dream the plane landed safely and the FBI arrested all the terrorists.  I think I was a hero.  Or at least somehow involved in apprehending the bad guys.  But Annie Jacobsen's article should definitely be required reading for every American citizen, if only to remind us of the dangers that are still present, and the risks that have just become a part of our everyday lives since 9/11.  One of the biggest arguments I've ever had in my entire life concerned racial profiling.  It was right after 9/11, and my college roommate and I had just read an article in Newsweek advocating the use of torture on terror suspects.  I'm unclear on how it got to profiling, but we wound up having a very vociferous debate, we wound up both thinking the other person was crazy and un-American, and it was awful.  So, I've tried to avoid the subject since then.  Jacobsen's article just re-opens the question... why does our government insist on screening every Grannie from Nebraska and four-year-old child and let young Middle Eastern men waltz right onto the jetway without so much as a sideways glance?  Now comes Steven Landsburg of  urlLink Slate  with an  urlLink idea  to offer every passenger selected for screening a crisp $100 bill in consideration for their trouble.  It's an interesting idea, but purely from that "interesting academic solution to a problem, but probably not feasible" perspective, especially since airlines are just tumbling into bankruptcy these days.  If United Airlines have to skip payments to its pension plan, it sure as hell ain't going to subsidize air travel for those high-risk passengers that are going to get searched. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If there was a line graph charting the average posts-per-day of this blog, it would probably look a little bit like a graph of Anna Nicole Smith's weight.  It starts off real low, then balloons up for a while, then suddenly, inexplicably, drops back down close to its original baseline.  Well, I've been a little bit busy of late... work has been crazy this week.  Hopefully things will slow down (ha!) and I'll be able to keep being funny, witty, articulate, you know how it is.  But for now, I'm trying to write as much as possible, with the warning that I probably won't be able to do it this weekend -- I'll be at the beach and away from the computer.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some of you might be wondering why I wrote in my  urlLink previous  post that I caught the end of last night's Yankees game on TV, while I had  urlLink previously  written that I would be headed out to Yankee Stadium to catch the game live. Well, I wimped out. The forecast called for rain, and I was broke. So I sold my tickets for less than face value to a friend of a friend, and caught most of the game on YES while eating dinner.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been quite lethargic recently.  Say that word several times, will you?  Lethargic.  Lethargy.  Lethargiousness.  It's a fun word.  The funny thing about this, is that I've had such high ambitions for myself.  For example, every single day this week, I've set my alarm for 6 a.m., and yet have not gotten out of bed until at least 7:15.  On Sunday I decided that I really wanted to hit the gym hard this week, and so I was going to train myself to get my lazy ass out of bed at 6, just like I used to do when I lived in Jersey and commuted to New York.  Unfortunately, in my current apartment, where the  urlLink gym  is about a three-minute bike ride from bed, the motivation just isn't there.  Take this morning, for example.  Last night, as I was heading to bed, I set the alarm for 6, as I usually do.  I didn't really get to sleep until about 11:45, after I had watched the end of the Yankees game (which went to 11 innings) and The Daily Show, which was probably a bad idea for the whole getting-up-at-the-crack-of-dawn plan.  I woke up at about 5:30 and thought to myself "I'm far too tired to be getting up in 30 minutes," so I re-set my alarm for 7.  Unfortunatley, when the alarm went off at 7, I re-set it for 7:30.  When it went off at 7:30, I hit the snooze button repeatedly until about 8:15, at which point I just re-set the alarm for 8:35.  That's when I finally got up.  Gave me enough time to read the paper and have some breakfast before heading to work.  If you're wondering how I can possibly be this lazy and still get to work on time, my office doesn't open for business until 10 a.m.  It's great.  So tonight I'm going to kick my own body's ass.  Going to lift chest and back, and do 30 minutes of cardio.  Probably the elliptical, since my legs took until yesterday to recover from the 30 minutes I did on the treadmill on Monday.  I don't want to be out of commission all weekend, when I'll be up in Cape Cod, so I'll take it easy on the ol' legs.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wednesday is here... and with it, Yankees tickets. Going up to the Stadium again tonight, which should be good times.  urlLink Last time  I got to see a Yankees 10-3 victory over the hapless Toronto Blue Jays, so tonight's game against the AL West leading Oakland A's should be a little bit more exciting. I got all of these tickets through some kind of season ticket package that I bought at the beginning of the season. I get 10 games for $80 per ticket. Not bad. Most of the games are mid-week affairs, and Oakland is the best opponent I get all year. I've also seen Detroit, Colorado, Toronto, and I think there's another Toronto game lurking later on in the year.  Things are good these days. The weather in New York is absolutely disgusting. Every day for the past week has been one of two things: rainy and miserable, or muggy and miserable. Today it's the latter. Today's forecast calls for a high of 88 and humidity around 75%. It's like walking around in a sauna. To make matters worse, New York doesn't have the most reliable sanitation system, so there's the ever-present stench of hot garbage wafting up from the street. Summer in New York is the air conditioners were invented. I think we've been running ours non-stop for the last week or so. Our ConEd bill should be fun, whenever it comes.  My landlord has yet to deposit the rent check I gave him on Sunday 8/1, so it doesn't look like it'll bounce. That's good news. I have  just  enough in there to cover my half of this month's rent, so that if the check were to clear today I would have a checking account balance of about two dollars. That's what hand-to-mouth means, isn't it? Tomorrow's pay day, so at least that'll recharge the ol' batteries for a while. My checking account balance sort of crescendoes as we get to the end of the month, reaching it's apogee during the final days of the month, and then I pay the rent and make my monthly deposit into my IRA, and it all comes crashing down as close to zero as possible. I have two dollars in my pocket of cash right now. Maybe I can sneak a hard-boiled egg into Yankee Stadium tonight. That's just as good as hot dogs and beer, right?  I know, it's pitiful.  New York is fine.  Nobody has bombed us yet.  But Slate has an interesting  urlLink article  about the Citicorp Tower, one of the subjects of this week's terror alerts.  Apparently it's cursed or something.  Wow.  Glad I don't work there.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In the annals of bad, crummy, depressing days, this has to rank up there. For example, just yesterday I wrote a rent check for the month of August and handed it to my landlord. Lo and behold, when I check my account balance this morning, I realize that I'm about 80 bucks short. So whenever Tomasz gets around to depositing that check, it's going to bounce higher than a tennis ball on speed. And that was at 10 a.m.  Oh yeah, and I fell off the South Beach wagon last night. Hard. Real hard. Pizza and beers hard. But you know what? Best pizza and beers I've ever had in my entire life.  And if that wasn't bad enough,  urlLink what   urlLink do   urlLink we   urlLink get   urlLink in   urlLink our   urlLink lovely   urlLink city  this  urlLink morning ?  Good doggie. Bad terrorist. Big flag.  urlLink     urlLink     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>