<Blog>


<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
        Christmas.....    Well as all of you people know  urlLink Christmas  is  urlLink wonderfully  celebrated all around the world today! Now im sure that all you people had your  urlLink fun  and spent it with you  urlLink loving-caring   urlLink family . All you people make me  urlLink sick  Psh! who needs when you can waste two bucks and go to  urlLink Dreamlabs ? Ha! you people. You guys are missing the true meaning of urlLink  Christmas  i tell ye!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Christmas Carols......   my my today was quite a glourious day! I went caroling with my good friends ben and......kevin....... Came across a couple of houses that were actually quite friendly.....while some were complete bitches...we started to walk on lemon street when we saw this house with a variety of christmas ornaments...and i thought to my self Hey this house looks friendly enough! Little did we know that we were about to fall into the hands of christmas-hating fag.....and so we rang the doorbell..after a minute the door opened and there standing was a guy in his mid 40s that probably never got layed in his life screeching and screaming saying that he was having phone sex with his mom and it was long distance and told us to go away.....well we did what anyone would do in that kind of a situation......we continued caroling and plotted to throw tangerines we received from an earlier participant...but we decided not to since kevin had to go home and have fun with his family for the remainder of the day.......i then returned to bens house and played fooseball.........cheers............. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Alas Christmas Vacation Has Finally Arrived......    YES! Christmas Vacation has finally arrived! NO MORE BRANNUM SUCKERS! JOY TO THE MOTHERFU**** WORLD! Since nothing much happened today..i will now leave the rest of this post with expressions of my hate for Mrs Brannum..................HAHAHAHHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHA...FU** YOU MRS. BRANNUM! LETS SEE YOU TRY TO ADENINE TRIPHOSPHATE THIS BITCH! ROT IN THE DIRT! HAHAHAHHAHAHAH! THE MOTHERFUC*** DIRT! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHHAHAHA!..........................toodles.......
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       My life is horrible...just horrible    My day SUCKED ASS..I was having a wonderful dream about me and my flying scooter...when these motherfu**** parrots woke me up..yea thats right PARROTS..you know those parrots that perch on a branch of a tree just waiting for you to fall asleep..they wait and wait until you look like you're relaxed and enjoying your wonderful sleep..they then fly around the whole damn place and start screaming non-stop..so then i went out side and figured that if i told them to SHUT THE FU** UP.........politely they might stop..and so i then said " Hey parrot...SHUT THE FU** UP!" It kept on squawking...i tried to communicate with it for about a hour or so...after that I realized that they couldnt understand me..so i made my way to school to find that i had two finals..........  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
                        BLEHHHH!!    Much thanks to  urlLink  kevin   for helping start a wonderful blog in which i am gratefully entitled to. Well people, this is my amazing new blog........amazing isnt it my lad?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      hello stuart this is your new blog.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Jackasses.......   As all of you know, today was the musical marathon. The marathon was basically a concert of performances by all the volunteers in the musical. Ben and I decided to do a little performance which turned out to be a real success. Although there were some flaws before the actual marathon, we did well. For example, the jackass that forgot the music to our performance at bens house when i put in  right  in his hand. I wont mention who since i know the person is going to complain afterwards, we will just call this mysterious person mr. k. Well mr k. is a real jack ass........thats all i have to say. And great glourious love to all of you that came to the musical marathon and supported your loving friends.....Well until next time....cherrio my lads.....
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Pissed..............   How fun is it to spend your Sundays going up to houses asking for money? The answer? Very! And so, my day started at Bens house. After 15 minutes of trying to get  urlLink ben  out of bed i realized that he wouldn't give up with a fight. And so the war begun...I started out by throwing all the things I could find in the house at him....he started making these gargling noises on the top bunk of the bed. He suddenly pulled out this long green stick from the covers and hit me on the head with it... I fell back and landed on his bottom bunk. It must of been half an hour that I was held captive with Bens brother Calvin. I then realized that I must fight back if the pledges were to ever get sent back to  urlLink King Byers . I summoned all the courage I can muster and stepped out....I was hit on the head again. This time I rushed and hit Ben with a pillow, this proved powerful since he clumsily slammed his own head against the ceiling and wall about 5 times. It was then till I got him out of bed and went out to get pledges. We went around temple city and asked people for money......I had worked so hard going around at least 15 houses and had only brought back 56 dollars............ urlLink Ben  on the other hand had gotten a 200 dollar check from only one house..........The  urlLink madness ............................................................................................    urlLink  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A Fair Warning.....   Hello my dear friends! It is me once again! I am writing this entry simply to warn you. You know those words that are highlighted and lead to a site? Yea um.....dont click them........so to those of you that still dont get it.......click+on blue words=bad.......I created those links simply to express my hatred for something and or the subject that i am writing about....clicking on one of those links can ruin your whole life. Take  urlLink Eric  for example, it just so happened that Erics dad was standing right next to him when he did this......so again do not to those  urlLink links ...i am not responsible for any of the viewer's actions and or  urlLink accidents . So then, there you have  urlLink it .
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Mopeds........they will be the death of us.....   Ah, wasn't it a wonderful day my friends? While you people were out with family and having the time of your life on a sunny sunday afternoon, i almost died on a moped thanks to my  urlLink trusty good   driver ben. We would never get in an accident if we were going at 60 miles per hour. Whos afraid of dieing when you have a friend that tells you that the human heads is magic and is invunerable to anything?! And so the day started with us trying to get the moped engine started but we worked our way through it. So we went around Temple City and almost got caught by the cops. But Hey! It was all worth it we went to go buy some groceries! After that we decided to drop by the highschool and waste most of our time there. It was then when these two old, fat retarded people went up to us and said something about how extremely gay they were and started telling us yo-mama jokes....(o yes they also  said something about a break-in). And that my lads, is how i spent my wonderful Sunday.   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       The Musical.......   Ah, the  musical . Isn't it just glorious to hear that one word uttered? Well, if none of you already know, auditions for the musical was held today. And so, my wonderful friends and I tried out for the musical!(most of which were forced to by retarded drama teachers) Anyhow, we tried out for the vocal part first and might I say it was horrible....None of us knew how  urlLink  any   of the songs went. We then came back to school for dance audition. We were then taught a few dance moves by these old teachers in tights. It was then when I thought to myself, "Why do we have to watch these old people in tights try to teach you how to do a "ass fault" when just drop dead on the floor and start spasming like a retard? They would never know the difference. I swear, all you do basically is to jump all around the room and make retarded sounds. Seriously, if I wanted to watch some do that I could of just sat through one of Mrs Brannum's lectures. Well after that I went home and slept.  -----------------------Until next time my good friends!-------------------------    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Crap.........   Days of our age fly by with such speed, dont you agree my lad? Well just for the record, the past few days of my winter vacation was totally a big pile of steaming monkey crap. I did nothing at all but wander the crappy streets of Temple City stepping on big piles of crap. I also went to my good comrades house to practice gay crappy songs for the crappy musical auiditions tommorow in which my crappy lesbian drama teacher forced me into. Well tommorow another school day begins and the reign of the she-male biology teacher from hell begins.Well i am off to go into hibernation now, cherrio. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       2004.....   Happy New Year my dear dear friends! Ah isnt it just wonderful?! All of us are off with a brand new start! And what better way to celebrate 2004 than to get up at 6 and watch the Rose Parade?! So i turned on the television and started watching...However, after waiting 2 hours to watch our school perform i concluded that the rose parade was utterly boring and complete crap....so i decided to turn around and walk back to my room. When i was half way there i realized something....i had to confront the evil  horrible peice of shit biology book from hell! So i figured what the hell? I survived the hell of first Rose Parade... why not watch the 5 other encores that followed? After 8 hours of listening to Bob and Stephanie insult each.......i started to go mad.....as i was on a verge of ripping my hair out... i suddenly heard a soft faint ring....i thought to myself, "Could it be?" I heard the ring again....Yes! It is! im saved! It was the phone! As i ran towards the phone i prayed to god that it was one of my good comrades that would take me away from this hellhole! I slowly picked up the phone........it was a telemarketer....................
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A Complete Transformation.........   To those of you who don't know what The Winter Retreat is...I will now take my wonderful time to explain. The Winter Retreat was basically a 4 day camp for those people who want to learn about Jesus or simply just to find themselves through Jesus Christ. And after coming back from the Winter Retreat, all I have to say is wow. Not only have I learned tremendously about Jesus, but I have rediscovered him as well. I have also witnessed Gods great power of healing people. I literally sat there and watched our preacher heal almost every one in the room. I have also made  such  great friends at this Winter Retreat. I've only known these people for 3 days, but it seems that we have known each other for like 3 years. We have created a strong bond through God, we are chained together through the Lord. I also have the most faith in God then I have ever had in my entire life. Lord Jesus just opened the doors to my heart and saved me. The Lord just literally turned my whole life around 540 degrees. I just feel that I have completed my life by building that ladder of faith towards God and building it so I can have a strong bonding relationship with him. To all of you non-believers out there I have only one thing to tell you guys: The Lord  is   real . You might say oh no God isnt real, wheres the proof? Just because there is not enough evidence to prove it  does not  mean that he does not exist. Everyone must have  faith  in order to reach out to god. God  is    real  and he  really does exist  no matter what  anyone  says. Our Lord Jesus Christ. I realize that our Lord Jesus Christ is what I have been missing in my entire life.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A Wonderful Movie.....   Today I went to go see the movie, " The Butterfly Effect". This movie is excellent and truly a work of art. I would have to say that it is the best movie i have seen this year. I highly recomend it to anyone out there who would like to see a movie that is both brilliant and sad. If anyone should disagree with me they should go watch the movie over and over again until they agree with me. that is all. cheers
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Busy.....   hello my dear friends......it really has been a long time since i have been updating. I have been really busy lately with homework and other things so it will be quite a while since I am going to update.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       April Fools!..Jackasses...   As all of you people today is the wonderful holiday known as April Fools Day. Horrible! Just Horrible! I mean seriously how can we categorize this as a holiday next to our presidents birthdays and other important holidays. April Fools just takes up space in the calendar to put more important things.....like pictures for example. We can replace "April Fools Day" a bunch of colorful squares and triangles to fill up the space. At least these decorations can at least look eye-pleasing...Take a lesson from another one of the adventures of...Todd and Fred. Observe.  Todd(laughing like a retard, runs up to Fred and slaps him on the head): APRIL Z  FOOLS Z ! HAHAHAHAHA Z !  (Fred becomes very angry but ignores Todds actions and walks away)  Fred then being the jackass that he is slams in to a pole while running and decides to go home, on the way back Fred is then hunted down by flying monkey-wombats from outer space( z  can save you now buddy)  See what happened to Fred kids? He suffered from a monkey-wombat beating to the max. Poor Fred. This is why you  never ,  ever  do something like what Fred did.     Kids, April Fools Day is the cause of all these smiling jackasses running around slapping people on the head whining, "April Fools!" Hahahahahahahah......Yea next time I'll take a pogo stick and shove it up your ass........APRIL FOOLS! Jackasses..........
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well hello there my fellow viewers of Stuarts' wonderful blog. This is Stuart and he is extremely awesome and cool. Well i never thought it would come to this,  but after going undercover for S.A.C (secret agency of anti communists) I have finally taken over the schools main control room. Now to all of you people that didn't know that the school had a main control room, you have been brain-washed by communist fobs such as, ben and kevin.This control room contains the most advance tecnology in the world and is located in a maximum security facility in the quad. Some people might question by authority, accuse me of lying, and even say that there is no maximun security facility! Well, there is! And anyone who disagrees with me will be hunted down by an agent of the Anti-Communists Agency and when we catch you, you will then be mated with a bloody, diseased infected Neanderthal. Now, my mission wasn't so easily accomplished, there were explosive blood-sucking communists on giraffes roaming all over the school campus so it was hell to even get inside the main hallways. As i walked towards the the main hall way i saw two paths i could take to get to the quad. The hallway to the right infested with bloody  communist zombies or the hallway to the left that would take me directly to the quad with no zombies at all. I chose the hallway to the right. As i entered i saw 10 zombies run for me. I smiled, took out a crate of eggs, and started to throw them a the zombies. I watched in horror as they devoured them one by one. I remembered thinking to myself this is it stuart! You're going to die! But then, suddenly a thought came into my head, the bible! I took out my bible as fast as i could and flipped to Matthew chapter 13 verse 20................ and threw it at the zombies. They immediately began to melt and in to a pool of crushed maggots and bloody body parts. I continued onward with my mission and rolled on a field of grass and flowers. There i rolled for hours and hours until i realized that my clothes were covered with dirt. So then, i got up and dusted the dirt off of my clothes. I then dropped to the ground and started to roll again, but  this time, i rolled all the way to the entrance of the forbidden quad. I got up and and walked slowly to the coke machines, my footsteps echoing as i did so. I walked and walked until i reached a coke machine. I then took out a dollar bill, inserted it in and selected a coke. The machine shook a little and then suddenly exploded! Not a single bottle of coke came out...... I dropped to my knees and started to cry. A whole hour passed before i could pull myself together. I stood up and walked towards a golden door, but then, a sudden screech made me jump....I turned around and looked....nothing......then it happened again...SCREEH WHEEZ!....i turned around...to my  horror i saw a monstorous figure in the distance looking at me, this creature was a half pig half woman infested monster that wheezed ever few seconds. Unexpectingly the creature suddenly ran towards me with such speed, that i barely had enough time to react. But then, a sudden unexplainable rage came over me , one so intense and powerful that i began to shake in fury. As it got closer i screamed and started to run away. For some reason after this happened i blacked out and when i woke up i found myself on the streets naked with eggs smeared all over my body.............Hey, its my birthday, give me a break....   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello Stuart,  Me am kevin. Me am stupid me is. HAHAHA!    -Kevin   Hmm, funny.  That was Stuart.  I'm going to leave what he said under my name intact; just to show how really stupid  he  is.    -The real  urlLink Kevin      Hmm, very cool. That was an amazingly cool sexy guy. I'm going to leave what he said under my name intact; just to show how really cool  Stuart  is.  - The real  urlLink Kevin     O yes and I am stupid. I am Kevin.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello people. It is your good friend Stuart once again, back online, and ready to blog. Now, I have gotten a tremendous load of fan mail delivered to me, asking me why I haven't blogged in such a long time. I  could  tell you guys but then that would ruin the fun! So lets just say, I was kidnapped by a pack of wolves, starved for 3 days, and then killed them all with salt and plastic. Well lets give a update on my life shall we? During the last few months of school I decided to join the Brighter Side Singers and see which path of hell it would take on. Now, people, let me tell you first of all, The Brighter Side Singers Organization is  not  all fun and games.....You have to  sing .......... dance ........... act ...be deprived of the money used to feed your family loaves of bread and oil.....give up your...... virginity  . Horrible. Well, about two weeks ago I decided to earn some money for my "brighter side expenses". So, I went to the snow cone machine snack bar place to work. Now being a somewhat normal person, I said, " Hey what the hell? Its a hot day! I'll be a son of a gun if we don't have thousands of customers!" Brighter Side.......manipulated me. For two straight hours I tasted 24 assorted flavors of snowcone flavoring. Cherry, Strawberry, apple, bubble gum, root beer, raspberry, lime....................................................... ............................................................. ............................................................. ................................................AHHHHH!!!!! Finally out of pure madness and rage I went blind and jumped through a brick wall..........    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Man today's worship was frickin crazy and amazing. I felt that today was a day where God really used his Holy Spirit to really just captivate all of our hearts. I really feel that God gave us a little sight and the smell of heaven and how it really feels like to worship God with all your might, strength, and heart. Amazing. Man i was frickin losing my voice and screaming all of the songs punk rock style. Well, I certainly got my 4 hours of intense excercise. My calves are so frickin sore.......BURGHHH! Well, until next time.    - stool from S.A.C. out    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>