<Blog>

<date>21,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        It's not about what you get (from the world), it's about what you add.  I received this  urlLink Suggestion  on the first  snowman  day of 2002.  I was in a good mood because I knew my kids and I would probably get out and do some snow sculpting when I got home.  I had already seen some kids up (7:00 in the morning!) planning their snow creations.  Half way through my run, I met two kids (3 & 5 years old?) who didn't even know  how  to make a snow man.  Their dad looked on while I taught them how.  They were really excited when I told them it was up to them to decorate their snowman. Only the  urlLink PBGs  could arrange that my unique talent would be useful to give joy to those kids and to bring that family together that snowy morning.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       From Mo: 
   Posted 12.14.2003 3:37 PM    urlLink Damsels in distress   
Sometimes the single act of a rescue which doesn't seem to have any redeaming 
qualities to it at the time may be that wink from a stranger that becomes a sign that there is a bigger picture than what we see. Who knew that my friendly smile in church to someone I don't feel comfortable with all the time would lead in a small way to that person getting baptised? In some ways I think 
it would be better not to know how a small action can ripple into something larger. That you could get a woman to smile at all in the midst of an angry, tragic change may be the angel in you reaching out to comfort her when she 
needed it most.      
  urlLink Red Faced Squirrel  replies  
Oh, I agree completely. I thought it was nice of the PBGs to arrange 
that she be there for my baptism too. She seemed even grumpier yesterday. But, my helping her out may have touched her on a deeper level and who knows how long that 'infection' will 'fester' in her heart. It is my job to be me and do what I do and let go and let God after that point. I have to focus on what is my job and let others take care of there own lives. I have decided that I am a servant of God and that I must do what is in my God madate (from either his Calls (can I have an unlisted number please) or from my own feelings of 'right-ness') for every decision that is presented to me by life. If the call is to go to Red Deer to help out a friend, I go to Red Deer (if Mo lets me to of course). In short, you gotta be true to who you are. Period. Oh, and listen for that small  urlLink God voice . That is important too.  
    Posted 9.29.2003 5:13 PM   Messy stories  
I really like where you're going  urlLink here , a proactive approach that has to ride out the storms and find happiness where it can. I hope to read more soon!    Posted 9.17.2003 11:47 AM   Humor  
Like fire,  urlLink humor   can warm the soul or burn the fingers and takes lots of practise. I follow that ancient clown, Jesus, who talked of being non-judgemental and kind but having goofy stories to make a point (anyone tried sewing with a camel stuck in their needle recently???).    Posted 9.17.2003 11:45 AM    urlLink Playing around , are you???  
What on earth is Noahidism? or Jainism? Is that like silly things that Jane of Jungle says? I'm glad that you're not into that youngest of femme fatale's, Miss Atheism. She really is quite young, only about 3 or 400 (if that). It's okay to play the field for a bit and we can learn so much from them all (ask me about Gnosticism some time).    Posted 9.4.2003 11:12 AM   Spiritual doggy biscuits  
But, I want some  urlLink doggy biscuits ! I'll be a good puppy too, and never miss the newspaper. I guess the PBGs' love is to treat me with more respect than that. I'm not a dog, I'm a partner and bribing implicates imbalance. 

 From Twisted Squirrel (TS): 
   Posted 12.16.2003 11:43 AM   Inspiration  
I think you may have missed your calling, or maybe you are on the path. Perhaps one day you will discover that people will look to you to minister in an official capacity. I admire the fact that you always look for the good in people and situations. 
A quote that I liked and recorded goes something like this "Perhaps it is not the goal but the journey we should appreciate."

Take care my good friend. 

 Encouragements: 

   Posted 10.07.2003 10:44 AM  To:  urlLink wazzoo   Advice  
You are each other's strength.  Give your daughter what strength you can spare and both of you will be stronger for it.

The night is darkest before the dawn.
If what you need is an ear, I will listen.

 urlLink Kia Kaha  

 Links   croxis   -  "Dream like you can touch the stars. Love like you have never been hurt, and Dance like no one is watching".  Warning, adult content 

       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        It's not about fee for service.  This  urlLink  Suggestion  , because it was the first, took a long time to formulate in my consciousness.  It is, I think, (so far) the most important tenant of the  urlLink PBGs .  I began to understand this Suggestion when they [the PBGs] provided cans on days I didn't clean up my 'alley' or chose a different path than the one they suggested.  For me, this Suggestion means that following the PBGs does not lead to monitory gain or  spiritual doggie biscuits .  Return on investment is   not   part of the contract.  The flip side of this Suggestion is that if you choose the way of the PBGs, you can be guaranteed that your participation is part of the grand scheme and will be beneficial to someone, somewhere, sometime in the big PBGs' time-frame.  No promises, just a guarantee!

       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you have found this on-line journal by an act of fate (or more likely because of a google search) you may be wondering what "PBGs" stands for. 

That is a long and interesting story.  Some of the answers to that question are contained in my journal entries themselves. Some of the answers are left up to you to find on your own spiritual journey. 

For the impatient here is the quick answer:  PBGs is a short code-word for Pop Bottle Gods.  

And now for the longer answer.  Here is what I have determined about the PBGs thus far on  my  journey. 

I am a  Runner  (no, not a  Jogger , a  Runner ) and I have spent many lonely hours pounding the pavement training for marathons.  If I were to go into the reasons I run, this would be an even longer story, so I'll leave that for another day. 

Anyway, over the summer I started a conversation (sort of a thought experiment at first) where I thought about God.   

Now, don't get me wrong... I am not a 'religious nut' by any means.  I go to church with my family, but for most of my life I have been a questioning Agnostic.  I am not, myself, a member of our church. Until recently, I didn't think I had  any  kind of faith. 

God was too big a concept for me to handle in my own musing. 

So I imagined my own pair of gods whom I could interact with (notice the lower case 'g' on that folks).  You may say "this guy is nuts! Not one but  two  gods!".  Well that is what came to me.  I have since learned not to argue with where my mind wanders. 

Bear with me while I digress a bit more.  I also pick things up on my runs.  During my runs, I pick up grocery bags (usually stuck on bushes) and fill them with pop cans and bottles I find lying around. This practice started out as a way to justify buying expensive running shoes ($100+) on a very small running budget.  Because of this habit of mine, I am always looking around and squinting at bits of garbage trying to determine if I am seeing a slurpie cup top or the bum of a beer can. 

The PBGs came into the picture when I started wondering to myself about why some days there were lots of cans and bottles and other days there were virtually none.  I invented small gods to be in control of a small aspect of my confusing world.  The Pop Bottle Gods were born. 

It wasn't until much later that I discovered that these small fragments of the 'bigger' God (you know, the one everybody else believes in) were simply a metaphor that made it easier to deal with my God phobia. 

After my run, I would often relate what I had been thinking about to my well-read church-going wife.  It stared out as a fun game and she would sometimes jokingly ask "How were the PBGs today?"  We came up with the short hand name to hide our embarrassment for inventing a god (2 actually) and so that we could talk about it without people asking a lot of questions that required long answers. 

One day, she said "You know, that sounds a lot like what I reading recently" in a book about spirituality. 

After this I started paying more attention to the thoughts that occurred during my morning runs.  In fact, I started a journal to record what the PBGs and I 'talked' about. 

  

This is that journal.  It is part running log and part spiritual journey.  Share it with me.  See where I am at.  Laugh at me if you want. Take away with you only the parts that make sense and discard what doesn't fit for you. 

  

Just a note about the   urlLink Suggestions   and   urlLink Suppositions   

   Suggestions  are the  commandments  of the PBGs.  They are meant to be followed.  Like most commandments, they are deliberately vague and can be interpreted anyway that makes sense to you. I call them Suggestions because, hey, these are minor gods, after all.  Who are they to tell you how to run your life. 
  Suppositions  are not quite strong enough to be Suggestions, but have a supporting role.  I haven't attempted to attach Suppositions to a specific Suggestion.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      This here is a list of ALL the pages in my blog by title. It is a handy tool for me when I am doing self referring links and it removes a long list of links from my sidebar. I will only be updating it periodically, so if you want current links look to the  urlLink current page  or the archive pages  
DATE: 4/2/2004 09:52:01 AM&nbsp; urlLink Spam Report: Is It A Stroke?  
DATE: 3/30/2004 11:34:00 AM&nbsp; urlLink Spam Report: $25 Million for nothing  
DATE: 3/25/2004 12:38:06 PM&nbsp; urlLink Bible: Chapter and Verse  
DATE: 3/23/2004 09:22:37 AM&nbsp; urlLink Spam Report: Not Tickle-ish  
DATE: 3/8/2004 09:54:42 AM&nbsp; urlLink Spam Report: Administration Masquerade  
DATE: 3/1/2004 02:03:12 PM&nbsp; urlLink Running Record  
DATE: 3/1/2004 01:00:27 PM&nbsp; urlLink Mel Gibson&acute;s &quot;The Passion of The Christ&quot;  
DATE: 2/27/2004 09:27:14 PM&nbsp; urlLink Given Up For Lent  
DATE: 2/24/2004 12:57:48 PM&nbsp; urlLink Phone Phobia Action  

DATE: 2/18/2004 04:00:02 PM&nbsp; urlLink One Step Back  
DATE: 2/5/2004 10:09:34 PM&nbsp; urlLink Memory Palace  
DATE: 2/4/2004 09:24:37 AM&nbsp; urlLink Consider a Change In Direction  
DATE: 1/29/2004 06:59:03 PM&nbsp; urlLink The Innocent and The Shy  
DATE: 1/28/2004 11:09:46 AM&nbsp; urlLink It&acute;s Blog-citing!  
DATE: 1/25/2004 02:59:04 PM&nbsp; urlLink Phone Phobia  

DATE: 1/23/2004 09:13:25 AM&nbsp; urlLink New Phase  
DATE: 1/14/2004 12:01:08 AM&nbsp; urlLink Revisit the Past  
DATE: 1/13/2004 10:17:57 PM&nbsp; urlLink Will Blogging save the World?  
DATE: 1/12/2004 12:39:01 PM&nbsp; urlLink Native Spirituality II  
DATE: 12/16/2003 06:49:47 PM&nbsp; urlLink Pop bottle of Intent  
DATE: 12/14/2003 06:59:54 PM&nbsp; urlLink Baptism day  

DATE: 12/13/2003 07:27:02 PM&nbsp; urlLink Rescue Mission - there will be a test  
DATE: 12/11/2003 06:41:07 PM&nbsp; urlLink Voice of God?  
DATE: 12/5/2003 07:58:10 PM&nbsp; urlLink Seattle Marathon Trip  
DATE: 11/30/2003 08:17:48 PM&nbsp; urlLink Seattle Marathon Race Report  
DATE: 11/10/2003 12:01:02 AM&nbsp; urlLink See a drunkard in the rain  
DATE: 11/8/2003 08:24:24 PM&nbsp; urlLink Fishy Philosophy  

DATE: 11/1/2003 12:01:48 PM&nbsp; urlLink Provided That Which I Needed  
DATE: 11/1/2003 12:01:42 AM&nbsp; urlLink Mustard Seed Advise  
DATE: 10/24/2003 05:50:59 PM&nbsp; urlLink Ants go working...  
DATE: 10/20/2003 11:42:25 PM&nbsp; urlLink Supposition d)  
DATE: 10/7/2003 06:15:29 PM&nbsp; urlLink PBG Club: not mere Doofuses  
DATE: 10/7/2003 12:01:40 AM&nbsp; urlLink Word of the Day: Arborescent  

DATE: 10/5/2003 05:43:30 PM&nbsp; urlLink Native Girl  
DATE: 10/3/2003 12:01:57 AM&nbsp; urlLink Spam Report: Sara Freder is a Fake  
DATE: 10/2/2003 12:01:09 AM&nbsp; urlLink  urlLink Suggestion  7  
DATE: 9/30/2003 08:51:00 PM&nbsp; urlLink Bridge to a new Stanza  
DATE: 9/29/2003 12:01:33 AM&nbsp; urlLink Boy&acute;s Group.  

DATE: 9/27/2003 12:01:37 AM&nbsp; urlLink A Matter of Focus  
DATE: 9/20/2003 09:15:13 PM&nbsp; urlLink ... And the Thought That Didn&acute;t  
DATE: 9/19/2003 12:01:22 AM&nbsp; urlLink Stay Strong  
DATE: 9/18/2003 09:51:51 AM&nbsp; urlLink The Thought That Got Away  
DATE: 9/17/2003 12:01:20 AM&nbsp; urlLink Bus Friend  
DATE: 9/16/2003 05:09:39 PM&nbsp; urlLink Promiscuous Faith  

DATE: 9/14/2003 10:03:06 AM&nbsp; urlLink Recommissioning Sunday  
DATE: 9/13/2003 12:01:20 AM&nbsp; urlLink Whose God is it Anyway?  
DATE: 9/11/2003 12:01:43 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 6  
DATE: 9/11/2003 12:01:12 AM&nbsp; urlLink A Dream for Hunter  
DATE: 9/10/2003 10:18:10 AM&nbsp; urlLink Hills Alive  
DATE: 9/9/2003 10:21:03 AM&nbsp; urlLink Time Heals All?  

DATE: 9/8/2003 10:23:05 AM&nbsp; urlLink Easy Community?  
DATE: 9/6/2003 12:01:35 AM&nbsp; urlLink On The  Path  (I think)  
DATE: 9/4/2003 12:01:33 AM&nbsp; urlLink Be Consistent  
DATE: 9/3/2003 10:12:04 AM&nbsp; urlLink Back To School  
DATE: 9/2/2003 12:01:32 AM&nbsp; urlLink OOPBGB, PPBGs  

DATE: 9/1/2003 12:01:59 AM&nbsp; urlLink PBGs Summary  
DATE: 8/27/2003 11:37:52 PM&nbsp; urlLink Supposition c)  
DATE: 5/4/2003 12:01:35 AM&nbsp; urlLink My New Run Group  
DATE: 5/2/2003 12:01:25 AM&nbsp; urlLink The Ground of Being  
DATE: 2/1/2003 12:01:18 AM&nbsp; urlLink Training again  
DATE: 1/5/2003 12:01:59 AM&nbsp; urlLink More training  

DATE: 1/4/2003 12:47:07 PM&nbsp; urlLink Just training  
DATE: 12/29/2002 12:49:29 PM&nbsp; urlLink Beauty, Eh?  
DATE: 11/10/2002 12:01:34 AM&nbsp; urlLink Have Oil, Will Travel  
DATE: 11/5/2002 12:01:14 AM&nbsp; urlLink Supposition b)  
DATE: 10/29/2002 06:49:11 PM&nbsp; urlLink Lion Baptism  
DATE: 10/29/2002 12:01:27 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 5  

DATE: 10/28/2002 12:01:20 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 4 (2)  
DATE: 10/25/2002 12:01:46 AM&nbsp; urlLink Thoughts - Freshly Squeezed  
DATE: 10/24/2002 12:01:53 AM&nbsp; urlLink Air Ferrets Aloft  
DATE: 10/21/2002 12:01:16 AM&nbsp; urlLink Gotta love those PBGs  
DATE: 10/20/2002 01:41:55 PM&nbsp; urlLink Where are you Love?  
DATE: 10/19/2002 12:01:09 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 4 (1)  

DATE: 10/18/2002 01:50:41 PM&nbsp; urlLink Fears of the Dark  
DATE: 10/17/2002 01:57:19 PM&nbsp; urlLink Spiritual Advisor?  
DATE: 10/15/2002 12:01:56 AM&nbsp; urlLink Mostly Quiet.  
DATE: 10/14/2002 12:01:03 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 3  
DATE: 10/12/2002 12:01:09 AM&nbsp; urlLink Quiet Running  
DATE: 10/11/2002 12:01:41 AM&nbsp; urlLink Supposition a)  

DATE: 9/21/2002 12:01:09 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 2  
DATE: 9/18/2002 08:30:42 PM&nbsp; urlLink Message Archive  
DATE: 9/16/2002 12:01:23 AM&nbsp; urlLink Suggestion 1  
DATE: 9/15/2002 12:00:36 AM&nbsp; urlLink Introduction to the  PBGs     LAST UPDATED: March 1, 2004 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       No run today, Clear, -16&deg;C!, no wind  Today was  urlLink my lion's  baptism day. I left the house at 5:45 so I could be at the laundromat when it opened. The automatic lock, however, didn't seem to have the correct time. I used the extra 1/2 hour to read about the story of Ruth & Naomi.  Pity it wasn't something about baptism.  Perhaps the  why  of that will come later I was struck by the grace & humility of Shirley, the laundromat's proprietor; definitely a P&nbsp;ot&nbsp; urlLink PBGs .   OOPBGB  most of her life.  I have a long way to go if I want to be as giving and selfless as her.  Or as tough as nails too.  They sure make them well out on the east coast! The lion survived the rigors of the baptism, and didn't spill any stuffing.  In fact, he could use a bit more stuffing.  I wonder why he was discarded.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        It is better by far to do something in Love, than it is to simply do something.   This was the  urlLink PBGs  answer for Mo's original "It is not what you do, it is how you do it," comment. Thank you Mo for your suggestion.  Nothing like running on an undisturbed path full of fresh snow.  There were several short stretches of virgin path. I also checked out the "river" in which Aslan will be baptized.  They are open for self serve at 6 AM.  There is also a change machine.  I do believe the proprietor is also a Person of the PBGs. Another thought that came today: My new friend at Bonnie Doon pool taught me how to break the ice with strangers.  Too cool.  Thank PBGs.   On Official PBG Business  ( OOPBGB ).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        The  urlLink PBGs  will help you reveal the part of the Plan inside your heart, but it is up to you to decide to act on it.   The PBGs are sneaky and relentless! So much happened on this run that I hardly know where to start.  First there was the pursuit of the runner in the green coat.  I saw him 4 times on this run.  I get the feeling that he figures in my part of the Plan somehow.  Then there was the commitment I made today to share my talents and start a boys group at church.  The PBGs admonished me for wanting Them to lay it all out for me.  They suggested that it is me that has to make the decisions. Choose the outlet.  Perform the duties. Get On With it Buddy!  So I did.  I got the ball rolling.  It was the easiest thing I ever did.  Everyone I talked to about it at church was very supportive.  Even eager.  You could almost hear the pegs clicking into place.  As if all everyone was waiting for was my acceptance of the task.  Needless to say, I am scared.  Deep down, I know I can handle it.  I do feel like I have jumped in the deep end though.  Everyone except me seems to be confident in my abilities.  ...And then there was the symbols I found on my run.  Purple feather, just like I had imagined.  When I took a closer look, it turned out to be a pen with a big downy feather.  Then there was the cheeky way the PBGs pulled me off the running path with bottles as rewards just to tell me to remember  urlLink Suggestion #1 .&nbsp; "Tim, keep a humble heart," They seemed to say.  Then to top it all off, They delivered  Aslan  the lion himself to me.  I am sure that "he" will come in handy for many things in my boys' group.  Now I know the PBGs have a Thesaurus and ample vocabulary to communicate with me.   I almost forgot the man in the green jacket.  I've seen him before on other runs.  At the start of my run, I saw a can.  Rather than carry it the entire way, I left it there to pick up at the end of my run.  I commented to the PBGs "I wonder what significance this will have at the end of my run."  Later, when I saw the man, I wanted to ask him why he only ran on the paths, never next to the roads.  I caught up to him at one point but held back, fearing his reaction.  He turned off just before I overtook him.  "Opportunities come and if you  wait, they fade away. They may come again, but they won't be the same twice."  I saw and greeted the man in green just as I went to get that pop can.  Guess what, he lives across the street! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 37:05.9, Dark 0&deg;C, 6 km wind  My mind is crowded with thoughts; not much room for the  urlLink PBGs . They don't seem to mind.  They are very patient. Work,  urlLink ferrets , relationships all jostling for a turn at the thought center of my brain. Consequently, it was only at the end of my run that the PBGs managed to squeeze a thought in: "Even when it seems like We are far away, we are right there with you." It echoes a scene from the ferret book: Baxter has just discovered that even though he is a ferret fairy, he   also   has a guardian angel who is watching over   him  . He sees his angel briefly and is startled when it disappears.  The angel says: "don't worry, I'm not gone."  I didn't despair this morning, but it is still nice to know that I won't have to.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       No run today  Just because I take a day off, doesn't mean that the  urlLink PBGs  do.  Mo & the kids have been reading " Air Ferrets aloft " by Richard Bach. It has been a very long time since Mr. Bach came to call in our lives. This book is very much, about the PBG conversations I have been having  Suggestions from a moderately high power; flying ferret fairies can only suggest! coincidences from on high to follow the "Path" or higher right gifts of seeing things as they already are destiny mixed with free will  Very interesting coincidence that this book would come to my attention when it did.  Apparently it was brought to Mo's attention by her atheist father!  Guess what the current book in the series is about? A writer ferret having trouble with his muse! (I just had to buy a copy for you Mo!) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 38:30.4, Snow -2&deg;C, 10 km wind  I asked the  urlLink PBGs  what they had to say about Love today.  Apparently not much.  They hinted that "that was beyond their scope; have to take that to a higher power (chuckle, snort!)".  Thanks, Guys.  Big help. When the guffaws subsided, they admonished, "What would you feel like if we withheld our Love?"  I didn't have an answer to that, and they continued to withhold Their answer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Only a short swim today  Tension was pretty high today.  Mo is stressed about making her Halloween bug things.  I haven't been too tolerant. In church today, there was a baptism service.  The focus was on relationship and love.  I got to thinking about all the "conversations" I have had with the  urlLink PBGs , not one of them has been about love, companionship, neighborliness, peace...  Is that a lack in me? Is it my conscientiousness that has trouble with this concept? " urlLink Even the poet spares a thought for love " Our minister told me briefly that there were no others interested in the Faith Inquiry so it has been cancelled.  I hope there will be some other small group meeting to take its place.  There is going to be a men's breakfast next week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
              The fact that you cannot perceive all of the  urlLink PBGs  Plan does not preclude you from being a part of it.  Right or wrong, your actions make the Plan unfold.      The PBGs  have  no hands of their own.  They control the world through their  urlLink Suggestions .  But they have a much better way of changing the world:   US  .  Since we have free will, we can choose not to listen to the carefully planned schedule of the PBGs.  It is my assertion, however, that even that is built into the Plan.  If the PBGs started creation and then sat back to see how things would unfold, the wouldn't need to be involved in our daily lives.  Free will and an involved god implies that THE PLAN must be constantly adjusted and monitored in order to keep it on track.  So every time a person makes a "Wrong" choice, the Plan must be altered to take that into account.  Or perhaps the plan is set up to work for either choice.  More likely, with a caring, loving present god, the Plan is structured so that many trivial choices are used to practice for the really pivotal choices in our lives.  Then again, how should  I  know how the gods have structured the world...  I am only a runner, not a PBG. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 37:09.9, Dark 0&deg;C, light wind  The turmoil of yesterday and this morning has left me confused and unfocused.  It is dark & silent on my run today.  My focus keeps coming back to the fears that are holding me lately.  fear of risking my current job  just  because it is unsatisfying fear of not being able to "fool" anyone else that I should be paid my current wage fear of appearing a "fool" for needing a god (even a couple of minor ones) to help me decide what to do fear that my current employer will decide a little more fat trimming is necessary for the health of the company (who do  you  think they would let go?).  I am sure I could go on.  It  is  encouraging that some of these fears I  am  addressing.  urlLink PBGs  be willing, I will be ready to jump when the time comes.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       ?? Km, ??:??.?, Cloudy 13 &deg;C, 25 km wind  I met with our churches Minister today for lunch.  I expected it to be 16 &deg;C so I didn't wear a coat.  I told him a little about the PBGs and he told me a little about his being a minister.  I saw some parallels between him relationship with his brother and my relationship with my brother S.  In the course of our conversation, I discovered that one of the strongest influences I had for creating the PBGs was a lack of direction.  Up to this point in my life, I always had some goal and some hope of getting there.  Now I have lost faith in all of my dreams and have no hope of attaining them.  So, I require an external source of direction.  Sounds like a perfect home for a roll-your-own deity to me. Why invent one (two)?  With my reluctance to make a fool of myself (be wrong?) it is much easier to believe in something I  know  isn't true than to risk saying I believe in something that cannot be proven and may in fact be total garbage. My minister says there isn't much interest in the "Faith Inquiry"; just me so far.  He says that perhaps we could form a small group of people; perhaps a book study or something. I told him that what I was really looking for was some community.  I also told him that I really didn't go for the "prayer" time or formal Christian tradition stuff.  He admitted that most groups have that component, but that it usually was a small component of any gathering.  I guess, from my limited experience, I agree with that.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:00.2, Overcast 1&deg;C, 5 km wind  Partly Cloudy, Relatively Calm, Mostly Quiet.  My spirit collects in small dark oily pools.  Calm, quiet, but not particularly  clear .  The dog barking in the distance; every bus in the city seems to be in Millwoods.  My repeating sounds; Breath, plodding feet.  My non-stop thoughts; work, home tasks, church concerns, kid concerns... I am striving for a quiet, calm, clear spirit, but even at 6:30 the world cannot be entirely shut out. Then the thought of the day comes (as it often does, near the end). Since the  urlLink PBGs  insist on free will (horrors!) and expect decisions (!) they must also proscribe actions.  Independent, creative, "because  I  think it is important", actions.  When deciding on actions I must keep  urlLink Suggestions    I ,  II  &  III  in mind. To have it any other way would not do.  PBGs do not lead children through the forest with trails of M & Ms to ginger bread houses.  Nor do they guide reluctant donkeys with carrots on sticks.  They do not intend to walk with your bloated ego floating above them on a string like a bizarre balloon. We are all the hands of the PBGs.  They work with us, through us and for us.  My mind and creativity are just as much at their disposal as my hands and my heart. One more thought to record: " I am On Official PBG Business ".  A motto for any People of the PBGs that I may meet or inspire. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        It may seem like you're being tested, but rest assured, the PBGs are not keeping score.   Not a lot of chatter around this one; it just popped fully formed into my consciousness.  Prior to this  urlLink Suggestion , I was thinking about the Purity laws and ritual purification.  I thought today's topic (eh?) was going to be "Who is your neighbor".  Who knows, it still could be.  Just because my run is over doesn't mean I am through with the  urlLink PBGs 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 37:23.3, Sunny -4 &deg;C, wind chill -9 &deg;C. Ice &amp; snow, clear  Quiet.  Too Quiet.  The  urlLink PBGs  seem to be taking a holiday.  More likely they are off somewhere else planning and scheming something I am not directly a part of.  Me?  I was not a particularly attentive student anyway.  Maybe I was not hearing the Sermon today because I was busy listening to the griping of my sore shoulder, the burning in my calves & thighs, aching knee and off balance posture.  So for most of my run I was content with the actuality of the PBGs' silence or my own reluctance to really listen.  The revelation came, (as so often happens, when you start to get tired or bored or both) near the end of my run.  "Hey there! There is no need to push," they said. Pushing in life, as in running, just wears a body down and decreases your overall endurance.  Save your breath! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
              A small coincidence can have a large meaning and a large coincidence can have no meaning; it all depends on your frame of mind.      For me, the  urlLink PBGs  use "coincidences" for much of the conversations we have together.  What I am thinking often meshes with what they have arranged to place in my path and, one would suppose, what I am thinking about.  This is only a  urlLink Supposition  (I am inclined to think this is their word, from their thesaurus)  because it only supports the other more important Suggestions.  I tried to introduce a  Covenant  with the PBGs today. Right off the bat,  Covenant  seemed too  strong  and definite a term for the PBGs.  I asked them to inspire me with a better name, but even though they seemed to  have  a thesaurus, they weren't talking.  The covenant I was trying to get them to agree to was that I would run along, thinking my thoughts, and anything they thought was important, they would mark with the appearance of a can or something.  The trickster of the pair, taunted me with a wayward rabbit.  "I know you haven't chosen this path; follow me!" said the rabbit ( Jack, the PBGs' pet rabbit )  The other of the pair, complied vaguely by providing two cans for the thought of documenting the "10  urlLink Suggestions ".  In the end I will just have to be satisfied that they will do what they want, when they want.  After all, it is  their  show, and I am but a bit player.  I can only act (or choose  not  to act) out the role I have chosen in the manner that is most comfortable to me at this moment.  PBGs, I am listening, and questing.  I hope you (and I) find myself worthy of the challenges you have planned. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       5.5 Km, 24:00.0, Partly cloudy -10&deg;C, wind chill -18&deg;C  The minister's sermon today seems to cover a lot of what I've been writing about in this  urlLink journal  lately. It was from Matthew 13:?? about 10 brides-maids and how they needed to have the oil supply in their lamps topped up and the wicks trimmed.  Prepare yourself for the coming of Jesus. In PBG terms: prepare yourself, for opportunities to be a part of the Plan will not wait for you! It's funny, I was just thinking on my run that I need to do some research.  The PBGs wouldn't provide inspiration; the minister was interested but not forthcoming; the intern minister was swamped (80 e-mails over the past two weeks). Then out of the blue, a new lady talked to me about church demographics and my new boys group.  She directed me to Noah's Arc and Paul's letters. I'm skeptical, but I'll take a peek.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        How things Seem and how they Are often differ.  Which is more important depends on the observer.   It's been a while since I got out to run.  My shins are a bit sore.  I've been feeling a bit abandoned by the  urlLink PBGs  so I thought I'd risk the streets to plan my first Boys' Night Out session.  The PBGs left me alone to plan.  "It is  your  group, after all," they teased.  What great Guys. What value would it have for me if they took care of all the details? Details of tonight are firming up nicely.  I just hope I can remember all "my" ideas. I am going to call the sour lady at the bus stop "4 of spades" lady.  I waved to her on the bus this morning.  I know it is  OOPBGB , but the details are still fuzzy (hint on Suggestion #6, don't push the plan...)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        God is about more than just Beauty   Quiet snowy morning.  Very peaceful. Mo gave me a book on "Advanced Marathoning".  EDIT: When I look back at this entry, I wish I had written more. I am as perplexed as you. What  DID  I mean? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       7._ Km, 39:19.4, Partly cloudy -4&deg;C, 6 km wind  A bit tight in the upper legs.  EDIT: Sheesh! Why did I even bother getting the book out! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       13 Km, 1:13:32, Partly cloudy -8&deg;C, 6 km wind  First day of training for the May 5 Marathon in Vancouver.  "Advanced Marathon" book is too advanced for me at this time.  I will stick to the Running Room program for now. Also swam with the family today.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       18.5 Km, 1:34:00, Cloudy -5&deg;C, 4 km wind
 Trail cleared but light snow   Today was my "first" long run (19 km) for this training session.  It was hard because I was out early, it was dark and I was on my own.  I was glad, however, that the trails were cleared. I like my new route "Helix" because it is extensible, and allows me to cut it short more easily if I need to. It also makes it tempting to quit too soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       2.5 Km, 20:00.0, Snowing! 2&deg;C, calm  First "small group ministry" with our new church running group this evening. We did 1 & 2's for 7 reps. [1 minute running and 2 minutes walking repeated 7 times] I think the group found it pretty easy.  Our goal is to be able to run a 5 km race, non-stop after 10 weeks. The group didn't seem very interested in my PBG story. It could be that I will not have the receptive audience that I had hoped for. Pitty.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:12.7, Partly cloudy, -5&deg;C, 17 km wind  I talked with the  urlLink man in green  again today.  Patience is also rewarded. Apparently he used to be a good runner but he currently does it for the exercise and to "keep his back strong." I really like seeing people day after day; slowly building relationships with these reluctant strangers.  I feel like I am adding colour to the world, one stroke at a time. My goal is to put rainbow colours into these people's grey lives (if they are willing to "reach beyond their boundaries"). My Conversations with the  urlLink PBGs  have been irreparably changed with the reading of John Spong's book " urlLink A New Christianity for a New World ". Since he called into question the idea that there is a "Being out there", I have wondered if there really is anyone there to converse  with . That is why understanding what his "Ground of Being" really means has attained such importance to me now. Marcus Borg, however seems to contain a way out with his "God is in everything" viewpoint.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Life is a Journey. Even the distractions laid in your path are part of the Journey.  It may seem like the distractions pull you away from "The One True Path" but that is a lie.  Your path is what you choose it to be.   The  urlLink PBGs  offered an interesting package to me on my last long run.  It has caused me to think hard about my actions.  Today's  urlLink Supposition  comes out of that thought train.  I must try to ensure that the distractions in my life are chosen to aid me in my journey (eg. provide stress relief, not procrastination), brighten my spirits, replenish my resources and/or support my aims and goals in life (i.e. my Journey). It is OK to be distracted as long as I am not neglecting my responsibilities.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:42.28, Sunny 2&deg;C, Light wind  This morning the  urlLink PBGs  confided that my online journal writing is just a bridge to carry me to a new path. They have been hinting this for weeks.  We came to this conclusion by reflecting on where I've been so far with Them. I've run many miles with Them now and They have lead me down many new paths. I am starting Boy's Group for the second year and it has a very different feel to it.  It is still exciting, but it doesn't seem to be as  risky  as it was last year. I will have to work harder to make it fresh again. The point is, new things and the associated reason for doing them turn into old things. If you continue doing them for a long time, often the reasons you started doing them fall away and are replaced by new reasons. More often than not, the old reasons are replaced simply by a mindless habit. It takes hard work to keep your workout fresh! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Non Run Day  Today was my first Church  Boy's Group . My lack of  urlLink planning  meant that most of the church didn't know that today was the first day. Sigh. There were 4 boys (counting my own son).  They are keen though. We played foot ball, and invented a new game that involved lots of running around, up and down the stairs of the church.  I think this new game is just a  little  too dangerous. Speaking of dangerous, I proposed building a go-cart to the boys.  I told them they would have to be on their best behavior and that we would need a few more boys to make a go of it.  I think they were excited about the project. I only hope to  urlLink PBGs  I can pull this off. I think with the help of other men in the congregation, I will have sufficient help to build this little project.  The more men and boys I can bring into it, the better.  Get those dads involved with their sons, or other people's sons.  Kids just don't get enough quality time with their male role models. Men just don't make enough time to be with their young boys. I hope I can make some men see that it is important to do things with kids. I hope I can fill some of those empty holes in my boys' hearts with excitement and feelings of accomplishment. Most of all I hope I don't make a fool of myself. Oh, maybe that is just  urlLink Servant Two  tripping me up again.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:00.2, Sunny 6&deg;C, light wind  There are two main facets of my life to this point.  I don't want to be predictable and I strive to be different from the run of the mill person, and my best yardstick for my achievement is  what other people think of me. These two servants help me stagger my way through lift.  Servant One  helps me to be spontaneous, creative, unique, flexible and humorous. But the bumbling fool gets in the way of my sticking to a schedule, planning things out carefully, being repeatable and being consistent.  Servant Two  helps me be a very  be conscientious, sensitive to other peoples feelings, responsive, loving and giving. In short, Two helps me care. Two trips me up too, though. He keeps me from seeing my own value, makes me second guess my own accomplishments, has me feeling insufficient and makes me long to 'prove myself' all the time. These two servants are part of the central core of me.  They influence everything I do and think.  They never leave my side.  Their positive aspects add light to my life and their negative aspects have a detrimental effect on my sense of well being. The catch is that I can't let these servants go without losing the better half of me. I can't dismiss the self reproving and retain the hard worker. I would have to let go of the spontaneity along with the erratic planning style. Do you have servants that are the root of both good things and bad things in your life? What are they?  Come on, take a chance and tell me about it. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:17.3, Partly Cloudy 6&deg;C, 10 km wind  I have been meaning to write about something that was first related to me by the PBGs a couple of weeks ago. That particular weekend was  urlLink swamped  with other messages and feelings, so this minor Idea was forgotten for a while. I was complaining to the  urlLink PBGs  that they weren't very good at telling stories. "Life," I said, "is very random and it is hard to find the meaning in a lot of what happens to us on a daily basis." You would think that They, being masters of randomness and coincidence and all, would be somewhat apologetic about this "weakness" in their dominion over the world. But no. In Their usual dismissive, yet completely serious manner, They said: "It is you Humans who like to tell stories." (Actually it may have been "... you, Human, who likes to tell stories." Either one applies, but they are quite different and I am not sure which one is better) That (those?) statement(s) seem very clear to me, but perhaps I should elaborate a bit for the sake of the reader. We like to tell ourselves and others stories. We expect life to follow the script. We look for the  happily ever after  endings. God, on the other hand, deals with "what is". God doesn't live in Hollywood. God's Plan wasn't commissioned in Hollywood either. Life doesn't start with a problem, move through a climax and end in resolution in 2 1/2 hours.  Sure there is some "character development" in Life, but sometimes that seems accidental.  Life is  messy  and we hate it for that. We want life to be neat and tidy Like a Sit-Com, we want life to have a purpose, message, interesting characters and be over in an hour, tops. We demand that the bad guys get punished We expect the Hero to get the Girl in a  really  good story, we want to see growth in the principle characters. In Real life, however, the good guy often dies. Sometimes even prematurely, for no good reason (as far as we can tell, anyway). Often what  should  happen, doesn't. The resolution refuses to come. The Happy Ending dreamed of remains a heart-felt wish. ( whew, how depressing!  Keep reading, it gets less heavy from here) So my point of view is that it is important for us story tellers (i.e. you and me) to get out there and make the stories come true.  Because  *WE*  have the sense that the stories outcomes are important,  *WE*  have to be the authors of the actions that  *MAKE*  those stories come true. The PBGs assist, but  *WE*  are the story tellers. Perhaps that isn't as "very clear", as even I thought it was. Who is telling the story?  Us? The PBGs? I guess I will have to wait until I read the last chapter.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Non-running day, Partly Cloudy, 8&deg;C, 8 km wind  A ' urlLink friend ' from New Zealand brought me a new phrase today. "Kia Kaha", which means " urlLink Stand Strong " or " urlLink Stay Strong " in the Maori language te reo Maori. I like the encouragement part of this saying. If I can help you be strong and you can help me be strong we will be strong together. That is a tenant worthy of the  urlLink PBGs  or any  urlLink faith  worth its salt!  

P.S. Mo will especially like the first 'kia kaha' link
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       8.81 Km, 47:44.5, Clear & cold 1&deg;C, 17 km wind   I had something I was going to write here, but I just couldn't figure out how to express it. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       
    I like  urlLink Frazz .  It is a lot like Calvin and Hobbs, but is  much gentler . It is also about a runner, like me, which is also good.  I met one of my  bus friends  on the bus today and introduced her to my son.  She is a teacher's aid in one of the elementary schools in Edmonton.  She is also slightly retarded.  A special person though.  She is always bright and cheery. She talks a lot and asks a tonne of questions.  She was quizzing my son on his French vocabulary. A  definite PPBG  if I ever saw one.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 33:25.5, Light Snow 4&deg;C, 11 km wind  Skunked.  Not a single can or bottle. No signs from the  urlLink PBGs  at all. I think the Guys have noticed that I have been looking around.  I have been trying on different faiths to see how they feel.  How do I like the fit of  Deism ?  What is this  Gnosticism  I've heard about at the water cooler? Am I closer to  Secular Humanism  or  Religious Humanism ? I called up my old flame,  Agnosticism , just to confirm that I am firmly out of her tent now. And what about her seductive sister  Atheism .  Naw, she was never  really  my type, although she certainly appeals to my logical mind. There are  lots  of girls in the spiritual meat market. Take a look at this  urlLink list  for starters. Here are some that I have heard about, but haven't dated yet:  Bah'i  Buddhism  Confucianism  Hinduism  Islam   Jainism  Native American  Noahidism  Pagan  Pantheism  Shintoism  Taoism    Unitarian Universalism  Zoroastrianism   Really, Guys, I am just sowing my wild oats here. I need to play the field before I make any ever-lasting commitments. Surely you understand that?  Don't tell me you are   jealous   gods!  That's a mark against you, in my books. Okay, you caught me.  For the sake of a good story I told a little fib.  When I said that I was skunked, that wasn't completely true.  At the end of my run I  did  get a bottle. Not completely abandoned.  Still there listening to me, just reserving Their judgment. As beings far more mature than I, They know that I need a little wiggle room.  They provide me with breathing space.  They are not in any hurry what-so-ever. "Besides," They flippantly add, "All roads lead inexorably to us, so take your pick."
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:00.2, Overcast 1 &deg;C, 5 km wind   Continued from yesterday  ... Then I got to thinking about how I "control" the  urlLink PBGs . My thoughts are in the drivers seat. It is my agenda that is on the table. They make comments about, and additions to my monologue, but it is me who is the script writer. Am I so vain as to think that I am "writing" myself a better part in God's play? Actually, no. In truth, I don't delude myself that way. Deep down I know who is in charge. I realize that I have influence on what happens around me, but that I have a very tenuous control. It would take very little for my 'house of cards' world that I have built up around me to come toppling down. The fact that I have any influence at all in this crazy mixed up world is the true blessing. That is why it is so important that I use the gifts God has given me to enhance the world around me. I cannot change the overall map of the Plan, but I still have the free will to mark my own trail on it. In fact , the Plan is the result of the sum total of all of Humanities reaction to what it is to be alive. When stated that way, it is obvious that I have a  say , but that I am  not  in control. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6 Km, 30:10.0, Sunny, 5&deg;C, 7 km wind  Mo & I ran together again today; I am so proud of her (OK, so maybe I  am  hoping she will read this and I'll get brownie points). She has progressed to running 4 min. and walking 1 min. Yeah Mo! You can do it! (Neal says, "Time to move up to 5:1's") While Mo was with me, she was trying to interpret what the  urlLink PBGs  were saying.  "Whoa there!... isn't that my job? That isn't how I would interpret what was said at all...", I said. I guess I don't want to lose control of  my  gods. On reflection, however, it makes sense that they talk differently to her than they do to me.  She has read my journal right from the very beginning and has seen the concept developing since I collected the first pop can. But she is on a Different Path and is engaged in an entirely different Conversation. No wonder they speak differently to her.   More about controlling the PBGs tomorrow... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Humor. It is a gift from the gods. Use it wisely.  Apparently, the sixth  urlLink  Suggestion   is  NOT  about pushing the Plan as foretold by some  lowly prophet . It has to do with breaking the ice with strangers.  There is nothing as good as humor for breaking through someone's reserve; to catch them unawares.  It is most successful when it is something undeniably true, positive in nature and just a tiny bit silly. But wisdom is also required when using humor. One must use careful timing.  One must be responsive to the mood of the target. One must be cautious about seeming to be laughing  at  the person instead of the much more desirable laughter  with  the person.   EDIT: Got any other ideas on how humor is a gift from the gods?  Drop me a note about it and I'll include it here    Mo :  Posted 9.17.2003 11:47 AM - my special someone.

Like fire, humor can warm the soul or burn the fingers and takes lots of practice. I follow that ancient clown, Jesus, who talked of being non-judgmental and kind but having goofy stories to make a point (anyone tried sewing with a camel stuck in their needle recently???) .

  MissFlibberty :  Posted 9.18.2003 5:15 PM

Some of the best humour can be found in normal, everyday events and occurrences - and all of our every day things are gifts from God! In finding humour in these everyday happenings we are recognizing God in all things- maybe helps stop us from taking them for granted. 

  Nobody else is brave enough to be listed here yet  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       8.81 Km, 44:09.1, Light showers 12&deg;C, 10 km wind  I had another brief chat with  urlLink Hunter  today. He keeps showing up on his porch just as I go by. It is almost like he is waiting for me to come along. Today he was concerned about a bad dream he had last night. He told me that in his dream, a drunk from across the street came and picked him up, hurting him.  He described the man as having a black shirt with a red dragon on the front. Interested, I asked him to draw me a picture of the man and to post it in his front window where I would see it the next time I went by. I told him I was interested in seeing what his black shirted man looked like. So, Hunter is  OOPBGB  today. He has his sword drawn and will chase down his fears.  He will draw a box around his evil dream and confine it to the 2D world of paper and crayon. Go forth valiant young knight, be afraid no more!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       4 hills, 7.2 Km, 35:06.4, Sunny 15 &deg;C, 10 km wind  Today was my first day of hill training of the 'summer'.  It was hard work.  I was  way  over dressed. It is hard to think profound thoughts when you are pounding up and down a steep hill, sweating profusely and trying not to look totally winded to the other runners passing by.  (Un)fortunately, there were no other people doing hills today. I got a  urlLink visitor  to my journal over the weekend.  First person to actually respond!  I am so relieved.  Now I can relax and just enter in stuff.  I hope that if you are reading this, you will be moved to respond.  I don't really care if you have something profound to say, just let me know you are alive and what you think about life and your path along the great Journey.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:41.0, Scattered showers 11 &deg;C, 15 km wind  I spent some time looking for journalizers closer to my own age.  Their language was more mature and the content was less self centered than the teens I read yesterday (they seem to realize that  other  people have feelings). The older journalizers, however, were still struggling with loneliness and depression. This certainly doesn't seem to be the outlet I was hoping it would be.  I doubt I am going to get any "Community" from the journals I find on EasyJournal. Back in the real world, I met an old church friend on the bus today.  I hardly recognized her.  She is divorced from her abusive husband and fighting for custody of her 3 children.  I am not entirely sure that she would be a better single mother to these kids than the father and his new partner are. The world is full of hurting and broken people.  Sigh .  Journalizer  -  Someone who keeps a personal or financial journal. I looked it up on  urlLink dictionary.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       No run, Cloudy 13 &deg;C   Still  ruminating on the Conversation of the weekend.  I have spent some time looking at other journals on  EasyJournal.com .  Most that I have found are written by young teens struggling with depression, school, boy/girl friend trouble, addiction and, most frequently, loneliness.  It is really quite sad.  A web log allows you to communicate with the entire world, but, realistically, very few people will read, consider and respond positively to your heart-felt musings. I feel that I want to help them in some way, but I also feel that it is not my place to point out the 'error of their ways'.  It would probably be pointless.  "The do-gooders do more harm than good."  I've sent out a couple of simple messages, but haven't received any messages myself. Okay,  urlLink Guys , I hear you whispering back there; "Don't push the Plan",  That doesn't preclude me from worrying and feeling frustrated!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       19 Km,1:50:08, Partly Cloudy, 13 ?C, calm   urlLink PBGs , please forgive your humble devotee.  You spoke to me with such insistence this weekend, but I just couldn't decipher what your message meant. I am sure that this material merits a  urlLink Suggestion  or at least a  urlLink Supposition , but I just can't boil it down to one general phrase;maybe You could break it down a bit for your lowly servant? I had a longer than usual run on this Saturday morning.  Mo ran with me for the first 20 minutes and we discussed my worries about my new online journal.  It seems to me that what it has to say is at odds with the other types of "Blogs" on the internet.  Does my "conversation" have any merit? Will it be useful to the regular online readership?  I told Mo I would take my concerns to the PBGs and see what they had to say. As I said, Their comments were profound but also confounding.  They warned about distraction.  Or maybe it was the comment, "Sure, distract yourself for a bit, the true direction change will come after this little side trip". Perhaps I miss read the signs all-together. Then there was the park bench with the bag half full of collected bottles and cans. I found it in the middle of a deserted park.  My assumption is that it was collected by some poor homeless person.  Why they left it behind (and some mens' clothing as well) is a mystery to me (and will probably stay that way too).  On a whim, I added the bottles and cans I had already collected into the bag.  I don't know if my action was participation in a mini miracle for a street person, annoyed an overworked city cleanup worker or whether my "contribution" will simply be tossed in the nearby garbage bin.  Only the PBGs know for sure what part this act plays in the Plan. Next, the PBGs, through various course corrections and distractions, brought me to a community playground that was under construction.  The park was well off my chosen path and it was surprising that I had arrived there at all.  It turned out that the community work crew was short 5 people and behind schedule.  They wanted to get the site ready for  pouring concrete that was coming in a couple of hours. To make a long story short, I volunteered to help out and worked from 12:30 to 8:00!  I am an Agent of the PBGs.  Where they lead, I follow (... sometimes, eh Jack?) After I had a quick shower, Mo & I went to the church movie night.  The movie they showed was " urlLink Thirteen Conversations About One Thing ".  Wow! Does that movie ever dove-tail into my weekend conversation!  It is a bout how interconnected our lives are and how small actions of one person can have dramatic effect on another person.  Hello?  Sound familiar?  Agents of the PBGs unite!


   BTW ... I even did a search on the internet to read the reactions of other people to the movie.  I found more interesting hits to the search string " Thirteen Conversations About the Same Thing ".  Sometimes a miss-quoted string gives you 'better' hits because it side-steps the corporate analysis and mainstream reviews.  It also takes you to the dough-head pages of people who are too careless to quote it properly.  Alas.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       8.8 Km,48:25.21, Hazy, 13 &deg;C, 11 km wind  The message for today, while comforting, does not seem, to me, to be a 
 urlLink Suggestion or Supposition .  The  urlLink PBGs  say "Count on Us to have the consistency of a sunrise and the Love of a Rose."  Our conversation was fixated on consistency & spontaneity/impulsiveness (my (?) fault, probably).  The PBGs reminded me that it is not They that are inconsistent forces in the world.  On the contrary!  It is  us , the hands of the PBGs, that are at the root of most inconsistent behavior.  If we didn't have free will, we would be more like a rose and bloom at the appointed time and die with the chill winds of fall.  Instead, we long for things we can't reasonably expect to have, strive for things beyond our grasp, and toil endlessly for things we do not exactly need.  Don't get me wrong, our free will is as much a blessing as a curse.  We are the builders of a new world.  The future is in our hands.  We also have the ability to be the destroyers of the world.  I believe that is why the PBGs gave us free will.  And also why it is imperative that all our actions be actions of heart-felt Love and thought-full reflection.  One more thought from the PBGs (I know, it has also been written down in some other popular Book):   "To thine own self be true"   Here is someone who seems to know the flip side of  urlLink being consistent . Randomness, the internet and the PBGs brought me to his site.  I sent a message of encouragement to him.  I like to call it blog tag. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       11 Km, 56:48.6, Partly cloudy, 11 &deg;C, 4 Km wind.  Yesterday was the first day of school for my kids.  Since my son is in grade 7 this year, he was especially nervous about going back to school. As it happens, Hunter, who is the boy I taught how to make a snowman last year (see  urlLink Suggestion #2 ) stopped me this morning.  He remembered me from last year and wanted to talk to me!  We had a short chat about his first day at school. He was worried and confessed that had cried the night before. I told him that my own son was going into grade 7 and that he needed a hug too.  Hunter seemed very glad to hear that. Today, I chanced to see Hunter again and his first day was great.  He was no longer concerned about school and seemed to think it was fun. I keep telling the  urlLink PBGs  that I want some connection with the people I see on my running route (perhaps I have that wrong; maybe it is  Them  encouraging  me  to connect with them).  Well it is starting to happen. I am now a fixture.  Someone to confide in.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       On Official  PBG  Business  Here I hope to list people or tasks that qualify as being  OOPBGB     urlLink  MissFlibberty   - kia kaha ( urlLink Stay Strong  in Maori) from New Zealand   Hunter  - on a quest to slay  the  red dragon  of fear   Ms. Grooms  - English teacher who inspired Nicki P to be a writer.  urlLink  Steve Conley   - Marathon runner(?) and Cartoonist raising money for "medical care and other vital services for people with HIV/AIDS in the DC area".  People of the PBGs  Here is a list of people I have met that are definitely People of the PBGs.    Shirley  - aka "the Slipper Lady" of the Lee Ridge Laundromat The nice couple who collect bottles on their walk and give the proceeds "to the kids when they ask for some" ( whatever  that  means )  urlLink  Hunter   - Grade 1 boy who struggles with his (ordinary) fears. I usually encounter him on his front porch  Janet Carter  - Elementary Teacher's Aid and  urlLink Bus Friend .  urlLink  Divya   - Shy "Bus Song" singer and pint size  urlLink Bus Friend .  People who have visited the PBGs and dropped me a note about it    urlLink  Ruizzle   - Wanderlust urges this Soul to Roam   urlLink  moonflower   - Just a place to ramble   urlLink  MissFlibberty    - Random thoughts occur at random moments... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Summary of Suggestions and Suppositions to-date  
Here is a quick summary of the "Inducements" ("commandments" is simply too strong a word for the  urlLink PBGs ).  For a full explanation of what these inducements meant to me at the time I was given them, follow the links.
 
   urlLink Suggestion 1 : It's not about fee for service.  
   urlLink Suggestion 2 : It's not about what you get (from the world), it's about what you add.  
   urlLink Suggestion 3 : It may seem like you're being tested, but rest assured, the PBGs are not keeping score.  
   urlLink Suggestion 4 (1) : The fact that you cannot perceive all of the PBGs' Plan does not preclude you from being a part of it. Right or wrong, your actions make the Plan unfold.  
   urlLink Suggestion 4 (2) : The PBGs will help you reveal the part of the Plan inside your heart, but it is up to you to decide to act on it.  
   urlLink Suggestion 5 : It is better by far to do something in Love, than it is to simply do something.  
   urlLink Suggestion 6 : Humor. It is a gift from the gods. Use it wisely.  
   urlLink Suggestion 7 : What's important is not what others think of  you , but what  you  think is  Right.    
And Here are the Suppositions so far:
 
   urlLink Supposition a) : A small coincidence can have a large meaning and a large coincidence can have no meaning; it all depends on your frame of mind.  
   urlLink Supposition b) : How things Seem and how they Are often differ. Which is more important depends on the observer.  
   urlLink Supposition c) : Life is a Journey. Even the distractions laid in your path are part of the Journey. It may seem like the distractions pull you away from "The One True Path" but that is a lie. Your path is what you choose it to be.  
   urlLink Supposition d) : It is just as productive to try to predict the plan as it is to try to push it.   
You may have noticed that there are two Suggestions numbered 4.  When I wrote them into my running journal, I didn't notice this error in numbering.  When I discovered it later on, the numbering seemed appropriate because both Suggestions are essentially the same. So I have left it that way.  The PBGs truly work in mysterious (and, I think, wonderful) ways.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       4 Miles, 32:02.11, Overcast 3&deg;C, 5 km wind   urlLink Carpe Diem  - Latin for seize the day. I was high-jacked by friends to go and see a movie tonight; " The Life of David Gale " starring  Kevin Spacey ,  Kate Winslet  &  Laura Linney . It was a difficult and engaging movie about Capital Punishment and Idealism and was also a bit like a murder mystery. There was also an under-current of the inevitability of death and the courage to face it. After the movie, my friend gave me a ride home and we got to talking. I told her I was feeling selfish for spending so much money and time on training for and going to the Seattle Marathon. "Just think of all the homeless people that could be fed if the tens of thousands of runners stayed home," I said. "What about the quality time with my family that I am giving up for this crazy hobby?" It makes running seem so foolish and selfish. My friend, who has recently experienced more the her share of people close to her dying, gave me this advice. "You have to follow your passions, because death can come suddenly and you may not  have  a tomorrow." Well there is no doubt in my mind that running marathons is a passion of mine. I am registered in the Seattle marathon at the end of November; the debit has shown up on my Visa. I am going! Eventually, you can look up finish times for Tim, Rita, Gina, Chris, Alesha, and Bonnie once they are posted. Running is a powerful drug and most runners go into withdrawal when they don't/can't get a fix.

       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       No Run, 30 to 40 km winds  On the way home from work today I got to thinking about the value of what I am doing with my life.  Although the work I accomplish is valuable (they wouldn't pay my wage if there was no value, would they?) It seems to me that it could easily be done by someone else. With billions of workers on the planet, I can hardly have a unique talent. In what way is what I do special? How do I contribute to a world filled with worker-drones? An ant hill has millions of virtually identical worker ants. Genetically, they are identical twin sisters. Almost like photocopies. Each ant wanders around ready to do any task that comes to hand (or perhaps pincher?)  "There is a stone in the middle of this tunnel, I'll move it down the passage so it is out of the way." "This chamber is vacant, I will make it ready to be used for a brood chamber; ready for the next occupant."  If some other ant encounters these tasks before me, they perform them and I simply look for something else to do. The task does not fit the ant, the ant simply finds the task. As I look down on this ant hill from my godly position, I see only a mass of ants.  They scurry here and there, each on their own "assigned task" Their ant hill, 100 times bigger than their diminutive size, is a marvel of their accumulated accomplishments. So, my ant accomplishments are insignificant when you look at the entire ant world. With my smarter than average ant brain, I could decide that the queen ant would never notice if I went down a side passage and had a little nap. Just don't tell the rest of the ants, because then nothing would get done and the hill would fall to ruin. I guess I had better do my work after all.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        It is just as productive to try to predict the plan as it is to try to push it.  7.1 Km, 36:44.11, Clear 3&deg;C, 7 km wind  Yesterday was our (Mo & my) first "Faith Enquiry" session at United Church.  None of the people I invited to come, actually came and the people who  were  there I hadn't expected.  So my attempt to predict what would happen as well as my efforts to influence what happened both failed. A strong indication (well, to me anyway) that I navigate the rapids, not control the river.  We talked about Baptism, Community, and a bit about our expectations for the class. I felt a bit disappointed about the class, but came away with a very strong need to figure out why I am attending. What need will Confirmation fill for me? I liked what Mo said to be about confirmation: "In action and deed, perhaps you are already Confirmed. The ceremony is simply the celebration of what you have already decided" (paraphrased by me, BTW). I don't feel like there are any particular things I want to learn about the process of Confirmation.  I have been going to church for long enough to know how the service works and what the Creed means.  I know there is still lots for me to learn, but I am not in a hurry.  Why am I here? What is the hurry? Why now? It just seems like time. I've tossed in my " urlLink Blind " and I have received my cards. Now I wait to place my bets and see what is on the " urlLink river ".  As the  urlLink Supposition  says, it doesn't pay to predict the Plan.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 34:00.2, Clear 1&deg;C, 5 km wind  Today I met not one, but three members of the PBG Club. First there is  Robert . I met Robert as he was out walking his Grand Daughter's dogs Chance and Shadow. He is a very friendly fellow and quick to laugh. He was also carrying a bag of garbage he had collected along his path and some cans he had picked up. I told him I appreciated his efforts to tidy up the neighborhood. At one point, Chance (who had a large cone shaped veterinarian collar on) dashed across the field to "greet" a lady and her dog. This turned out to be the second PBG Club member. She also admitted that she liked to have a clean neighborhood to walk through. She also cleaned up while she walked her dog. After 7 years of waiting to encounter people who appreciated my cleaning up on my runs I didn't expect to meet two people with the same idea  on the same day ! Then about 3 minutes later, I met  another  PBGer. This time it was another  runner &nbsp; with a bag full of pop cans. I had never encountered her out running before and have not seen her since. She didn't seem at all embarrassed about being seen carrying bottles. I offered her some of mine, but she didn't want them. I met  all three  of these people on the same run! Within 5 minutes time! They are all concerned with how messy the neighborhood is.  They all are lending a hand to make a difference.  They are all members of the PBG Club
 I like the idea of the  urlLink Doofus tribe  used by nikkip.
I would like to start my own tribe too.  Hopefully, my tribe will be more uplifting, but it is also tempting to just make it funny. Perhaps I will still illustrate the funniness of people without actually condemning them or laughing at them. Yah, that sounds about right. I intend to have a series of these posts, so look for the words  PBG Club:  in the title 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Word of the day:  urlLink arborescent  found in a quote on the  urlLink Darwin Awards  site:

     &quot;Humans are not the end result  
of predictable evolutionary progress, 
but rather a fortuitous... twig on the 
enormously arborescent bush of life "  
-      urlLink Stephen&nbsp;J.&nbsp;Gould   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       15 miles, 2:21:11.0, Clear and cool, no wind  I met a  Native Girl  on my run today.  As Neal said this evening, "I fell in love" instantly. It was as if I had known Her for a long time. This Native Girl is so much like the Spiritual Girl I am seeing now that it was breath-taking. Unfortunately, like Neal, I saw her for only a brief glance, in passing on the trail. Actually it was one of the few moments that I was not chatting with Neal in 2 ? Hours of running. Native Spirituality.  Everything has a voice; birds, animals, trees, rocks. And Natives claim that they speak to them all. I imagine that a hunter would "hear" a lot from the twigs and blades of grass that have been displaced by his quarry. Moss on a tree tells him the direction he is facing. A bare rock marks a game trail or the den of an animal. This seems pretty similar to the way the  urlLink PBGs  communicate with me. A bottle here, a playing card there. Perhaps a Milk jug or Jack, my prophetic rabbit. Symbols.   urlLink Vocabulary  from my conversations. I live in the city and the city  "talks"  to me. Ok, not exactly  to  me, perhaps, but through me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a public service announcement.:  &LT;Ahem&GT; To those who choose to believe in strange things; beware. Astrology is not exactly a science and not all practitioners are, &LT;Ahem&GT;, exactly, um,  urlLink honest .  If this link goes dead, I'll tell you what it said here:  Sara Freder is a fake and a lot of people have been suckered by her. What surprises me most about these people is that none of them seem to consider that Sara Freder is probably not even a real person.  Ever wonder who did all the fancy programming for 'her' site? Who set up all the programming for the accounts for people who are silly enough to register? You might think *I* am crazy for inventing gods of my own, but I don't ask you to send me money. Well, I thought about doing just that, but the PBGs slapped my hand and told me to get a life.  [Edit] Judging from the number of hits I get from Google searches for Sara Freder(2 or 3 A DAY!), there are a LOT of people who wonder about Sara Freder's service. If you want to get rich, try becoming a  urlLink Motley Fool  instead. With a small monthly investment you will gradually make that million you are hankering for. Once you are a millionaire, who can help being sexually attractive? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        What's important is not what others think of  you , but what  you  think is  Right .  10.2 Km (hills), 49:26.5, Sunny 15&deg;C, light wind  It's a wonder that I learn these things at all.  For days and days (ok, so it has been my entire life, what of it) the  urlLink PBGs  have been pounding me with the same message over and over. It's one of those types of messages that you know in the back of your mind, but you choose to ignore it. How else could I miss something so obvious. If you are outward focused like me, you are pretty sensitive to other peoples' mood.  Sometimes you feel like you can read their minds just by watching how they react. Over a lifetime you get pretty good at it. But often, if you take the trouble to ask them, you usually get a surprise. They invariably are thinking something quite different than what you expect.  Sometimes they are busy with their own lives (The NERVE!) and not thinking about you at all. I was running hills today and saw a woman who was running hills too. She was going slower than me, but seemed to be a pretty good runner and being very relaxed about her exercise. I was thinking, "I wonder what she thinks of me", my efforts, my form, etc. Then it occurred to me that she didn't even seem to recognize that I was there running past her again and again. The observation that she wasn't even aware of me, caused me to be aware of all the other reminders from the PBGs. They have been trying to get me to not be so obsessed with myself and how I appear to others. So what if my 'gems of wisdom', my 'unique perspectives' are languishing in obscurity. If I am to write, I should write because I have something worth saying.  If someone finds my viewpoint valuable, that is what the PBGs intended. If not, just as the PBGs predicted, this is a valuable side trip from my path that I have learned from. Yes, MTRF, you told me that weeks ago, but there is hearing and there is understanding .   Yesterday, there was a bus driver who was acting in a very OOPBGB'ish way.  He was being extra friendly, asking trivia questions, wishing riders a 'good day' over the loud speaker... If you have ridden an ETS bus, you will know that this is  extremely  un-bus-driverly. I was supposing what other passengers thought of this behavior. "He's crazy", "Is he drunk", "He seems to be in a good mood", "Is he serious?", "Where did this guy escape from?".  Those are the thoughts I would worry about, if I was that bus driver. I don't really  know  what  all those people thought (I was probably close, but I bet there were some people that thought other things). But what was more intriguing to me was what  the bus driver thought he was doing . What was his motivation?  Why was he acting so strangely?  Did he know that it seemed strange (I am betting he did, but that he did it anyway)? What did he hope to accomplish?  And, did it work? Were people positively affected by his unusual behavior? To act with purpose (any purpose) is to go beyond just thinking.  Right or wrong, an action is better than just a thought.  And a fear of a thought, which kills an action, is murder in high degree.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       42.2 Km, 4:18:47, Partly Cloudy, 6&deg;C, 12 km wind off Lake Washington  Well, it's official, I've run a marathon 3 times now. I finished at 4 hrs, 18 minutes and 47 seconds ( the official clock says 4:19:27, but that is because it took me 40 seconds just to cross the Start line). That is a Personal Best (PB) for me and  so  much better than my last marathon in Red Deer. I felt really strong the whole way. I wasn't at all "tired" aerobically. What gave out on me was my legs; I developed severe leg cramps 5 miles before the end of the marathon. The Seattle course has some killer hills at 19 miles. Soon after I hit the hills, my legs cramped up so much I had to stop and massage them. It got so bad in one place that I asked a volunteer to support me while I leaned on him and stretched.  It was  very  painful.  But I managed to keep going for the last 5 miles. The weather for the marathon was really good for Seattle at this time of year. About 6&deg;C, Partly cloudy although, there was a fairly strong wind off of Lake Washington. One of my traveling partners was able to run roughly at my pace, so we decided to run together. It certainly is nice to have someone to run with. BonBon & I got off to a screaming start and by mile 4 had accumulated 4 minutes ahead of our target pace.  We slowed down and were able to keep on pace for the next 11 miles. Then, around mile 15, we started to slip up a bit. When we reached the hills, I left BBS behind and thought I wouldn't see her until the end of the race. To her great delight and my surprise, she caught up to me in the middle of the hilly section! We ran together for a while, but my cramps kept slowing me down and she left  me  behind. So she actually beat me! That's OK, BBS, You certainly are a stronger runner than I am and if I didn't have those terrible cramps, we both would have finished together and had an awesome finish time.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this quote in  urlLink someone else's  journal:   "The weather was an apologetic drunkard who kept spilling rain at inopportune places, and then trying to say how sorry it was for the accident. The weather isn't due to sober up for a couple more days, so I imagine it'll have a substantial backlog of shame to work off once it gains a more or less clear head."  I can certainly picture the drunkard stumbling apologetically about, barely in control of his actions. Should I aspire to this kind of writing? Should I stick to my own brand of prose?  Hey, how about another  link  while we are at it. This one is a marathoner who is also a cartoonist.  I guess not all marathon runners are free-loaders like me. Some use their talents to do  urlLink people some good . It is a pity that Steve didn't finish documenting his marathon training.  I noticed that the page was last updated July 2002 and stops at week 11. He is using that same program the I am and I think it is 19 weeks. Apparently he finished, but the journal didn't. Doesn't Steve look a LOT like me?    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     Steve&nbsp;&lt;======&gt;&nbsp;Me   
Link to a friend  A CIV friend   [edit] CivGeneral link removed for privacy sake. Leave him alone already. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       32 Km, 2:53:14, Sunny -10&deg;C, 7 km wind 
Yes, you read it right. 32 KM in 2 hrs and 53 minutes. For you Americans, that is 20 miles at 14&deg;F. To the athletes in the crowd, that isn't terribly fast. The rest of you are probably thinking, "What, is he crazy?" Today was my longest run between now and the  urlLink Marathon  at the end of November. My run started out pretty cold. By the time I was finished, the temperature had risen to almost the freezing point.  Mo sent me this  urlLink link  she received in her email box. She told me that she found it very  urlLink PBG ish. I am inclined to agree with her. I wasn't too impressed with the layout of the site, so I thought I would look for other sites on fish philosophy. I did some searching and found out where this "fishy" business started out. Who ever thought a fish mongery shop would  urlLink have a website ! I must admit, the first link says more about the fish philosophy and what it is about than the second link.  I guess the gurus at the fish shop were advised to sell their ideas through their business consultants.  How very American to sell your grass roots ideas to the highest bidder! What I have seen of the concepts, however, are great!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 35:42.2, Snowing -3&deg;C, 9 km wind, wc -9&deg;C  I forgot to "tithe" today. Well..., I didn't exactly  forget ... OK, I didn't want to tithe today... I was being greedy. Do you know how the  urlLink PBGs  "punished" me? They gave me more cans. They gave me more bottles.  Soon I had so many cans, covered with ice and snow, that I had to stop running.  They were so slippery! They were damn cold. I had too many! And I kept finding more. So I gave in.  I "tithed" by placing most of my found containers in a position where some other PBGer would notice them. How did the PBGs reward me for this generous tithing? They gave me more cans. They gave me more bottles. And before I had more than I could handle, the gave me a bag to put them in.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Double Entry DAY! Woohoo!  I had coffee with a friend on Thursday. She is worried that her husband doesn't love her. I know that he does, and she is pretty sure that he does, but he doesn't show it to her very well. *I* know that he loves her because I see it in his actions.  He treats her with a great deal of respect.  He honors her wishes and lets her be in control because he knows it makes her happier. Her well-being is his highest priority. While my friend sees some of these ways he expresses his love for her, it isn't what she is looking for. She wants to receive cards. She wants "I love yous". She wants flowers. She wants tender touches (you know the kind that have nothing to do with sex?). She wants, in short, what most women want and what most men really don't understand. She wants a clear sign that she is loved! Now, my friend is wise enough to know that her great need for external approval stems from her own insecurity. If he tells her he loves her, she will be more able to love herself.  If he tells her she is lovely, she will feel slightly more beautiful. If he appreciates her appearance when she makes a special effort, she will take more care and look nicer for him. So, for all you guys out there; pay attention. It isn't critical for you to understand your woman. Your route out of the dog house could well be very simple. Notice the special efforts she makes. Take a sticky note, write a positive comment on it and leave it stuck to the microwave. Bring her an aspirin, without being asked and when she thanks you, tell her "you are worth it".  She'll love you more, and in the end, you will find you love her more and show it to her better.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       5.5 Km, 28:00, Clear, -7&deg;C, 9 km wind  Well, today was my first run since the Big B. at church. I ran with Mo and we saw a rabbit. We decided her name was Jill as opposed to Jack, who is  urlLink my rabbit . After her 20 minutes, I got down to my own 'meditative' run. I got to thinking about the failure of my Go-cart project with the Boy's Group and other things that are not 'going according to plan'. The inabilities I have are a part of me. But that doesn't mean I can slump down on the road and wait for someone to rescue me. My Go-cart project failed through my unwillingness to plan and act. Through procrastination and fear, I  let it fail . It would have been nice if the  urlLink PBGs  would have made it all happen effortlessly. Like they did with  urlLink Aslan the lion . But even in that case, it was me that decided what actions were necessary. I am the one who brings him to every Boy's Group meeting. I protect him from the boys rough handling. It is all a matter of intent. My whole spiritual inspiration was started by one pop bottle. Its value is insignificant taken by itself. I now take that bottle and tithe it to the PBGs as a token of my commitment to Them and my intention to live a life in Jesus (still hard to type). It is like the bottle I carried for TS in the Marathon. The bottle itself isn't nearly as important as the message it carries to the recipient. The effort expended is what matters as does the love and caring implied by that effort. I have an over-supply of caring in my heart. I intend to share it with those who will allow it. Some of you who are saying to yourselves, "The road to hell is paved with good intentions." That may be so, but without intention, there is no direction. Without direction any action is futile. Undirected action or uncaring inaction are both aspects of evil. So the road to hell is also paved with futile undirected action and uncaring sloth. Intention is a starting point and a moral compass. Action comes from within and direction comes from without (if you  urlLink are listening carefully )
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was the "big day". Today was the day I publicly made my commitment to my congregation and to God to follow Jesus (Hard still to even type that name. I hope you will allow me the eccentricity of using place holders like the  urlLink PBGs   or just God). I make this commitment for the sake of the community I want to feel a part of; their well being is now my well being. I make this commitment to myself so that "with god as my helper" I will become all that I can (am meant to be). I also, dear reader, make the same commitment to you.  I woke up calm and relaxed. Mo will tell you, I was also in a silly mood. Old habit; when things get serious, I react by "lightening" the mood. I volunteered to be a Greeter with Jackie and we had wonderful time welcoming people to the church. Many of my good friend where present, even though my intention to be baptized was a closely guarded secret. Church was pretty usual until my son and two friends did an announcement skit for a church sleepover in January. They dressed up like Harry Potter, Ron and Hermiony. My son wore a black wig, round glasses frames and a face-paint scar. Mo wrote the script. It was great. The second unusual thing was me up at the front getting baptized. My kids were asked to pour the water into the font for the ceremony. Then it was time to get down on my knees and be baptized. The minister sprinkled the water on my forehead. He said some words about the significance of the ceremony. Then he called up my 'family members' and he and they placed their hands on my head.  I was surprised to see that Marnie and my mentor, Ken also came up along with Mo and my kids. That was a pleasant surprise. It is a pitty that Jackie also didn't feel comfortable enough to come up as well.  After the Baptisms were over, we weren't through yet. Val and I, as well as another lady, still needed to be confirmed. The confirmation was the part were we had to affirm our faith and agree to live a Christian life. Then after that, there were two more people, Mo being one of them, that were moving their memberships from one United Church congregation to another.  After all the ceremonies had be done, we went back to the normal routine. After the service I invited some people out for a celebration lunch at Tim Hortens. Someone asked me if I felt any different. I had to admit that I didn't feel anything new. My feet still touch the ground. No halo appeared over my head. Marnie says the miracle happened long before I stood in front of that congregation. I think she is probably right.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       No run today  I went on a rescue mission today. Hardly a damsel, though she had reason to be distressed. You see, last week her husband ran out on her. She has a low paying part-time job. Her apartment costs too much so she is moving from a small city 1 1/2 hrs south of here to live with her parents. That is where I come in. Her parents go to my church and a couple of weeks ago I offered to help out with any lifting they needed around their house (the gentleman of the house recently had a heart attack). Who did they think about calling to help with the move? Yours truly. My brother-in-law often says  No good deed goes unpunished.  Today I wondered if he was right. The gentleman didn't have a visa, so the van had to go on my card instead. I spent about 4 hrs driving the moving van. The gentleman had no idea where the damsel lived or worked. For the most part she was surely and negative. The woman has ash trays in her ash trays. I can still smell the smoke in my clothes. She gave us loading directions while her daughter's boyfriend and I did all the lifting and packed the van. It's a test. I'm being tested already. One simple act of faith, and here I am being tested. Well, I still enjoyed my day. I wouldn't want to live in her life for even one day. But I was still good natured, pleasant, helpful and kind. Hey, it is in my nature. I helped lighten her load. I think I even saw her smile once. She certainly didn't deserve  another  kick from a complete stranger.   Oh, and BTW, tomorrow I am getting baptized and Confirmed as a member of the United Church of Canada. My wife, Mo is so happy. I am just nervous. I think I am past being scared about it. I feel pretty calm about it, actually.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Run later today, Clear -20&deg;C, 6 km wind  I had a spooky experience on the bus the other day. Well, not exactly spooky in the Hallowe'en sense, but in the spiritual sense. I was watching a 3 year old playing with the zippers on her coat and thinking about my own kids when they were little. Out of the blue, a thought occurred to me about letting go of old business from the past. The spooky part (for me anyway) about it was that the experience was exactly like the 'Aha' moments I get while running. It seemed to have a quiet ring of truth to it that I sometimes get after thinking about something on my run for 4km/30 minutes. I am tempted to say it was the voice of God.  DO-do-do-do. I don't know about you, but that creeps me out. It wasn't scary or anything. I didn't  hear  a voice.  I just recognized the tone of the thought. And it seemed to have a source beyond me. This thought wasn't telling me how to run my life, or which stock to buy or anything crazy. It was simply a continuation of my life conversation. It had meaning in the context of the issues I hold and think about. What meaning, you may ask? Mind your own business. That isn't important for me to relate. If this was a God experience, it wasn't at all what I expected (where were the trumpets?).  The important part to relate is that the 'God voice' wasn't any different from my usual self talk, but that with the practice I've had listening to the PBGs, I could distinguish it as important and separate from myself. I can't believe I just wrote that. Crazy Nut Case!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Marathon trip report  This entry is about my Seattle Marathon trip. If you are looking for a race report  urlLink look here . What a great trip. What started out as a compromise race (just happened to coincide with my training schedule) and a cost cutting measure (traveling with other people to reduce costs) turned into a wonderful excursion. My traveling companions were three ladies I met through a friend at the Running Room. Before the trip I knew next to nothing about any of them. What a crazy threesome I hooked up with. They, of course, knew each other and were great friends. They have participated together in other events before this one. I was the wild-card in the group.  For journal purposes, they will be referred to as Twisted Squirrel (TS), Flasher Squirrel (FS) and BonBon Squirrel (BBS). I, by the way, became known as Red Faced Squirrel (RFS). We all started out nervous about the trip; the unknown traveler (RFS of course), the new Marathon (for all of us except TS), driving a rental car across the U.S. Border, and what to expect for weather during the marathon. As it turned out, everything went really well. Our slightly delayed flight was bumpy, but uneventful. Our border crossing was slow ( hr) but we had a very nice crossing guard who was more interested in the marathon and how long it was than the apples we were smuggling across the border. And as for the weather, it was the best we could have hope for; not a drop of rain the whole time we were there (well, it  did  rain when we were in the car a few times, but that doesn't count, right?). When we arrived in Seattle, we were greeted by the eerie specter of the space needle glowing in the dark, surrounded by mist and a spooky glow. It looked like a UFO getting ready for take-off. After a few wrong turns, Mother Squirrel guided us to our hotel, we grabbed a late-night (2:00 AM) snack and retired to our beds. On day two of our trip, we visited the marathon Expo to pick up our race packages (you know, the timing chip, race number, race shirt and a ton of pamphlets and other goodies) The expo also had lots of other running paraphernalia available as freebies or for purchase. Since the weather was cooperating, we decided to take a walk down to Pike Place Market. I actually went to the " urlLink World Famous Pike Place Fish Market ", but they weren't throwing any fish at the time. While we were there, we heard these three black gentlemen singing a wonderful Christmas Gospel song; Their voices were very rich and beautiful. TS bought some prints, we got our picture taken and then went to have dinner. We had fresh seafood, of course ($$). Day Three: Marathon day ( urlLink look here for a race report ) We ran about 1 1/3 miles to the race as a warm-up. FS was running in the half-marathon, therefore, her race started earlier than the rest of us. We took pictures wished her luck and then checked my post race bag, did some last minute business and mentally prepared ourselves for the race. A short time later(!) we were all finished our races and ready to head back up the hill to the hotel. (FS didn't manage to save us any clam chowder! Poohie Sulk) We were quite a sight to see, hobbling back to the hotel with our shining silver warm-up capes flapping in the wind, finisher medals displayed proudly around our necks and big grins (and the occasional grimace) on our faces. We somehow managed to make it through the rest of the day without a long soak in a hot-tub; for me, a hot shower really doesn't cut it after a long hard marathon. BBS & I actually managed to muster enough energy to walk down to Eddie Bauers to do some cloths shopping before supper. After a celebratory supper and a few toasts  we all decided we were tired (I wonder why) so we trundled back to our hotel room and retired for the evening. For our last day, our travel plans called for a leisurely day with an evening flight from Vancouver to Edmonton. We packed up our stuff by 11:00 or so and all went window shopping. We expected our border crossing to take time, but were pleasantly surprised when it only took a couple of minutes. We stopped by BBS's aunts place and also had a brief stop at the Richmund waterfront.  Airport security also took very little time so before we knew it, we were raising a glass in the departure lounge and ready for the flight home. I was really fortunate to have my three squirrel friends as traveling companions. We shared a lot, laughed a lot, shopped a lot (well, more than RFS is used to, anyway) and when through a lot (remember, the marathon? Oh yeah, that). I hope I won't soon forget this wonderful adventure. I also hope I have more adventures with these wonderful people, ah, ahem, squirrels.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do you remember when I wrote about the small  urlLink Voice of God ? Well, I met up with the little girl who triggered that small gift of grace on the bus the other day. 
She told me that she was singing a bus song. You know, that is what we need more of. Songs for every occasion. Bus songs. Work songs. I love you so much it hurts songs... 
Oh wait, perhaps we have too many of those last type already ;) Anyway, this little girl is just a little bit of a thing and she and her mother are pretty shy. Without the girl, I doubt I would ever have been able to talk to the mother. So her mother recognizes me from the last time we met on the bus and shyly says that the song in question was "The Wheels on the Bus". Thinking of my  urlLink OOPBGB list  I asked her what her name was. She shyly said it was Divya. Welcome to my OOPBGB list Divya, I hope that you and your mother grow in the spirit and learn to break the silence, take a relational chance and  urlLink get messy . 
 If you ride city transit, you will know that there are lots of unspoken rules that everybody follows, like "Don't look at anybody else", "Don't touch anybody else's stuff" and "Never talk to anybody you don't know". I'm tired of these rules and try to break them when ever I can.  I LOVE looking at other people and trying to guess what kind of people they are. I have also decided to break the silence too. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All sorts of interesting things in the Blogoshpere. I just added a meta tag for locating my blog source on the planet and discovered who my net-neighbors are. You can click on the GeoURL link below to see who else is freezing their butt off in this nasty cold snap. I also added myself to blogwise, a site for categorizing web logs by self-attributed keywords and geographic locations. I am not registered yet as they have a backlog of 1200+ pages to view (!).  I wouldn't want THAT job. I got both these ideas from visiting  urlLink Ms. Frizzle's blog . I haven't looked at it too closely yet, but she seems to be a teacher in a middle school. Guess what, she uses the same template as me! She gets WAY more hits than me. She also seems to post twice a day.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Note, I wrote this in my paper journal on Jan 17 but entered it today.  Last night, Mo shared an "Oprah moment" she taped recently. Actually the Oprah segment she taped was about financial security, but she also taped a Dr. Phil show about a woman who has a phone phobia. Mo knows me pretty well, but some of you may be surprised to hear that I also have a phobia about calling people on the telephone. The guest on Dr. Phil's show doesn't like answering the phone and talking to people. She gets her husband to answer the phone. She never returns calls to friends who call her and leave messages for her. She always worries that she will get bad news when she answers the phone. She rationalizes that if she doesn't talk to people on the phone, she won't jeopardize her relationships with those people. From outside her phobia, it is obvious that she jeopardizes her relationships MORE by NOT answering the phone or returning peoples calls. MY phobia is using the phone to get information from strangers (and to a minor extent phoning acquaintances who are not expecting my call). I get very flustered, don't know what to say, miss important questions and get the details confused about details because I just want the call to be over. I often feel like I am stuttering too much and that the person on the other end of the phone thinks, "Who is this moron, anyway?" My anxiousness is usually strongest just before picking up the phone.  The mood of the person I am calling is totally unknown. I can't tell if I am interrupting them or catching them at a bad time. I feel like I don't know the proper protocol and feel incredibly stupid. I have developed some coping mechanisms over the years to mentally prepare myself for calls that just have to be made. I am much better than I was. I often try to get Mo to make calls to the doctor, order pizza, make reservations and the link.  If she catches on, sometimes she forces me to do it myself. Facing the fear is hard. Not using the phone is also hard in the modern world. Each time I face this fear, it gets a little easier to do. I still don't like it. I still have to work up my courage and get as prepared as I can before picking up the phone. But I do it. Do you have a fear that immobilizes you? Is there something you face every day that drives you to do irrational things?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am beginning to think that it is time to retire the  urlLink PBGs .  They have served me well in the past, but now I am a bit more comfortable with saying 'God' I don't really need my own personal pair of gods. That said, my own brand of gods have brought me a long way. I am so glad I was able to formulate my own understanding of the 'More' than physical referred to by Marcus Borg in his book " urlLink The Heart of Christianity ". Having my own grounding in  what I believe  makes it much easier to evaluate what others have written about what one  should believe . It is very surprising to find that many of the ideas related to me by the PBGs (I can't really take the credit for the ideas, can I?) are very similar to the ideas I am now reading about in Borg's books. His writing makes being a Christian much more palatable for me. On the other hand, I can see how his viewpoint is like stirring up a hornets nest in the 'earlier paradigm' crowd. I can hardly wait until my book study group starts discussing the chapter on Jesus.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well folks, I spent a moment or two and updated all the posts in September of this year. Wow, I wrote a lot of entries in September. That seems to be the time of year when I blog the most. I like to think that it is because the PBGs have more 'material' to speak to with me with (i.e. everything isn't all covered with snow). Mo proved me wrong in this regard the other day by finding a three sided bottle. It was great to go over all the posts from September as I brought them into the new site. There is a lot of great stuff in there and I tend to forget how things developed and what went on before. Hopefully revisiting the past will inspire me to post more than once a month (like in December).
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The PBGs don't think so, but  urlLink The Cluetrain Manifesto  thinks that the internet will serve a very big role in the future development of business. 
Literally, gotta run. 
Now it is later and my run is over. Due to the freezing rain we had on the week end and this morning we thought our valley run would be pretty treacherous. It turned out to be relatively good footing and the temperature was just right. You never can tell what the path will be like until you get out there and do it. Hmmm, that sounds like something the PBGs would say, doesn't it?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Prayer of Approach &nbsp;&nbsp; Quoted from my church bulletin  
O Great Spirit whose  urlLink voice we hear  in the winds, and whose breath gives life to all the world, hear us. We come before you as your children. We are small and weak; we need your strength and wisdom. Let us walk in beauty and make our eyes ever behold the red and purple sunsets. May our hands respect the things you have made, our ears be sharp to hear your voice.  urlLink Make us wise , so that we may know the things you have taught your people, the lessons you have hidden in every leaf and rock. We seek strength not to be superior to our brothers and sisters, but to live in harmony with ourselves and all of your creation. Help us to be ever ready to come to you, so when life fades as a fading sunset, our spirits may come to you without shame. Amen. 
  Traditional Native American Prayer   
 Benediction  
We have heard God call our name here. But this is not the only place God speaks. We listen each day for the voice of God, calling out our names. God is with us, always.   
Old words, new feelings; others have passed this way before me.   God be with you also.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know very little about Lent. Sure I know that it is 40 consecutive days leading up to Good Friday, the 'anniversary' of Jesus' crucifixion. I also know that people 'give up things for lent'. Back in November  urlLink Flasher Squirrel  told me and my marathon travel mates about her various Lenten self denials. So this year I decided to give up a few things for lent too. First, I have vowed to give up  clutter  for lent. How does one give up clutter, you may be asking yourself? Well, I have decided to pick up 100+ things around the house.  Every day! This may sound stressful, but you will be relieved to hear that I count picking up a bit of paper as one thing. Putting a dried fork away is another thing. Therefore, doing dishes is a very rewarding activity, indeed.  Just a point of clarification, however. Finding a dish in the living room and putting it near the sink does not count.  To count the item has to be put in it's final home. The dish has to be WASHED and DRIED and PUT AWAY before it counts. Therefore, actually collecting and washing dishes is not quite as rewarding as drying and putting away. I started practicing this Lenten commitment in January just to get a feel for how hard it was going to be to accomplish. The real deal (you know, Lent) started on Ash Wednesday. So far I have logged 110 and 128 things. Today I am up to only 38 things, so I had better get cracking!  Oh, and the other thing I am giving up for lent is having snacks at coffee time. Not healthy things like carrots and apples, but the over priced stuff they sell at the coffee bar. I already drink mostly water, so it is the snacks that have previously been my Waterloo. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I installed a new gadget to my Blog recently that allows me to see what kind of visitors I am getting. It tells me things like what browsers you are using, what links you are following to get here and what search terms you typed in to get here. Perhaps a bit snoopie of me, but then again, I am bearing my soul here so I want to know who is taking a peek. One of the interesting things I have noticed in my page stats is how many people are arriving here by searching for varients of two particular key phrases. The first is   Sara Freder Fake  .  On a whim, I subscribed to  urlLink Sara Freder 's 'service' to see what kind of advice she would give me. I made up a name and answered the questions as if I was someone else.  It was amusing reading for a while, but there was SO much repetition. After I refused to pay a few times, I decided enough was enough. On another whim, I decided to see what other people thought of Sara Freder by doing a Google search. I found some very serious people who, after being taken posted that she was a fake and a long list people replying with 'me too'. Since posting the page linked above, I have received quite a few hits from people who I assume are also coming to the realization that 'she' (if indeed there really IS a Sara) is not what she pretends to be.   The second frequent Google key phrase hit is   Phone Phobia  . I was quite surprised at the amount of interest this term generated for my little blog. I only  urlLink mentioned it once  in a declarative post that wasn't intended to help anyone else deal with this fear. I can only guess at the reasons people are searching out information about phone phobia:  looking for fellow sufferers  wondering how common it is  searching for testimonials or successful strategies  looking for resources for a signifigant other who has this debilitating fear  just looking for some  urlLink hope   or some other reason I will never fathom without it being told  Whatever their reasons, they ARE coming. And I thought to myself, "How can I facilitate these visitors and give them something worth come here for?" The  urlLink PBGs  suggested that I put my money where my mouth is. They said, "you have been spouting off about Action all the time.  Get busy buddy!". What?  Follow my own advise? Are you crazy? So They want me to face my own fear of phoning.  urlLink I procrastinate . I prevaricate, I stall, I rationalize.  They charge me to be the leader. The shining example. The call me to go boldy where no Star Treking Phone Phobiast has dared tread before (should that be 'dialed before'?). If YOU are one of those visitors, please, please, PLEASE leave a comment for me so I can understand why you are coming. You don't have to identify yourself. And now, I have a phone call I have been putting off, so if you will excuse me...  
 Progress report     &lt;DONE! Feb 24&gt;  - Phone the Space Sciences Centre Re: Boy's Group field trip   &lt;Pending!&gt;  - Phone church to get permission sheets and put notice in bulletin   &lt;Pending!&gt;  - Phone Parents (multiple calls!!)  

       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       7.6 Km, 38:03.7, Overcast 1&deg;C, 5 km wind  
I was thinking about  The More , the IS, the cosmic power on my run today.  You know, God. The thing that is more that just the reality that surrounds us. That additional thing, that mysterious unexplained factor that keeps us guessing and seeking. In my thoughts I was questioning again. Is there really a More? After all I have gone through from the beginning days of the  urlLink PBGs , the  urlLink Adult Baptism , I still question my faith in God. Is there really more than what I can see and understand with my own senses? So I take 'One Step back' on my faith journey. Ok. So. No god here. Just me. That brings me back to one of my original questions, pre PBGs, doesn't it.  Why am I here. What purpose is there that keeps me (literally) putting one foot in front of the other? Aha! The answer is right there in front of me. Even if I decide that there is no god (how rash!) I still need to believe that there is some purpose to my existence. It is easier to believe there is something worth living for than it is to live a life not worth living. Having no belief would cause me to despair and eventually I would give up. Hey, I don't like the direction  THAT  thought train is headed. So, I step forward again.  Ok. Maybe there isn't a god and I should just pretend I believe. If I am going to pull this off, I had better pick something that gives me purpose and that is not easily  disproved  because that would just leave me  One Step Back  (or perhaps even more steps back). But wait! Now I have purpose. I am on a quest. I am in pursuit of the 'More' that makes life worth living. I can handle that. If what I have discovered in my pursuit of God is anything to judge by, there are loads of things I can learn just by chasing this mysterious God concept. I step one  extra  step forward and decide that I believe in the More and use the God concept as my stepping stone to learn more about the mystery that is life and what makes it worth living. In a word, I choose to follow God.  
For more inspiring words about the 'More' concept, look into  urlLink Marcus J. Borg: The Heart of Christianity . There is other inspiring/challenging/thought provoking stuff in there as well.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.8 Km, 36:11.7, Sunny -11&deg;C, calm  I Ran at lunch today and took a trip around the scenic Edmonton river valley.  After puffing up a steep hill I took a breather at a bench in  urlLink Ezio Faraone Park  (actually the link shows a view that is virtually from the bench I am about to describe!) This quaint little park is very small and is dedicated to an  urlLink 33 year old policeman  who tragically was killed by two thieves he cornered in an alley.  Anyway, the bench I mentioned looks out over the river valley. On the bench is a memorial plaque remembering a couple who lived near by. The plaque said that they always admired the beautiful view from Ezio Faraone Park. I thought to myself, "Why do people bother putting up memorials like this? The couple are no longer here to appreciate either the view or the plaque." I mean, after all, there are billions of people on this earth.  Everyone thinks they are special and wants to be remembered.  What makes this plaque so special? The PBGs answer, "Well, the couple have surviving relatives, and it helps them remember the departed couple." "Fine and good,", I respond, "but what does that mean to the rest of us who never knew this couple?"  Ever patiently, the PBGs respond, "Lots of people admire this view. Lots of people remember lots of beautiful occasions and people. This memorial helps people revisit those good memories." As I returned to my running, my thoughts turned to my blogging and to the book I am currently reading:    urlLink Holy Fire   by  Bruce Sterling   In this book, Mr. Sterling describes a 'Memory Palace'. This memory palace is a place to store all the accumulated e-stuff its owner collected over a lifetime.  You decorate your memory palace like you would an office or a house, keep files, pictures, movies, and other memorablia in it.  Actually, it sounds a lot like a blog to me.  A very fancy blog with virual reality walls and a lock and key.  Probably not a public blog, but who knows, you might invite people 'over' to your memory palace and show them some of your stuff. I have been thinking it would be nice to have a virtual place to call my own.  A place for my memories.  A place to remind me of the beautiful views in the world. With this blog, maybe I already have the start of one.

       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       10.5 Miles, 1:40:41, Overcast -23&deg;C, 14 km wind, Wind Chill -32&deg;C  
It has been pretty cold with lots of wind; not conducive to running outside.Well, I managed to get two runs in the past 7 days. By myself for a change. 
Not that I don't enjoy running with my running buddies... But... 
It is hard to meditate when I run with others. As I tried to pick my way through the snow clogged paths and drifted snow, I also ruminated on my career path as well. The City was in the process of clearing the sidewalks, but often a stretch would be cleared and then the driver would double back and head off in another direction. Thus, I would choose what looked like a promising path only to have it abruptly become much more difficult to navigate. I deliberately chose some questionable paths because they were headed in the direction I wanted to go.  Sometimes they were better, sometimes worse than I had expected. At one point I was forced to run on the road and this path seemed quite unsafe. All in All, it was a hard workout but I reached my destination in one piece with no frostbite.   
Wendy Edey is a member of our church. She is also involve with the  urlLink Hope Foundation of Alberta  
she has written and posted many  urlLink articles  about hope. She spoke to us in church this Sunday about hope and dispair.
She told us that studies have been done that indicate that people usually don't hear good news. Wendy said that people, when told 4 positive things and 1 negative thing, usually remeber the negative thing and not the postive things.  She also mentioned that 95% of the news we get is negative.  If newspapers devoted an equal amount of space to positive news, there wouldn't be room for the advertising and the paper would be too heavy to carry. Is there room in your life for some hope?  
One of the things that also came out of my run was the idea that I want more than just a realationship with God.  My meditation helps me speak with God and  urlLink God speaks to me  through my experiences, but there is more to love than that. The Spirit in me wants to speak to the Spirit in others.  We are the expression of God. We are the  urlLink story tellers .  Without us God has no voice,  urlLink no hands .  I filter the God experience through my emotions, senses, life conversation. My expression of God wants to experience your expression of God. They are entirely different. Weather I am speaking to an reformed alcoholic, an Iranian man or a Chinese janitor, I still see the small voice of God within. I take the risk and speak. The path is hard.  But I have hope that it is worth it. ...and faith 

 refrain:  
        O Jesus, you have looked into my eyes;
        kindly smiling, you have called out my name.
        On the sand I have abandoned my small boat,
        now with you, I will seek other seas.

 
 Pescador de Hombres , "Fisher of Men."  by Cesareo Gabarain 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This spam yells at you "We're giving away up to $25,000,000!*" and the 'fine' print says: 
*No purchase necessary. See www.iwon.com for official rules, odds and prize information. Promotion ends 3/31/04. Open to US and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) age 13 and over. Odds of winning depend on number of entries received. Annual Grand Prize winner's odds of winning $25 million are 1:250. Annual Grand Prize paid in equal annual installments over 40 years without interest.  Come on people. Use your heads. If your math skills aren't very strong, let me help. $25 Million for ONE person over 40 years would be over $600,000 a year. This is a 'no purchase necessary' contest. For the odds to be 1:250 that would mean that  there are a maximum of 250 players in the contest and one prize of $25,000,000 (over 40 years)  there are  less  than 250 players in the contest and multiple multi-million-dollar prizes  They intentionally misrepresenting your chances of winning anything as the chances of winning the big prize  There isn't really a contest at all and they just want your email/contact information   Think it through. Remember, this is an unsolicited email received from a company that only asks for your email address. It has likely been sent to 25 million email boxes.  On with the test: Which is the most likely? What product do you think they are selling? How many units would they have to sell in order to be able to pay out $25,000,000 over 40 years? All contests are intended to increase sales. Businesses are willing to take a 10% hit for 'advertising'.  $250,000,000 in sales??? Must be a  huge  company. In business for 40 years? Must be a well known company. But wait,... ...there isn't any logos! What are they hiding? No identity. No known products. No Thanks!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This site shows bible quotations, chapter and verse in 30 odd different bible versions. Free reference like  urlLink Dictionary.com  without the advertisments. Take a peak:  urlLink PHIL 4:12  I found this on  urlLink Dave's Supergalactic Megafantastic Blog-o-rama . The quote seemed appropriate for my current situation too:  "I know what it is to be in need, and I know what it is to have plenty. I have learned the secret of being content in any and every situation, whether well fed or hungry, whether living in plenty or in want."  

       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As part of my on-going  urlLink service , I would like to provide you with a report on a questionable banner ad you might have encountered in your e-travels.  urlLink Tickle  is primarily a match making site or on-line dating site. But there are banner ads you may have encountered that are for various tests you can take. The test that caught my eye was an I.Q. test. You know the one, it has a picture of  urlLink Einstein  on it or some  urlLink colourful I.Q. test blocks . If you are curious, you click through. You are then brought to a 2 page I.Q. test which promises to tell you great things about your intelligence profile and even what careers that you would be suitable for. And it is "developed by PhDs" and "PhD certified" Great. I'm in. So I start answering the test questions. It takes a significant amount of time. Some of the questions are really easy, and others are quite tricky. After the second page, I am  interested &nbsp; in what my report will be. It seems like a valid test. But at this point, I know something that you might not be aware of.  I have encountered tickle before. I know that it is a match-making site. I have seen the popup ads for tickle at one of the sites I visit all the time. I have seen them enough to know how persistent they are. I am also wary of dating sites because of a spam email I received, got curious about and investigated. This spam mail dating site was an email and personal information collection scheme! Anyway, back to the test... Sure enough, after the final page of the I.Q. test, there is a screen that basically says, "Register on our site and we will give you the results of your test."    WHAT???!!  Grumble, grumble, ... waste my time ..., should never have clicked,...  Okay, so I want my results. I know that my name will go into the tickle dating database (They don't actually  tell you  that it is a dating database at this point). I have an extra (free) email that I am willing to sacrifice so I made up a name and some other contact details and filled in the fields. The  next  screen tells me the I.Q. results (134, not that I am bragging) and then offers to  sell me the full results  from an "actual PhD" for $9.95 (Access to the dating site is 'free', test results $9.95)! I just thought I would try and save you the trouble of going through this test, getting your contact information stolen and have you tempted to pay for a useless report in the bargain. Talk about sophisticated scheme, eh?   SO... be wary! There are lots of offers out there. Some are very sophisticated and it may seem like you are getting great value for a small price. But you have no idea what they will deliver. Consider the cost AND the benefit. Your personal information is very valuable. Don't provide it on a whim. It doesn't cost much to make a web page LOOK like it is backed by a reputable company.  [Edit] There are others who have  urlLink been burned  by not being wary of enrollment schemes like Tickle's IQ test. Note: I hesitate to link to the complaints.com. It appears to be a low maintenance site designed to attract click-through advertisement. There does not seem to be ANY filtering of content posted by visitors. Consumer-Beware with anything you read on this site. It does add some anecdotal evidence, however, allowing the reader to assess other people's experiences. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got a notification in my email from BlogPatrol.com warning about hackers masquerading as 'admins'. I am glad that they notified me about this particular dodge. The attachment is, no doubt, a virus or some other malicious program. The twist that makes it notable is that the file is zipped and has a password. That means that the content is encrypted. Email and virus scanners, therefore, cannot scan the content of these files and must skip them. That means, dear reader, that YOU are your own worst enemy. If you are unwary, you put in the password, decrypt the virus and run the program, thinking it has already been scanned. IT HAS NOT BEEN SCANNED! Don't be fooled. Most, if not all, reputable services will NOT  urlLink send you an attachment  with executable code. Exploits are changing quickly. Be wary of anything that seems suspicious. If you are not sure about something, ask someone you trust about it. You can also do what I do when I get something fishy in my email. Use a search engine to see if  urlLink other people  have encountered the same thing. More than likely, others have had your problem and can offer  urlLink additional information .  For your reference, here is the text of the fake message. 
 
   Dear user of Blogpatrol.com,

   We warn you about some attacks on your e-mail 
   account. Your computer may contain viruses, in 
   order to keep your computer and e-mail account 
   safe, please, follow the instructions.

   For more information see the attached file.  For 
   security reasons attached file is password 
   protected.  The password is \"52335\".

   Cheers,
   The Blogpatrol.com team
   http://www.blogpatrol.com

   Attachment 1 
   Type: application/octet-stream
   Filename: TextDocument.zip
   Encoding: base64 Download  
 I find the most scary thing about this hoax is how  friendly  and personal it seems. It comes from a site I trust and seems to be directed right at me. The level of  urlLink psychology  that spammers are using is increasing. It could be that it is only a matter of time before I am fooled too. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so I have decided to bear my sole (take off my running shoes?) and let you have a peek at my running log. I have been keeping track of my running progress on  urlLink Running-Log.com  for almost 2 years now. The site only shows you a monthly view of my running, not the more in-depth statistics it provides me. If you are a runner who is still using an old paper log (or an old calendar like I did at the start), perhaps it is time to upgrade and use an on-line log. On the other hand, if the site or the net goes down, you may lose access to your log (don't laugh, it happened to me once).  I guess I just like to live dangerously.

       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In Sunday School next week I will be teaching my  urlLink rotation  on the Crucifixion of Christ.  Challenging material to discuss with adults, let alone a mixed group of kids from kindergarten to grade 6. I thought I would make God's Eyes with them and somehow tie in all the cross aspects. I haven't fully fleshed out what I am going to do. I just hope I don't wait until the last minute to get things figured out.   While we are on the subject, have you heard about the movie " The Passion of the Christ " by  urlLink Mel Gibson ? I haven't seen it yet, but there is a group of us from my church going.  One of the leaders at our church directed us to a news release the United Church of Canada has put out about the concepts in this movie.  Here are some links:  
     urlLink The United Church of Canada issues statement on Lent and The Passion of The Christ  
     urlLink Deepening the Dialogue about "The Passion of The Christ"   I am doing more thinking about church this lent than I have done in all the past 40 years. Wait a minute...  40 days  of lent...  40 years  old...  40 days  in the wilderness... Is there a  significance ?   urlLink Nah ! Anyway, like the greater church, my minister also directs my attention away from "Jesus died for our sins on the cross" to "Jesus loved us so much He made the ultimate sacrifice for championing the cause of the oppressed and suffering". He was willing to stand up to an oppressive and unfair social  system .  It does not seem to matter what identifiable group you are considering, there is always an elite group that takes control. It is the elites who separate, marginalize, put themselves above and apart from, denigrate and impoverish, take advantage of and oppress the masses. Could Jesus have chosen a bigger red flag to wave at the elites than " The meek shall inherit the Earth "?   Just for the record, I am in no way anti-Semitic.

       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate my current work. I don't like the environment. Our office is scummy. Our focus has changed from 'Science' to 'poker'. I don't feel like I get any respect or positive feedback for the work I do. I sometimes feel that the 'decision makers' above me have lost touch with reality. 
Sure there are lots of things about my work that I do like. That is what makes it so hard to look for other work. I don't intend on listing what the good things are... ( EDIT: not much point of doing that now is there? ) So I took my troubles to the  urlLink PBGs . Ok, I'll say it, I prayed to Them... while running, for help. Let me tell you, that is not my way of doing things at all. I am uncomfortable with prayer and I think it is ONLY in the context of running that I could possibly be comfortable with 'voicing' a prayer. As my run progressed I came to the conclusion that I really  didn't  want angels sliding down gossamer beams coming to my rescue. I have never had difficulty getting work in the past. I would fluke out and someone would offer me a job and I would accept it. Bang, bang, bang. It did, however seem like a pretty random process. I hardly ever considered if the job I was accepting was the right job for me. Not exactly career  planning . Sort of career  wandering . So in the end, I ask Them NOT to help me get a job. "I would like to take a hand in it myself."  Much to my surprise, They agreed that "that would probably be for the best." But, they didn't leave it at that.  They also sent me a couple symbols that notified me that their hand would be hidden, but their influence would still be there (and visible if I cared to look). They also said that blessings would be mine should I choose to accept them.   God paints the sky every moment of every day. If I choose to look at the ground, I can keep my world grey and negative. But when I am ready, all I have to do is look skyward to see the wonders placed there for all to see.   EDIT: This post is  way  overdue. I didn't actually post it until March 23, after I had been looking for work for 3 weeks 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I read Rebecca Blood's book  urlLink  The Weblog Handbook : Practical Advice on Creating and Maintaining Your Blog . I like the book and I like the Author's style too.  I think, however, I am not interested in maintaining a "filter" style blog. I tend to be too conservative. I stick pretty close to my own corner of the internet. I read a few blogs on a regular basis, but I limit my time to explore. I like to link to interesting articles, but it takes such a long time for me to compose decent remarks (I am pretty fussy) that I don't even do that often. The  urlLink PBGs'  path was originally an expose of my experiences in running. Things have drifted a bit recently. I am focusing more and more on the process of blogging and attracting attention and less and less on the important matter of my spiritual growth. The PBGs have told me time and again that the web stuff is simply a distraction. So if you'll excuse me, I have a job to go search for.  On the other hand, I still like blogging. Maybe I'll get one of those sites that allows you to divide your posts into categories. That way, I can have PBGish thoughts and web-linky thought and keep them separate. Tell me what you think. If you know how they do that, leave me a comment.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On my lunch break, I took a stroll around the building. With the wierd weather this year, I wanted to enjoy the lack of wind and sunny skies. Nice and warm. On a whim, I sub-verbalized a "prayer" of thanks giving to God for giving me so much in my life. Of course, God didn't make a sunny day just for my pleasure. She would have made it sunny anyway. But God also brought me to the point where I was able to be glad to experience the day. Those of you who are parents will probably understand that we give to our children not because we need their praise. We don't feed, clothe, bathe, shelter, ..., (we don't want to be here all night) them because we want them to make us cute little statues in school. We do it because we love them unconditionally. We forgive their mistakes. We love them because of their imperfections. God's love it like that too. That helps me feel more comfortable about thanking God. God doesn't demand my thanks. Every parent knows that a child's 'debt' is not repaid by strips of burlap, glue, tissue paper and pipe-cleaners. It is repaid with a look, a touch, a smile and just the fact that they are who they are. That they are growing to be who they are destined to be. So in your life, do your best to make your God proud of you. Not for his praise. Not as a repayment of the goodness you have received. Not even for the praise you might receive from God's other children. But simply because it is the right thing to do.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       6.4 Km, 30:27.36, Sunny 3&deg;C, light wind  Ran by myself today on Neal's School route. I pushed myself much harder than I would have prior to running with Neal (approx. 7 min & 37 sec per mile!). I guess in a way, I am pushing myself to be a better Christian too. My friends down south would probably say that I am getting a healthy shove from God too. Can't deny that. It would be tough to pull this old camel through a particularly tiny needle eye without some spiritual assistance. Looking back on my spiritual quest, I am amazed. When I look back on my marathoning path I am equally amazed. I wouldn't say I was in  bad  shape before I started running. It is just that I am in so much  better  shape now. Then there is my quest to be a good group leader. There are  loads of  a few skills I don't posses that are necessary for being a good leader:  planning skills  organization skills  ability to call people on the phone (remember my  urlLink phone phobia ?)  administrative experience   Well I guess I have a bit of all of those skills. Pushing myself to do these things is what makes me stronger in these areas. God's support helps me to face what I would ordinarily shy away from. Having a Godly purpose makes the doing easier and the 'pain' worth it. Heck even the pain doesn't seem all that awful.   One final note. I am under immense pressure and stress. But my attitude is still relatively positive. Thank you everyone, Mo especially, for your support  [editor note: I want to bring the running back to the PBGs' Path by listing the run stats at the top like my earlier posts.] 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I learn more from preparing for a  urlLink Sunday School Rotation  than any other time.   Parable of the Empty House -- taken from  Jesus Christ and the Christian Life: Vignettes of Truth   When the unclean spirit has gone out of a man, it passes through waterless places seeking rest, but it finds none. Then it says, "I will return to my house from which I came." And when it comes it finds it empty, swept, and put in order.  Then it goes and brings with it seven other spirits more evil than itself, and they enter and dwell there; and the last state of that man becomes worse than the first.    Matthew 12:43-45   Here, vividly if grimly, is dramatized the peril of the uncommitted life, of one who may have had a genuine religious experience of forgiveness and deliverance but who does not follow it up with the positive acts and discipline of discipleship. The cleaned house needs to be occupied by the Holy Spirit.  I think this is an answer to the discussion I had recently about why "just being a good person" isn't enough. If your house is empty, who knows what will take up residence. If you do not know where you stand, you open yourself to drifting without purpose and conviction. Who knows what 'demons' will 'possess' you. Drug addictions, workaholism, sex addition, depression,... there are lots of demons we employ when our lives are empty and without purpose.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonight, Mo and I read an article in the paper about Easter becoming too commercialized. This all-too-familiar rant appears for almost every holiday season now. It is almost as predictable as the changing of the seasons. While I agree with the sentiment, it has definitely lost a lot of its bite for me. But it did get me thinking. Having recently been to the  urlLink Passion of the Christ,  the contrast between Bunnies and Blood is very much at the forefront of my mind. On one hand there are those who want to shock you into believing. They want you to believe that God will be angry with you if you don't acknowledge that Jesus died a horrible death on the cross because we are intrinsically sinful from birth: BBC news reported at the end of March on a  urlLink mock crucifixion,  complete with fake blood and gore that shocked shoppers and bystanders in the town of Reading.  Here is another article about the same story in the Guardian: urlLink Gory crucifixion makes town's shoppers cross   And on the other hand, there are whole stores set up to sell us Jesus' merchandise:  urlLink Devine Treasures  is a store that is having a sale on Easter paraphenalia. I checked out the rest of their site and found a plethora of religious items for sale. Crosses, plaques, plates, crucifixes, statues, angles, music boxes etc.   Why don't they set up a temple, get some money changers and sell some indugences as well?  It is the Golden Calf that we pay homage to, not God or Jesus. So it isn't  just  secular society that is selling Jesus down the Via Dolorosa. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just couldn't resist quoting this little gem from  urlLink Ms. Frizzle's  blog: You can safely assume that you've created God in your own image when it turns out that God hates all the same people you do.   -Anne Lamott   While I am not big on hating anybody, I am moved to think about who my 'created' gods, the  urlLink PBGs , hate. LOL. I also got a giggle from her lab rat story about infrequent blog posters. I hope the  PBGs Path  is on the Frizz's visitation list.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have knowingly put my hand into a hornets nest. My post  urlLink Yes, but am I a Christian?  has attracted attention from the USA bible belt. No fur has flown yet, but I fully expect that someone will see my attitude as blasphemous. I assure you that my intent is far from blasphemy. When I use the term "Pop Bottle Gods" or PBGs it is really a placeholder for the God we all hold so dear. Due to my past non-involvement with organized religion, my PBGs were an access point that I found less threatening and more palatable during my spiritual awakening. They (the PBGs) allowed me to have a dialog with the divine that would not be possible in any other way. Through this conversation, I have become more involved with our church (through the grace of God) and I have far less discomfort with the term "God". As I have written elsewhere, I have a knee-jerk reaction to the word "jesus" (lower case 'j' intentional).  I continue to have associations between jesus and evangelical-born-again-Christians. The negative connotation stems from the secular world's general disdain of all things religious. It also stems from the witness attempts by groups such as the Mormons (more formally The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints), Jehovah's witness, and others. Now that my own attitudes toward my own spirituality have changed, I am less dismissive of these witness attempts. I am less vulnerable because I am more comfortable with my own faith. More importantly, I am more able to discuss intelligently with witnessers the merits of their position. Sometimes I can even leave them with thoughts about their own beliefs. After all, I have just as much to learn from these children of our common God as they do from me. The details of their beliefs are different from mine. But that doesn't make them less human, nor does it make them less my neighbors in God. Join the discussion! I now have my TrackBack thingy working.  Thank you  urlLink Ron Shank  for your prayers and your plea to potential "blaster" to hold back. I am indeed, as you say, "called by God". I do not know where God leads me, but I do know the place I go will be far grander than the place I would have gone with out Him/Her.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On one of my blogrolled sites, Susan says  urlLink  Is He a Christian?   From her description I am not at all sure that  I would qualify  as a Christian. So I left her a  urlLink comment  to see what she thinks. I hope she responds either on her site or mine. Susan, if you are reading this, check out my  urlLink PBGs introduction  page. My journey has been pretty non-standard to this point and I wonder what you think of it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do you get emails from friends and relatives that say, "Pass this on to everyone in your address book"? Most of my acquaintances know that I don't respond to these and I usually don't forward them either.  But when I do get them, I don't just delete them. I am usually a little more proactive about the "spam" I receive. I like to inform myself about the messages I am sent. (Hence my "Spam Report" series) Then, if I find something dangerous or interesting, I send a reply to the person who sent me the email. Sometimes I tell them they are propagating a hoax. Sometime I tell them that they have been tricked. To my surprise, the latest "pass it on" email I received from my brother contains valid  advice that is based on fact rather than fiction! The email concerns three warning signs of stroke:  ask the individual to smile.  ask him or her to raise both arms  ask the person to speak a simple sentence   You can read more about it  urlLink here 

       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got the word from on high. Today is the start of my Marathon training for the Edmonton Marathon in August. No, not  that far  on high, just from Neal. We start our first training run of 4 miles tonight. He will be celebrating the event with some new shoes. If you want to check on our progress, I will be setting up a countdown clock  urlLink here . I doubt that I will be posting training comments or anything else there, so no need to bookmark that page. Our training program is 12 weeks and Larry, Neal and I all have a pretty good base. Larry is running 24 Miles a week and Neal and I are running 27 miles. Our longest run will be 23 miles! Yikes.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink Ron Shank  and I are making progress of sorts. We have taken our discussion about things religious off the public stage into email and chat. Ron and I are surprisingly similar. There are, however, things that we strongly believe that differ. Here is a brief summary. 
   Assertion  Ron  TM90    Bible is Infallible  Yes  No    Bible is Valuable  Yes  Yes    homosexuality is an Abomination  Yes  No&dagger;    There's more to Christianity than being a Good Person  Yes  Yes    Promiscuous behavior can be physically harmful  Yes&Dagger;  Yes    Promiscuous behavior is a Mortal Sin  Yes  Yes    Homosexuals should be allowed to Marry  No  Yes*    Marriage would 'Save' Homosexuals  No  Yes     Notes:   I haven't passed this table before Ron yet, but I think I have captured his intentions in the table. If he disagrees, or wants other qualifiers, I will update this post.  &dagger; &nbsp;God and the Bible would seem to disagree with me on this point.  &Dagger; &nbsp;perhaps Ron would say that unrepentant promiscuity is  always  dangerous to your salvation  * &nbsp;I do not think marriage  must  be supported by churches; I would be satisfied by a secular service that had some legal weight. If they wish to profess their commitment to God, that is up to them, naturally.   Ron and I have yet to discuss Salvation. I suspect that my beliefs as listed above preclude me from Salvation. Then again, it has been pointed out that I am an  urlLink idolater , thief, adulterer, liar and a murder.  I probably wasn't going to Heaven anyway. 


       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Note: Look here for the  urlLink entire spectrum  of belief in  urlLink this issue . No, Ron, you  urlLink have it wrong . I wasn't saying that  you  were intolerant. I was implying that your interpretation of  God  and the messages you take from the  Bible  as being intolerant. I looked at the links you suggested in your post. I particularly liked the flash presentation. The concepts in that presentation have been laid out by you in your blog again and again. This presentation sums up your position quite well. Here are some highlights:  He will punish all liars, the lustful, adulterers, idolaters, and blasphemers (Revelations 21:8). The place of eternal punishment is Hell.  This comes after some explanation of what God considers a lie, lustful, adultery, and idolatry, which, of course includes nearly every action we, as human beings, take. It then goes on to say that:  God does not want you to perish. He is rich in Mercy and compassion, and has provided a way for you to be forgiven.  God expects an almost impossibly high standard (well, god-like, actually) and then gives you an easy out. Sounds a lot like a used car salesman to me. ("Just $19.95 three times a week buys you all this!"). The presentation goes on to say that if you simply say the magic words (and to its credit, it says the intention behind the words is more important than the words themselves) that all will be right again. Oh and read the bible. That's important too.
 So God is willing to pay your bail as long as you admit that you are worthless and useless. God is offering it to you as proof of His love for you.  This portrait of God, to me, implies that God has very little respect for his creation. He knows that we are filthy as hell and expects us to be darling little angels and promises to throw us into the fiery furnace for eternity if we don't relent and become his puppets. If Ron and the people of his faith are right, then many of us are in mortal danger because:  No one comes to the Father except through me.
  All must come to God through Ron's faith. God has no tolerance for slackers. God does not take gays. God does not take Muslims. God  certainly  doesn't take Jews (because they don't except Jesus). God is so intolerant that He is only willing to give you a chance if you dangle on His strings. But if not, it's the rubbish tip for you. I am not at either extreme in my stance. I have no solid answers. I don't know if homosexuality is biological or not. I don't know if sexual orientation can be changed. It, like handedness, can probably be changed if your 'treatments' are extreme enough (with questionable humanity, I might add). I just don't believe that homosexuals are any more evil than heterosexuals. I am sorry Ron. I just can't buy that. It is your  interpretation  of how God works that I find intolerant. Ron 'knows' he has solid answers because he believes that the bible is  THE TRUTH .  Even if that is the case, the bible is still open to interpretation. Those who choose to interpret it one way and deny all other interpretations have solid answers. But they do come off sounding intolerant.

       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Intolerance ( n-t l  r- ns)  urlLink \In*tol"er*ance\ , n. ...   The quality of being intolerant; refusal to allow to others the enjoyment of their opinions, chosen modes of worship, and the like; want of patience and forbearance; illiberality; bigotry; as, intolerance shown toward a religious sect.   In response to  urlLink Ron Shank's post  on  urlLink Same Sex marriges  in the State of Massachusetts. In  urlLink another post , Ron accuses  urlLink this nice couple  (and I say couple because that is what I believe they are) of calling the wrath of God down on the entire USA. I don't believe  urlLink this man  needs any help at all from  them  in accomplishing that. 


       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing is gained by dwelling in the past; who knows what the future holds; I think I can deal with the present. So 'Happy Birthday' to me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am experimenting with a new picture posting product called Hello. I think I will be able to start sprucing up my blog with some small graphics. The only trouble might be the automatic sizing that happens when you upload a picture. I hope I can work this out. Until then, here is a picture you may or may not have seen before:   urlLink      Me in the 2003 Seattle Marathon&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For the runners (new and old) in the crowd, join  Phillip Martin  in his preparations for:
 Fall 2004 Marathon Season. I've Rejoined the Leukemia and Lymphoma Society's Team in Training and hope to raise $2000 and complete my 3rd Chicago Marathon.  
on his new blog  urlLink TNT18  I encourage others to take fitness into their own hands and dare to dream big. Don't kid yourself, every marathon is a struggle. But it is the challenge that makes all the effort worthwhile. I have completed three now and I am about to gear up for the Edmonton Marathon in August. Now all I have to do is find money for new shoes and the entry fee.


       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been reading  urlLink Nikki P's  journal for some time now. She is a spirited lady who always tells it, if not how it really is, exactly the way she sees it. With Passion.  While I don't always agree with her outlook, I always respect her ability to cut to the heart of any issue. She gives a long list of personal aquaintances, in the link above, who have been killed senselessly by  gun-toting 'morons'. In my opinion these people have no business owning guns. In fact, the number of people with guns  is at the heart  of the problem. But I digress... Nikki goes on to say that what we need is more prayer and "more time [dedicated] to Jehovah". Amen. But what strikes me as ironic is this part: In 2001, a co-worker of mine was shot and killed....because someone didn't like the way he drove.  Senseless......  I wish people didn't care about the things that didn't matter. I wish that people would think more and act less. I wish that people would learn to rely on and trust in God more than material things and pride.  I respect her stance on this, but Nikki is also quick tempered and often posts  urlLink rants about bad drivers  and other blatant acts of 'stupidity'. If she is going to preach lessons of tolerance, perhaps she should re-read her own journal and grab a little tolerance herself. 

       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What every mother wants (well, the mother in this household, anyway).
 urlLink Chocolate, Bar None . From the article:  And it's not enough to just drop subtle hints ... we must provide our children (and our mates) with all the information they'll need to properly show their appreciation for the wonderful job we mothers do: We must give them recipes. Chocolate ones. With this in mind, I feel it is my public duty to share with you some of my personal favourites - all eminently suitable for Mother's Day, and all  easy enough for even a dad  [emphasis added] to help make.  Well, I for one know my way around the kitchen. And I have also received some not-so-subtle hints from Mo too. Chocolate, must buy chocolate! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The internet is a weird and amazing place. I was just listening to a CD I picked up at the local Folk Festival many years ago. There is a song about "The Movie With The World's Worst Title". 
 urlLink  Cannibal Women in the Avocado Jungle of Death  &nbsp; (also known as  urlLink  Piranha Women of the Avocado Jungle of Death  &nbsp; as popularized by song writer,  Christine Lavin   I thought Christine's version of the story (see second link) was funny, but apparently the actual movie (yes, there IS an actual movie with this name) is even funnier. I haven't actually seen the movie, but all the accounts of it I found say it is hilarious. The first link above  has some snapshots, audio clips and one video clip. Enjoy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I  think  my comments are working properly. Then again, I haven't exactly been flooded with comments lately.  urlLink Susan Prince  of  urlLink Sisters'  emailed me to say that she couldn't open the comment window by clicking the comment link below. It works for me and I have received comments from  urlLink Ron  and  urlLink Mike  among others. Is there anyone else who can't make a comment? Leave a comment below... No, wait, that won't work. Um.. Alas, I will have to for-go my usual shyness and paranoia and release my email address so you can contact me that way. I guess it is time to dive into the deep end of the blog-o-pool and start standing by my words. I can be reached at  Terminal  Man90&#64;g  mail &#46; com    Susan says she has JavaScript turned on and thinks that the Haloscan popup isn't being suppressed by a popup suppressor. Anybody have another idea about what might be going wrong on her end?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I admit it. I am a stats junky. I haven't started a 12 step program yet, but I admit that I have a compulsion to check my  urlLink website stats  at least 4 times a day. I just can't resist the temptation to see how many new visitors I have. I love to see what posts are getting the hits. I want to know who I am drawing in with what. Call me vain.  There is no question about it Holmes. Curiosity killed this cat.  But I am sometimes at a loss to figure out what people where  really  looking for from the search terms they type in. What do you think the person who typed in "Rat Food" was looking for? I  can  tell that they  didn't  find discount rat pellets or  urlLink weed rat stew  recipes on The  urlLink PBGs ' Path. Some of you might be asking yourself, "Why was TM90 posting  urlLink about Rat Food anyway ?".
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Mike posts on  urlLink Waving or Drowning?  (which, BTW, is a poem I love and wrote an essay about at university. The poem is " urlLink Not Waving But Drowning " by Steve Smith.) about Works and their importance to Spirituality. We do not do the work. On that I agree with you. I do think we have the responsibility to "prepare the soil". In our little tribe we talk about doing our part so God can do His part. He makes all this available to us, but we are responsible for working with God in this formation.  The  urlLink PBGs  really agree with this post. Works are as important as faith. You cannot control God nor can you " urlLink push the plan ". On the other hand, God doesn't make all the decisions either. If you are unwilling to play the part cast by God for you, the plan is altered irrevocably. That doesn't mean it is ruined, just changed. When you work  with  God instead of against God, things go in the right direction. When you work against God, good things still happen, but I suspect they are not as grand as the were meant to be.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Okay, so I have been giving Faith and Salvation a lot of thought lately. And, sure enough, at church today, that seemed to be the focus of the sermon. The PBGs are relentless. Or maybe that is just me. Briefly, the reading today was about Jesus eating with the Pharisee, Simon. Along comes a woman of 'low social standing' who crys on Jesus' feet, drys them with her hair and anoints them with perfume from an alabaster jar (Luke 7:36-50) (not to be confused with Mary and the Alabaster jar). Listening to the viewpoint of our Minister, I heard that God's grace is given to all.  I asked him after the service my "Chicken and the Egg question." I said, "Which comes first, Faith or Salvation (i.e. the grace of God)?" He said that in his opinion we didn't have to do anything special to earn God's grace, it is available to anyone who is willing to accept it.  I expect that means he doesn't think too highly of the concept original sin then either. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Here is a series of pictures depicting the birth of a humming bird. Thank you  urlLink Mom  for the link. This is truly amazing! Be sure to click on NEXT PAGE at the bottom of each page...there are four pages.  Adults and children will find this very interesting.  Enjoy!!!  This lady found a humming bird nest and got pictures all the way from the egg to leaving the nest. Took 24 days from birth to flight. Very neat and good pictures.  urlLink Humming Bird Nest   I was told to share it with the grandkids and kids, which I did, and I also thought I would share it with the PBGers too. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This report, due to circumstances, must remain a  Buyer Beware  report. I simply don't have enough information to prove any wrong doing by the company Bernard Haldane. All I have is a very bad taste in my mouth from the bait dangled before me. I received and invitation to an 'interview': We have had the opportunity to screen your resume on [websiteName] and upon review would like to invite you in for a consultation meeting/career evaluation  Right away, I thought, "This is some head hunter," so I was already on my guard. So I googled the company up and investigated their career change form (the one that offered a report). After three pages of forms, they referred me to the local Bernard Haldane office. Okay, so I phoned the number from the original email. The lady asked me to set up an appointment, and, wanting to practices my new-found  urlLink phoning skills , I proceeded to ask what I could expect to get out of the consultation. I was surprised when the woman's hackles went up. Her abrupt change of tone rang warning bells and I pushed a bit harder for more information. She said that "if I didn't already know what kind of service they were offering, then perhaps the consultation wasn't for me." What? Now who was sounding out-right rude? So I canceled the interview. And did some more research. I was surprised to locate at least 12 different web addresses that hit on a google on company's name. The sites were all variations on haldane or jobhunter.  The websites vary from very professional-looking to clunky and old-school. The hype level is high but actual company information is sparse. My first visit to the highest hit was professional and stated that this 50+ year old company has offices in North America, Europe and the UAE. What I didn't see on my first exploration was that there are  urlLink other  people complaining about or suing this company.  urlLink One guy said  that the company are members of the US BBB but that he had found 500 complaints about this company. My search of the Canadian BBB also found a lawsuit from 2002. Like I said, I don't have any proof that this is a bad company, but I certainly don't regret canceling my appointment with them. I don't need practice saying no to high pressure sales and a fee of excess of $1300 [edit]  This post has languished as a 'draft' post for more than a month now. It is time to post it and move on.  On digging a bit deeper, I have found a little bit more information about this company.  I found a transcript of a  urlLink W-Five program  about the practices of this company.  I found a reference to the original company in the latest copy of  What colour is your Parachute?, 2004 : A Practical Manual for Job-Hunters & Career-Changers by Richard Nelson Bolles.    Mr. Bolles states that Bernard Haldane, the founder of this company was a brilliant man who started a job placement company just after the second world war. Haldane sold the company about a decade ago and it has grown exponentially to 90 locations. Mr. Bolles couldn't recommend the new company services either.  So I leave it to you. If you are desperate enough, perhaps you want to spend $3,000 to $7,000 getting a spruced up resume and some job search pointers. Apparently, this is the only service they provide and there is no guarantee that you will be successful landing that perfect job. Or you can pick up a copy of Parachute for $17.00 and it will give you the skinny on how you REALLY can get the job of your dreams. The choice is yours.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm on a roll tonight. Here is another link from a link. Thanks to TNT18 for the running related PBGish  urlLink link .  urlLink Ravi Zacharias International Ministries (RZIM)  This story also has the elements of obedience, fear and recognition of our sinful nature. But it seem much more gentle somehow. Less focused on guilt and self loathing. More about building me up than tearing me down. I may be a lonely guilty sinner now, but with hope, faith, and the love of God, I can become more Christ like and fulfill my destiny.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Following the links on the  urlLink International Weblogger's Day  (June 9) lead me to the  urlLink Innovators for Christ  site. While I have yet to discover a post that seems remotely innovative to me, I did  urlLink discover a post  that touches on some of the things  urlLink Ron Shanks  and I have been discussing, dealing with homosexuality (in this case ordination of homosexuals) and recent changes in the USA.  There are two basic principals at the root of this problem.  The inerrancy of the Holy Scriptures: You have to believe that what Paul wrote to the Romans in chapter 1 verses 26 and 27 is false. You have to be able to read that and justify unnatural and indecent behavior in your ordained leadership.  You have to be able to justify unrepentant sinners as qualified to lead believers in a life committed to repentance. I don't think that homosexuality is worse than any other sin. The type of sin is not the issue to me. If Mr. Robinson stood before the church and said "I steal all my food from the grocery store because I love the rush I get from it, and I don't intend to stop". People would be outraged and Robinson would be run out of the church.  How and when, did the sin of homosexuality receive amnesty?  This sound very much like what Ron has to say. Very succinctly put. Gets right to the nub of the issue. Even uses the same Bible quotation Ron gave me. If I had more faith in the infallibility of the Bible, I would have to change my mind about the ordination of ministers too. On the other hand, if Ron is right that I am an  urlLink Idoliter  et al, then I wouldn't be suitable as a minister either. Case-in-point, all humans are sinners so no-one should have amnesty. Therefore, nobody has the right to represent God as a minister. Except for God's grace. So why should we single out the Homosexual sinner? Or the one who steals his groceries for that matter?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Alas, my ' urlLink session ' with the  urlLink PBGs  didn't help me much. My thoughts kept coming back to my conversation with my blog friend, Ron. It did seem to confirm the importance of faith in all of this. I also got the feeling that I am being a bit stubborn and that I really need to ground my decisions with additional Bible reading. That can't be a bad thing. I have some quick things to say about  urlLink Ron's latest  (and last? I think not!) post.  I did not mean to imply that I didn't believe in God or that God didn't create the universe. On the other hand, I don't think that God created the earth in 6 literal days. I see this creation story as a metaphor only. Ron won't like that, but that is tough.  I did not mean to imply that I think the Bible is  false , just that it isn't  infallible .  I only tried to take the Bible out of the conversation regarding faith because I wanted to hear what  Ron  felt about faith, not what was written in the Bible. He has quoted the Bible enough and I wanted to get past that to what he felt. More on this later in this post  I don't want to argue about evolution either. We have differing opinions about it; enough said.   Based on your (presumed by me) assumptions about me, Ron, you have lumped me in with other Bible haters. Ron, I am surprised by you. I would have thought it was apparent to you that I am ready to read the Bible with you and see what I could get from it. I am just not ready to see it as a tautology. I am not ready to accept a 10,000 year old earth because the Bible is from God and God doesn't lie. As you know, the Bible is a valuable repository of useful social guidelines. I even accept that the Prophets were influenced by a direct connection to God in some way I can't fathom. Just because I can't fathom that process does not mean it isn't possible. On the other hand, have you read the description of Ezekial's vision? It sound like he was tripping out on magic mushrooms! I am positive there is a metaphoric meaning to this vision, but I don't know what it is. You spoke at length of conscience. I wasn't clear on what you were getting at, however. Were you trying to imply that conscience and soul are somehow linked or words for the same thing? Surely a soul is more than just a persons conscience? Anyway, the difference between our positions seems to be that you see conscience as a trait or fundamental and I see it as a set of learned behaviors. I see it as a learned behavior. There certainly seem to be people who never developed a conscience due to improper upbringing. I see conscience as a creation of society that is transmitted to an individual. It is a fabric of rules that allow us to co-exist without falling into anarchy. It is taught to a child by his/her parents to assure their survival and procreation in society. Having said that, I have no intention of our discussion wandering into the realm of Social Darwinism. Let us press on. ...when you start to question one part of scripture, the whole things starts to unravel pretty quickly.  If it was my intention to discredit the Bible, unraveling it would be my goal. That, however, is not my purpose. My point is that making allowance for poetic license, imagery, metaphor or other elements of  urlLink story telling  doesn't diminish the power of the content of the Bible, but is certainly changes what you believe the document is telling you. If you find a quote in the bible that says that women are property and you believe the Bible is Gods final (unchanging) word, and you believe that God must be followed at all cost, then By God, women shouldn't be allowed to vote (among other things). I can see why Bible literalists are tying themselves in knots trying to get everyone to see that the 'progress' we have made in so many equality issues have being a denial of Gods Holy Word. But we have been around that merry-go-round before too. I am running low on bullets too. Yet there is no great appeal for you to accept that grace, because you don't want to be  motivated by fear . Solomon reminds us repeatedly, that "fear is the beginning of wisdom", and Heb 10:31 says, "It is a dreadful thing to fall into the hands of the living God." Tim, God means business when it comes to sin. You don't want to be motivated by fear,  but you should be . We all should. We should tremble at the thought of standing before a Holy God. Even if there is only a chance of it being true, you should tremble at the thought. No, it's not pretty. But that is where wisdom, and repentance begin. Faith will follow - God will reveal himself to you as you take those small steps of faith. But you must humble yourself first.  I realize there is a chance that it is true. I am not ready to swallow the pill whole. I am an analyzer. I pick things apart to see how they work. For me, the pieces just don't fit together. I think that Ron is saying here that he attains faith through his fear of God. I have come a long way into faith. My entry into faith has not been through fear but through purpose. Through action. I strive for community, to become a part of a grand whole. I want to be the  urlLink hands of God , to act on His behalf. It is my belief that a God who loves me would not want me to quake in fear. A God who is all powerful would not set up a system were only the fearful would survive. That kind of creation makes no sense to me. I don't believe in a God who will punish my bad behavior with eternal suffering. That does not seem all powerful to me. Fear is a base human emotion. Love is a complex set of emotions and actions that defies attempts to describe it. God is love. God is NOT fear.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I found this little bit of speculation on the Motley Fool site.  urlLink Fool.com: Google's Billion-Dollar Shopping List [Commentary] June 3, 2004 : "Perhaps Tickle was Monster's most interesting acquisition"  Apparently Google's IPO may spur it to buy Monster who recently purchased Tickle in May. So say the Motley Fools. I guess it is all about who has the eye-balls. Amazon, Ebay, Google, Monster are all recognizable to most web-surfers. Other companies like Double-Click, most gambling sites, Blind Date, Lava Life (and other various dating sites) are infamous (but still well known) sites. If the reputable companies buy up all the Tickles, hopefully the amount of spam on our favorite websites will decrease. Or maybe it will quadruple!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Some of my  other  readers have mentioned that I seem to have lost my  urlLink original focus  on the PBGs' Path lately. True. But then again, the PBGs have already indicated that my blog  urlLink is a distraction anyway  and that I will get from it only things I can expect from any human distraction. On the other hand, I tried to do some PBGish meditation on my most run yesterday and it was disappointingly unenlightening.  I  did  come home feeling blessed with riches. ... and I came home hot, sweaty, sticky and tired. I have a long solo run tomorrow (13 miler). I'll try to meditate again tomorrow and report back.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink Ron Shanks  and I have talked about the  requirements  of salvation in our on-going discussion. What I meant when I said we hadn't discussed Salvation is that I haven't told him yet that I  don't believe there is a heaven  or a need for salvation (Feel free to check the chart; it isn't in there). I know from my  urlLink handy chart  that Ron's faith in the Bible (hmm, perhaps faith is the wrong word here?) means that he has no choice but to believe that there is a heaven and a hell. It also means that he believes that God created the earth in 6 (presumably standard) days, that humans were co-existent with dinosaurs, that the age of the universe is under 10,000 years and other  urlLink interesting tidbits . But lest we get sidetracked, we were talking about Heaven or more succinctly, Salvation. I am more of a scientist than a theologian. I understand the principles of carbon dating, asteroid impacts, fossilization, speed of light, plate tectonics, rocketry, and a host of other scientific disciplines that call into question the infallible "truths" of the Bible. If there is a heaven out there, beyond the clouds, why hasn't the space shuttle discovered it? Behind the moon? Beyond the furthest unmanned probe? Is it in some other Galaxy? Probably not. Some other Godly dimension? Possibly. I can't prove there is no heaven. But nobody can prove there is one either. I know, Ron, you will say, "Do you want to spend eternity in hell wishing you had seen that your pride was blinding you to the Truth".  Ultimately, that is my choice (at least we agree on that, no matter how much it grieves him). Then again, I never thought I would join a Christian church and read the Bible. Look Ma, no hands! Ron, here is the hard question: What is it that gives you faith that you will rise to Heaven (bodily or just your 'soul') when the final judgment comes? (And don't say the Bible, `cause that just redirects the question) I am talking about your own personal experience. I simply refuse to make that faith leap with only fear of death pushing me. &lt;--- serious here Ron. Or the threat of eternal damnation. Or any other fear tactic. If it is simply a choice between reward and punishment, it is a no-brainer to pick the reward, but it doesn't help me with faith. Am I being clear here?
 Discalmer: Ron and I both have a habit of being flippant without warning. This has got to stop. But it won't, so don't hold your breath, dear reader.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       WaHOOO! Mo just got the word that she will be working for the City during the Municipal Election campaign as a researcher. Her position is officially a  Clerk II  but she tells me that she will be doing more researching and phone answering than typing. It is a full time position with every second Monday off. The position goes for 6 months. If you know Mo, you will know that she is both excited and fretting the details of becoming a full time employee. I get to to be "Mister Mom" for at least the month of June. I plan to continue to look for work, but Mo's job will take away a lot of the money pressures we have been dealing with. My EI premiums won't last forever, after all.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Thank You  urlLink Susan  for recommending The PBGs Path to " urlLink Celebrating the Underblog 2004 " list.  Do you know of (or run) a quality blog that deserves a bit of extra attention? What blog/s do you read that you wish others knew about?  Susan added a comment linking my site and added a quote from my  urlLink Introduction to the PBGs  page. On her Sister's page, she also describes what the  urlLink underblog list  is about. So far I have only had one hit from the underblog list, but since my page is way down the page (on page 8!), it is surprising that anyone even looked down that far. I guess I need to consider updating my blog more regularly if I am actually going to have visitors. Sorta like keeping a clean house. If nobody is coming, what is the point of cleaning up? But when someone   does  come, you spend the whole time of their vist bustling around cleaning dishes and moving stacks of magazines. Hmmm. My dishes are done, but the house IS a mess. Posting will have to come later, I guess &lt;Grin&gt;
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>