<Blog>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Reasons why I am strugglefest:  1.  My car had 2 flat tires last nite.  2.  Therefore, I had to get drunk and dance at Rock Nite.  This was fun!  3.  Construction worker who tried to help me fix the tire asked "Do you always sit with strangers on the sidewalk?"  4.  Was asked to dinner by the tow truck driver - to which I responded  "I have too many issues to go to dinner."  5.  The tire was replaced at in this tire alley (a la Adventures in Babysitting), where one of the tire guys tried to pick me up as I was driving away.  Memo to you:  Do not try to holla at girls driving in cars.   They will just drive away.  6.  Finally, I got home, showered, got dressed (skirt), coffee, work.  So to recap:  Broken car, drunk dork, asked out twice on a Monday before 10:00 AM.  My office is like a hospital, it is quiet, tv noise in the background with additional white noise and people are coughing in rounds.    Check out  urlLink  Liz  and  urlLink  Sarah's  new blogsites.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I feel like crap.  I am sitting at my desk waiting to leave work so that I can go to the doctor.  I hate being sick, especially when it ruins my plans.  I am supposed to go to Liz's house tonite for xmas eve, but I don't want to infect her family with my germs.  I can't stop blowing my nose and my face is getting red from all the tissues.  I hope that the doctor gives me some drugs so that I can kick this cold in the face.  I guess after the doctor I will stop by Video Americain and rent some DVDs.  Jeepers Creepers 2 was pretty scary, but not as scary as the first 20 minutes of the first one.  I mean ... Liz and I watched the first one a few days before Halloween and we had to hold each other on the coach because we were so freaking scared.  Anyways,  I am just going to post up in bed and watch movies today.  Maybe at some point I will feel well enough to practice my bass.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today is December 23rd and I am coming down with a cold.  I have a headache and a latte and some Orange Juice, but where is my bagel?  I hate when you finish your bagel before your coffee and you look around your desk for the bagel and you cannot find it because you realize that you ate it already.  I think that this basically sums up how my day is going to be today.  I have decided that my New Year's Resolution is going to be to start a blogsite, but since work is slow today and my head hurts I am going to start it today.  I just read that The Strokes stayed an extra day in Rome so that they could visit the set of the new Wes Anderson movie.  My friend Liz describes this as a "total fuckin fantasy land."  I have been trying to find really cheap airline tickets to Hawaii to see the Strokes show on the eve of my 24th birthday, but I can't and that makes me sad.  There is no other way that I would rather spend my birthday than playing with the Strokes one nite and then rolling in the ocean the next day. That's okay - I am planning a trip to L.A. in April with Liz and Sarah.  And tonite Liz and I are renting Jeepers Creepers 2.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love Liz Crow.  Today she wrote the funniest thing ever in life and made me have a laughing/crying/stop breathing moment in my cube.  Ask Sarah about it - she called me during this breakdown and I could not speak.  Sarah sorry that I had to hang up on you.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Come be a part of the fastest growing trend in the DC Metro area.   Sign up at the DCI Mammal Playcenter today and before you know it you can be one of many who leaves notes for me on my dry erase board, calls me at my desk, sends me e-mail, takes smoke breaks with me, as well as joins me for lunch in one of the many delicious Silver Spring restaurants.  Membership also includes exclusive invitations to the Silver Spring lunch crew, which meets every Friday at 1:00 p.m.  What are you waiting for?    The DCI Mammal Playcenter is the place to be.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       *The stars love me*   Stars are improving today, and you may feel as if a huge weight has lifted. You are brought into contact with your need to accept attention and (yes!) even perhaps adulation. Also, you're asked by the universe to learn how to relax and have fun.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Haircuts, t-shirts, Wizards and Unicorns!   What a fantastic weekend I have planned.  After finding Paris Hilton's new apparel (see picture below) I must spend time this weekend putting cute little slogans on t-shirts.  Some of the approved slogans:  * Front:  Messy hair. Back:  Big Face. * Front:  Want to Back: or no? * From Mammals to Robots  (which is the new band name)  * I mean ...  I also NEED to get my haircut.  It is so dry in this weather and I definitely need some new  urlLink  BedHead  products.  They rule my world.  We saw the most amazing show last nite at Fletcher's -  urlLink  the Unicorns  and the Stills.  The Unicorns wear pastel pink - one in a suit, one in a vest and one in suspenders.  Suspenders has the most beautiful lips and his eyes glisten through his straight hair that covers all of his face except for his lips.  Mwah!!  During their set a man with a mullet wig (he was with the band) spat beer on Sarah and I.  After the show I bumped into this boy and told him that he spit beer on us.  He asked me how I felt about that.  I mean ... at first I was totally grossed out, then I wiped Sarah's face with my scarf and she did the same for me.  Then we laughed and then I felt really rock-n-roll.  The Unicorns' drummer asked us to come party with them - but Sarah had to take care of some business back in D.C. and even though I was pissed we left.  The Stills were unbelievable.  We were right up front - I could see up their nostrils.  During the last song, "Yesterday Never Tomorrows" I cried.  I know it sounds cheesy, but I was so moved.  Cigarettes - silhouettes.  Liz invited the Unicorns to her Super Bowl party because they are playing a show at the Black Cat on Sunday and they need to watch the game and party before the show.  Yay party with the Unicorns/Super Bowl Sunday. In other sports news I am going to see the Suns v. Wizards game on friday.  If you remember back to Junior year - I was obsessed with  urlLink  Tom Gugliotta .  Why you may ask?  Because he went to my high school and I'm sorry but that's fucking cool.  And maybe I will venture to the Diner at some point and try my luck again.   I hope it is a magical weekend for all!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you noticed that the blogspot ads that run at the top of your blog?  I know what you are up to even though you haven't told me.   Avram :  Jewish Young Adults and Free Roommate Ads.  And in a related search girlfriend.   Sarah :   Publishing Blogs.  And in a related search dream lyrics.   Liz :  Insominia Remedies and Sleep Disorders.  And in a realted search Mars Global Surveyor.   Berger :  Hollywood Movie Posters and Kill Bill.  And in a realted search Tarentino, the Matrix and Comics.   Me :  Punk Clothing and Emo/Indie Rock.  And in a related search punk lyrics and bands.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yeah, I am going to see  urlLink  the Stills  and  urlLink  the Unicorns  tonite at Fletcher's.  Yay!  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another reason to love  urlLink  Insound :  "So, maybe it's just me and maybe you all don't see what's going on here but every week I am completely enthralled and baffled by Seth Cohen's storyline in 'The O.C.' I mean, this kid is like knee-deep in tail. He's literally fighting off the hottest girl in school and some other totally adorable, but maybe a little clingy, punk rock girl who has definitely bought the new Belle & Sebastian DVD to impress him. Not that the show explicitly says that. But I think it's kind of implied. Anyway, my point is that the whole Ryan/Marissa love story is really the 'red herring' of 'The O.C.' and that the real story here is the triumph of the indie rock kid in the face of high school superficiality and materialism.   And so all this reminded me that real life isn't like this except for on Valentine's Day, which is coming up soon.  On Valentines Day, the indie rock boys totally get rewarded for their mix tapes and their hack poetry and that's sort of why all you guys need to buy pretty much every new release below.  Air. Notwist. Numbers. Stereolab. Seriously, you've got mix tapes to make. And really, how many times can you recycle the same Elliott Smith and Bright Eyes songs. Plus, I'm dreadfully afraid that because of 'The O.C.' that the jocks are onto us and then what happens if they start making mix tapes with like Death Cab and American Analog Set on them. See where I'm going with this? We must advance and evolve. Constantly coming up with new songs for the mix tapes. Float like a butterfly. Sting like a bee. Look out prom queens. It's our time to shine. Our time."   Where is my indie rock boyfriend?    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Things are weird:   1.  I had a David Lynchian dream last night that involved planning a camping trip in the woods with a map that appears in my dreams from time to time.    2.  This morning on CNN I watched an interview with a college-aged woman who's $20,000 winning scratch off ticket was stolen by the store clerk.  I won $2 on a scratch off in Olney about 2 months ago and I have not yet cashed it.  I think I should because maybe this story is a sign that when I trade my ticket in for a new one I will win big.  I have been lucky lately.  I won tickets to the John Waters Meet n Greet and yesterday I won a  urlLink  backpack  from  urlLink  MTV.com  for being in the top five for week 14 of the RW/RR Fantasy Challenge.  Also, I think that things (both good and bad) come in groups of 3.  3.  I aged like 10 years in my sleep last nite.  I have two defined wrinkles on my forehead and wrinkles under my eyes.  I think I need a shot of Botox.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
        THE END HAS NO END   I don't think that I have been sleeping properly since Thursday.  On Friday I woke up with a sharp shooting pain in my left back.  On Saturday nite, I had a dream that Sarah, Perry and I were walking down the street and all of a sudden a duck got out of a taxicab and and b-lined straight toward us and started poking us with his beak.  Our only response was to lay down on the ground while the duck did this.  (The duck was white and not cartoonish at all.  It was a real duck.) So all day Saturday, I was on a mission to find a duck that had a likeness to the one I dreampt of so I could befriend it.  Alas, you cannot find a duck on a keychain in DC, at least one that is not a cartoon.  Sarah - being the good little mammal that she is - deciphered what this dream meant:   To see ducks in your dream, either represents spiritual freedom (if flying) or it represents the unconscious (if swimming).  Ducks are rather multi-talented animals that can walk, swim and fly and thus may represent your flexibility and in blending into various situations. Alternatively, the dream may also indicate that you are setting yourself up or being set up for the kill as associated by the phrase "sitting duck". Also, the duck may be a pun on "ducking" some issue or situation, instead of confronting it head-on.    To see a white duck in your dream, signifies falsehood and deceit.          I like to fall asleep with the TV on.  It keeps me company while I enter into dreamworld.  I keep the remote on my bed (either over or under the covers.)  If it is over the covers it usually ends up on the floor next to my bed.  Well, this morning when I woke up the remote was on the other side of the room, which can only means that at some point during my sleep I must have flicked my comforter up and the remote soared across the room.  I mean the back (where the batteries go in) came off.     Weekend Recap:   Friday nite Liz and I went to a party in MT. Pleasant.  We had to take a lot of breaks, but we also got to ride in a mini cooper. Saturday, I met Phantom Planet - so cute.  They signed my CD - I'm sucha dork. Then we went to Saint Ex for Liz Ruby's birthday.  Our group got spilt up - Sarah and Liz got wasted - i got belligerent - big surprise. Sunday - I slept til 1:30 p.m. and then we went to the diner.  I have never seen Diner Boy look cuter than yesterday.  He was wearing a white thermal with a white vintage baseball jersey over it.  OMG.  I need to stop thinking about the boy and just forget him. And  urlLink  logic  will break your heart forever.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Strange dream:     Last night I had a dream that I was acting in a porn movie with Liv Tyler.  This may have to do with the fact that last night I watched Friends,  urlLink  "The One Where Chandler Can't Cry"  and we find out that Ursula is making pornos using Phoebe's name.    Other weird things in my dream:    1.  My cousin (my Dad's cousin's son - I don't understand that once/twice removed crap) Drew was dressed like a pimp.   2.  There were other "actresses" upstairs, one of which was the HR Assistant in the UK, Jo.  I have never met her before in my life, I only speak to her on the phone.  In the dream I never see her I can only hear her voice.  3.  There was another cousin of mine there as well, but I did not know who she was.  4.  I never actually got to "act" in the film because there were too many distractions like the aforementioned characters as well as some additional characters that were visiting the site where we were shooting.     This is what I have learned from my dream:    To dream that you are in a porno film, suggests your desire to be more sexually adventurous. It also implies lust and wish-fulfillment.    This is true.     To see your cousin in your dream, represents something or some aspect of your character that is somewhat familiar. Perhaps you need to spend more time in cultivating and developing some emerging ability or character.   So, I need to pimp myself more?   To see an unknown person in your dream, signifies a part of yourself that is repressed and hidden. Alternatively, it symbolizes the archetypal dream helper who is trying to offer some insight and advice.     *Memo to the dream helper*   Find me a boy, while you're at it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I want this sweatshirt:   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been told that I need to blog, so here we go. . .  This is a 3-day weekend and I am thrilled about this.  Tonight I am going to see Cold Mountain with Harris.  I hope I can sit through this movie.  My mom loved it.  But its like 3 million years long and it is cold enough outside without having to watch a movie called COLD Mountain.  I have won tickets for the John Waters Meet-n-Greet at the Velvet Lounge for tomorrow.  This is pretty cool.  Other events for tomorrow include Cob's tea party and The Frequency at Velvet.  Other things that I would to have happen tomorrow include going to the Diner (cuz I love to torture myself) and Liz and I are on a mission to find dates to  urlLink  The Butterfly Effect  (starring Kutcher with a beard - so hot!) which comes out in theatres Jan. 23.  I have also been toying with the idea of pretending that I have work on Monday, like set the alarm clock, the whole bit, so that when I wake up on Monday it will be so refreshing when I realize that I can go back to bed for a million hours.  But really its a toss-up between that and getting really drunk at a dance party.  Back to The Butterfly Effect.  For those of you who don't know The "Butterfly Effect", or more technically known as the "sensitive dependence on initial conditions", is the essence of chaos.  It is the assertion that the beating of a butterfly's wings in Tokyo can eventually change the weather in New York City.  I think that I would like spend Monday discussing this in depth with somebody.  To prep for this you can search "chaos theory" or "nonlinear dynamics."  Let me know if you care to discuss.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love  urlLink  Insound .  (taken from my Insound listserve e-mail):  L I Q U I D A T I O N  S A L E  :  T H E  O . C .  E F F E C T  "I don't know if any of you watch Fox's new break-out smash 'The O.C.'  as much as I do. But I'm guessing that the answer is probably 'no'  because I Tivo it every week and watch it, commercial free, in repetition  all day Saturday. Then, on Wednesday night, I host an 'O.C. Tivo' party  at 9PM where my friends and I get to act out all the parts. Sure, most  of those friends are imaginary, but at least they let me play Summer,  the show's sexy and superficial, but maybe-with-a-good-heart 'Miss  Popular.' Anyway, so here's where I'm going with this. One of the shows main  characters, Seth Cohen, is a total Insounder. His favorite band is  Death Cab and whenever he comes on screen they roll the Belle & Sebastian  track.   Noticing this, I quickly got the Insound staff together and said, 'Do  you realize what's gonna happen? Seth is gonna totally turn Ryan into a  Fugazi fan. And then kids everywhere will be clamoring for indie rock  and they will all flock to Insound so we MUST make sure that we have  enough records for them. Go. Buy more records for the O.C. kids. Go. Now.  Dammit.' I called this the 'O.C. Effect' and I was certain that it  would make me filthy rich. Suffice it to say, those damn kids never  converted. And now we're sitting on lots of overstocks. We simply bought too  many records and now we need to sell then dirt cheap to you. Yeah. We  messed up. Damn you Seth Cohen. Damn you Ryan Atwood. Damn you Marissa  Cooper. Damn you all."   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am in the process of developing a new theory on the strange behaviors of the boys that we know (and basically all men in general.)  These behaviors surfaced at the start of 2004.  Since I have yet to begin the research on this project, I will only be able to tell you that it involves the Mission to Mars, the possibility of misaligned planets, possible alien abductions and the fact that Prez. Bush plans to colonize the moon in the next two decades.   I wish that I could blame these weird behaviors on the  urlLink  Santa Ana winds , but hopefully we will know the real cause soon.  Stay tuned for frequent updates . . .  In the meantime, Liz, Sarah - please keep your heads up and your eyes dry.  Help is on its way.  Soon we will be on Oprah.      
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink  Which O.C. babe are you?   My results: Your life may be a bit confusing, but that doesn't stop you from caring about what other people are going through. Which is why you're most like Marissa. Now all you need is a next-door neighbor just like Ryan . . .   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
        We are cute, we like Karaoke.  :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This just in ... The Strokes are currenly planning an eight-week tour starting in March.  Tour dates to be announced at the end of January.  Finally something to live for.     
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh my god... I just found a sesame seed on my desk and it made me realize that I have not had a bagel in over a week.    HELP - where the fuck is my bagel?!?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Highlights from Jan. 8 to present:  January 8th:  * My cubicle was festively decorated for my birthday, including a special birthday tiara that I wore most of the day.  I received two bouquets of flowers, one from my boss Ted and one from my parents.  I also received some Bath and Body Works lotions from Gwyneth - the best assistant from the UK ever.  There was cake and my bosses gave me a Dave and Buster's giftcard (yay I'm 12 now.)  * Finally found Levante's in Dupont (across the street from the Olsson's that Phantom Planet will be doing an store appearance at on  urlLink  Jan. 24th. )  Ate a lot - got really full - got some of the best presents ever (tea set, hair brush, wallet, anti-wrinkle cream, Phantom Planet CD.)  * My boss (the same one that got me flowers) called me at 10:30, while I was still at dinner, to ask me some retarded questions about work - yeah that was so important to interrupt my birthday dinner for.  * Went to the Raven - where I got more wonderful presents including some bling from Aimee.  Paul tried to get me to do shots (but the thought of it made me sick since NYE).  I also found out that I am the only girl in our group of friends that he has not made out with.  That made me pissed for some reason, but do I really need reasons.  Then I was pressured to either take a shot or make out with Paul (this pressure came only from Paul.)  I chose to do neither.    January 9th:  * Slept til 11:00 then spent all day in bed watching TV and reading  urlLink  Franny and Zooey.   * Took a nap from 2:00 - 5:00.    * Used my new hair brush, which worked beautifully.  * Went to the Raven again.  * Went to the Diner with Liz and her troubled teens.  John (aka Diner Boy) was there - said hi, asked what I was up to all while touching my shoulder.  MEMO to Diner Boy:  I gave you my e-mail address twice - but you never used it.  SO - please don't touch me when you see me.  If you don't like me, then don't talk to me.  You are too cute and I am trying to not like you.  January 10th  * Woke up at 11:00 AM to go to the bank and buy cigarettes and gas.  * Watched  urlLink  Confessions of a Dangerous Mind  - really good.  I love Drew Barrymore in everything - she is so cool.  * Sarah came over - she is sad and going crazy.  We tried to watch the  urlLink  Shape of Things,  but it sucked, so we smoked a lot of cigarettes and watched SNL, it was funny.  January 11th  * Spent my time divided between my bed and the couch. Read Franny and Zooey.  Watched The Original  urlLink  Italian Job,  so funny - I love that late 60s humor.    * Watched the untitle bootleg cut of  urlLink  Almost Famous  - which I decided is definitely in my top five favorite movies.  January 12th  * Work.  * Took my car in to get an estimate - it makes the most awful noises.  So, that is my unexciting life.  Maybe after this spending detox I will have more exciting things to report.  Right now everyone just wants me to council them - like I have all the answers or something.  But I love to help out my friends and give them advice. I have always been told I am a good listener.  So I am here to help as long as it doesn't conflict with  urlLink  The Gaunlet. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This just in . . .   Tomorrow is my birthday.  I am going to be 24.  I am also broke.  I am in detox for spending, but not drinking.  So get ready to drink with me tomorrow nite.  But you are going to say, "Don't you have work on Friday?"  And I am going to say, "Nope, but has that ever stopped me before?"    Things I have already asked for when I turn 24:  1.  The new  urlLink  Phantom Planet  self titled CD 2.   urlLink  Anti-wrinkle cream.   Wrinkles are sad and I am getting older.  I have been asked to come up with a birthday wishlist, but I can't think of anything else to put on it.  What does this mean?  That I have everything I ever will want in life.  NO.  What I think this really means is that I am a complete spur of the moment shopper.  I buy what I see and feel that I need at the time.  So I can't really think ahead like that.  I did want  urlLink  eskimo boots,  but I read that if you don't have them already then you shouldn't even bother buying them.  But, you can buy the variations (platforms, with pom poms), but I just wanted the basic eskimos.  I also kinda wanted one of those  urlLink  Von Dutch  hats that  urlLink  Kutcher  made so popular, but once a  urlLink  bride  wears one down the aisle, the trucker hat has kind of jumped the shark.     So to conclude ...  Tomorrow is my birthday!  :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This just in . . .  The Stills are playing at Fletcher's on January 28th.  If you are smart you will attend this show.  I have been listening to the Stills since the summer and I am  urlLink  Still in Love  with them.  I finally had the opportunity to see them open for the sold out Ryan Adams show at the 9:30 Club (thank you Ben for helping me get a ticket.)  They even opened for themselves in the guise of another band, a joke band.  The set was amazing - they have very good rock moves and are very cute.  If you are not convinced yet then visit the website - they will let you listen to the entire album.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry to tell all of you cell-phone addicted kids out there (Liz you won't have to worry about this one) - DC has finally banned driving while on your  urlLink  mobile .
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ray Davies from the Kinks was  urlLink  shot  in the leg by thieves in New Orleans' French Quarter today.  "Don’t wanna get myself shot down ... I’m a twentieth century man but I don’t wanna die here." 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ah, 2004.  So let's recap.  I didn't want to go out on NYE, but I did.  I kind of went with an 80's themed outfit, even wore sunglasses at nite.  The party started at Liz's house.  Sushi, champagne, cavier and amstel light, oh yeah Jay Z dance party too.  This lasted until 10:30 when we realized that we needed to get over to the Velvet Lounge to see the Hard Tomorrows.  We chugged the last of the champagne and hopped into a cab.  At the Velvet, I remember another beer or two and some shots.  The Hard Tomorrows were great.  I was trashed.  All I really remember is 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1 Happy New Year and Liz handing me another shot.  I couldn't even finish the shot (it might have been whisky - can't remember.)  I whispered to someone that I had to go outside and started to fumble through the crowd almost falling on a few people.  I made it outside and into an alley where I proceded to sit down and puke.  Apparently people were concerned about me, but that's how I do it - alone.  When I was done and realized where I was I called Liz and told her to help me, I was in an alley.  She came and got me out of the alley onto some stairs where I met up with Sarah and Liz Ruby.  I think I puked a few more times, no one seemed to mind.  I tried to get into a few random people's cars and I think I also called a few people on my cell phone prior to the alley incident.  Eventually I was put in a cab with Liz Ruby and I went back to Liz Crow's house.  I somehow managed to change into PJs (but not without smashing a champagne glass to pieces) and passed out on the couch.   urlLink   Liz  and  urlLink  Sarah   went to Rishi's party after they left Velvet - but you will have to ask them about that.  The next day was truly a hard tomorrow.  I woke up at 8:00 AM and a few minutes later Sarah woke up.  We walked down to 7-11 to get gatorade and croissants.  It felt like the apocalypse because we were the only ones outside.  Back at home, we got into Perry's bed and watched music videos for hours.  Every single thing was making us hungry - so eventually we got up and drove to Popeye's and bought a lot of food.  We ate so much on New Year's Day it is disgusting:  chicken, fries, mashies, biscuits, Liz's roommate Maile bought us fruit and made us ice cream cones and mozarella sticks and cookies.  We also went out to dinner and had salads and mac and cheeses.  That is so much food.  We watched hour after hour of  urlLink  I love the 80s  and the same commercial for  urlLink  Hotwire.com  where the dad is about to help his kid jump into the deep end of the swimming pool for the first time ever in life.  The kid is so cute - he has little swimmies on, but then the kid tells his dad that there is a quarter in the pool and dad pushes kid out of the way into the pool and jumps in to get it.  Sarah laughs hysterically everytime she sees this.  I took 2 naps and felt gross the whole day.    On Friday, I went home and slept all day and then went to the movies with Sarah to see  urlLink  Something's Gotta Give .  It was so depressing because of the wrinkles and now I am afraid of getting old.  I love  urlLink  Amanda Peet  and Keanu was so cute as the doctor.  Now I need wrinkle cream for my birthday (which is on thursday).  I also saw Anything Else and loved it.  On Saturday, I went grocery shopping for the first time in months and it was hard. I hate it - it gives me anxiety.  Then I met Liz and Run Run at the musuem and we looked at the mammels - they are so cute.  That nite I watched TV at Liz's and was in a bad mood.  Sunday - I did nothing except realize that I need to go into spending detox - so that brings us up-to-date.    Oh yeah and while I was doing all of that -  urlLink  Britney Spears   got married in Vegas and had her marriage annuled.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hope  urlLink  this  works for you, because you won't be disappointed when you open it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The weekend looks good:   My horoscope tell me:  Today marks the beginning of the end for an impasse within the relationship sector. You may attract friends who can help you climb out of the proverbial hole you find yourself in. Changing your mental attitude is the first step.    So I think that things are looking up.  The goal for the weekend is to get out of the proverbial hole that I have been in.  Changes  were  no good.  See things change!!!  They has been talk of something going on at the Pharmacy Bar and Asylum for tonite.  Sarah and I are going to go to my place after work to watch last nite's Conan (on Comedy Central at 6).  This means that we have to jet at 6 so that we are home in time to watch Spader.  Then its off to the bar to start drinking - I mean it is so beautiful and warm out today that a beer in the sun cannot be beat.  But I suppose that it will be dark by the time we order that first beer - but the spirit of sunshine will still be with us.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hey folks, the Megadork is back!!!!   It's been awhile since my last blog and those have been few and far between and have only included cute pictures or sob stories of my non-existant boyfriend.  Seasonal affective disorder really got the best of me this year.  Last year I was able to get through it even though Liz was in Baltimore and I was stuck in my apartment in Takoma Park and I even though I discoved Bright Eyes.  Maybe I should thank Conor Oberst for helping me through the Blizzard of 2003, because I vowed to stay away from B.E. this year and I was a mess after Thanksgiving.      "I'm no good in winter. These gray days, they're so sad." - Jason Slocumb,  Igby Goes Down    It's getting better all the time:   *Today is Matt's (my brother) birthday.  He is 20 and he happens to be driving through Silver Spring today.  So we are going to lunch and I got him  urlLink  this  cute tshirt from Urban.  *Sarah and I found an apartment in Mount Pleasant and we move in 10 days.  *I am going to see the Walkmen in 7 days and the Strokes in 19 days.  *I am also a genius for knowing that something weird was going on with Mars - Sarah's horoscope for March in Vanity Fair mentioned something about Mars moving out of her 12th house.  See Sarah for more details.   Fun things to do in 2004:   *Familarize yourself with the Dunne family (Dominick Dunne is an incredible writer for Vanity Fair and also an author - his son Griffin is a very handsome actor - his daughter Dominique was in Poltergeist and was mysteriously murdered shortly after she made the film- his brother John just recently passed away and was married to Joan Didion.)  This is a very interesting an talented family who I would like to know more about and I think you should too.  *House parties - these have been very fun for me so far.  *Stop going to the Diner - I may love the coffee and the waiters, but this is not how to deal with a sad day.  *Start practicing with your band.  Mine is called From Mammals to Robots.  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------  The only thing that plagues me right now is that I can be replaced by a  urlLink  robot .     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is my brother's IM profile:   "I didn't take no shortcuts I spent the money that I saved up Aw mama runnin' out of luck Well like my sister don't give a fuck!!  Quoting Julian - it doesn't get any better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I stayed up until 5 AM on both Friday and Saturday nite.  I have been writing songs and listening to the Walkmen's new album.  I have been thinking about Diner Boy and trying to realize that it is never going to happen.  I have been trying to be happy, while my friends fall in and out of love. And I am still stuck on the same boy, who can only stop by my table, say hi and smile at me for 2 minutes and leave.  I have been invited to a "rip your heart out before someone else does" party on Valentine's Day.  I want to wear pink and red and stay up until 5 AM and avoid love because it is too mentally damaging for me.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Okay, here is my fucking haiku:  You want depressing - you got depressing!!!    I am a zombie Answering phones at the morgue. Is this my calling?  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       We love you Tim Fletcher:      (this is the same view we had at the show on 1/28/04)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Bunnies!!                                This is the next book on my reading list.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       NATION???   The Strokes are playing at Nation on March 9th.  I want to go but, I do NOT want to go to Nation.  This is a dilemma.  I am devoted - so I think you know the answer.  Want to or no?   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Superbowl Weekend   fridaysaturdaysunday!  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       More fun stuff - thanks to Avram.    I am a book:         You're  Love in the Time of Cholera !   by Gabriel Garcia Marquez    Like Odysseus in a work of Homer, you demonstrate undying loyalty by sleeping with as many people as you possibly can. But in your heart you never give consent! This creates a strange quandary of what love really means to you. On the one hand, you've loved the same person your whole life, but on the other, your actions barely speak to this fact. Whatever you do, stick to bottled water. The other stuff could get you killed.     Take the  urlLink Book Quiz  at the  urlLink Blue Pyramid .       I am a country:           You're Colombia!     You do a lot of drugs, and these have kind of distorted your view of  reality, to the point that everyone looks like an enemy. &nbsp;You keep trying to restore  order over your schizophrenic world view, but you don't even know which goal is your own  and which is someone else's. &nbsp;You're pretty sure someone needs to be punished for all  this, but who that is changes all the time. &nbsp;Things would be a lot better for you if  you switched to coffee, or even to decaf, but all this money would be hard to give up.    Take the  urlLink Country Quiz    
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hipp Hipp Hippies Bunnies Easter Jellybeans Beer   A stream of consciousness poem by megcasablancas 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks  urlLink  Avram  for fun games.         I am  a Scorched Earth Tank .   When I have a mission, it consumes me; I will not be satisfied until the job is done. I have a strong sense of duty, and a strong sense of direction. Changes in the tide don't phase me - I always know which way the wind blows, and I know how to compensate for it. I get on poorly with people like myself.  What Video Game Character Are You?     
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just remembered that my favorite cutest consultant will be here tomorrow for a meeting with my boss  i need to buy stockings tonite and wash something cute.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Love the Killers, Don't Kill the lovers.    Last nite was the first alcohol free nite after almost 2 weeks of boozing up.  I remember telling Sarah the other day that if I am not at work then I am drinking.  I came to the realization that I needed to ease up for at least a day because of the events that occured on Sunday, March 28, 2004.  On that nite, (at the Hard Tomorrows show) I was hostile, agressive, belligerent and dangerous.  I called Kyle the devil and then made him buy me a drink.  I repeatedly shouted "see you in hell,"  not directed at anyone at DC9 but at one specific person who was NOT there.  I told Liz Crow something mean for no reason.  I burnt 2 of my fingers with a match and almost burnt up Liz's jacket and bag after I accidently flicked the lit match (becuz it burned my fingers.)  I made Sarah and Liz follow me to Kingpin to look for the aforementioned absent person.  I had a fight with Liz in the cab and then repeatedly called her when I got home - and she hung up on me three times.  Drinking makes me hostile and kinda scary.   The next day thank god that I had asked off from work cuz I felt shitty - and my eyes were totally puffy.  I was supposed to get stuff done on my car but I blew that off to take care of easier things like rent and address change.  I thought everyone in the world hated me and I drove to Tower in Rockville to buy some CDs and periodicals.  That was very fun and cathartic for me.  Got  urlLink  Ambulance  and  urlLink  The Coral  and 3 awesome little periodicals that I higly recommend to all:  urlLink  Venus ,  urlLink  Filter  and  urlLink  The Fader .  On the way home, I heard some gossip, which upset me again and I had to call Kyle to apologize and set the record straight.  That went well, but then Liz had to yell and call me psycho which made me cry all over again.  But I had to be okay - life goes on and what was I going to do kill myself - NO!  Drink a beer - NO!  So I cleaned the apt and listened to my CDs and read my periodicals and smoked cigarettes and resisted the urge to open a beer. Finally Sarah was home from work and she made me feel better about what had happened.  We listened to Ambulance and read and then I took a itty bitty mini nap and she chatted with LCrow on the phone.  Then we got ready for show(s) at the BlackCat.  Mainstage:   urlLink  The Killers , Ambulance, Stellastarr*  Backstage:  Panthers, TV on the Radio  Mainstage:  Fun, party, dance, rock - DC people just standing around looking bored but really having fun.  Me chewing gum and trying hard not order a beer and drink water instead.  Purchased the Killers 3track EP, debated buy some more merch, wandered around a little - checked out the Backstage (since I had stamps for both)  Backstage:  Crowded, hot, yelling, technical problems, no sight of the band from the back.  Mainstage:  cuteleadsinger (killers) and cuteguitarist (ambulance)  Backstage:  don't know - I CANT SEE YOU.  ************************************************************ Sarah and Liz looked beat up at the bar and the zombie barback wasn't helping the mood any. Chatted with Liz - ignored our fight - this worked - I gave her gum - planets realigned but threw others off course.  Sarah was sipping beer and secretly waiting for her better half to appear.  I was exhausted because I had not been drinking.  After we left, we had a sneak preview of  Mammal Hostility: Crow v. Claxton . (Which can be viewed on the Discovery Channel after  Half Day Bathroom   starring Eli Rosenberg.)    Cold, cab, curb.  Crush?  Crushed!!  Outcome:  I love the Killers!!!  I (still) love Diner Boy!! (sorry - I do) I love having greasy hair - its fun and makes me wish I was a boy and in a band. I love the Lou Reed/Strokes article in Filter - so insightful. I love my apartment -even though we have no couch and a roach. I love Take Down (thanks Rishi for the guitar solo) I love my friends - they are fucking crazy.  But the best.     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       What will your  urlLink  future  bring?    You will live in Apartment. You will drive a navy mini cooper. You will marry jules and have 4 kids. You will be a rockstar wife in nyc.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       and so it goes   Velvet on a Monday nite.  We stopped into Velvet to see what was going on and someone told Sarah that AC was upstairs - so we go upstairs and it is packed and there is some band with Bjork in their name and the singer has like a huge afro and a hat on.  We find AC, Erin Worley, John (from the Frequency) and Ditrich (who we later find out has been fired from Velvet.)  Liz Ruby and I both sense that it is time to move on so we get Sarah and we leave and walk about 2 steps over to Kingpin (the DC speakeasy that stays open pretty late.)  Let's not forget that it is Monday and we should be sleeping and preparing mentally for work, but we are taking the town like its Saturday.    The first time I went in Kingpin was last weekend and I was freaked out because there was an altercation outside between the doorman and a homeless man.  The doorman was pissed because the homeless guy was panhandling (or maybe just sitting in front of Kingpin) and he asked him to move down.  Then he threw homeless guy against a van and I just stood there and watched because Liz C. had gone in to talk to someone and I was waiting outside.  But I mean, what's the big deal is homeless guy sits outside, its not like you run this fancy ass bar.  It's a small upstairs dive bar.  The only other time that I was going to go to Kingpin was the nite of the Walkmen show.  Apparantly, Paul's (not Rihani - don't know his lastname) friend's cousin is Paul from the Walkmen (I know - that's too many Paul's in one sentence) and we were going to meet up with them and the Walkmen at Kingpin.  The Walkmen are from DC so family members are always at the shows, hence the old people getting lost on V Street.  I really wanted to go and snuggle up to Hamilton on the couch, but it was a Wednesday and Liz C. and I were trying to be responsible.  Okay - back to Monday nite.  So we went in and I wasn't scared this time and it was fun - Liz Ruby and I admited that we were both on missions to find the boys that we liked and even though there had been a DB sighting earlier that nite by Kyle, Coop and co, I was unable to find him and even though 2/5 of the Frequency were at Velvet that nite, there was no sign of Sebastian.  This made us both a little sad, but I guess that's why we kept drinking the beer.  Eventually, we left Kingpin for home, a little disappointed, and a lot drunk.  Overall, the nite was fun and a nice change from the usual Monday nite.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       it all started with a bottle of wine   So, you say that it's monday and that you aren't going out, but that's before you drink 2 bottles of wine and eat some delishy couscous with sarah and liz ruby.  Before you know it you are doing the dishes and fantasicking the countertops and then brushing your teeth and putting on a black sweater.    We thought we could be homebodies for one nite, but the urge to hit the town was in us.  - on a monday.  Maybe this had something to do with the fact that we had spent the past 2 hours talking about our crushes and boys in general.    Our first stop was the Black Cat - the Red Room was empty, possibly due to the fact that there was British Sea Power show on the mainstage.  I saw BSP last August when they opened for The Libertines.  That was one of the best shows that I have ever seen up there with the Strokes in Asbury Park and The Stills/ Unicorns at Fletchers.  At the time of this show, Pete Doherty was in jail and not touring with the band.  Why bye Pete?  BSP took forever to set up because they had to display all of these tree branches.  it was like being in the forest with a cute little band. -since then I have seen too many horror films set in the woods and I am not ready to go back.  so we had a drink at the bar and played some Lord of the Rings pinball - and Liz Ruby kicked ass.  Ran into Ian who cuts hair with AC and who LR does not like running into so we left and walked down to St Ex for trivia.  They do not have trivia at St Ex on monday nites anymore.  Why bye trivia?  but now they have Kyle, Rishi, Coop and Paul sitting at a table playing crossword and drinking gin and tonics.  Somehow when I walked up to the bar there was some sort of talk of DB being out and about.  I don't really like that Coop knows about this now - I mean this guy's seen and heard all over DC - I mean he was mentioned in the city paper this week as being the "guy in the letterman's jacket" at the Walkmen show.  After a few drinks - and Paul giving us shots of SoCo and Lime - we decided it was time to move on to DC9 - which was really fun when I went there with Liz on Saturday nite.  DC9 was empty - we did one lap of the whole bar to check out the scene and the rooms - which are all different and fun.  Liz Crow and I decided that DC9 is a fancy velvet - Liz was going to post about this - so maybe when she's back from Iowa she will blog again.  We were bored of this place and since we didn't run into anyone we left and walked around the corner to Velvet.  to be continued tomorrow. . .  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Clampdown   What are we gonna do now?  Taking off his turban, they said, is this man a Jew? 'Cause they're working for the clampdown They put up a poster saying we earn more than you! When we're working for the clampdown We will teach our twisted speech To the young believers We will train our blue-eyed men To be young believers  The judge said five to ten-but I say double that again I'm not working for the clampdown No man born with a living soul Can be working for the clampdown Kick over the wall 'cause government's to fall How can you refuse it? Let fury have the hour, anger can be power D'you know that you can use it?  The voices in your head are calling Stop wasting your time, there's nothing coming Only a fool would think someone could save you The men at the factory are old and cunning You don't owe nothing, so boy get runnin' It's the best years of your life they want to steal  You grow up and you calm down You're working for the clampdown You start wearing the blue and brown You're working for the clampdown So you got someone to boss around It makes you feel big now You drift until you brutalize You made your first kill now  In these days of evil presidentes Working for the clampdown But lately one or two has fully paid their due For working for the clampdown But ha! Gitalong! Gitalong! And I've given away no secrets Who's barmy now? 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last nite, I, like Liz,was all ready to watch the OC, but not for Peter Gallagher (even though Sandy Cohen is a HOT dad!) but becuz of his son Seth Cohen.  However, Fox has decided that we are not ready to watch Marissa and Ryan find out about Luke and Mrs. Cooper's torrid love affair just yet.  But they have decided to put in its place a cute litle show starrring Schwartzman as a psychology student.  What a fabulous idea.  Especially, when it guest stars Zooey Deschanel and is directed by Mike White (of The Good Girl fame who I also had weird eye contact with him on a subway car in NYC - I recognized him and he could tell, but I didn't want to be weird and talk to him).  Also the Weitz's of American Pie fame have something to do with this show, which is called "Cracking Up"  and it pretty much makes me crack up.  Its quirky - check it out.  My alarm clock has been doing its own thing lately.  On Wednesday morning, I woke up at 8:18 am and freaked out cuz I needed to take a shower and i think I was still drunk from the show the nite before and I stumbled out of bed and looked at the kitchen clock and it said 7:20 am.  So I went in Sarah's room and woke her up to ask her what time it was.  She confirmed the 7:20 and then I was releaved.  I am not sure how this happened - how did my clock change itself - this might have something to do with me spilling a glass of water all over the floor when i went to bed the other nite, but it did not touch the clock.  Did I do it in my sleep?  Possible.  Did someone visit my room in the nite and change it?  Possible.    Anyways - Part 2.  So this morning I woke up at 7:35 am and I never heard it ring or anything and it was set and said that it should have gone off at 7:00 am.  Sarah said that she heard it ringing - how come I didn't - what is wrong with me when I sleep - what is going on here?  This is kind of a mystery to me.    This morning I was on the phone with Liz and she wanted to talk to Sarah so I was going to transfer her, but then, being the genius that I am, decided to do a 3way call.  And that was so fun.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "kyle don’go’no salisbury!” –meg casablancas, in her prime, march 9, 2004 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am just about to go into a training class at work called Expressing Yourself: Presenting Your Thoughts and Ideas.  Discovery classes are a great way to be away from your desk for 3 hours, eat snacks and drink bottled water.    I saw my boyfriend, Julian, last nite at Nation.  I acquired a few free tickets to the show and found that Liz, Rishi and Kyle wanted to join me and Liz Ruby.  Yay - carpool to Southeast.   Poor mammal is sick and could not come out and play.   I don't know if you have been to Nation, but it is crazy there.  They have three check points when you go in.  First you get your 21 + wristband, then you get patted down by a same-sex security guard.  Female Security Guard w/ piercings as she feels my jacket pocket:  "What are these?" Me: " These are keys."  Final check point was to get our tickets ripped.  Next stop bathroom since I drank 5 beers from 6:00 - 8:00.  Check out the merch.  Then walk through a maze to find a place where we could sorta see Julian.  Nation sucks.  You can't see anything and the sound does not carry well to the balcony.  But the Strokes are great - even if you can't see Julian and his rock moves - you can at least see me re-create them.  Befriended this boy who looked like Chris Santulli and he bought me beer and sang all the songs to me during the show.  This was kind of annoying cuz I was trying already to see Julian and now I had to try to hear him too.  We also saw Lil Liz (aka Hippie Liz) whose birthday is on Friday and Liz and I might be going to Upper Marlboro to see her and get a painting.  (Liz we need to discuss this).  Friday nite is also the Frequency/Trans Am show at the Black Cat.   I hope that I am not stll recovering on Friday from last nite.  I was pretty drunk (which explains the tugging on my jacket lapel Julian re-enactments.)    I also just remembered that we went to the Diner last nite and I was acting stupid, thank god D.B. was not there - that's all I can say.  I had to go into great detail about my thing with him and then Liz gets all pissed at me.  What can I say though he does bear a striking resemblance to Julian.    Time for Expressing Yourself class.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I was such a strugglefest mess on Saturday nite.     Saturday was spent all day driving around with Sarah and shopping.  A little over my budget - I funded myself a White Stripes inspired get up for the evening event of Perry's birthday.  I looked cute, but it took me like 45 minutes to find a parking spot and for some of that time (only like two DC block) I did not have my headlights on - crimeny!!  Once I got to the Helix Hotel I downed some vodka tonics and we headed over to Dragonfly.  I started drinking at 11:00 and was a goner by 12:41.  I remember the specific time because I was in the bathroom stall with my head in my hands and I heard someone say this was the time.  It made me think of the Strokes song 12:51 and I wanted to start singing that in the bathroom, but sung it in my head instead.  I tried to go back to the party, but the beats of the music made me want to jump to my death so I had to go outside for some air.  I sat outside for like 20 minutes before everyone left the bar.  Then it was off to Cafe Citron.  I seriously could only be in that place for like 5 minutes before I had to sit down on a couch and it only took another 5 minutes before I headed to the bathroom.  The line was too long so I ran outside.  I sat there for like an hour in the cold (but I didn't even know that it was cold.)  A bunch of crazies came up to me for different reasons (ie "can I have a cigarette, a dollar, a fill in the blank?) or to see if I was okay - and I told them that I was fine and to leave me alone.  Soon I was acutally starting to freeze so I went back inside.  Liz bought me a water and I felt like I might be okay, but as everyone started closing their tabs I ran outside and finally finally I puked.  As I was walking and then in front of an office door entrance.  And all over my new shoes.  But I didnt care - after I was done with that I felt like I had been revived from the dead.  Or like the undead becuz I was shivering and confused.  I felt great though.  Soon I found everyone - who had just left the bar.  Liz was carrying around a huge sheet cake with a sushi knife in the box.  Every so often she would open the box to eat cake with her hands or show someone the knife.  Sarah kept falling down on the ground and her thigh highs would no longer stay up.  I kept having this problem where I would walk down the street and my heels would get stuck in the sidewalk cracks and then i would keep walking and my shoe would be stuck and my foot would be on the pavement.   That was pretty painful and annoying and really not good for my new shoes.    Tyler lent me his coat so that I wouldn't freeze.  We waited for Perry and Cooper in Fuddruckers for like 30 minutes and then got a cab back to Helix.  I ate some spicy fries and felt able to drive home.  I was home and in bed at 4:30 a.m.  Listened to a drunk message from Liz and fell asleep.  Sunday was spent packing, watching the Independent Spirit Awards and Short Cuts, unpacking in the new apartment and watching the Academy Awards.  Weekend over - back to work.  Next weekend is the BIG move.    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I haven't blogged in a long time fuckers!   So, what's new in the life of Meg Casablancas?   I still drink coffee at my desk, but I have stopped eating bagels at my desk.  Now, I know that this blog came about because of my office angst towards the bagel v. latte race.  Bagel always won.  But bagels are not good for you everyday.  First of all, the Everything bagel, my bagel of choice, was so appropriately named because it leaves a mess on everything on my desk.  I try to clean my keyboard out weekly with that spray air stuff and without fail, I point that little guy in between the keys and out flies poppy seeds, sesame and onion, salt, what have you.  Second, I usually get cream cheese on my finger, which in turn ends up on the keyboard.  (Maybe I should call IT for a new keyboard.)  Third, I am in the middle of having some extensive dental work done, and god only knows how those itty bitty mini seeds get caught in my teeth.  Seeds are not good for teeth.  And finally, carbs are the new enemy and since I am not Jennifer Aniston and have never ordered a scooped-out bagel in my life.  Its easier to not order the bagel at all.    This morning I ate fruit, paid for by my starbucks gift card that I got for Adminstrative Professionals day.  That was yummy, except freezing cold when it hit my tooth that I had filled last week.  I called the dentist's office immediately following this pain to see if I could get some painkillers and they said that I could come in for another appointment tomorrow.  I said, I will just see how it feels on Monday.  I mean, crimeny, can't you just give me something over the phone?  I already have to go get a root canal in the next few weeks and then you are going to put a post in my tooth and then crown it.  That sounds so fancy, like my tooth is getting knighted or something, (Sir Meg's tooth) but in reality, for me, it is a fate worse than death.  I hate going to the dentist.  I hate the light that they shine in my face.  I hate looking up people's noses and I hate that they are starring my mouth and putting shit in it.  My biggest fear is that they are going to cut my tongue off.  I hate when they talk to you and you can't talk back you just have to shake your head and that makes me even scared more because what if that little shake causes them to cut off my tongue, then what am I going to do.  I like talking, I can't just not have a tongue.  I also hate novocaine.  I don't like not feeling my face.  I chew my cheek off and that is so scary.  I used to have the coolest dentist, he would listen to classic rock when he would work on my teeth.  There is nothing better than walking up from wisdom teeth removal all drugged up to hear the Doors, break on through to the other side, literally.  I might have thought I was Jim Morrison at that point I was so out of it.  I kept laughing and they put me in a closet that they called the "recovery room."  What the hell was that all about?  My dad kept saying, so this is what it's like when you are drunk.  I think I was just about to turn 21.  In other news, Liz is in Iowa, the land of Ashton Kutcher.  However, from what I gather, Iowa is a fate worse than death.  I have discovered (thank you IMDB) that other famous celebs from Iowa include Elijah Wood, Ron Livingston (Office Space) Johnny Carson, John Wayne, Lara Flynn Boyle, Julee Cruise (Twin Peaks Roadhouse singer), Laura Leighton (Sydney from Melrose Place), JEAN SEBERG, and T-Boz!  Liz, these people turned out great, you will too.  Saturday, is the long-awaited Rites of Spring party at Liz's.  This party is also know as Sarah's Birthday party.  Dresses are being created, decorations are on the way, bands are rehearsing.  I am extremely excited for this weekend.  Sunday brunch to celebrate the mammal on Erin's rooftop.    Oh, but how could I forget to mention that Thursday is French Kicks and Ambulance at the Black Cat. Have you seen the pics of preppycuteguitarist from Ambulance? Have you heard the new French Kicks  urlLink  song?   So that is what life is handing your dear Meg Casablancas for now.  Check ya later.        
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So  urlLink  this  is why I am getting stupid.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ew, gross.   Conversation I had on the elevator today:   Man:   Are you going up? (gets in elevator) Can you hit 8? (I hit 8 and notice that he is looking at me and look up.)  Man:   How old are you?  You look like you are 16.  Me:   (I pause and as the elevator door opens I start to walk out) I'm a lot older than that.   Why are you A. hitting on me and B. why do I look like I am 16?  Is it because my hair is in a ponytail today.  Well, it's raining and my hair would look crazy if it wasn't and I don't want to look crazy.  I am trying to look professional.  Do I have to wear a business suit to look 24?  Back at my desk, Kelly starts talking about sex offenders and how her boyfriend, Mike, just sent her a link to all the sex offenders in Germantown.  In cube world, this is what everyone will talk about for the next 15 minutes.  Tara says that she knows one of the sex offenders because he lives on her street and apparantly in Germantown they put stickers on the mailboxes of these sex offenders.  I don't think that you are allowed to do this because on the webpage it says that you can not harass these people.  So, I start looking up NW DC to make sure my landlord or people on my block aren't sex offenders.  I can't find anyone that I recognize.  But it would be safe to say that there are a large number of sex offenders in Mt. Pleasant.  If you have ever been to the 7-11 on the corner of my block you will know what I am talking about.    I decide to look up Takoma Park and see if any lived in my old apartment building.  Cuz I did have those crazy Hatian crack dealers living next door for awhile, so anything goes.  These crazy hatians had pix from penthouse taped up all over their apartment and once even hung it on the outside of their door.  And they were always blasting the bass over there and I would just call the police, but Anna thought it was a good idea to go over to crazy Hatian crack apartment and tell them to turn it down.  Then they knew it was us who had called the police and would kick on our door and threatened Anna one day while she was doing laundry. I mean before Liz moved out they would sit on the balcony and feed the birds and hit on any female walking by and invite them in for rice (the same rice they were throwing around for the birds.)  I think this may be one of the reasons that Liz had to move out.    It took about 10 complaints before crack apt tenants were evicted.   I did not find any sex offenders living in Montgomery Gardens.    To continue my search I looked up Silver Spring and as I was scrolling down I came across a man that had temped in my department for a week.  Not only did he temp, he was my temp and not only was he my temp, but Sarah had to sit in an office with this man for three days and stuff envelopes.  I knew he was weird because he listened to a radio the side of a 2x4 post-it pad and he made personal phone calls.  Sarah was my spy and would tell me that he was really slow and talked about headshots and being an actor.  I went in there at one point to help them out because we had to stuff about 5,00 envelopes with 2 labels and 3 inserts.  I forwarded my calls to the phone in the office and once when I picked it up they asked for Andre.  This made me really pissed.  I said that he was unable to come to the phone and hung up.  Then I had to repremand my temp and tell him NO PERSONAL CALLS.  I mean duh.  I went through Adecco when I started here and they make sure to tell you no calls.  And if you don't have a job that requires you to use the phone then definitely do not use it.  This guy also had to be late everyday because for some reason he had to go to court every morning.  Well, it turns out that he was a third degree sex offender, which means that he molested someone under age 15.  This is disgusting and the fact that we had to work in a small room with him is gross and we all know that mammal looks young and is little and apparantly I look like I am 16.      urlLink  Capturing the Friedmans  screening in the cave tonite. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Okay, you know you want to play:         &hearts; Julian Casablancas and  &hearts; Sara Kaplan 
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       For y'all who I've been telling about the cuteguitarist from Ambulance:  (this is the same thing in wore in DC - preppybabyface!!!)    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Seder with the Cladlerbergs:   Last nite was the first nite of Passover and Seder with Sarah's family.  I couldn't go to Seder at my aunt's house because they decided to spend the Jewish holidays in Italy.    Betty had adorned the table with little Passover props - hail, locusts, cattle, frogs, baby Moses made out of clay and paper.  Afikomen cover that A.C. made in 1980 (while on mushrooms?).  The cows had heads that kept falling off and when you wound them up, they actually looked diseased.  They would fall down and their heads popped off.  Erin Worley kept throwing little pieces of hail at Sarah and Betty.  A.C.  kept trying to takeover passover and speed his way through it so that he could watch the NCAA final game.  Danny kept getting blamed for eating all the food and being the youngest child.  Simone decided not to  play Seder with us (she is only 4) and build a farm for the mad cows out of legos.  Everytime she ran away David had to go retrieve her and when he would sit down they candlesticks on the table would sway.  Liz started to get a little thinky at the table and I had to rub her shoulder.  Bubbe was so cute and must have thought we all were crazy.  5 glasses of wine later Betty was singing Passover ditties at extremely high speeds and recalling a time when she was 10 and thought that Manashevits was grape juice and got drunk and then had to go up and sing these same songs at synagogue and won a silver dollar.    After dinner I made a skirt out of the taffata napkins that we used.  These napkins were hilarious because if anything fell on your lap it would slide right of the napkins and onto the floor.  Before dinner A.C. asked if the napkins were made out of leather and we all joked about how they couldn't absorb anything.  Sarah got a new cellphone and I was so excited and could not stop thanking Pop, because now she doesn't have to use my cellphone anymore.  It's funny when we are out and I take out my cellphone because before I know it Sarah has slid it across the table so she can view it.  I also had to have a small panic attack after dinner because while playing with the locusts (grasshoppers) on the table, we started to discuss Brood X (see Sarah's for more  urlLink  info )  I was almost crying as everyone was discussing the swarms of locusts that we are going to have this summer.  Honestly, I don't know if I can handle this.  Either I am dating an exterminator or taking Danny and driving out West.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      These quizzes are fucking scary:           I have issues with...        selfishness  cost  society  fate  murder        urlLink Take Word Association Test  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I found more quizzes!!!!!  (results from 27 question quiz)       urlLink What Classic Movie Are You?  
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The story of a car that almost blew up   It was Halloween 2002.  Liz, Kyle, Paul and I drive to a party in Adelphi.  I got really stoned at this party and have never felt more existential in my LIFE.  I cannot remember anything about this party.  I couldn't even tell you if I wore a costume.  Actually, I don't think any of us did because the party was not actually on Halloween, it might have been a few days before or after.  But that is irrelevant for this story.  We left the party pretty late, it was definitely past 2:00.  I remember driving on 193 past the courtyard apartments.  As we made the right turn onto Metzerott, we saw some smoke and started to smell something burning, and I said that it must be the car we just past cuz the smoke was behind us.  But the smell did not go away, it got worse.  The car was a little smokey at this point.  We made it down Metzerott a bit until I started freaking.  I pulled over at the 7-11 where the Golden Bull is and we decided what to do.  It was too late to call AAA to have the car towed and be stranded at 3:00 a.m. in Adelphi.   Since we weren't too far from my apartment, someone suggested that we just try to make it.  This seemed like a good idea at the time.  The more we drove the worse it got and when we made turns it was horrible.  The smoke started coming into the car through the vents and I thought that either we were going to die from smoke inhalation or the car was actually just going to blow the fuck up.  There was nothing we could do, stop and be stranded or die.  I think we all kind of excepted this, even though we were all really freaked.  The smoke was unbearable by the time we pulled into the parking lot of the apartment.  As soon as we did, I stopped and we all ran out.  We ran out so quick that I forgot to shut the car off.  The car was engulfed in smoke, but Kyle ran back into the cloud and shut the car off.  Then Paul and Kyle pushed it into its parking space and we were so relieved that we had survived.    I took the car into the shop the next day the prognosis was a broken tube in the engine and what we were breathing in was probably anti-freeze.  Yay!!! So we could have died but we didn't and that is good.  But it is experiences like this that make me less freaked out about car problems.  It's not the end of the world when you car breaks down.  It is just really annoying and costly.  I need to get rid of my car and embrace public transportation.  Or if you are my brother, you are a genius and you don't have to study - you can just sit around in your house at Brandeis and get stoned all day and still manage to get a full tuition and A-'s and have Beryl and Mike lease you a brand new Mazda6.  This car is fucking awesome.  It is a sports car and incredibly fun to drive.  I whine about this to my parents frequently, but they always tell me that they made a deal with Matt, that if he got a full tuition to school then he would get a car.  Bribes are bull shit.  The other option for Matt was to go to MIT.  My stoner brother is so smart that he actually got into MIT.  But since MIT is $40,000/year and he got a car and a spot on the soccer team at Brandeis he went there.  Life is so nice for Matt.  But really, I love my brother he is hilarious.  He dresses like Kayne West.  He owns Jay-Z's sneakers.  He is a label whore.  He also loves the Strokes.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I just got back from HELL!!!   During lunch today, I went over to the gas station to have my cracked headlight replaced.  It took about 15 minutes for them do.  I was going to get gas as well since my gas light was on, but it was $2.20/gallon.  So, I decide that I would drive up toward White Oak for cheaper gas.  I found the place and was just about to take a U-turn when the car started slowing down.  I was actually running out of gas.  I was able to get into the left turn and then nothing.  The car wouldn't even roll, except for a little bit backwards.  If this had happened a few years ago I would have freaked out, but I have been through so much with this car that its old news when something happens to me.  (I will tell you tomorrow about the time my car almost blew up.)    So, I called AAA and asked them to send someone over with gas.  They told me that they would put it as a priority call since I was in the middle of an intersection and I was on my lunch break. The time was 2:15 and they said that someone would be there by 3:30, 4:00 at the latest.  Then I called Gwyneth at the office and told her of my troubles.  She always understands my stupidity and that's why it sucks that tomorrow is her last day.  It was freaking hot in the car, I haven't been sweating for a few days and it felt like a sauna in the car and I couldn't run the airconditioning because it would wear out the battery and I couldn't open the windows becuz there tons of cicadas flying around and I already had the excitement of a cicada in the car for today.  So I sat in the boiling hot car with no gas and bugs flying all around.  I think that this is what hell will be like.  Sweaty and full of bugs.  So I called Liz and told her I was in hell and that I was stupid and she suggested that I call Mike, so I did and he attempted to come and help me, but he couldn't find my car, but it was okay because AAA had just called to say that it would only be another 20 minutes.    People are stupid (besides me and my problems.)  I had my hazard lights on, but people still came right into the turn lane and came right up to the back of my car and then started honking even after I waved them around.  Don't honk at me I cannot go anywhere get over and stop giving me dirty looks.  This went on for over an hour.  Finally, the AAA, who had a University of Maryland Facilities shirt on, arrived and filled up the gas and I tried to start the car, but the fucking battery was dead becuz I was running the hazards the whole time.  So he gave me a jump start, I gave him the $5 for the gas and I was on my way.  I finally got back to the office around 4:00.  I took a pointless sweaty 3 hour lunch break.  Sometimes I don't know why I do the things that I do.  They are so illogical.  Normally I don't care how much gas costs I just get it cuz I need it.  I have never run out of gas before.  Why today did I decide to drive out of the way to get gas?  I will never understand.  Am I subconsciously testing my own boundaries?  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       So far today . . .   a cicada flew in my car window.  I have been told that I am dressed like Flashdance.  I have been called Bunkian Bunkabunkas.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Good News!!   I found my sugar lipgloss behind my bed.  My lips taste yummy once again.   urlLink The Hard Tomorrows  have a website.  I have airconditioning.  I have a carton of marlboro lights thanks to Matt's trip to South Carolina.  I have beach plans for 4th of July.  I love Ambulance LTD (esp. Benji on the left):     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Sweating is the new makeup   Since the second I left work on Friday til about 2:00 today, I have been sweating.  Chuck, our landlord, kept saying that he would install the air conditioner and told us that we would be okay until this weekend, but I beg to differ.  Waking up every morning in sticky sheets is not comforting.  I yearn for the days when I lived on Long Island and Beryl would set the central air at arctic temperatures.  My friends used to come over to my house in the summer in sweatpants and sweatshirts because they knew how cold my mom kept our house.  Beryl likes it cold year round - she sleeps with the window open in the winter.  I am embracing sweat though, I have no choice.  It's very rocknroll.  That nice sweaty glow has replaced my MAC foundation.  If I attempt to put makeup on it melts off my face.    Friday nite was the first time in a long time that I stayed in.  I watched the Strokes on David Letterman.  They performed "The End has No End" which was nice because they just ended a 3-month long tour and I'm sure that they must have been happy to be back in NYC.  Julian wore a white blazer with a black T-shirt and white unlaced hightops circa 1986.  He sang a little slower and had a little more acne, probably due to sweating.  After the performance, I hopped on the internet to do a little Strokes research and stumbled upon the news that Julian is engaged to Juliet, the Strokes asst. manager.  In fact, Julian and Juliet had an engagement party in Providence the night after I saw him in Boston.  (side note - there was a girl that resembled Juliet in the audience at Boston - the more I think about it the more I think it  WAS  her.)  And he announced that they were engaged at the Central Park Summerstage show last Wednesday.  This news makes me sad.  But Liz predicts "that the marriage will last approximately three months before julian accidently stabs his new wife with a broken beer bottle and they get seperated and he goes to rehab."  So this makes me happy.  It's not that I think that I am going to marry Julian, cuz god only knows I can't even get Diner Boy to like me, but to think of Julian as a married man is crazy to me.  Part of the whole appeal is that he is a sweaty drunken rocknroll bachelor.  That is hot.  Now he is going to be a sweaty drunken rocknroll husband?  What next? Is he going to have an MTV reality show about married life, please fucking spare me.  I would rather eat a cicada then have to deal with that.  So I am dealing with the news and I am sweating.  On Saturday, I was able to see my new rocknroll obsession, Benji of Ambulance LTD.  I love Benji - he looks a bit like Diner Boy and closes his eyes when he plays guitar.  They sounded great.  I was up close to the stage, I do this because I like to escape the talking people and the less people in front of me the better I can see the cute rocknrollers.  (this is why I am the Hard Tomorrows superfan.)  The best part of the Ambulance shows are the last two songs.  They always close with Young Urban followed by Yoga Means Union (which always reminds me of Urban Yoga)and I love when Marcus and Benji start simultaneously wanking.  It sounds incredible and it looks so good.  I love the disc, but I prefer the live show.    After the show, Liz and Mike dropped me off at the Stripes v. Polka Dots party on Irving.  People were dancing inside, but it was unbearably hot inside and Sarah, Rishi and I among others hung out on the front porch.  Funny things that happened at the party:  Kelly in bikini and Alex in underwear, Ben talking about Dillybeans and going camping, Bobby climbing onto the roof, cops stopping by 3 times, tug of war, people calling people at 4 in the morning and giving out the address.  At about 4:30, Sarah, Rishi, Bobby and I were hungry and went to the Diner, where we saw Maile at the counter and were waited on by none other than Diner Boy - whose name for the record is John.  I had a headache and masacra under my eyes (from being sweaty) and looked a mess and I can't believe that Diner Boy saw me in this condition.  However, his hair was sticking up all over the place and Rishi asked me why his hair looked like that and I said that it was cute.  Diner Boy thought that I was a vegetarian.    Sunday I sweated, took the airconditoner out of the boiler room, moved my bed away from the wall so that Chuck could install it, drank a iced soy latte, walked to Pop, drank a smoothie with the mammal, walked through Meridian Hill Park, watch Hollywood Homicide with Liz, swooned over Josh Hartnett, ate Astor, watched Viva La Bam, swooned over Tim Glomb(he builds stuff and has really hot tattoos), by the time I got home I was still sweating and Chuck did not put the air conditioner in my window so after killing a roach I took a cold shower and went to bed.   It's easy to wake up at 7:00am when you are sweating in bed.  The sheets get all wrinkled and the last thing that you want to do is hit the snooze button, which is a good thing because I had a big meeting today and had a lot to do, so I had to run all over the building today, which made me fucking sweaty at work.  Finally around 2, the running subsided and I could sit and do desk work again and enjoy the airconditioning.  I also enjoyed the catering.  I did not enjoy my cigarette breaks, because there are dead cicadas everywhere.  Gross.  I am getting ready to leave work now.  I hope that Chuck has installed the airconditioner like he told Sarah that he would do today.  I want to drink beer outside though.  Want to or no?  Let's sweat some more. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Don't talk to me.  I am in mourning.  Now  urlLink  this  is totally ruining my artificial reality.    "Spare me."  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Artificial Reality - Part 3   So Pri thinks that my name is really Meg Casablancas.  Last nite I stopped by his house and he asked me if we were related.    And at this point I'm not so sure if there isn't some truth to that.  At the last Strokes show, Liz said that I was able to  urlLink  channel Julian.    This time it was Casablancas vs. Casablancas:   Julian the drunk sweaty lead singer.  Meg the drunk sweaty leadsingerlovergroupie.  Julian climbing over seats while he sings ...  Meg climbing over seats to get to Julian.   Julian singing from a seat 3 feet away.  Meg standing on a seat 3 feet away from Julian.  Julian falling into a seat closer.  Meg leaning over and grabbing Julian's sweaty head, sweat dripping from his hair.  She whispers in his ear, "Julian what's wrong with you?"  Julian answering Meg's question into the mic, "I'm fucking tired man."    Meg still drunk and still in love.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Artificial Reality - Part 2: The Artists    urlLink  Frank Bauer    urlLink  Arnout Killian    urlLink  Glen Rubsamen       urlLink  Bret Easton Ellis   and Julian Casablancas . . .  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Artificial Reality   "We live in an artificial reality. Our inner life is flooded with images of better worlds evoked by mass media.  These images shape our desires, as well as our experiences.  But not only our inner life, also in the physical world around us, artificiality has become accepted as part of reality.  In the design of our daily surroundings - landscape, shops, public and domestic space - spectacle and experience often seem more important than concepts like authenticity or reality."  -  urlLink  quote   Part 2 of Artificial Reality - coming soon.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and you thought the rites of spring was sweaty.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Julian takes Boston  So, I just got back from the Strokes show.  I cannot even begin to tell you about it now.  But its coming and its pretty unreal.  That's all for now, cuz I'm too drunk to tell you right now.  But get ready cuz this is good.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       megadork:  i chugged a starbucks doubleshot in the car this morning   mike:  why are those so good? i could go for a starbucks double shot kegstand. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was so drunk last nite that I lost my brand new sugar lipgloss :-(   This is where I burst out into song "What are we gonna do now?" I don't really know, because this morning I couldn't find my cellphone either. But this has to be in my apartment because I called my brother last nite when I got home. Lipgloss might be in Mike's car. Cellphone has to be in my apartment.    Missing:  Sugar lipgloss, cellphone with butterflies on the face. Please call bunkablancas if you have any information leading to the recovery of these important items.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry that these blogs have become few and far between.  Here are some updates:   Rites of Spring   I called out sick on the Friday before the party, because I had partied a little too much at the French Kicks/Ambulance LTD show.  Waking up at 9:00 a.m. makes you feel like you shouldn't bother going to work at all.  If you are still in bed when you are supposed to be at your desk makes you wish that you could actually work from bed.  Like a good mom, I drove Sarah to work and then went over to Hobart to wake up Liz who the nite before had to lie down in my car after the show she was so drunk.  I found her in her tropical room in bed.  I didn't care that I had to wait for her to wake up, I was so happy to not be at work.  I spent the next hour trying to motivate Liz to get up while going through her cds in order to create some killer mixes for the party.  Then Liz goes How did I get yellow highlighter on my hand.  I am fucked up.  I am like Paris Hilton... Hold on, I might puke.  Then she got up and ran to the bathroom.  We thought she was better, but Dos Gringos was hard for us.  Liz became Bunkenstein shortly afterwards as she crossed the road with her arms stretched out in front of her.  Later that day we went through things in the basement showed the man from the dump what to take which was basically anything that we deemed trash and swept for the party-prep.  After the house looked super clean we took a trip to the party store followed by a stop at Sephora to buy Sarah her birthday presents and some presents for me too (purple eyeshadow and lipgloss that tastes like sugar.)  This took to long and I was late picking Sarah up for spraytan.  (We have missed the opportunity to do spraytan one time too many that we have since abandoned this plan - besides it has been really sunny out lately and I am getting a lot of natural color.)  The day ended by getting really stoned and decorating for the party.  Actually, now that I think about it I didn't go to bed until 5:00 a.m.  I stayed up later making the killer mixes for the party.  The party was excellent.  I realized early on in the nite (possibly 9:30/10:00) that there were no boys with bigbabyfacemessyhair so I just concentrated on me and my state of partiness.  By 11:00 I was wasted.  The Cause started it all out with a bang.  They did a cover of Hey Ya - and everyone went fucking crazy.  Other highlights for me were the Thundersluts - they make me feel like I am in the 80s - Elizabeth is so incredible up there and the lyrics are rad.  The Hard Tomorrows sounded so good - I was falling down they were so great.  They played the song that Liz calls the Rocker and I call It Get Heavy.  And I really love that song.  It replaces Jaywalker as my new fav.  When they didn't play TakeDown (my true all time favorite song ever) we whined and cried and screamed that they had to play it - we even threatened with the fact that it was Sarah's birthday so they had to and they DID. After that it get foggy.  I watched a little bit of Reizou's set and then went outside - Betty and Becca arrived and I told Betty that I would watch her car while she went inside for a little.  I was good at doing this for some reason.  However, I missed Reizou wheeling over the keg during their set and doing keg stands - bummer.  Like I said the rest is a haze. But I did NOT get sick - that is the key.  I did have to sit in the alley for a little bit, but I persevered and eventually was able to walk home with filthy feet and dirty jeans.  Champagne Brunch the next day at Erin Worley's was fun.  We were all pretty hung over, but we sat on the roof in the sun and drank champagne.  It really does not get any better than that.  After brunch I changed to an all american clean up outfit and headed over to Hobart for cleaning crew.  We swept and mopped to the Strokes and rearranged furniture.  That nite Liz, Mike, Perry and I sat in the clean house got stoned, watched The Sopranos and Deadwood (everyone's favorite new show) and ate yummy organic chinese food.   DC9 - an introduction to Paul Michel the band   I had missed Paul Michel's prior shows and was very excited that this one was on a Friday.  He was incredible.  I was really into his set and he has a cute brother that plays bass.  Sarah and I got there at 8 so that should tell you something about the state of mind I was in by the time we left.  There was talk of going to Lucky Bar cuz Maile was working the back bar, but we ended up going to the Cat.  I left my umbrella at DC9.   New York Minute   On Saturday, Carrie and I went to see New York Minute - yes this IS the Mary-Kate and Ashley movie.  And YES, I loved it.  The twins run around New York getting into trouble in towels and rocking out. This is fun.  I wish that I could do this.   It was nice to see Carrie.  We used to live together back in college and I don't really see her enough anymore.   Drunk in the sun on sunday   On Sunday I thought that I would go down to the museum via Pop (sarah's store,) but somehow I ended up at St. Ex for 5 hours.  Drinking in the sun really does not motivate you.  I then watched the Sunday nite shows with Liz and Perry again stoned, so Deadwood is really scary and confusing for me and I love it.  It is about Cowboys.  Then this stoney dork decided to go to the Diner with Sarah and Becca and ask Diner Boy 101 questions.  I think he kinda liked that.  He is funny.  Like tripping on a chair and smiling at me when he does it.     Present Day   Right now I am drinking Orangina at my desk and listening to the Stills. I love Orangina because its fizzy and its juice and the bottle is really fun to hold.  I also love the Stills and I am excited because they are playing tonite at the 9:30club.  So after work I am going to make dinner and meet up with Liz and Mike for drinks (and Sarah although I do not know her plan since she is at her dad's house right now) and we are going to go to the show.  The last time that I saw the Stills we were right up front and it was really emotional for me and I cried when Dave the drummer came out from behind his drums and they played Yesterday Never Tomorrows.  They played with the Unicorns last time and that was one of the best shows ever.  Liz keeps saying that Mike says that the opening bands tonite (metic and sea ray) are really good and we should go see them.     What am I doing tomorrow?   Well, first I am going to attempt to get out of bed before 8:20 and try to make it to work before 9:20, but we all remember what happened the last time that I went to a show and then tried to go to work.  I cannot call out sick tomorrow because I am going on vacation starting at 6:00 p.m. tomorrow nite.  I am flying up to Boston to visit my brother and see the Strokes (who the Stills are opening for.)  So my energy level is really up right now and I am fighting to make it through one more day.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Carbon Nanotubes   I am getting extremely freaked out by the space elevator project.  NASA's Institute for Advanced Concepts (NIAC) program, Research for the Institute for Scientific Research  and Eureka Scientific in Berkeley, California are planning to build an elevator that goes from Earth to space within the next 15 years.  This is no "love in an elevator" elevator, this is an elevator on a cable made out of a carbon-nanotube-composite ribbon.  Yes, a RIBBON, like the ones that Sarah loves to wear in her hair.  Except this 62,000 mile long ribbon, made using nanotechnology, will transport a platform looking cable car up into SPACE.  Nanotechnology is the manipulation of matter on the molecular and atomic level. Carbon nanotubes provide the highest strength-to-weight ratio of any material ever seen, some 50 to 100 times stronger than steel and one-sixth the weight.  There is a video demo you can watch of the elevator at work  urlLink  here .  This shit is crazy and terrifying.  They say that in the long run this is going to save money, because it costs more money to fund each space shuttle flight and it will eliminate disasters such as the Challenger and Columbia.  I have a little theory though that this could be some sort of escape root for the wealthy, those that can afford to ride the elevator are going to go up there and live in outerspace or on the moon.  So, instead of spending money on programs to help to poor, the biggest elevator known to man is being built and they are just going to escape and start an intergalatic war with us.   "It will change the world economy. It's worth what ever it costs to put it up," Westling said. An initial elevator, he added, is sure to give birth to even larger systems, capable of handling larger loads of up and down traffic."  Okay, this  urlLink  space  website is awesome.  You can watch live coverage of satelites in space near Saturn.  When I lived with Liz in Takoma Park we had this TV station that was a constant feed from inside the space shuttle.  So, you could turn this on at any time and watch real people inside the shuttle doing their space thing.  Mostly, they were just sitting, but for some reason I found this station really relaxing.    We are leaving the geosynchronous orbit.    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I stuck to the promise that I made to myself pretty well this weekend.  I did not go out and spend a lot of money.  Friday night, Liz, Sarah and I ate pizza, drank wine, watched 50 First Dates and cried our eyes out.  This movie, although hilarious, thanks to the cutest penguin and walrus, was devestatingly upsetting for me.  Drew Barrymore is so cute and Adam Sandler is so endearing and their courtship is so sweet.  Thinking about it now makes me want to cry.    On Saturday nite, we had a lovely BBQ at our apartment.  Another reason I need to get my digicam.  Then I can post pics of it and write captions.  I have too much energy right now to go into details about the event, but the funniest thing ever said:   Liz:  "Avram, it looks like you are learning about irony."  Avram looks down at his shirt.   Me:  "No, not ironing, IRONY."   E-mail from Liz regarding Sunday:   Bunk you are the best. It was so fun getting shitfaced and listening to the undertakers with you yesterday afternoon  And it was really funny when we had to tell the mammal “ok, we got wasted.”  :)   SEE EVERYONE AT THE CAT TONITE!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "For a good time try carlo rossi and shooting bb guns." -  urlLink  Avram   Thanks Avram, that actually does sound like a good time.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I might have to quit this shit.  Things are getting too weird in my life to continue for now.  I am taking a break for today.  There really is nothing that I can say.  Too many cosmic forces are trying to fuck with my life.  The internet is a wonderful and SCARY place, as is my world.  BREAK ..........
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "I am unable to comply"   Last nite I was feeling sad and listening to sad songs ( Made-up Dreams , Built to Spill) and staring into space.  Alone in my apartment, I become a zombie with ADD.  Actually, I took a  urlLink  quiz  yesterday that said that I am a Night of the Living Dead Zombie.  Liz called me around 10:30 to remind me that she had been at dinner with her family and that's why she didn't answer my numerous calls to her cellphone.  Liz is good at raising the dead and she invited me over for bong hits and tv with Perry.  This was the best remedy for my craving for the heavenly taste of spicy brains to stop the pain of being dead.  We watched Terminator 3: The Rise of the Machines.  Best mindblowing action movie that I have seen in a long time.  Everything in this movie is awesome and every five minutes I would remind Liz and Perry of this fact, when I would scream, "That's awesome."  Schwarzenegger is awesome.  The machines are awesome.  Nick Stahl is awesome.  Claire Danes is awesome.  Explosions are awesome.      Anyways. This movie may have revived my work spirit.  Claire Danes makes you want to kick some serious ass when you are at your desk.     When gun control laws are not passed in Congress, Liz said that I can get my uzi.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Sunday came.  I trashed it out again.   I am ending the saga of my fucked up weekend.  First - I have been playing around with the look of the title.  It's still a little bit of a work in progress, but I am happy with it for now.  (It is my favorite pic of Julian ever - before he got all crazy and alcoholic.)  So in brief, I woke up at 2:00 on Sunday in a great deal of pain from my fall the day before.  I immediately started icing and medicating, at least as soon as I was able to pick myself out of my bed.  Sarah had been at a shoot with her mom since 9:00am, ouch!!  We hadn't gone to bed until 6am.  The rest of the day was spent hobbling around my apartment, hobbling up to 7-11 for snacks, trying to get in touch with the mammal and trying to decide if I really should be going to the Franz Ferdinand show later that nite.  Around 8:00 I headed over to the 9:30 club to get my tickets from Ben.  I couldn't get in touch with Sarah until it was too late and she still needed to celebrate father's day.  In the end I went to the show alone, met up with Warnock and rocked out to FF.  They were fucking incredible and I wish that I wasn't so hungover and drugged out and in such pain that I could have been down on the floor dancing.  What a shame.  But I still enjoyed them.  Loved the drummer's gold chain and v-neck sweater and the Agent Cooper look-a-like on guitar/synth.    Of course I hit up the merch table, you know, we like merch.  For myself, I purchased the green/yellow shortsleeve bball tee and for Sarah (since she missed the show and all) I purchased the cute little underwear.  She loves them, ask her about them and maybe she'll show you, but then again, I doubt it.   As I was catching a cab home, another girl was trying to get in my cab.  After chatting with her briefly, I figured out that it was Sara, Popular Cult, the girl who knows Kappy at Brandeis.  Such a small fucking world and now all DC Bloggers are trying to unite to try and overthrow the NYC scene.  Something about purple ribbon and paperclip bracelets.  I am just trying to get people out for the HT show.  Folks, do you realize that HT is playing the Black Cat on Monday and that there will be a merch table.  Whoa!!      
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Saturday I said I'm sorry   Sarah came into my airconditioned room on Saturday morning trying to convince me that I needed to go get food with her.  I told her that there was no reason to get up because it wasn't nice out anyway.  However, that wasn't the case, it was a beautiful day.  But in my room it was dark and I was a little strugglefest.  So we went to our favorite weekend brunch place, Tonic.   After brunch, I went to the mall to buy some weekend playclothes.  I ended up with new jeans, that I don't really like and a new pair of Chucks, which I love, but caused me a great deal of pain, which I will get to in a minute.  Back at home, Sarah was calling me every five minutes to tell me to come home cuz there was a mob of people outside at the Alley Party.  Finally, I got home and got ready for the 1st Annual Kilbourne/Kenyon Alley Party.  I laced up the new chucks and went outside grabbed a beer.  A few minutes later it started to rain.  I realized that I needed to go inside and blow dry my hair before it got all crazy.  As soon as I stepped on the first stair I slipped, due to my new shoes and fell down all five stairs.  I landed on my back at the bottom crying and laughing.  Now I have a HUGE bruise on my back and I have trouble moving around.  I feel elderly and I need assisted living.  I was supposed to start pilates yesterday, but I can't really do that now.  I am going to attempt to go today and have the cute pre/post rehab guy tell me some stretches that I can do.  I should have stayed in the rest of the day, but I figured that if I got really drunk and drugged out than I would be ok.  So I took pain pills and drank the rest of the day.  Saw the Hard Tomorrows at Ft. Reno.  The weather was beautiful, the band looked refreshed.  They sounded great.  I love listening to my favorite bands outside, the music just floats around in the air.  After their set I went over to Guapo's for Margaritas with Kelly, Perry and Warnock.  After 2 pitchers, I wobbled back over and caught end of the Carlsonics set.  Another chick bassist - yay!!  There was a family there that was dancing all over - another reincarnation of urban yoga from Silver Spring.  Also in the family was skinny shirtless dancing man, running baby and blanketed thing. At one point Bobby got up and started dancing with urban yoga.  I think that there are digipics of this out there.    We were supposed to go to the Carlsonics after party, but you know plans are for shit.  So, we went home to change into our hotfits, but really Kelly was the only one who truly captured the essence of the hotfit.  She wore a safari jumper hotshort hotfit and heels.  (Kelly is here and she says that she emulated Bridget Bardot).  First stop was the Washington City Paper party on Hobart.  After a little bit of philosophy, drinks and dancing, it was off to the Dressed to Get Screwed party.  Here are the things that I  do  remember about the party:  * Everytime that I had to go to the bathroom there was a long line that I waited in for at least 20 minutes.  Later that evening I went to the bathroom with Sarah and the sink was on the floor.   * Ben (not Vivari) was wearing a cuban shirt, which prompted a photo shoot of close-ups on people's outfits.  Rishi's pre-distressed hole in his jeans, Rishi's pocket, Ben's pattern on his shirt, design on Sarah's t-shirt, the word Quebec on Paul Nighties t-shirt.  A few minutes later Kelly came out looking for Warnock's camera.  She thought she had lost it, but she had handed it to be so we could do a pornographic photo shoot on the sidewalk.  I need to post the photos, if I ever get them.  I think there is also a picture of my bruise on there and I would really like to post it if possible. * Bobby called me to ask where the party was and when I told him T and 16th, he said that he was on S and could here the party.  About 20 minutes later, we were still on the porch and we wondered where Bobby was.  Rishi decided that he should go look for him, so he left.  About an hour later, Sarah comes up to me inside and asks me where Rishi went.  I had no idea.  Sarah said that he went to look for Bobby.  This came as a surprise to me, since I had been hanging out with Bobby for the past hour at the party.  He somehow had snuck in while we were on the porch. * They also had put the couches on their ends in this little little room that leads upstairs.  Sarah and I had to use our cellphones as flashlights to navigate through the small coffin like space.  * I somehow employed Ben and then Perry to get me beer from the keg and bring it to me.  This worked out well until Perry tried to steal my cup and drink my beer. * Sarah reminds me that Rishi put us in a cab.  Before we even went a block, Sarah said that we needed to go back because Warnock had her phone.  Luckily, the cab driver realized that we were idiots and just let us get out. * Back at the party, the cops came, so the hosts were standing on the porch making sure that we kept it inside. For some reason, it was easier for everyone else to follow these simple instructions, but for Sarah and I, we were in and out and in and out.  I don't even know what Sarah had to do inside everytime.  But the people living there would get pissed that I was outside and then when I would go inside Sarah would be ready to leave again.  A few minutes later, however, she was back inside.  This little game went on for awhile. * Sarah and Warnock had been in communications with Sebastian and group (AC, Erin, Julian, Annette) all evening.  Finally just as we were about to get into another cab they showed up.  Sarah was on the phone with Rishi trying to convince him to come back to the party.  They had been trying to find us all nite, but didn't know where the party was, but somehow they found a bunch of other parties.  We moved this whole group back to Hobart in 3 cabs.  I showed Erin my bruise and she flipped out.    * Back at Hobart, we sat around the big dining room table under the 70s lighting and I listened to Erin Worley lecture me on how to clean my stairs so that I wouldn't fall again for about 20 minutes.  Bobby was sound asleep on the couch and for some reason, everyone decided to go and sit on the couch that he was sleeping on.  He did not seem to wake up.  But on Monday nite, when asked about this incident.  He said that he didn't know why everyone was sitting on him and said that he was going to try to switch couches, but he didn't.   I am sure that more happened, but I cannot remember so clearly, so if you have other memories, please share them with me and I can edit my post later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Friday Nite I crashed your party,   My Friday nite started as soon as I left the office at 6pm.  I met up with Liz and Anne at Island Jim's Tiki Bar.  This place is incredible, as soon as you enter, you feel like you have been transported to Key West or something.  They have sand and Rum Runners in DC.  It wasn't long before Sarah started calling to ask when we were going to be back for Reizou at DC9 at 8.    Jesse quit Reizou last week, but they still sounded great.  All that practicing has really paid off.  Liz always asks me why the have a DJ after the bands.  She said that people are paying for the bands, not the DJ and that it drives people out early.  But they played Reptilia (makes me happy) and they were screening Blow Up.  We ditched DC9 for the Black Cat aroun midnightish.  Kyle drove us.  I quickly recounted my strokes dream to him (which I knew he would crack up at) and sarah and I ran out of the car.  Liz was supposedly going home to hang out with her roommates, bobby moved in on friday and there was a massive cleaning, chilling out thing going on.  Earlier that day someone from the MC5 came into Pop and bought a shirt from Sarah and put her on the list + 1 for that nite.  After being upstairs for less than 5 minutes I had to buy cigarettes and went back downstairs where I ran into Liz.  Apparently, she was confused why we left her in the car.  So I explained how we thought she was going home and she thought she was coming with us so she went in without her and since she wasn't on the list she didnt know how to find us.  Liz and I sat at the bar in front of Chuck and texted and called Sarah til she realized that I ditched her and we were downstairs.  Chuck pours us all a shot and gets us into 80s alt pop dance party.  This was fun, until it got too sweaty and Sarah disappeared to make a phone call.    Soon we were on the street and then we were at Rishi's banging on his door at 3am.  (I have already apologized for this repeatedly, but once again sorry Rishi.)  Sarah was pissed that we were there cuz me and Liz were wasted and apparently, Rishi's roommate's 4 year old daughter was sleeping there, but no one told us, so we were being loud.  And, really no one was trying to control us so we just continued on our drunken tirade.  Sarah said that she was coming over so Liz and I decided to hide out and take a break on the back stoop.  Liz was messy, she fell down into the marshland that is Rishi's backyard.  She showed me her scrape last nite. We drunk dialed Perry and Bobby and then we decided that Sarah and Rishi didnt want us there so we ran down the alley, apparently, Sarah ran after us, but we didn't even see her, let alone know that she was calling our names out.  We were going to take a cab home, but Liz said that we should just walk up 16th street.  This was quite the adventure.  Sarah called to yell at us but we didn't know why she was mad.  First she didn't want us there and then she was mad cuz we left. Liz picked a flower to give to Sarah, but the roots and a lot of dirt was still attached.  Instead of giving it to Sarah, she threw it at me and got dirt all over my shirt.  We drunk dialed Avram. Liz and I were still laughing so hard from the dirt incident that she kept telling Avram "please hold while I process your account information."  Liz sat down on the sidewalk.  We were a fucking mess!  I called Sarah back and she was kinda pissed at us so we went back to Rishi's to get her.  Liz and I ran upstairs to the bathroom.  Usually, when we are fucked up Liz gets in the bathtub.  This time she told me too. I think Liz might have blogged before about the old stupid drunken things we have done in the past, and if she hasn't than she should, but y'all should know how we roll by now.  Across the street these 3 guys called us over to look in someone's window.  They said that there was a guy in there who was wearing a speedo, but by the time we peeked in the light was off.  We tried to get the guys to give us a ride back to Mt. Pleasant, but they said no and Sarah called us prostitutes.  So, we started walking, but Sarah made us get in a cab and there was a lot of yelling in the cab.    The thing about Sarah is that she never stays mad for too long.  Even though we were acting like drunk assholes all nite she forgave us.  It was all blamed on miscommunication.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What ARE we gonna do NOW?  They cancelled  urlLink Lollapalooza  due to poor ticket sales?  Why bye?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I woke up laughing.   Okay, so I am ready to tell you about the hilarious dream that I had last nite.  I dreamt that I was at a Strokes show at the Palladium, which is in Hollywood.  The venue was practically empty.  Sarah and I were sitting in the front row.  Almost everyone was playing drums.  Julian was on drums, Matt Romano was on drums, Juliet was on a mini drumset, and of course Fab was on drums.  Nikolai and Nick were playing their correct instruments, bass and guitar.  But where was Albert?  He wasn't even there.  They were playing and these yuppies near us were booing. I turned to the yuppies and said that if they didn't shut the fuck up that I was going to kick them in the face.  Then Fab said that he was going to go get Albert who was at home and Fab left.  Then Juliet started rolling around on the stage and Julian stood up and took off all of his clothes and he had little white underwear on.  He stood near the edge of the stage and there was a camera guy filming him, crotch shot.  Then Albert finally came out and said that the show was cancelled because they didn't feel like playing and he threw all of the ticket stubs into the audience and they walked off stage.  Then Sarah and I went back stage and my parents were there and they said, "You've been punk'd."  I was really pissed and embarassed so I ordered 6 different kinds of beer all at once and proceeded to drink them and spill them and hang out with the band.    I woke up laughing.    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A conversation that Avram and I are having over e-mail right now:     Sara:    I just saw Ed Norton!!!!     Avram:   oh my gosh!       where?       if you see him agian tell him wilde lake sucks and oakland mills rules!       also tell him he is awesome and gives hope to everyone from columbia, md        who wants to get it with hot chicks like selma hyak     S:   ok Avram i'll tell him     A:    awesome! you are the best where is he at? can i go take a picture of him on my camera phone? too cool invite him to lunch with us also     S:    actually we are going back to his hotel so  wont be able to make it to  lunch     A:   ask if i can come too     S:   It's a private engagement .    A:    wait a second why would the most famous Columbian, and the grandson of James Rouse, the founder of Columbia need to stay in a hotel in DC? that makes no sense.  thats like saying the queen of england needs a hotel when in manchester     S:    cuz he is a CELEBRITY     A:   would rudy guliani need a hotel room if he  was in long island? i dont think so better luck next time but if you are telling the truth ask if i can hang out too i can go chill in the lobby for an hour or so if you need private time     S:   i dont need you hanging around- he is only going to be here for tonite and then its back to la.  maybe he doesnt have time to see his family      A:   can i at least say hi to him you can call me if he's around it would mean a lot to me i bet he likes hearing from his subjects i mean fans from columbia     S:  i  bet he doesnt.  i dont know what you would say you asked schwartzmen when rushmore 2 was coming out   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just saw  urlLink  Ed Norton  in my building. He is incredibly hot in person.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       What are we gonna do now?   So says Liz:  1.	Here’s what I say, in number list: 2.	it is rishi’s birthday 3.	the hard tomorrows are an awesome band 4.	I need to give rob a key to my house 5.	if it’s raining how is the mammal going to get over to rishi’s anyway? 6.	remember you said you would never, ever go back to town hall again (meaning that you would not go back there for another three months).  Well that was on march 12 – three months and a few days ago.  I think it’s funny that there’s a good possibility that we’ll end up out there tonite. 7.	regardless, let’s hang out later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       An idea that I have proposed:   Dear Mike, Info and Liz:  My heart breaks when I hear of Bobby's troubles.  As the lead singer, he needs to be more careful, there are people out there who cannot wait for June 19 and 28 and they are waiting for Bobby.  I have seen the message board and I know about the Bobby fans (circa Army of Me.)  They don't know about the other members or the music, but as soon as the first note is played they will be hooked. These girls are crucial to the success of the Hard Tomorrows - they are the street team.  They spread the word to the people.    Also crucial to the success of the Hard Tomorrows is practice.  Since Bobby has been arrested and been in an accident, there is no way for the HTs to get to practice unless Mike takes the Oldsmobile out to DC and then back to Summerhaus - this involves stopping at Swann, Emerson and Hobart.    I would like to propose a deal to you, mike and info:  Meg Casablancas aka Sara Kaplan would like to offer her services(car) to the Hard Tomorrows.  If allowed to attend practice and act as liaison between the HTs and the fans, Meg would drive Bobby, Rishi and Manny to practice.  (I mean, you guys don't practice too much.)  As liaison, I would (during practice) answer fanmail/email, get the band to sign posters for the fanclub, publish the newsletter (liz would write the articles and sarah would take the pictures), etc.  Really the possibilities are endless.  I would like to follow in Juliet Joslin's footsteps (except I won't be marrying the HTs lead singer.)  This both provides to future success to the HTs and gives back to the fans.   its 11:22 and I have not done an ounce of work.  I am looking for a way out of the desk.  please help  -meg (superfan/asst. manager?)   Responses:   from liz:   Bunk this is very cute.    from mike:   well, the fanmail is getting overwhelming...   me and the cutlass S like yr ideas, we'd be forever indebted.    the bucolic splendor of summerhaus awaits you, who would hitch their sail to the winds of bobby. riberious chakramooga, your thoughts? viva la bobby, kit 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I should be sleeping.   Sarah and I stayed out way too late on Sunday night.  We were supposed to leave Baltimore after the Frequency finished playing, but we were waiting for AC to finish up with his stuff and then we were going to go and besides we were having way too much fun.  The second band that played were really horrible.  I couldn't stand them.  The Talking Head is cool because it has all these hidden rooms and little spaces and staircases that go up someplace and down another place.  They also have a really good jukebox with a lot of Sonic Youth in it.  I couldn't drink, since I had spent most of the weekend in either a state of being drunk or hungover and I was extremely tired.  So, I drank club sodas all nite.  When the third band went on, Warnock told us to go downstairs, and he was not wrong,  urlLink  Bobby Conn  was incredible.  Sarah described it as Rufus Wainwright meets the cast of Cats.  6-piece band in tracksuits, boys in skirts.  Glitter makeup.  We were completely blown away.  Warnock told us that they have been around for like 9 years.  Where the hell have we been?  People are always telling me that I have a knack for knowing about the next big thing, but this??  This IS the next big thing - almost.  I mean I want everyone to experience this band.  Sarah and I had to stand on a bench to see them and dance.  We kept looking at each other and shaking our heads in disbelief at how amazing they were.  After their set, we went to check out their merch.  Erin Worley bought us their CD and we finally got a copy of the Frequency.  At about 1:00 we decided that we were completely wiped out for the weekend, but Sarah was drunk now and it was hard to get her to leave.  She had to check out Sebastian in a speedo while he was drumming and then we left out one of the secret back staircases.    The ride home was interesting.  Sarah's job was to talk to me, because even though we were listening to Bobby Conn, I kept trying to doze off.  While on the BW Parkway I started talking to Sarah about the idea of the body not tiring.  It would be great if the human body did not require sleep.  I mean I love sleeping, but sometimes you feel like you loose important hours in the day.  It would be incredible if people did not get tired.  Think about the possibilities.  You could exercise all the time and not tire.  You could work 2 jobs.  You could go to work, come home, go out and then go to another job without ever breaking.  You could drive for hours and never shut your eyes, road trips without ever stopping except to go to the bathroom or get a snack.  As I was talking in depth about this to Sarah we passed our exit for Washington.  I was so tired and stupid.  Then we were hungry and Sarah had to pee.  I kept asking her if she wanted me to stop on the side of the road.  We were near Dream and I kept changing my mind that it probably wouldn't be the best idea.  Then we wanted snacks, but we didn't have any cash.  Finally, we found a Wendy's that was open, so she went in, but we didn't want to eat there.  But as soon as we left, we saw a McDonalds.  The drive-thru line was really long and we were only really waiting to see if they took credit, but I had a feeling that they didn't so we left.  The rest of the drive was very silly, we stopped at 7-11 for out snacks and walked home.  I felt drunk, even though I had only been drinking club sodas all night.  Maybe the only problem with the body not requiring sleep would be how would you recover from being drunk.  You really can only do this with sleep.  The alcohol needs to leave the body without you ever knowing, otherwise it would be hell.  That's why your body hurts so much the morning after you have been wasted.  The next day I left work early to go home and sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink  Juliet  is on the right.   The more and more I see pictures of Juliet, the more I like her.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For the record, Avram did not puke in the shower.  His sister did.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       On Friday night, it was pouring rain.  Liz, Sarah and I were planning to go out, but the rain was depressing so we decided to drink beer at home and go to the Raven.  We ended up playing Scrabble without keeping score, which so much better, you can really focus on the words that you make such as clit, vulgar and musketeer.  Then Anne Ray came over and we listened to Franz Ferdinand, The Killers and The Faint and attempted to find a good place in DC to dance to rock music.  We realized that they is no such place and went to Mantis instead.  I wore my white Pierre Cardin jacket which is so 80s and so HOT.  It had stopped raining, so we walked.  Mantis is super trendy, but super lame and super empty.  So we strolled down 18th, ran into Rishi, debated where to go and decided on the Ghana Cafe and danced to dance hall music upstairs and a reggae cover band downstairs.  The evening ended back at my house, where Kelly met up with us and told us about her nite at Cafe Citron.  Eventually, we were all too wasted to stay up any longer.    Saturday morning was very hard.  I woke up with a headache, met Liz and Perry at Dos Gringos, where we ran into Kelly who was trying to jog, but couldn't without her head hurting.  I was having trouble with just drinking my latte.  Sarah and I spent the rest of the day driving around Bethesda and sitting at Bubbe's pool.  By the time we got back home, I was such a wreck.  I had no energy and it was 7 PM and I still had a headache.  Apparently, the cure was a combo of Aleve, meat and beer.  BBQ at Perry's on his new grill.  Sean, Ben and Avram were there and at 12:00 we headed over to the Raven where we met up with Kelly.    Things started to get really nuts around 1:00 a.m.  Shots every 15 minutes.  We were celebrating Avram's birthday a few days early and Kelly told him that if he took the silver birthday banner off the wall and took of his shirt and wrapped it around him that she would buy him a bottle of rum.  So . . . he did it.  And then everyone started taking off their shirts and pulling down their pants and it was crazy.  We were all dancing in the small space in the Raven.  Avram and Perry took turns "macking" on this girl, Marion.  Perry made out with her, Avram got the digits.  Avram was more wasted than I have ever seen him, and we left the bar at 3:00 stood around outside for a bit.  There was no way that Sarah and I were letting Av crash on our extra mattress, too drunk.  So we went down to the diner to fill him belly and send him on his way.  He was such a mess, he kept getting really outraged or really sad.  And it was totally annoying.  I had to yell at him a bunch.  I am such a trooper because I can drink and drink and drink and leave the bar completely sober, well not sober, but not acting like an idiot. So I can apologize to people for his behavior, which is completely embaressing, but completely necessary.  I left the diner with a milkshake, a drunk roommate, and a belligerent drunk.  On the corner, there about 10 cops arresting about 4 men.  Avram felt the need to start yelling, "this is infringements on their civil rights" really loud right in front of the cops.  They started looking at him and I thought that they were about 5 seconds away from arresting him.  We told him to shut the fuck up, but he just said it again, but louder.  Then Sarah attacked him with her purse, which made the strap break again.  We basically had to leave  Avram on the street and walk away, but we knew he would catch up - he was just acting like a drama queen.  Avram left, I called him to make sure that he got home okay - he did.  I had a great nite!!      Epilogue:   Sarah woke up for work and I drove her there.   Avram puked in the shower this morning.   I had a bass lesson at 1:00 at Ben's.   We designed the flier for his show.   I have to go get ready to go to Baltimore for a BBQ with the Frequency and Trans Am. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally a  urlLink  picture  to post from the Boston show.  That is Julian.  And you can see ME in the background (in the top left, I am turned around, but I am right behind Julian's head, I see my earring and my bag.)  Totally fucking awesome dude.  I am stoked, but I am getting yelled at by Liz for listening to her ask me where we can go dance to Franz Ferdinand.  So I got to go.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Not to be redundant, but ...    I just found this pic of Julian's fiancée, Juliet.   Just thought you would like to see my competition. Happy Friday. Hand me a beer.     
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       You've Been Bamboozled!   It was cool and quiet, the complete opposite of what I expected.  I thought that it would be hot and crowded.  The weather that arrived on June 6 was the perfect condition to complement Asbury Park and the music that we were going to listen to.     Ambulance LTD.  I just cannot get enough of that guitar wanking at the end of  Yoga Means Union .  It gives me such an adrenaline rush during the build up to the end of the song.  It's great.  Also great, is Benji Lysaght, the adorable dinerboy-resembling guitarist.  Liz yelled at me in Tower the other nite for singling out these bandboys and obsessing over them.  Is this concept something new for her?  Liz has known me for like 6 years, she should already know that I do this.  Marcus, the leadsinger, was a little peeved because his mic had a lot of feedback.  I didn't think that this really effected their performance, it sounded fantastic to me.  This performance made it the 4th time I have seen them and it just gets better and better each time.  Liz noted later in the evening how their label, TVT Records, whores them out.  They were promoting the disc by having Ambulance stand around near the merch table and sign stuff.  Mostly aging indie rockers were going up and whispering in Marcus and Benji's ears and posing for pics and having CDs signed.   Stellastarr*  I saw this band before when Ambulance and The Killers opened for them at the Black Cat.  To me they are a combo of Interpol and Hot Hot Heat, except they have this hot female bassist, Amanda, who is my new inspiration.  I have decided to take real bass lessons because I realized that I have listened to music for so long and now it is time to take it to the next level.       French Kicks  FK had been wandering around all day with their girlfriends.  Pretty little NYC indie rock chicks.  Mike pointed out that the new New York style was hooded sweatshirts with blazers over them.  Benji was sporting this look as was Matthew Stinchcomb (such an awesome fucking name)except his blazer was seersucker.  They turned a bubble machine on during their set and their new songs sounded so good in the air floating around with the bubbles.  I took some really nice pics with the waterproof disposable camera that Liz bought for me.  I really need to purchase a digital so that I can post pics here.  When FK were done with their set Liz went up to Josh Wise and asked him why they don't play China Girl (she had seen them perform this on Last Call a few months ago.  Liz loves China Girl.)  Josh said that it was a one time thing.     Waiting for Sonic Youth  There were a few other acts to see before Sonic Youth played, but I was drinking a lot of Bud and drifting around aimlessly checking out the hippie vendors and the merch table, talking to the mammal on the phone.  She had to report to me that she had just passed the Unicorns on 14th Street and she didn't recognize them at first because pretty lips cut his hair, but then she noticed lil shrimpy checking her out.  Mike and Liz had posted up under a tent and were listening to My Morning Jacket - who I can only describe as hippie rock - but I liked them.  I also checked out some of the other acts:  Jesse Malin, Patti Smith and Dios.  During this waiting period I smoked all my cigarettes and was getting progressively more drunk, so the thought of running out was disturbing me.  Unfortunately, the cig machine in the Stone Pony was broken, so we went next door to the Golddigger.  The Golddigger is a local townie bar.  Liz and I had a few beers here before the Strokes show in 2001.  In 2001, George Harrison had just died the day before, so all the news stories on tv and music on the jukebox reflected everyone's sadness (george was always my favorite Beatle.)  This time there was just a gross couple sitting at that the bar that was making out in a very "get a room" way.  However, the cigarette machine was also broken at the Golddigger, so we were told to go next door to the hotel.  As we approached the hotel, we realized that this was just another condemned Asbury Park building, but I heard some sort of party going on around back and led Liz and Mike under an archway of the building to a field.  As I suspected there was a party going on behind the hotel, a LGBT party (there were a lot of festivals going on Asbury Park that day.)  The party was spilling out of a niteclub called  urlLink  Paradise  that was the only part of the hotel that was open.  And it was a gay club.  So I am sent in to purchase our cigs and they are $7 and the only ones that they have left are Lucky Strikes, which I find out are toasted and actually really fun to smoke.  On the way back we stopped back at the Golddigger this time for a beer.  It was around 8:00 p.m. The beer here was cheaper and I realized that I had been drinking since 3:00 and that I was pretty drunk.   Sonic Youth  It was dark out.  Ambulance and FK were nowhere in site.  They must have made an early escape from Asbury Park, back to NYC.  I sat on a counter waiting for Liz and Mike to come back outside and waiting for Sonic Youth to start playing.  Liz has been obsessed with Sonic Youth since before I met her.  And she and Kyle were always trying to push SY on me like drugs.  I was blown away by their performance.  Maybe listening to them secondhand for 6 years really affected me.  Maybe all the bud I had been drinking all day really affected me, but I was so happy that Kim and Thurston were on stage and singing their songs.    Aftermath  Liz busted out the dictophone - I interviewed Liz and Mike on bands and fans and fashion, but mostly I talked about myself and Julian, and reenacted my Julian moment on Mike.  (Liz may or may not transcribe the tapes on her blog.) I tried to convince Liz and Mike that we should stay for the group jam, but Mike said that it was going to be a bunch of hippies and that we had to go. Mike drove home, which was good, cuz I was a MESS.   We decided to get stoned in the car.   I put on  Is This It?   I felt like we were either on the way to my funeral or on a highway to space.  (Everything gets weird and foggy after this and most of the following has been retold to me from either Liz or Mike.  Some of this I remember in bits as the days pass.) We weren't even out of NJ when I told Mike to pull over.  I think we were on 66.  I opened the door, thought I was going to puke, but I think that the fresh air on my face revived me for the time being.  I was falling in and out of sleepmodes.  But somewhere along the NJ turnpike I started yelling at Mike to pull over again and since he was stoned and paranoid and thought that if we pulled over on 95 that we would get arrested.  So he made me wait until he pulled into the upcoming rest stop.  I kept yelling that if he didn't pull over now that I was going to die.  He handed me a plastic grocery bag that Liz realized that I wasn't going to want.  I can't do it like that.  So we made it to the rest stop and then for some reason Mike had to park and not just stop where I wanted him to, so finally ran out and puked (got a little on my shoe) and got back in the car.  I think I passed out shortly after that.  The next thing I remember was waking up at another rest stop at a gas pump.  Liz was in the front seat and I was in the back and Mike was not in the car and I got really freaked out and started screaming Mike's name out the window, as if he had abandoned us.  I think I may have passed out again before he even got back in the car.  Apparently, I was really bad at changing the CDs, since I would pass out as soon as I put one in.  Liz told me that Mike made her talk to him so that he wouldn't fall asleep at the wheel and she was just telling him random things.  Eventually, I woke up with a second wind and Liz passed out and I think I started telling Mike random things.  I don't know how he dealt with us all day.  But really, Liz and I are fun to take on road trips, we really are. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My stamp has worn off and I cut my wristbands off on Monday nite.  I made it through Monday at work, even though I couldn't decide what would be worse: to go home early or drop dead at my desk.  On Saturday nite, Mike and I drove up to Baltimore to rendezvous with Liz at the Ottobar to see  urlLink  The Unicorns .  Liz had been in West Virginia for 24 hours at a family reunion.  The show was great.  It was so fun to be reunited with Liz and help her out of rainy family hell.  The Unicorns was the best relief for this, and it was relief for us all.  Nick, Alden and Jaime (otherwise known as Pretty lips, lil shrimpy and big & crazy) were so great!!!!  Better than the last time we saw them.  Shrimpy had so much stage presence this time and pretty lips cut his hair and big & crazy was still big, but not so crazy.  After the show I told pretty lips that they were so great and their show was more professional and that I saw them in February (maybe january) and that show was so crazy.  And pretty lips agreed that last show was insane (I mean some mullet wig wearing dude spit beer on me and the mammal.)  I told him that I was on my way to Asbury Park for the Great Bamboozle.  He was really interested in this and I told him about it and overall it was lovely to chat with the cute Canadian.  After the show, we met up with Mike's friend Brian also know as the Ghoul.  We followed him back to his apartment in Towson where we got really stoned and watched the Chris Cunningham DVD of music videos.  This proceeded to scare the shit out of me, with the exception of the Madonna video.  Most of the videos on the DVD were Aphex Twin and possibly the scariest things ever created in life.  I don't know what is wrong with Cunningham.  Around 4 am we realized that it was time for bed.  I slept on an egg crate in a burrito sleeping bag.  I woke up to the sound of an owl alarm coming out of Mike's phone.  I was really excited for the trip up to Asbury Park and THE STONE PONY.  This is the place where Liz and I first lost our shit.  We saw the Strokes there in 2001 and have never had such an experience since, (I will blog more about losing our shit in Asbury Park later.)  Finally, Liz and Mike awoke and we left.  Stopped for some Starbucks and we were on the way. Mike rode shotgun and Liz sat in the back and played with origami, wrote a letter to her aunt and changed the CDs.    When we got to Asbury Park we were hungry and we spent an hour driving around trying to find this diner that Liz and I had ate at the last time we were there.  But for some reason we couldn't find it.  There was a good possibility that it closed.  The thing about Asbury Park is that most of the buildings are closed and condemmed.  This adds a mysterious vibe to the town and makes you very nostalgic for the past.  You can imagine how the place used to be when Springsteen ruled and people would stay at the Metropolitan Hotel and play on the Boardwalk.  But now it is rundown and gloomy, and basically a ghost town.  The sky was grey and as soon as I hopped out of the car tears welled up in my eyes as I remembered the last time we were there.  To be continued tomorrow...  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       24 Hour Bamboozling   I still have the word savage stamped on my right hand.   I still have two wristbands on my arm.   I might even still be drunk.    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The first picture from John and Kelly&#39;s Birthday Blowout.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MK is  urlLink out.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Got my hotfit all ready for Kelly and John's party!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Okay,     wow    look   at all the    f  u  n   s  t  u ff you can   do   with    Blogger     now.    &nbsp;   AW  E S O  ME!    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    With the underage girls at the beach: Tara, Liz, Me, Double EE, Run Run and Britt  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Run Run, Me and Britt during our pre-fireworks Power Hour.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Liz kept time while she talked to Mike on the phone and even made a trip to the bathroom.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Don't know about the future, that's anybody's guess.   I have been watching I love the 90's all week.  My favorite thing about these shows that VH-1 produces is MO ROCCA, media gadfly.  I want to marry this man and have little baby gadflies.  Sarah is planning to marry Michael Ian Black.  And we all can live happily ever after in medialand.   urlLink Sara  has brought to my attention that they have left out the suicide of Kurt Cobain in 1994.  This was huge!!!  It defined the generation.  Another thing that was my life in the early 90's was Blossom.     I was the biggest Blossom fan ever.  I have about 4 video tapes of Blossom episodes including the Blossom movie, which takes place in Paris.  I was obsessed with Joey Lawrence.  I belonged to his fan club and one wall of my room in 6th and 7th grade was plasted with pictures of Joey.  WHOA!  In 6th grade, I dressed like Blossom.  I wore the hats, the weird clothes, everything.  I was always voted Best Dressed in ever Slam Book.  I memorized almost every single episode.  My best friend, Diana, and I could recite the episodes line for line.       So, VH-1, where the hell is Blossom?  "Whoa" was a huge piece of pop culture in the 90s, how can you just ignore this fact?  ---------------------------------------------------------------------- Okay, let's talk about Slam Books, while we are on the topic.  Do you remember these things?  They were huge in 6th grade (1991-1992). You would get a spiral notebook and number each page and then put a topic at the top of each page.  The first page was always your name.  The following pages would be things like your favorite song, actor, actress, where you want to live, Best dressed, Best Hair, Best Whatever.  Then you would fill out your self as number one and then pass it around your class.  It was fun to get the book back at the end of the day and read what people wrote.  Some page were "draw me a picture" or "write me a note."  I miss Slam Books, I might try and bring these back.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Happy Hour at the Reef.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    My roommate and Warnock.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Let the kids dance!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    What are we gonna do now?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Reasons why Ben Vivari is the best date in town.   1.  Picks you up on time and offers to come inside. 2.  Drives you to the 9:30 Club and gets a spot right out front. 3.  Takes you to find a bar, but since none are open at 6 PM takes you on a little walk instead. 4.  Gets you into the 9:30 Club to see Washington Social Club and Phantom Planet (he works the ticket window on Mondays and Tuesdays.) 5.  The bartender is so excited to see him that she says whatever we want all nite is free, "top shelf, whatever you want." 6.  Takes you to the VIP section. 7.  Makes funny jokes about the crowd and the bands and keeps you entertained before the set. 8.  Watches your seat when you go to the bathroom. 9.  Stays through some of Phantom Planet's set when he really hates them and is too cool to even be there anymore. 10.    urlLink    Ben.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       There's a lot to make me crazy, and a lot is always going on.   This past week was bullshit.  My vacation was great and relaxing, but of course as soon as you go back to real life it is always the same.  Tuesday morning someone that I have had a major crush on for months deleted me as his friendster, after we had only been friendsters for a week.  I guess he couldn't handle the pretty innocent message that I sent him or he was just an asshole!  It was a big kick in my face and of course I had to cry about that at my desk for a little bit.  The positive outcome of it was that it made me realize that what everyone was saying for months, that he was crazy and not good for me, was true.  I feel good about it now, I think I am finally ready to get him out of head, for the most part.    On Wednesday, I had the worst cramps ever in the world.  They hit me around 3:30 p.m. and I had to stay at work until 6;00 p.m. because it was just me and another assistant in the office and she was leaving at 4:30 and someone always has to be at their desk to answer phones until 6:00.  So after that I came home and went immediately to bed.  Sarah came in my room at 10:00 p.m. and woke me up, she didn't know if I was home or not and my light was on.  When I looked at the clock I freaked and out and shot straight up and couldn't believe that I was late for work.  Sarah has to reassure me that it was 10:00 at night.  Then I got up for a little and then read in bed and was asleep around 1:30 a.m.    Thursday morning I felt great and had a pretty good day, until late in the afternoon, when I had to tell people at work that they were being contradictory in their email.  For some reason, this one person would not listen to me and I had to control my anger over that.  I am smarter than a lot of people in my office, but since I don't know jack shit about Compensation they don't take my opinion seriously and think I am stupid.  Wrong - asshole.  Anyway after that, I went to happy  hour, which turned into happy nite. It started at the Reef on the roof - me, Sarah, Kelly, Pri, John and Liz.  Then Caroline met us and we went over the Asylum for snacks.  I had already had 3 beers at the Reef.  As Caroline and I were walking over to B&K for cigarettes, I saw aforementioned ex-crush walk into his place of employment across the street.  I had to freak out for a minute, but then I was over that.  At Asylum, we had a quick beer and bite to eat.  Everything is quick at Asylum because they play this crazy metal music that possesses your soul and makes you stand up and punch your fists in the air as your head has to flair around.  We knew we had to get of there quick.  I kept trying to say that we should take a shot and then throw the shot glasses across the room against the wall.  Kelly had the password to get into Heaven's 80s nite for free, so we decided to do that.  At some point Caroline had given me a Xanax. We danced in front of the John Hughes movies at 80s nite and it made me very happy until, I started to get done with dancing and Caroline drove me home.  I had to cry a little in the car, that's what xanax does to me, make me all emotional and crazy.  Then I went to bed.    The next morning I woke up with the most massive headache and had to call in sick for work.  I literally could not walk into the light, it hurt so much.  Then I spent the rest of the morning in various positions on the matress and in the bathroom throwing up until most of stomach lining was in the toilet.  I know that is pretty graphic, but I felt like shit.  Then I went into work like a real trooper.  Because I had left the other assistant there all by herself and I knew she had to leave at 4:30.  I got a lot of sympathy from people when I told them about my headache, but really I had been fucked up all morning and I felt guilty.  But they put me through so much shit there that I didn't feel that bad.    Friday nite I took it easy and stayed in a watch cheesy dating shows and cleaned my room.  I felt a lot better, but I realized why I always go out, because those dating shows make you feel depressed and that's all that's really on tv on Friday.  I always feel so much better when I clean my room.  I woke up this morning feeling well rested with no alcohol in my body.  It felt really fucking great.  I met Kelly for coffee and I didn't even drink coffee (I didn't need it for a first).  Instead I had a soy chai, now I am waiting for Sarah to come home so that we can go to the pool.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Don't forget to vote for Reizou as your favorite local DC band.  Vote  urlLink here .
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I give it a day before  urlLink this  shit  BLOWS UP !!!  My mom was right, DC is the 2nd best place in the US for singles. (Denver is #1.)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Report - What I Did On My Vacation by S. Kaplan   I am back from the beach.  It was fun.  I have a tan.  The ocean is pretty.   I got drunk.  I watched fireworks.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The OC   Liz and I are off for the beach in a few short hours.  Currently, I am doing laundry and kicking myself for thinking that it was Friday all day and that the bank would be open until 7:00 only to realize that its Thursday, dumbass.  So, I have $7 for this evening, can you even get anywhere these days with that little cash in your wallet.  Things may get a little out of control, but ya know, that's how we roll.  I want a report on Skinner if anyone goes to see him tonite.  peace.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Weird Stuff   I had the most bizarre dream last nite.  I dreamt that my pointer finger nail was decaying and under it were all these sugar crystals that looked like clear little fish eggs, but they were sugar.  People were telling me that I should pull off the nail so that it could heal, but I was afraid to do that.  I have a real low tolerancy for pain.  Finally, the nail came off with ease. There was another nail underneath.  The strange thing was that the nail came off with part of the skin on my finger, but the skin that came off was plastic, like a mannequin.  The skin underneath of the plastic was new and smooth, but now I had webbed fingers.  Throughout the dream the webbed part of the finger continued to grow, but now I had mini fingers coming out of the main fingers.  I had about 8 fingers on that one hand.  I might have to try and draw a picture of this for you, so you can really see what I am talking about.  Last nite I had to park my car on Mt. Pleasant Street in between Hobart and Irving.  On my walk to the car this morning I saw bird brains laying next to the dead bird they came from covered in blood in the Irving Alley.  In the Mt. Pleasant Deli, at 9am, as I was purchasing my juice, a man was buying a six-pack of Natty Ice. But what really takes the cake for me, is what I saw yesterday on my drive home from work.  I was stopped at a light and saw on the left a few people crossing the street in front of my car toward a group of little boys.  I would guess that these boys were about ten years old.  There were two boys standing near a hedge close to the corner and a kid on his skateboard going up the corner near a big computer box.  Just as a man finished crossing the road, this adorable little messy haired boy jumped out of the box and screamed and startled the man.  It was hilarious.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Some necessary recaps:   On Wednesday nite, Kelly, Liz and I went to Jaleo for a Spanish Moment continued. We drank 2 pitchers of Sangria, ate some yummy tapas, talked about our problems and I cried at the table. ay! It poured periodically throughout dinner. After we finished all the of the fruit in our Sangria and it stopped raining we paid the bill and headed off the Rhumba Cafe on 18th Street to meeting Sarah, EW and Warnock.  Our loud drunken table pissed off our waitress, but we racked up a $200 bill drinking Mojitos.  Then off to Toldeo, where we cleared out the bar, did some shots and ruled the jukebox.  When the bar closed I thought that it was a good idea to go over to AC and EWs for the post party. We listened to the Killers and downloaded Ashlee Simpson songs. Finally, a cab was called for me and I headed home.  The next morning when I woke up I was still drunk, but I made it into work on time and was hungover and spacey the rest of the day. OMG!  Thursday nite, Liz finally got me to watch Swimfan with her.  Friday after work, I met up with Paul and Tom at Austin Grill and then I kidnapped them to join me at Saint Ex for Anne Ray's going away happy hour. We stopped at my house to smoke a bowl and then walked down to Saint Ex with Liz. Met up with Sarah, Liz Ruby and Kyle. I broke the news about Julian's engagement and everyone thinks I have my chance now. At some point, Paul disappeared and was never to be found again that nite (it turns out that he took a phone call outside and just decided not to come back in and went home.)  After Saint Ex, Liz, Tom and I walked to Adams Morgan, called Avram and had some drinks at Asylum. Liz got in a funk and left before Avram got there. Av finished the last of her beer and we went over to Toledo. I was starting to fade, but played MASH with Av and Tom. Av's future looks great, something about being a comedian who drives a tank and marries a Skupas sister. Tom's was not as great, he married some girl from high school and drives a Taurus in DC.  Walking home, we ran into the diner boy, who told  ME  that  I  looked fucked up. HA!!!  Saturday was a lovely day. Shopped at pop, went to Cob's tea party, back to Pop for cocktails and then off to The Side Bar in Baltimore for Caroline's boyfriend's hardcore show. The thing about hardcore music is that the instruments are punk rock (I like them) and the singer is more like screaming (and I don't like it.) Basically, hardcore is for angry teens who flail around. It's pretty interesting, not scary like I thought it would be. I apparently missed a pretty fun and long nite in DC. When I got home I called Liz and Sarah and when they called me back I was in my room blasting Ashlee Simpson (Caroline gave me her burnt CD.) They were having a big crazy postparty/danceparty.  I was glad that I didn't stay out until 3am, because I had a lovely Sunday of sleeping in a going to the National Gallery of Art East Building. I starred at some beautiful paintings:     urlLink      Brice Marden, For Pearl 1970  
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       BREAKING NEWS - THIS JUST IN  (thanks to  urlLink Gawker  and  urlLink  Sara )   'Stroke'  Julian Casablancas  Back To Banging Groupies?  We shed a few tears when we heard New York's pride and joy, The Strokes' Julian Casablancas, drunkenly announced his engagement to the band's assistant manager, Juliet Joslin. How could he leave us like that? It totally hurt us, like, bad. We even took down the JC poster hanging over the bed and burned all of our Strokes t-shirts! A music spy informs us, however, that perhaps our great unwashed proto-hipster is back on the market:  Julian Casablancas may be single again. The word is that he and Juliet Joslin have called off the engagement but remain friends.  Yeah, we didn't see that coming.    This gives me reason to get really fucked up on this gorgeous August day, just like Julian would. HAPPY FRIDAY!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I totally had to steal the new Paris Hilton  urlLink song   from  urlLink Stereogum's blog  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Photo of the Day (from Washingtonpost.com)    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have some things to say:  1. I take back what I said yesterday about Craig Kilborn. The man, although a pompous dick, is hilarious. Besides Ambulance LTD, the highlight of the show was the interview with Ling Bai, starring in the new Spike Lee Joint  urlLink She Hate Me . She did not speak English very well, but described how when she met Spike she offered her ideas for a sex scene which involved her making out with chicken feet. Spike liked her ideas and she was hired. Craig asked her how she came up with that idea, was it from her culture or from her brain. Then she described how a litle spirit in a mini skirt talks to her and told her about it. This mini-skirt spirit also tells her what to wear. In fact, the spirit was sitting on Craig's shoulder, which prompted him to ask if she was naked. Totally bizarre and totally hilarious.  2. I was in Florida this past weekend and I would like to share a little story about a bird with you. There are tons of wild birds roaming/flying around in Florida. While I was there I saw pelicans and cranes and weird ducks. BUT, I also saw a peacock. This bird is amazing. I have never seen one out and about. I was in the car with my parents when I spotted it. My dad was just about to make a left turn onto the main road from a parking lot. I told him to wait a minute so we could watch the bird. So we watched as it looked both ways and crossed the road. Then it started coming closer to our car. Actually, it came right up to our car window. That's when my mom and I started freaking out and yelled at my dad to close the windows. We were thisclose to being pecked by this crazy bird. (Once I had a dream that I was being pecked by a duck.)  3. I might have posted about this before, but what could be better than a film written by Richard Kelly (Donnie Darko) and directed by Eli Roth (Cabin Fever)? The film is called  The Box . It revolves around an unhappy married couple who receive a small wooden box on their doorstep. At the push of a button, the box brings its bearer instant wealth but also instantly kills someone the bearer doesn't know.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The music of Ambulance, as described by Craig Kilborn's producer:  "Amazing," "It's the Beatles meets Mozart meets Chaka Khan."
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I totally missed   Ambul  ance     LTD   on Letterman the other night. Bummer!  But, I have a second chance. Tonight they will be on Kilborn. I hate him, but I love them, so it's a fair trade off.  Also, don't forget that the   French   Kicks   are the house band on Last Call Tuesday - Friday.  And finally, check out my upcoming shows list, as I have done some research today and have found that  ALL  of my favorite bands are playing shows in the area soon.  Oh my gawd!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>