<Blog>







<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink MAHARAJIBLOG  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A book I am enjoying at the moment: The No.1 Ladies' Detective Agency- Alexander McCall Smith 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    click on the pictures to make them larger&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "So make the effort to be fulfilled and enjoy yourself. Enjoy this Life. You will appreciate more and more. Don't waste another moment on a wasted moment. That's what we do. We waste one moment and then we waste four more on that moment. Go forward"  -Prem Rawat Amaroo, 2004   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    the most important&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Bonjour I don't know why but I can't post on the navire blog,  technical problem.  so you can see the new cards for us on this new blog.  Thank you, but you can see the other too.   http://present2.blogspot.com/   Marie  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thank you...to whoever changed the google ads.&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Learn&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Magpie&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    globe&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Our privilege&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There is always a time when someone comes to terms with existence and recognizes the magic of this breath. Of course for some it's no surprise that we wake up and go on doing our dayly routine. But for the one who's life is a gift and knows its value, the surprise is always a pleasant one.  One day we may fall asleep for good and never wake up again. Same goes for our consciousness. That is the reason why, at times, I need to feel awaken and surprised. It's human nature to know and to feel this magic. I only have a prayer... please keep me always conscious of the gift I have when at times I may forget its value. Always let me rejoice for this existence you've given me. Always let me have gratitude and recognize where I am truly coming from. Because this is where I reside...inside... my true home.   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Photos by Kay&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    "Give God the Glory"&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There is one that keeps coming up at the top about God. I clicked on it, and at the start, it has an interesting concept to ponder on. It is something like, whatever you do, do it for the glory of God...eg. eating, etc.  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Follow&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Click on the title for the             WEBSITE OF MAHARAJI 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thoughts&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   http://navire.blogspot.com  If you want you can take here cards.  I do it for us.  If you have a problem with it  please say me,  because it is new for me.  Marie  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Permanent spectacle&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For me, when I tune into the source of appreciation, the more I find I am able to enjoy what's around me in greater depth. This blog is a space for people to post, or enjoy visual creations (text too), and other things they enjoy. 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The words of peace are seeds, which germinate in the compost of our heart. When we feel vagueness in our soul, let us suspend the instant and with respect and grace, let us choose one inspiration from the river of the breath, that one very particular, which carries us to our secret garden, where we can admire the small growths of serenity. And if the feeling delights us, then to talk of all these inspirations  which become a permanent spectacle .  Marie    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi ... first just wished to thank-you for the invitation.  Any opportunity to express is a joy to me.  There is so much fulfillment flooding our individual doorsteps, that one has to allow that outlet to pour, so more joy can enter our domains.  I know that when we share in the moment the love that has been revelaed to us, it only brightens us further, as we enter that light that has infinite capacity.  In a world starving for this experience, it would be the ultimate level of selfishness if we did not allow it to be brought forth out into the public domain.  However really there is nowhere we cannot be where this love is not.   Just sometimes we can laser that concentration so it becomes more obvious.  So may we shine ... and in so doing assist in this noble endeavor to light the lamps that stand in wait, for just one strike of that matchless match. 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   HELLO Kay, it is a nice idea for you to do this blogger. Thank you. I understand now. Marie 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...the inner experience is enjoyable.  ( Of course other things are enjoyable too, but everyone already knows that!) 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This blog is for fun! 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Step by step&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Inestimable  existence&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..the steps &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    River 2&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The River&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..to the River&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Tree by the River&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    HOW BEAUTIFUL IT IS !&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "There is a joy, and it is the joy of existence—not what is happening in existence. They are two different things. There is the joy of existence, and then there is the joy of what is happening in existence. What is happening in existence we try to control and manipulate.   Sometimes things go our way. Sometimes they don't.  But then there is another joy. That joy has been there through all the years of your life, waiting to be discovered. And that joy will be there for as long as you live. It is the simple, simple joy of being alive.   In my life, there are good days and there are bad days. The days I call good are the days when everything goes according to my plan. The days when things do not go according to my plan, I call bad. Yet every day that I have been given is above and beyond being good and bad. Each one has its own meaning and its own beauty. And I can get in touch with that beauty. My plans will change. Sometimes the days I call bad actually end up being good. And some days when everything looks like it is going according to my plan turn out to be a disaster.   Good and bad. Life is not just about good and bad—it is beyond that. When we begin to understand that, we begin to understand that it is a privilege to be alive. It is a privilege for which this heart needs to be filled with gratitude. What we have been given is far more precious than all the good and the bad put together. All of that is transitory.   We can know that which isn't transitory, that which will be here as long as we are alive. That is our solace. That is our harbor. That is where we need to be when the storms come." -Prem Rawat(from Inspire newsletter 17)   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Love per se, needs no words, to speak Love expresses itself through a different medium Love speaks from the heart The heart speaks Love, it travels from one heart to another Only the heart can recognize,  and detect its presence Love is within, And without boundaries   Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The day ...  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We're not that different extrait de Inspire  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Gerber daisy&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Gerbera&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Gerbera bud&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Lavender- National flower of Portugal?...CONGRATULATIONS!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Not Wimbledon...&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Love is within, and Love is without boundaries      Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Picture (Marie and Kay)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     That's better.....yes,4 goals!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Welcome-Flowers for Lou&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   BEBE LOU  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Pansy flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..should have chosen cream for the colour of the words?(first time I have  put words on a picture though)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Bee&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Orange Poppy&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Listen to Prem Rawat speak on this radio station. 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Love watching clouds move!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     Sky 687&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Sky &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    One for the English football fans!...or should I say 3 &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Peace  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A NEW SITE : MAHARAJI EN FRANCE 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Make Peace&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A practical way&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Not one for the fans ( unless you are French!)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   YES  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   .....to be alive, and conscious?!! 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Little riddle  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..nice red colour&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    one for the fans&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   DANSE  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Inspire  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is the feeling you feel anyway,  when the words make no sense.  Not hindered by meaning, or concepts, or reason  Not to be distracted  following 'trains of thought'.  Free from the constraints of mental understanding  to absorb uncensored, undiluted, the atmosphere of love  the feeling  The language of love, beyond all words.      Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink      My cat...&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "People travel to wonder at the height of the mountains,  at the huge waves of the sea, at the long course of the rivers, and the vast compass of the ocean, at the circular motion of the stars,  and yet pass by themselves without wondering."   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "One joy dispels a hundred cares."    -Confucius 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   LOVE  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Nice day..&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Big family!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Swans and geese&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A nearby river&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A wonderful day (Kay and marie)  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Apprécier  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Rhododendron&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Red Poppy&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Anemone &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   HAVE ....  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Knowledge  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Grace   Grace is a word in the dictionary Grace is a concept Grace is a feeling Grace carries you when you can't walk the extra mile Grace is one step ahead Grace is a helping hand to grow, even when it doesn't look like it Grace is the invisible hand of love Grace is tangible Grace is kindness Grace Is compassion Grace is Love     Kay     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Ducks&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Deer &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A stream&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Le mot joie me va  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   LOVE from kay et Marie  urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   GO ...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Bougie&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   GO ....&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ....the turning point in a still world.   Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   To live in the moment Within each breath of life Tuning in to the life force, here and now Not to be living for the future, or the past But to let go to be here now, and be aware of it No baggage to carry In the moment, inside each breath, In each moment of time The timelessness within the moment the still point in a turning world.      Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The evening sky&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Love&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A park near to where I live(photo-Kay)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers( photo-Kay)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   MEMO (Kay et marie)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   NO WORDS&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ONE TRUTH&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ENJOY (Marie et kay)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    SNOW&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    PRECIOUS&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    FW: Subject: A Small Favor to Ask I'm going away for a while and wonder if you could water my plants in my absence. Thanks in advance.  urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A way in a beautiful garden&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Palavas les Flots&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Palavas Les Flots in france from Patrick&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Hydrangea&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     A painting by Stojan&nbsp; urlLink       

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    War and Peace( Stojan), translated from Slovenian: Vojna in mir  Èe noèem biti  v notranji vojni, je mir nekaj, kar moram poèeti zdaj.&nbsp; urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Know Yourself ( by Prabhat)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Peace is inside every human heart(Prabhat)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    From my friend Fabienne&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    I Love You&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thanks for saying YES to the photo.To start with it was going to be a photo of just the sign, but a human being is more beautiful than a sign or any scenery&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Love&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A joy within &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    water lily&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ..."We have to be strong in this world. To be safe, to be conscious, to be real in this life comes from inside. I can’t fix the political system. What I can do is help people get in touch with their heart. I go around the world telling people they can have peace in their life. I started helping people when I was very young, and this is what I’ve been doing all my life. The dream was to be able to go from place to place, village to village—and that is becoming a reality.  Every day is new. And that’s wonderful. Enjoy your life, every moment. That’s how it should be. Don’t lose the shield of hope. Learn how to hold onto it. You want that hope.  Sadness will always be there; sadness doesn’t go away. All the sadness that you will ever feel is within you. And all the love that you will ever feel is within you. It just depends which door you want to open.  You have everything. Let me help you discover all those things again, how to hold onto the shield of hope. The world has pushed it away. But every day we can have hope. We can learn to smile again. We don’t have to be sad. I can’t tell anybody that their business will be better. But I know one thing: a centered person is what the whole world is looking for, because that’s what we all need. So, just enjoy the ride..."  -Prem Rawat (from Inspire 14)     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     water lily&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Pottery France south&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ..."You are beautiful. Why are you beautiful? You are beautiful because you are alive, not because of what you have accomplished. That’s not what makes you beautiful. You are beautiful because this breath—the most divine gift of all—comes into you. This breath comes in unchallenged, without judgment of good or bad, right or wrong. Every day, every moment, it comes into you—as personal as it possibly can be, touching only you. You can be in a room full of a hundred thousand people, and it will come and touch you. It will come and enter you. It will come and bless you.  Many people will tell you what you are not. I am here to tell you everything that you are. People will tell you everything that's wrong with you. I am here to tell you everything that is right with you.  Remember when you were a baby? I don’t know when you realized you existed. It was probably at a very young age. “I am here.” The world revolved around you. You didn’t know that, but it did. It was day, and you opened your eyes and you looked. In great majesty, you accepted this day because it was not for anyone else but you. Ideas of other people weren't there. You had no inhibitions. You had an incredible passion for one thing. It is what helped you grow up. That one passion you had when you were a baby was to find out for yourself. This was your passion. Your mother said, “Don’t put that dirt in your mouth.” For you, it was: “What’s the big deal? I had to find out. Now I know.” &nbsp;  At some point, you gave up your great passion. Then anybody could come along and tell you, “That’s no good.” And you would say, “Okay, that’s no good.” Why was it no good? You didn't know. He said it was no good, and that was sufficient. This was a right you had. This was a power you had that you abdicated. Today, I would like to remind you of that power. I want you to get it back because the day you get it back, you will stand on your own two feet. That is the day you will start to say, “I need to know. I want to know. I must know for myself.”&nbsp;  You must know, not just have an idea or a concept. Those who are able to go beyond concepts are the ones who know. They are the ones who walk on their own feet. It's not that they walk on softer carpets or only on roads that go downhill. They walk the same road as anybody else, but they walk on their own feet. They make a simple determination in their lives, not in words, but by feeling. That’s what you need in this life—that feeling, that understanding..."  -Prem Rawat ( from Inspire 18)      

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Paint with flower's petal&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    3&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Dog&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    2&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Boats&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Hello Patrick!&nbsp; urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Patrick and his boat in France&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    I like the bird on this one&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ...more&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Boats&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    One Bird&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Seagulls&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The Sea&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Sand worms&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Shell&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Seaweed&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Keep&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Expect results,  without expectations  Try, but let go  of trying  Do it, anyway  Invite it,  let it wash over you  Make it happen,  receive it  Surrender,  its your choice  Feel the feeling,  let it emerge  Make the effort,  effortlessly.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   Kay     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I'm nothing but 'you',  and when I'm not you,&nbsp;I'm nothing. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Kay   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    WHERE ?&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Peace for the heart&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Maharaji&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The  end&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ....&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..this one looks like it has a face in it, if you enlarge it&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    I think I  need more practice!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ...more&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Firework&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    YOU(K&M)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Maharaji&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..fireworks trail&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    FEUX D'ARTIFICE&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "So often peace is defined as the absence of war. There is war that happens between two countries. There is war that takes place between two people. There is war that doesn't even require two people; it takes place inside of a person. For a war on the outside, maybe a cease‑fire can be negotiated. Between two people, maybe an understanding can be negotiated. But even in the absence of those kinds of wars, there is a war that takes place inside a human being—a much more ferocious war that devastates the very elements that are the foundation of a person. Which of these wars will become absent so that one day we can stand up and say, "Now there is peace"?   Those people who have talked about peace in earnest have said, "What you are looking for is within you. You are the source and you are the resource for peace on the face of this earth."  -Prem Rawat (from Inspire 19) 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A message for us&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "You must be the change you wish to see in the world." -Mahatma Gandhi 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    THANK YOU&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A firework, like a bird &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thank you(M&K) &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Friends&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Grey Pony&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..only grass here&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers..  can I eat them?&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Marie's 'Heartfelt'(click on the title). 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The sweetest Love of all-Kay(word design by Marie)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Marie said...  Thank you KAY for your beautiful photo and words, I have pleasure to make this with you. YOU AND ME YESSSS, a good team !!!!! AND THANK YOU MAHARAJI, I LOVE YOU.  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Peace so vibrant-Kay(word design by Marie)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A PEACE SO PASSIONATE-Kay(word design by Marie)&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Sunflower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "What is it that we want? What is it that we are all looking for—not as a universal thing, but each one of us as an individual? What does this heart of ours want? It wants joy, but not the kind of joy that is temporary in nature. It wants peace, but not the kind of peace that is temporary in nature.   A lot of people think the absence of war is peace. What I have come to understand is that, considering how long people have been fighting, the absence of war may never happen. That should not preclude the possibility of peace. Why do I say that? War has nothing to do with peace, and peace has nothing to do with war. There is a peace that transcends war. There is a peace that exists in itself. It does not need the absence of one thing to become the presence of another. That is the peace we are all looking for. That is the peace we want—the peace this heart wants."  -Prem Rawat(from Inspire newsletter 18) 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    You and my heart&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Perhaps I think&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself."    Leo Tolstoy 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    'different' from the others, and very beautiful..&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Words of Love, rising like balloons from the heart  Filled by the breath of Life.  Words playfully tagging on to a stream of Love  become lifeless when tossed aside,  washed up on a shore of time.  A passer-by revives them with the kiss of Life.      Kay 

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thank you for this life !!!&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Our appreciation - Kay - Marie -Thank you my friend - we don't speak the same language but our appreciation of the beauty from within us can make all things possible. Marie&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "..It is individuals that matter. It is you that matters. It is in you that the gift of breath comes. It is in you that there is consciousness. It is you who can see the good and the bad. In you lies the ability to appreciate. In you lies the ability to enjoy".. -Prem Rawat (from Inspire 17)  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    River view&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Thank you&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Love is free&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Force et douceur&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    this is a nice one&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..and duck&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Bird&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    "Its kind of fun to do the impossible."   -Walt Disney   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..close up&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ..."Rule number one is: Don't put yourself down. When you see a beautiful tree, that tree is about the seed that worked, that germinated, not about the one that didn't. Your life, your breath, your existence is about what worked, not what didn't. So light the lamp. Enjoy this life. This is what you have been given. This is your opportunity. Some things in life will be bad and some things will be good. Life is not about the bad. The most important thing is that you have this opportunity to be alive. Just accept that. It's an incredible gift. Enjoy this life. It's so important that you do. Everything is there to make the impossible possible"... -Maharaji/Prem Rawat (Inspire 15)  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Love for fun   urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Se sentir vivant&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Journey to the heart of the heart&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Indoor Gerber daisy plant  urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    It looks like an eye this way up..&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    LOVE IS FREE      The language of love, beyond all words   The language of love, beyond all photography   The medium of love, beyond all art forms   Free from capture,   freely available   free         Kay   

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ..this one grew from a bud, well half grew.&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Patrick's guitar music for all of us  urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    I'd like to take a photo of love...(and other feelings), but I can't!  urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    2&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Music&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Une liberté unique&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ... "Good will happen; bad will happen. Right will happen; wrong will happen. It's like a wheel that goes around and around. But in the good, we can know the source of peace, and in the bad, we can still know the source of peace.." -Prem Rawat ( from Inspire 2)  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Camomile&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Grâce et douceur&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Painting by Stojan:Breath's swing  A swing of the bird's wing is like this breath, within your light, between the window and the door of your life.    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    3&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    2&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Music&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Tune in to your heart &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Freedom is from within&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink PRESENT2 CARDS AND PICTURES    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Flowers&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "The happiness that we are looking for is inside of us. Something needs to be felt within. Peace happens to be one of those things. Joy happens to be one of those things—not a joy that comes and goes, but a joy that permanently resides inside. Not a happiness that comes and goes, connected to the outer world, but a happiness that is always there. Even in the darkest moment, that joy resides within me. There is a solid feeling of peace when we go within and find that place.” -Prem Rawat  

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A Rose&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A flower&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>


</Blog>