<Blog>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      why do relationships have to be so hard!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      okaayyy..... this thing is kinda confusing. dunno my way around the website .yet.nway, since my frens are bz at work, i'll just entertain myself with this thing. is this some sort of a diary or something? i haven't actually written a diary. not for a long time anyway. so, how do i get nad's website kat my link? nak call but mesti he's bz gak. been calling a tad too much today. he's probably annoyed with me by now. heh.. talking bout nad, i'm going to newcastle this friday. hopefully i can wake up early coz the train's at 6 am! crazeee or wat? can't wait!coming back on tuesday..very long weekend indeed...sigh....have to do work...hate it. i hate this research shit. have to have a lot of of self-will and motivation. which are two of the main things that i'm not good at.  this is a shame. so much things happened for the past few weeks, and i just discovered this thing. takkanlah nak cerita everything kan? tempted jugak... but kalau i dah start, mesti jadi a long cerpen.haha.. this is cool...i can say watever i wanna say. all the things that i'm not able to say to anyone. sometimes not even to nad. kool... let's see...my family came 3 weeks ago. dah balik dah pun. so, as expected i pun cuti 3 weeks. sepatutnye 2 weeks je but wat the hell..bukannye slalu pun buat dajal..hehe.. i was tired pun after the night out. went to GC concert with luqman n azzam (no, they're not my guy frens .they're my bros) and nad gak. kinda like a birthday present for him. although he paid for it. well, i paid for the tickets la but after dah kira hutang and langsai kan...nemmain.. nway, the concert was awesome. sugarcult did the opening and they were as good as GC. best gile.. totally worth it. and nad was supposed to go bakc on that thursday but ended up staying till saturday. siap bonding lagi ngan my mom. siap kutuk i lagi..kureng assem betul.. went shopping almost every day after that. kalau tak pun window shopping. harrods sale was crazeee...some women broke the door so kitorang pun masuk lambat. mom decided not to queue up for gucci coz they were so many ppl you wuld not believe it. managed to get soem beautiful CD jewelleries. murah je.. we went to the boutique jugak. 200 ppl were there, and they couldn't control the crowd so the firemen and policemen were there to sort things out. gile... but it was a nice day coz london snowed that day. haha...best... sket je though.. they went back last friday. sad. i actually cried, which is like probably the first time i cried kat airport. pathetic kan? sigh...went back to soton the same day. didn't stay in london with my uncle n aunt. just a thing i do to control my emotion. dunno... hmmmm..................waaahhh.....kena start buat keje..esok...sob...i wanna win 10 million pounds and live in a mansion and not have to do any work...wishful thinking zana...sob..  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      was browsing through nad's blog and thot this is kinda interesting. i have a few more hours before uni officially starts, and i'm doing absolutely nothing productive, sitting in front of the computer with two of my frens. they're doing their work of course. no one's as lazy as i am. =).. so i thot why not rite? shud give this a try.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Am I bad-mouthing people by saying how I feel in my blog? 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Leaving the house in an hour's time. Coming back on Thursday and after that, balik kampung for the weekend. I haven't been back to BP for nearly 2 years, and I think Tok Mak mesti dah start merajuk. She has not been very well since my grandfather passed away 2 1/2 years ago. And come to think of it, I don't think I have visited his kubur. Feel so guilty now...  Received an email from one of my closest friends just now, and it was nice to hear from her. She's coming back to Malaysia in 2 weeks time I think, and probably coming down to KL for her birthday. I don't know how that will work out coz she's friends with both me and my ex. And I really don't feel like seeing him at the moment. I hope she understands. I feel so bad for putting her on the spot but that's not my intention. Sigh.. And my other friends jugak..   .... I better go and check if I've got everything in my bag. Redang, here I come! Ciao.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Tall men Strong hands Cuddle Ashton Kutcher Irish accent.. on Irish men Sense of humour Cheekiness (if there is such a word)  Gakki handbags =) Shoes Cosmo mag    Just some stuff that make me go ooh (u know, as in the McD song).. Although not everything in a single person. and not in any particular order..Will update when I have more to add. Hehe..=D  And I swear by:  1. Lush's American Cream conditioner - for lovely-scented hair 2. Lush's Aqua Mirabilis body scrub and Body Shop's Cocoa Butter - for smooth skin 3. LK Bennett - for lovely lovely shoes 4. GAP and UCB - for super comfy clothes 5. KL and Penang - for finger-licking food 6. My cats and the Net - for keeping me entertained 7. F.R.I.E.N.D.S - for making me laugh, whenever where ever 8. Moccachino - for making me high 9. Him - for making me cry 10. My few treasured precious buddies, my family and God - for everything 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Was browsing through a friend's blog, and saw this:   I would have given you all of my heart but there's someone who's torn it apart and he's taking almost all that I've got but if you want, I'll try to love again baby I'll try to love again but I know  The first cut is the deepest, baby I know The first cut is the deepest 'cause when it comes to being lucky she's cursed when it comes to lovin' me she's worst but when it comes to being loved she's first that's how I know  The first cut is the deepest, baby I know The first cut is the deepest  I still want you by my side just to help me dry the tears that I've cried cause I'm sure gonna give you a try and if you want, I'll try to love again but baby, I'll try to love again, but I know  The first cut is the deepest, baby I know The first cut is the deepest  'Cause when it comes to being lucky he's cursed when it comes to lovin' me he's worst but when it comes to being loved he's first that's how I know  The first cut is the deepest, baby I know The first cut is the deepest.  First time I heard this song was in the early 90s, if I remember correctly. Back then it was Rod Steward who sang the song, and me mom (who's a fan of his music) was listening to his album in the car. It was one of my favourite songs, but I was probably too little to know the meaning of it all. Too young. I like Sheryl Crow's version better personally- can totally relate to it.       
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      0438, KL.  I'm a sucker for reality TV. We watched American Idol last night and Miss Barrino won. Totally awesome voice. As Randy put it nicely- "It's a cross between Mary J Blige and Aretha Franklin". I'm glad I'm not in the UK at the moment, kalau tak mesti I'll be wasting my time watching people lazing around in a big house with chickens (but not eat them? I thought THAT was the whole purpose) doing nothing and staring at and bitching about each other. Yes, this is one of my deepest secrets- I watch Big Brother. In fact, I sometimes enjoy watching it. Forgive me God, for I have sinned. I know, it's embarassing and it's such a waste of time. But there's usually nothing else to watch on TV, and once I tune in I am hooked. It's like one of those moments, you know, say, you're addicted to the food at this particular stall and your mate goes "wei, diorang taruk ganja ke apa dalam makanan ni".. See what I mean? It does not mean that I've got a big 'L' on my forehead.    Maybe it does.. But oh, so what.. =)  Was reading Cleo (my saviour kat KL) and they had an interview with their 'most eligible bachelor of 2004'. I must say, he IS fine. If you wanna check him out try this       urlLink ">Link    http://cleo.time.net.my/results.cfm Don't think the link worked but..OH, but that was last years' results. Oh well, check out MR Ramon and Mr Jahan.. Woo Hoo.. Anyway, I was reading some stuff and I thought Hazeline and Sharmayne are such nice names. Don't you think? My seniors kat BB, and they're so beautiful. But NO, I won't be able to hook them up with anyone coz I don't know them. haha..  Gosh, it's only 5.30 am (I've been writing for an HOUR???) and I'm sweating. Panasss.. Going out with me mom and youngest brother later, do some shopping before we jet off to Redang Island tomorrow, and gonna have a look at the new crib. Cheh, cakap macam bagus je..;).. But Seriously, I can't wait to move to this new place. Should be exciting to have a room for myself. Right now, I'm still sharing my bed with my little bro (Hey, he's only 9).. Yes, another confession..  *yawn* Yah Man..I better do something useful now. I've been saying that since the day I knew how to talk. Okay, I'm exaggerating.. *yawn* Adieu....  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      God, how many times did I write yesterday??! But this is fun. At least I have something to do during my holiday, instead of watching crap shows like Oprah etc. Gasp, did I say that out loud? That could have been misconstrued as a form of betrayal to women around the world. Oh well..  Had a few hours to kill before Subuh this morning, and decided to go through some stuff that I still keep from my school years. We're moving to a new place at the end of the month, and I'm sorting out some stuff- you know, things to keep etc. Some old pictures from primary school, one of my diaries (I was 10 or 12, and reading it made me cringe..=)..think I'll get rid of it. I'm quite sure my mom has read it somehow) and yearbooks from secondary school. Gile nostalgia.. I still can't believe that for almost 9 years (since standard 1) I had to wake up at FIVE am, showered in the cold and wait for the bus to come at 5.45 am. It can even be categorised as a form of abuse. =) But God, I miss those days. I was in BB till form 3, and decided to go to a boarding school far far away when I was 16. Things were not as exciting at the new school, but looking back, I wouldn't change a thing. But sometimes I do think- where would I be now if I had stayed in BB? and sometimes I wish I had stayed coz I miss the friends, the atmosphere, the school, the teachers.. We really had fun back then. Sekarang ni, sekolah pun dah takde. Such a waste..  One of these days, I should compile all the photos I have and put them nicely in a photo album. Or I should buy a nice digicam like Kudo's and store them in my computer. =) I can only do the latter when I have money though. One of the things I hate about being a student. Tis ok. Only one more year to go and I'll start earning some cash. I'll be the girl you see running down Oxford Street, shopping till I drop. Too bad Tom Ford is not with Gucci anymore (Gakki?hehe) or that would be the first place I go to spend my first cheque on. Cheh, cakap macam ada duit je..   *Yawn*... I shall go and do something useful now. Like watching MTV or [V] (DJ Utt!!!) or whatever there is on TV. Ciao bella. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      SIGH... This is ugly. But what do I expect, it's only been a day. I slept last night, but was woken up by a bad dream. It's only 3 in the morning. Why do I need them in my dreams? My friend warned me that after my anger has subsided, I'll feel like shit. God, how I look forward to that.  It makes me sick. To think that only 2 months ago, I was the one he was holding hands with. I was the one he called when he had problems (at least, that's what I think). and I was the reason he came down to London. But NOW..everything has changed. I can't help but imagine him with her, laughing and holding hands. They have probably even kissed for all I know. It's him, I won't be surprised. SIGH.. I should't be thinking about this.  I was doing alright. I was beginning to move on. But his news threw me off completely. Why LIE? He could've kept his pride. I used to look up at him with admiration- I didn't know anyone could be this nice, and such a gentleman. But NOW- He's SO little to me. I try to search whithin myself, what do I feel about him? I can't find anything. Nothing. Not anger or hatred. Jauh sekali lah admiration or respect. Is he not embarrassed? To have someone hate you is one thing, but to have people lose their respect for you is another. And his friends- "If you're happy, then I'm happy for you". What crap is that? Why are they afraid to say that what he did was wrong? I am not in denial. Think about it. Someone told you he wants to break up with you because he does not want to be in a relationship at the moment. But a few weeks later, fall for someone else? What crap were you feeding me? I invested a lot in the relationship, and this is how I was treated in the end. And I was moving on, but now he gives me more crap that I have to deal with. I have to go through the whole thing again..  They say "How soon is too soon?". Sooner or later he's gonna be with someone new. I know that. But that's not the point. I am tired of explaining, read my other entries. If someone still thinks that I was bothered about that, I'm afraid I have no choice but to label he/she as ignorant.   SIGH.. I want this to end as soon as possible. I am so tired, mentally and physically. I am SO tired.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Good God.. Found this picture in my brother's page. It's so old. I must have been 7 or 8. This is SO funny.LOL. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There's a saying old says that love is blind Still we're often told, "seek and ye shall find" So i'm going to seek a certain lad i've had in mind Looking everywhere, haven't found him yet  He's the big affair i cannot forget Only man i ever think of with regret I'd like to add his initial to my monogram Tell me, where is the shepherd for this lost lamb?  There's a somebody i'm longing to see I hope that he turns out to be Someone who'll watch over me I'm a little lamb who's lost in the wood I know i could always be good Someone who'll watch over me  Although he may not be the man some Girls think of as handsome To my heart he carries the key Won't you tell him please to put on some speed Follow my lead, oh, how i need Someone to watch over me  -Frank Sinatra-  I'm such an old soul at heart..
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Noooo....i slept for 6 hours during the day....not gooood. this means i won't be able to sleep tonight. sigh..the worse thing is i woke up wondering if i had a nightmare involving him and another girl. and i immediately realised- no, that wasn't a dream, that actually happened. But well, I was expecting things like this to happpen anyway. Early mornings would be more difficult for the next few days/weeks.  The same happened first time he broke up with me. I'm familiar with the process, well, more or less la. Just have to go through it. Again.  I think contrary to what he said in the email, I'm not really pissed off with him. I'm a bit angry, yes, and disappointed, and again, so betrayed. and it feels so weird but i feel like i'm having one of those out-of-body experiences, know wat i mean? i'm constantly thinking to myself- i really don't know this guy anymore. He has changed SO much, and I really don't know him. Which is sad, because when u've been friends with someone for like 5 years, you'd think u know everything about that person. But suddenly, he/she does things completely out-of-character and u just feel cheated.. it's like- why didn't u show this side of you before this? why now? and why do you this to your own best friend? is this how you show respect to your friends?  People change. I know. I have changed, although I'm not sure if it's for the better or worse. And I guess, at my age, this is the stage when most people start to understand who they really are, and if they don't, find something to give an edge to their characters. And I guess when you get into a relationship too young, this is one of the things you should prepare yourself for. But i was naive, and i didn't know any better. And i guess this is one of the blessings- now I know that I can't trust anyone 100% (it's impossible) and I have something to tell my children about in the future. haha =)..I'll be one of those moms who go "no, you're too young. he's only after one thing. love? what love?" =)..gosh, hope not.  This is actually the first time I've ever had to end a friendship. No, I'm not proud of it. 5 years man. And I really liked being friends with him. But he let me down big time. It's not about ego or shit like that. It's for my own survival. I need to do this for myself. I have to stop cheating myself, I'm not that strong. I don't have to have a perfect life. I don't have to be friends with my exes. A lot of people don't. I'm not mad that he broke up with me. When I think about it, it's actually for the best. We were so different. We come from different backgrounds and upbringings, and we value different things. Back then, to me, opposite attracts. And I still believe it does in some cases, but maybe it was not for us. I thought "hey, we have so much fun as friends, this thing can work".. But I do not regret saying yes. It has been a bitter-sweet journey, and I have learnt lots of things from this chapter of my life.   Holding on to anger is like grasping a hot coal with the intent of throwing it at someone else; you are the one who gets burned.     -BUddha-  I shall be repeating that mantra in my head. I'm physically and emotionally tired. I'm tired of giving and caring. It was all wasted, and I have now stopped caring for others, except for a few important people in my life. I have stopped believing in others, and I don't trust anyone. It's sad. This is not who I want to become, but we'll see. This is a life-changing experience for me. I don't wanna change, I don't want to be a cynical bitch. But I have doubts. =)  Someone told me this:  "realize that you will need to take baby steps to get through this. When you put all your trust into another person, it is completely devestating to have those feelings crushed. You need to take care of you now.  Your realizing you can't be friends with him is wise and empowering. You take care of you and not worry about him. It will be hard and challenging to do, but you are a strong beautiful person who deserves better. Keep reminding yourself of that, it's easy to loose sight of when you are so hurt and betrayed."  Sigh..I can do this. I'm built of steel. =)..I have other friends and I don't need anyone around me that has hurt me so much. I don't want to put up with more of his crap. I shall be happy from now on.=)   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    me and ninie in newcastle.A weekend I would prefer not to remember, but i thot this picture is sweet.my lesbian luvver!;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm such a chick-flick kinda girl. Right before my flight to KL (yes, i'm in KL!!) I did this chick-flick marathon and watched, among others, When Harry met Sally (soo sweet), The Wedding Singer, That Thing You Do (love it love it love it) etc. Guy Patterson- well, he's the drummer from that thing you do and boy, is he fine..=)  Life has been shitty these past few months, but I'm still surviving. It is so weird but I find articles from magazines and advices from strangers so comforting. He laughed when I told him that, and that hurts a bit coz hey, he's not helping is he? I should probably stop talking about him.. Right?  Chin up me... =)  Been back for nearly a week now, and I haven't done anything productive. Still jet-lagged, and I still haven't slept since yesterday. Probably a first time for me. Study pun tak pernah stay up. hah.. I have so many things to write about but later la.. Will try and stay awake for as long as I can....zzzzzzzzzzzzz.....
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This song was sang by Al Green me think, and was in one of my fav movies- How to lose a guy.. Was also in Pulp Fiction.. Absolutely love it!     I'm, I'm so in love with you Whatever you want to do Is alright with me Cause you make me feel so brand new And I want to spend my whole life with you Ooh  Since, baby Since we've been together Loving you forever Is what I need Let me be the one you come running to And I'll never be untrue  So let's, let's stay together Loving you whether, whether Times are good or bad, happy or sad Ooh Good or bad, happy or sad  Why, why people break up and turn around and make up I just can't see You'd never do that to me Cause being around you is all I see All I wanna do is  Let's, let's stay together Loving you whether, whether Times are good or bad, baby, happy or sad  Let's, let's stay together, yeah Loving you whether, yeah, loving you whether Good or bad, baby, happy or sad, yeah Good or bad, baby, happy or sad, yeah Good or bad, baby, happy or sad, yeah Let's, let's stay together Loving you whether, yeah, whether Times are good or bad, baby, happy or sad  Yeah, that's what I'm talking about     This song reminds me that "true love", whatever that is, still exists, even if it's not for me. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      http://members.boardhost.com/Tigress/index.html?1085603553
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I received an email from him a few hours ago, and I haven't slept the whole night. But that's probably because I slept for nearly 7 hours during the day time yesterday.=) Nothing I didn't suspect. But I was still surrised to hear about that, and I feel cheated and betrayed. I was literally shaking. He said it's been like that for the past few weeks, but someone told me that it started a week after we broke up. Why do I feel so sad? I don't care if it's now or later. I was already expecting this to happen anyway. Sooner or later, I will still feel hurt and sad. But how could he have lied to me? Told me that he doesn't want to be in a r'ship at the moment. Why couldn't he be honest? Is this the same guy I fell in love with? Is this the same guy I once trusted my life with? Why are people so deceiving? I really do not care when he developed these feelings. I have heard what I need to hear, and that's that. The best friend that I once thought was my life, lied to me. No, this is even worse than lying. I do not want to care about him. He is not worthy of that. I invested so much in this, and this is what I get back from him? Shows me how much he respects our relationship/friendship. Shame on me for being a fool, and not seeing him as he is. Shame on me for kissing him with my eyes closed. Shame on me for lying to myself, and think that he will change. Shame on me for not listening to my instincts. Shame on me, for making such a big mistake. From now on, I will trust no one but myself. That way, I won't feel disappointed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow...brad pitt was gorgeous... have i said that he's gorgeous?? sigh..he has got to be the most gorgeous guy on planet earth. wait..no..in the whole universe!!..=)  less than a week before my flight..can't wait.. i think i'm over him..kadang2 tu rasa la sedih but siapa tak kan?? yeah, i'm over him.. but i think i've kinda develop some feelings for a certain someone. i know this is so stupid. i'll just keep it to myself lah. nothing is going to happen, and if this person accidently dapat tau pun, he's not going to want me. nah..it's impossible. everyone says (just to be nice and polite) oh, you're a nice girl, you're sweet, mesti ada orang nak..but orang yg cakap tu bukannye nak..they're just saying these things to make me feel better. which is nice of them..but honestly??? tak kot..  and i shouldn't think about being in a relationship pun right now..i seriously need some 'me' time.. i need to sit down and think what i really want in my life. i'm not the kind of person yang nak main2 je. i'm a serious girl. i thought it was goin to work with us, but i guess that's just me thinking naively and rather stupidly. i am getting tired of this kinda thing. people who gets into relationship and think that it's all for fun (which is selfish really coz kalau the other person tu serious about the r'ship then jangan lah nak try2 konon) and kalau tak jadi, say things like oh, i'm sorry, i couldn't help it, i didn't have a choice etc. i hate orang yg suka main2kan hati orang lain. may they burn in hell. literally.   wow, i have got some serious temper. anyway, i need a grown-up really. commitment-philic rather than commitment-phobic. someone who knows what's real and what's not. someone mature. =).. someone right for me. not a kiddo.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was angry. i did not mean everything i said. hate is such a strong word. dislike is more like it.but i do feel sick if i think about how people perceive him. as though he's a martyr. i don't know. at least i'm not saying all these things to his face. he hates it when i do that. he hated it when i told him how much i hate him. well, i thought i was just being honest. tu lah.. at least, i'm just writing this down for me to luahkan my feelings. don't mean a thing. maybe...??
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Should I care that we are not close anymore? NO. I don't want to care. He does whatever he think is right without thinking about other people, so I can do the same. Right? Dno't know lah. He is overrated. His friends semua regard him as their best friend. Ye lah, dia tak pernah hurt them. As someone said to me, label them as ignorant. I feel sick in my stomach everytime I think of how people look up at him. Oh, he's so nice, he's so considerate, he's such a gentleman, he's so sensitive, he's a good friend etc. it makes me SICK!!!!! i hate him. i despise him. and he gets to my nerve. kalau boleh, i never wannna see him again. biggest betrayal in my life.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I need to do this. Lay out the reasons why logically, I should not be with him, so that whenever I even think about missing him or getting back to him (not that he wants to) I can go back to these reasons and make a rational decision.  1. He does not love me 2. He has changed. and he is not the same person I fell in love with in the first place.  3. He hurt me. 4. He has changed and he's not the same person I got to know back then. 5. Come on zana, sampai bila you nak live in sins? He does not bring the best in you. 6. He hurt me. really badly. even worse than what my ex did. 7. I deserve someone better, someone who would not even THINK of doing something like this to me. He's not worthy of my love. 8. He has found someone else 9. He betrayed me 10. He hurt me.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      shit happens..and a lot has happened in my life. i don't know where to start..and i don't know what actually happened or why it happened. well..shit happens. fuck the world.  i don't trust anyone now.not a single person. except my family. i gave all my hopes and dreams and trust to a person and i was betrayed. he was supposed to be my best friend. my BEST FRIEND. he was my bestest friend ever. but not anymore. i am pretty sure that if my heart were to be surgically removed, i can see cracks. i hope they will turn to scars soon. i am so tired of being in this phase. i just want to move on and get on with my life. i don't need him in my life. but because he wants to stay friends then ok.i will let it be. i am tired. and i'm only 23. i am so fucking tired. i wanna die. it's only been 2 months. if anyone is reading this at all, please say a little prayer for me so that i will forget about this and be happy again? i hate being miserable. i don't want my life to be controlled by him. i have had enough. i wanna die.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How much should one reveal in one's blog?   It depends on the individual I guess. I've been thinking hard and I still don't know. There are things that had happened in the past that I want to let out from my chest, but it was such a  huge  secret for me, I'm not sure how people will react to it. On the other hand though, I guess it will be good as I know there are lots of people out there who must have gone through the same thing and really, there's nothing to be ashamed of. On top of that, it happened in the  past , and I'm over it.   What about all this 'keeping the mystery' about yourself crap? I guess that's necessary to an extent. I mean, once I've revealed everything, people would think differently of me and see me in a different light. But I guess that's just how you have to take it eh? And really, just because something happened or I did something really stupid in the past, it does not mean that I'm a different person. I'm still me. Just with flaws. As with everyone.   I'll keep thinking.   p.s: Update on my exercise 'regime' (if you can call it a regime la..:P). Cycled (on the cycling machine) for 15 km, did a few squats and lunges, and collapsed on the bed. My legs felt like jellies. Literally. One more aim to add on top of the one-stone-to-lose: to be more fit. Fit as in not-breathless-after-20-minutes-run (or rather, my 'power-walk' stunt) fit. Good luck me! :P
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I did something pretty amazing today. I actually exercised (woo-hoo!!). I haven't been to the gym since I came back (yeah, yeah..that was five weeks ago..). So just now, after all the guilt from eating, lying down, watching telly all day and blogging; I decided enough is enough and instead of moaning that I'm getting fatter I should really do something about it. So i braved myself and stepped on the treadmill, and 'power-walked' for 25 minutes. Okay, not much. But that, plus some ab-crunches and push-ups is quite enough for the first day right? :P.. Dah lah kononnye 'power-walk' pulak tu. I don't run you see. I look funny running (imagine a Friends episode, TOW Phoebe Runs and you'll see what I mean) so I avoid humiliating myself in front of people by adopting this new (well, not really new...) thang they call 'power-walking' on a 7.0 point inclination. Hey, I still sweat. And at the end of it, my gluteus muscles were screaming at me for putting them through the torture. Poor babies..:P   Since The Breakup, I have lost in total 7 kilograms (and hopefully, still counting, fingers crossed). To those who have not seen me since ages ago, NO, I am not thinner. I gained a few kgs, and this just means that I'm back to my 'before' weight (and 'before' means last year, not 4 years ago). And don't worry coz in my case, weight loss is actually needed and truth be told, even if I lose a lot of weight I will never be able to fit into one of those size 6 jeans. I will still be a two-digit-size woman, proud and all (hope so!). I'm one of those women who are 'blessed' with low metabolism (apparently, there's no such thing. dammit you know-it-all scientists). Or what you call big-boned (blame it on ayah's genes..hmmph..). Or whatever. :D  My aim is to lose another stone and be back at my 'Hey, Baby' weight. According to this book I read (which is oh so hilarious, check out my latest 'literature') the 'Hey, Baby' weight is the weight you have to be in order to date again and to have random men on the street call out, 'Hey, baby...'. In the UK, especially in London, that would actually be a challenge. In KL (okay, in Gombak..), any girl with a pair of boobs and ass would find themselves attracting men of all ages. From teenagers to atoks. Men here ogle at anything that moves! *criiinge*  So there. I have put it for the public to see, so I would be more 'pressured' to achieve it. :P .. In the meantime, I'm due for a shower. I smell awful. And I'm tired. God, I'm so unfit. Till later people.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1202, Gombak.  Dear Blog,  I did something that I never thought I would have the guts doing.  I took the box hidden under my table, and opened it. There they were, bundles of letters, each carefully folded. The box was full of letters from him, back when we were in college. Best of friends, we were. Me, him and N. Never went anywhere without each other. We would meet almost every night at the counselling room (we were kind of like PRS, but weirdly, we never had the chance to actually counsel anyone) and 'studied'. Talking and bitching was more like it. We were so close that people thought N and I were fighting over him. Yeah, right. The narrow-minded ones did not like us girls hanging out with this guy. You're not supposed to do that, they say.   We were in the same class, and chatted everytime we had the chance to. We even wrote letters to each other when we were bored during lessons. We would exchange letters every two days or so (more often if the mood was good), just writing about things in general. What we did in the evening, what we thought about that particular Nazi-ish warden, relationships, friendships, what we were planning to do that weekend. All sort of things. There were little bounderies as to what we could tell each other. I would lie on my stomach, on my bed, and started writing away my worries, feelings and hopes. It only took us 3 months to really get to know each other, and the rest was history as they say. There was nothing that anyone could do to separate us. With one exception. Rumours were going around that we were an item. N was spared as she was seeing someone at that time. I did not like that. To me, it was just a very special friendship. Nothing more. And I backed off for a while, which I later regret. It was one of the 'challenges' we went through as friends, but we pulled through it.   He's the only one I know who calls me Ash. That or Zona Pellucida. I liked it. It was special. The night we broke up, he said "Zana...". I knew it was over even before he finished his sentence. He used to sign off his letters with 'Luv, bro'. Once in a while it was 'Devil #1' (some not-very-funny joke we had). Or just simply his name.   Sitting here with the box on my lap, I'm still thinking of what I should do with the letters. I used to read the letters over and over again whenever I came back home, and they never failed to bring a smile across my face. It brings back fond memories from those years in Banting. Those letters were one of the few things that kept me sane while I was there. That and a few special friends that I still treasure.   I tried reading some of them, but this time, instead of the warm feeling I usually get, there was nothing. Zilch. I did not feel a thing. No happy thoughts, no regrets. No anger. I was half-expecting myself to cry. But I didn't. I guess it's time to really move on. And get rid of them. I shouldn't hold on to these, should I?   Part of me feels sad that I have to do this. What else can I keep from my college years if I don't have these letters? But some things aren't meant to be. And maybe I should keep searching for that Banting yearbook that I misplaced somewhere.   Love,  Ash..   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I woke up this morning and checked my e-mail. Guess who wrote me? He wants to talk.   Honestly, I don't know what he means by that. Does he:  1. Want to explain himself? And by doing that, how exactly will it benefit me? Nothing will change, and I only have this little energy to focus on myself right now.  2. Want to make himself feel better? He's happy at the moment, and having the time of his life. Why bother I say.   3. Want my forgiveness? I can forgive no-one. I have no such rights.   4. Want to 'clean his name', as one of my friends suggested to me? Look dear, everyone else still thinks very highly of you. Don't worry, yeah?  I deleted his e-mail. I am not replying. I don't know what to say.  No, wait. Actually, I DO know what to say but it will only hurt other people and I'll be left alone with the guilt. I hate that feeling. So, taking the easy way out, I'm keeping quiet. Coward you say? Oh no.. I'm doing this because I know myself best. Trust me, you wouldn't want me to meet up with him. I will only resort to violence. The next day, you'll see me on the front page of The Star, beating a boy with a hockey stick.   It's true isn't it? He was looking after himself when he broke it up, and went out with another girl. I am merely doing the same thing. I'm looking after myself by not giving him any chance to give me more crap. Selfishness: sometimes it's necessary for survival. Kan?      
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Please don't kill me if this entry is rubbish. I really AM getting the bloggers' block you see. That, or I ate way too much pasta, and am now suffering from one of it's side effects (fikir pun L.A.M.B.A.T semacam..).  One of the funniest things happened the other day when I was in the car with my cousin. She was driving, and we were heading to one of the Giant hypermarkets to buy 'a few' things for her son's second birthday ('a few' turned out to be, among others, 16 chickens, 8 packets of nasi impit, a huge go-kart car for his birthday present, and the list went on). No, it really did go on. Lucky kids these days. When I was little, I only had one birthday party where I could invite my friends. And they weren't even my friends from school, only kids I played and fought with in the neighbourhood. I was 5, and it was so 'happening' (kononnye) because I was getting all these presents! And the one thing that I still remember from that day was when my brother begged me for this barbie doll that I got. Of course, now he denies it.   Anyway, on our way there, my cousin turned to me and said "Hey, I'm doing the same thing you did". She then told me that I (me? this naive girl? don't believe everything I say la..) gave her the inspiration and motivation that she so needed to get over this guy she was seeing. After her divorce, she went out with this guy (who's still a bachelor with no emotional baggage etc) and things were looking pretty good when, after 7 months, he ditched her.   Apparently his parents did't agree with him dating a 'janda'. With two kids.   How awful is that? If one only assumes 'bad' things about a single mother, then I can do the same and assume that people in KL, to say the least, should be open-minded about this sort of thing. But as the saying goes, assumptions are the mother of all fuck-ups.   I don't know. Is status that important? Status won't guarantee you a life-long marriage. Status won't guarantee you a happy-ever-after ending. When did we stop looking at people's inside and judge a book only by it's cover? But I shouldn't really complain should I? Because we KNOW this kind of thing happens. In fact, we accept it so much, that we call it 'reality'.   "It's reality, dear. You shouldn't feel so sad"  Really? Shouldn't she feel sad? Just because it's what expected of people, we should tolerate it? Maannn... I have so much learning to do.   She's a strong woman. I know she can do this. She's only trying to find a good father figure for her children. It's not so much for her you see. She wants her kids to grow up loving her and another man they can really call 'ayah', not someone who left her when the roads got rocky.   Once in a while, I say a little prayer, for her and her children to meet that someone. And have that happy-ever-after ending. I hope it will come true, if not for her, at least for the little ones.    (Think I DID have way too much pasta. I'm tricked into thinking that it's bedtime and am now in my pj's. It's only 5 pm!!) 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "He's not the physical kinda guy. Guess that's a good thing. You know, won't get into fights and stuff" "Yeah, but if I get into a fight with him, I'd win" "Really?" "Yeah. sure."  (Voice inside head:I've got bigger biceps AND gastrocnemius than he does.. *horns sprouting through my skull* See? I'm a mean person.)  "Maaannn...if my girlfriend has thoughts like that about me, I wouldn't be able to...perform.."  (Voice inside head: Then I guess it WAS a blessing in disguise)  I went out with this friend of mine yesterday. We went bowling, had lunch and coffee while discussing about *stuff* (Read: any guesses?). He's currently back in KL for the summer holidays but will be flying off to Edinburgh in a week. This guy has helped me a lot. I can't thank him enough. Sometimes it hurts when he tells me stuff that I'd rather not hear, but he's ALMOST always right (hehe..men would love to hear a girl say that they're always right, kan?). Sometimes it takes time for me to really digest what he tells me but most of the time, I get what he's saying. Life is not always perfect. Life is NEVER perfect.    "Dah lah tu. Don't think about this. Buat sakit hati je" "Yeah, I know. I just.. think it's unfair that I'm still sad, but he's out there enjoying himself. As though it meant nothing" "It wasn't fair when I left you. But that's not the point. This is not about whether it's fair or not. Why do you want to be sad?" "No, it's not that. I know I'll get through this. It's only him. I won't let him 'ruin' my life."  *him showing two thumbs up*  Yeah, we were together back in 2000. Four years ago. For four months. At that time, it felt as though the world was crumbling down. I thought he was my 'first love' (I was SO naive) *sheepish grin*. Looking back, we were too young, it was moving too fast and we didn't know a thing about all this relationship stuff. Entah macam mana, we're good friends now, and I'm really grateful for that. Sometimes I wonder, macam mana our group (6 of us, now 5 to me) can stand all the challenges and really weird stuff that had happened between us. Seriously, if anyone is interested in writing a Mills-and-Boons type of novel (or a Sidney-Sheldon even), just drop me a line and I'll tell you a true story about 3 girls and 3 guys who fell in love (or so they thought) with each other and .... (to be continued). Hihi..  I don't know. I believe in the goodness of people too. Most of the time. Not always. I believe there should be some rules that you have to live by in your life. Some things, you just shouldn't do. You can't do. However selfish you are, you should think of other people jugak. It's not always about yourself. I guess I still  think  that I'm living in a perfect world, because so far, from my observation, people can be very selfish and deceiving.    "Shit happens"  (Voice inside head: Really, I wish people would stop telling me that. I'm starting to hate that phrase)  "I know, but it shouldn't be like that. If you have the means to un-do the shit, then you should" "Well.."   You see, I would like to think of myself as a 'loyal' person, and I hope that as much as I can talk the talk, I will be able to walk the walk when the time comes. I know I'm still young, and have not had that many experiences, but if something happens to my (future) partner, I would stand by him no matter what. And if I have the means to make things 'right', I would. I was at fault once. I wanted to run away from my previous relationship. I was suffocated. I wanted freedom. I wanted to meet other guys. I didn't want to 'settle' for my best friend. I wanted something new. But I stayed, and learnt to love him, and love him I did. Was I stupid? Should I have left? I don't know. There are so many what-ifs, it's not worth thinking about.   "Has he done any significant sacrifices, that you think it was such a great love?" "Hmmm...Honestly? I can't think of any... But I did love him" "This is how I see it. If I love someone, I wouldn't mind sacrificing something, without expecting anything in return.."    Yeah.. I would too. But everyone thinks differently. What you think is 'right and justified' might be wrong to others. What I can do now I guess, is just wait. and be me.     To my friend, if you're reading this: I hope you don't mind me transcripting our conversation. I'm getting the bloggers block jugak you see. :P And really, thank you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've been thinking, and I think I'm somewhat 80-90% over him. You know, I have passed that stage where I would  NEVER EVER  in my entire life, no-matter-what-happens, want to be with him. No hopes, no expectation, no more trust in him, no nothing. But why do I still feel 'one kind' whenever someone mentions his or her name? Rasa  sedih  yang teramat. I can literally feel my heart cracking again. Is this normal, or is it just me?  Will I survive when I'm back in UK on my own?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        You have a heartsick soul! You're the type of girl who always has a crush and is writing their name on all your books. You are a hopeless romantic. Waiting for that prince charming, you take love seriously, but still play any chance you get. You can have a lot if boys who are friends, but waiting for that perfect boyfriend. Sometimes you are discouraged because there are no sparks but even if the smallest thing happens, you're on Cloud 9.  You believe in true love and wait for it. Just dont be afraid to take a chance. Love is all about risks.    urlLink   What Kind of SOUL do you posses? (For Girls only)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Dibalas Dengan Dusta by Audy    Semudah itu kau ucapkan  Kata maaf kekasihku Setelah kau lakukan lagi Kesalahan yang sama Di mana perasaanmu Saat kau melakukan salah yang sama Inikah cara dirimu Membalas tulus cinta yang telah kuberi  Menyakitkan bila cintaku dibalas dengan dusta Namun mencintamu tak aku kusesali Kerna aku yang memilihmu  Di mana perasaanmu Saat kau melakukan salah yang sama Inikah cara dirimu Membalas tulus cinta yang telah kuberi  Menyakitkan bila cintaku dibalas dengan dusta Namun mencintamu tak aku kusesali Kerna ku yang memilihmu   Went out with two of my closest friends. Watched Harry Potter, had lunch and coffee, and chatted. This friend of mine gave a very good advice to me, and I shall keep repeating that in my head everytime I feel down. Why can't I have faith in myself even when others believe in me?   Today is a day for reflection, and usually, on this kind of days, I start to appreciate the 'little things' more. Like the sunset, and the laughter of the kids. A stranger's smile. The character of the trees along the highway. The way the clouds form a picture, as though someone is narrating a story somewhere. That sort of thing. It's therapeutic in a way, and I'm happy being immersed in these happy thoughts. That's how I get away from the harsh reality of this thing we call life. Try it, it works wonders.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm high. I think I'm in loovveee..  urlLink      My heart beats fast everytime I see him. And I feel giddy everytime I hear his oh-so-sexy voice. People, I have a MAJOR crush on Hans Isaac.  I actually had a crush on him when I was younger (back when I was in BB). And it faded away after I left BB coz no-one in Taiping seemed to share the same interest in guys. Everything was about books, books and more books. I had pictures of him in my purse. If he's just an ordinary guy, I would have said 'Ahh..it's just meant to be. One day we'll be together'. The thing that ticked me off a bit was that, after I left for Taiping, he actually came to my old school as one of the judges for our drama competition. Hans Isaac came to MY old school and I was NOT there?? Luckily, my friends understood how crazy I was for him and sent me pictures and autograph etc. (I probably should stop now to avoid sounding like a pathetic loser)  Anyway (who am I kidding? It's a bit too late for that), I was in Redang recently and I saw one of his documentaries on scuba diving, and seeing him on TV again made my hormones go haywire. The fact that he was wearing a wetsuit didn't help at all. And now that I have found his website I can go there and stare at his face all day long. Sigh...=D  Don't you think it's SO much easier to have a crush on a famous person? You:      1. Won't get hurt coz you know there's no chance of any of your fantasies coming true     2. Can let everyone know about your crush, coz let's face it, thousands other people         have crushes on him too     3. Don't have to face the prospect of getting rejected  But, you have to know where to stop coz you do not want:       1. Other people to think that you're a psycho stalker     2. And send you to a mental institution  Alright. I'm going to pay Hans' website a little visit now.  urlLink     .. Hehe..A good evening to all. Ciao.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The other night, I had dinner with my cousin and her two kids (Nana and Azrai). We talked about issues like relationships, breakups and marriages (it seems like THAT is the only thing I talk about kan?).   I haven't seen them since last year, so it was no surprise when they didn't warm up to me at first. Jual mahal jugak budak-budak ni.. But at the end of our 'outing', Nana was literally forcing me to stay with her.  Nana: Auntie Ashghah (kids can't pronounce 'r' right. but then again, my brothers pun tak boleh pronounce 'r'). Jom la tido ngan Nana.  Me: Tak boleh la Nana. Next time ek?  Nana: *silence* Auntie Ashghah, jom la tido ngan Nana.  Me: Cannot la Nana. Lain kali eh? (I changed the language hoping that this time she would understand)  Nana: *silence*  Azrai: Ashghah (he's only 2 and it was so funny when he called me by my name je), jom lah.  After much persuasion and declining, I told them I have to go home.  Nana: Ok. Cium sikit.  Azrai: ha'ah..Nak cium!!  SO sweet.. and they kissed me on my cheeks for like a hundred times!! (OK, more like 4 or 5 times but still sweet right?). I love them to bits! =)  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                 You Should Date An Italian!  You love for old fashioned romance, with an old fashioned guy  An Italian guy is the perfect candidate to be your prince charming  If your head doesn't spin enough, just down another espresso with him  Invest in a motorcycle helmet - and some carb blocker for all that pasta!      urlLink  Which Foreign Guy Should You Date? Take This Quiz :-)        urlLink Find the Love of Your Life  (and More Love Quizzes) at Your New Romance.       
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have not been feeling very well these past few days. Emotionally. But I don't know why.   The worse thing is I don't know who to talk to. Everyone seems to be busy etc, although I don't blame them. It's just that..I need to talk to someone. And because I've been keeping it all inside me, I've been feeling crappy and moody, and treating people around me in ways that they do not deserved to be treated. Sigh...  I don't like feeling like this. Is there something I can do to control it? Someone told me to concentrate on small things like making other people smile etc. Is that possible if I myself am not smiling?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Consider this..  Boy meets girl. After some time (days/weeks/months/years) Boy realises Girl is a psycho. Boy runs away from Girl.  What would you do if you're in the Girl's situation? Would you change yourself i.e personality, character etc that makes you a 'psycho'? Or would you wait until the so-called 'Mr Right-For-You' comes and 'rescue' you? And accept you as you are- psyco and all?   *Ninie! Jawaaab!!*   Hehe, joking..  p.s: right guys, now I have to think whether I should go to my friend's wedding or not (we weren't that friendly but i'll be seeing my long-lost friend from Down Under and we have A LOT of catching up to do) but I'm SO different now, I'm afraid to imagine their reactions to this 'new' me. Tough choice eh.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Boy, I sounded pathetic.  Have you ever noticed that cats are like your friends? I mean, there are different types of cats (character-wise) as there are differet types of friends. I started realising this when I was playing with my cats (innocently) and somehow it strucked to me how similar cats are to my friends. These are some observations that I have made.  1. The cat that sits, eats and sleeps with you i.e Simba    This is similar to friends who stand by you no matter what. They would do 'anything' for you, and they really mean it. Of course, sometimes, things get in the way and they can't so-to-say 'perform their duty', but you know they would have if the train was not cancelled, or their boyfriend/girlfriend was not on the phone with them etc. This is what they all call a 'true friend', and we usually only have one or two of this type of friend. That is, if we're lucky enough.   2. The cat that sits, eats but doesn't sleep with you i.e Tiger    This is the friends who are with you in happy times, but disappear when you're down. It doesn't really matter why they suddenly disappear. It can be that they can't be bothered to make you feel better again, or that they just feel uncomfortable dealing with depressed people in depressed situations, or that you've done the same thing and he's now in revenge. The main point is, one minute he's laughing with you, and the next you're crying by yourself.  3. The cat that only comes to you when you have food i.e Coco    This is the friends who only comes to you when they need something. You know the type. I don't need to say more.  4. The cat that you don't see for days and comes to you at times when you need them i.e Ricky    This is similar to friends you haven't talked to for a LONG time i.e months/years (maybe because of distance, laziness or whatever), but you know that you can still call them out of the blue and catch up with each other (read: how are you? fine? did u know...) and cry your hearts out to him/her.   5. The neighbour's new cute cat i.e kucing-oren-tak-tau-nama    The new friends you got to know only recently but you feel totally comfortable talking with. About everything and anything. It doesn't happen that often, not unless you're a very talkative person who talks about everything and anything to everyone anyway.  There you go. These are what I have observed so far.   Oh, and I have 5 cats, not including the kucing-oren-tak-tau-nama cat. Coz technically that's not my cat. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Get a grip, zana..
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhhh... who am I kidding? I just want to be manja-ed..
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I long for someone.  Was in the clinic today when these newly-weds came in for a consultation. They got married a month ago. I know, baru je sebulan right? But they look SO perfect for each other and SO happy. Blissful even. I want that.  You know all this hoo-haas about women and men should be treated as equals? I don't agree with that. Personally, even though I would like my (future) partner to respect me etc, I would not mind a man who can 'control' me. Not in a "I tell you what to do 24 hours a day" kind of thing. But, you know, someone who can tell me if I'm doing something wrong and correct me. Someone who can guide me I suppose. Someone who can drive and one who won't make me feel scared sitting in the passenger's seat (been there, done that).:)  Someone to ground me  I don't like being the dominant one. I feel like I'm the big sister all over again. Age is not an issue, but I'm thinking of dating someone older next time. I've been with guys younger than me (7 months, 10 months..). Not that much difference but I don't like feeling like I'm older than they are (of course, I am). But then again, I guess age is not really an issue, as long as the guy is matured.  It all comes down to one reason- I think I want these kind of things because I don't want to be able to 'lawan cakap suami'. You know, I want to be able to respect the guy. I want to be able to say "yeah, he's right. I'll do that", not "he doesn't know what he's saying. Know-it-all". I guess for me it should be 80% equality, not 100%.  That's why I think my break-up was a blessing in disguise. It really is (cuma the way it happened and the process are so damn painful). We were equals. Sometimes I feel I was the dominant one, and I didn't like it. But somehow, that worked well. Most of the time. I guess he thought that's what I wanted, but I have never really thought about it until we broke up. I was unhappy about a lot of things but I didn't know WHY. I still don't know the reasons. Is it because of the fact that he used to call me his 'big sis' when we were friends? and somehow subconsciously that idea stucked in my head until now? and why can't I trust his driving? (it's a small issue but it's so frustrating)  And do I really believe in everything I've written so far? At the moment, yes. But I realised that I don't know the answers to a lot of questions. I'm confused now..
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My youngest brother was playing this song just now, and I know I've heard it before but I never paid much attention to it. When I listen to a song, I don't usually listen to the lyrics. I lagi suka dengar 'irama' and layan blues.. heh. layan blues best jugak kadang2. especially when you have a crush on someone. you know, that 'lovey-dovey' feeling you get when that certain someone is somewhere within 100 metres radius, or when that certain someone accidently looks your way and you turn your head around so quickly it could have been dislocated. that sort of stuff. i miss those days in college. i had crushes on loads of guys and boy, did i go for it. and when i think about it now, part of me can't believe how much i have changed and part of me miss it. i do.    A BETTER MAN by Robbie Williams (the cute ass man)   Send someone to love me I need to rest in arms Keep me safe and warm In pouring rain Give me endless summer Lord I feel the cold Feel I'm getting old before my time  As my soul heals the shame I will grow through this pain Lord I'm doing all I can To be a better man  Go easy on my conscience coz it's not my fault I know I've been told to take the blame Rest assured my angels will catch my tears Walk me out of here I'm in pain  As my soul heals the shame  I will go through this pain Lord I'm doing all I can To be a better man  Once you've found that lover you're homeward bound Love is all around, love is all around I know some have fallen on stoney ground But love is all around  Send someone to love me I need to rest in arms Keep me safe and warm in pouring rain Give me endless summer Lord I feel the cold Feel I'm getting old before my time  As my soul heals the shame I will go through this pain Lord I'm doing all I can To be a better man   P.S: I just HAD to copy and paste this thing in my blog. It's such a good advice that I know I'll be going back to this entry in the future to remind myself. See? Told ya i was gonna record it..=)   "the concept is simple. to get out of it completely, it is a continous battle. a battle uphill. everytime you get news of things like these, you'll lose a few hundred meters. and fall a bit back down the slope. then you've got to do the few hundred meters all over again." 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have never written about my brothers and so thought it would be a good idea to do that now that I have got a lot of time in my hands. PLUS, someone thought I anak tunggal since I've never mentioned about my bros (rasa bersalah je). PLUS I don't have anything interesting to talk about, just some crap about what I do during the day and stuff like that.. Hence the topic for today..  So, where do I start?..I have 4 younger brothers. Yup, you heard it. FOUR. I'm the only girl, and I have to admit that sometimes it works to my advantage. :) BUT I also have to say that NO, I am not the manja/spoiled type of girl. At least, I don't think so. :P  The first boy in the family is now 20 years old. His name is Luqman but his friends call him Berg. If you know my dad's name, you would understand (Ramli=Burger=Berg). KIDS.. We have an interesting relationship. I remember how we used to quarrel like there's no tomorrow. Come to think about it, kesian my mom and dad. When i say gaduh, we really GADUH. Tarik rambut and everything. Siap pernah try nak pakai pisau. sheeeshhh... When he started taking martial arts (I was 8) I tried not to cari gaduh with him, coz I knew I'd lost. We were not that close as kids. We played together ( me being the only girl always played with the boys in the neighbourhood) a lot. You know, football and that kind of stuff.  I went to Taiping in 1996, and at the same time, he went to RMC. I noticed that we mellowed down a bit after that, and recently (when I went to the UK to study) I find myself talking to him more. Not that much but enough to update him about things that are happening in my life, and vice versa. The sweetest thing he has offered to do is to beat up my exes when they broke up with me. =) I knew he was just joking (but I DO know that he can arrange this kinda stuff) so I declined, jokingly. Hehe.. Nah, I'm not that bad.  Academically he's alright, and I know that he feels a bit 'pressured' by my parents, being the first son and all. I'm sure he can do whatever he wants to do cuma sometimes he can a bit lazy. I envy (in a good way) his PR skills. He can talk to ANYONE at ANYTIME and most people feel comfortable talking to him. I, on the other hand, am quite quiet in public, unless I'm in a familiar crowd. Not that I have a problem with self-esteem or anything like that (well, sometimes I do) but I feel that if someone else is doing the talking why should I interrupt right? But that's me.   The only thing I'm worried about him is his health. He eats a lot and smokes like a chimney. I know he's still young, but I've seen a lot of young people in the hospital with health problems. I don't want him to be one of them.   And I hope he won't get married before me. But I have doubts. ;)    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      She's the love of his life? fuck, that hurts..  What can I say though? I thought HE was the love of MY life, but now that I think about it, I realised I have NOT met the love of my life. and as I said before, I'm not even sure if i believe in it. sheeessshhh, how people change..  But to those who believe in the 'love of my life' shit, how do you know if it's love or lust? and if it's the 'love of your LIFE'? that's pretty serious right? and do you wanna know why i don't believe in that? Coz he said the same thing to me! Is it something EVERYONE says to someone (s)he is love with? Then what is so special about it? What did I say about professional bullshitters?  I shouldn't have been a busybody. serves me right.:)  p.s: *what goes around comes around...what goes around comes around...what goes around comes around..what...*
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did a half-day of clinic today, and watched Shrek 2 with a friend at KLCC in the afternoon. Quite a funny movie. I absolutely looovvvee the puss-in-boots. He's SO cute, reminds me of my cat, Ricky.   We (me and two student nurses) followed Dr Salim for his ward round this morning, and he belanja-ed us breakfast. We were talking about families and stuff and one of the nurses told me that her brother used to study in Taiping. Turns out that we were in the same batch and I know this guy! What a small world it is eh? Sigh...those days.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is the 14th of June, exactly 3 months since The Breakup. I started writing again (in my blog) in May as I felt that it would be therapeutic for me to keep a journal after the first few stressful weeks. And after 3 months, it is probably a good idea to reflect back on how far I have come after that big dip in my life. And these are what I have concluded so far.  1. I think I'm doing just fine. I have not broken down (as in proper shirt-drenching crying) since at least 6 weeks ago. That is quite impressive for miss ash (yours truly that is) coz at times i can be quite emotional, and compared to my first breakup, i'm doing waaayyy better at the moment. probably because i'm 'numb' to these feelings dah? i dunno..  2. I miss having a close friend like him, but I know that I'm better off without him. I can befriend other people, that should not be a problem. BUT yeah, I do miss his companionship now that I think about it. ALTHOUGH.. that does not mean that i want his companionship. not at the moment anyway.   3. I don't hate men. Really, I don't. :).. In fact, quite a few of my close friends are guys, and I really appreciate their no-nonsense attitude when they're listening (or trying very hard to listen) to my problems.. or maybe whining by their definition.   4. I would not be this strong if it was not for my family and friends. and i now realize who my best friend is all along- my mom.  5. I don't believe in 'i will forgive but i won't forget'. it's noble but i just can't do it. I will forgive (sedangkan nabi maafkan umat, i know) but it takes a long time before my heart catches up with my brain.   6. I will get through this. It's only a small glitch, and everything will be ok.   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was browsing through some blogs and came upon one that caught my eye. and my heart. a single dad, dedicating his life to his only daughter. part of me find it heartbreaking, part of me is in awe. what i went through was so minor compared to what he's going through. but i've heard of , and seen a lot of cases like that. it has become a norm these days, but it shouldn't be. i think it's wrong. although, in some cases these kind of things are inevitable. my cousin got married 4 years ago to a man we thought was 'alright' for her. but he meant the world to her so my uncle and aunt obliged. they got a daughter a year after that, and soon after the first-born, another son. he was not there to witness the birth of their first son, had an affair and left her a few months after that. they're now divorced, and the two kids live with their mom. now, he has remarried, adn i can't even imagine how my cousin is feeling at the moment.  this is a part of what was written in the guy's blog. it's a letter that Ronald Reagan wrote to his friend in 1951, from the book 'Reagan- a life in letters'   "...You say you believe there is one love in life for each of us-this is just not true. Can you believe that God means for millions of really young people to go on through life alone because a war robbed them of their first loves? Maybe you'll resent this Florence but I must say it - you have to look into your own heart and ask yourself if you really believe in one love now lost to you or if this is a shield behind which you hide because your past experience did not measure up to your girlhood dreams and now you fear men.  I will grant you that all of us grow up with a "moonlight and roses" outlook on romantic relationships and sometimes it comes hard to reconcile this dream with the actualities of physical contact. To show you how "over idealistic" my training was - I awoke to the realization (almost too late) that even in marriage I had a little guilty feeling about sex, as though the whole thing was tinged with evil.  A very fine old gentleman started me out on the right track by interesting me in the practices of, or I should say, moral standards of, the primitive peoples never exposed to our civilization - such as Polynesians. These people who are truly children of nature and thus of God, accept physical desire as a natural, normal appetite to be satisfied honestly and fearlessly with no surrounding aura of sin and sly whispers in the darkness. By our standards they are heathens but they are heathens without degeneracy, sex crimes, physcho-neurosis and divorce.  I guess what I am trying to say is that I oppose the dogmas of some organized religions who accept marital relationship only as a "tolerated" sin for the purpose of conceiving children and who believe all children to be born in sin. My personal belief is that God couldn't create evil so the desires he planted in us are good and the physical relationship between a man and woman is the highest form of companionship.  If I can, I want to say all this to my daughter. I want her to know that nothing between her and the man she loves can be wrong or obscene, that desire in itself is normal and right. There is one other thing I think she should know. If some man she finds attractive or likeable feels desire for her, like any parents, I hope she'll have the common sense and good taste not to be promiscuous or involve herself in casual affairs but (and this is equally important) I don't want her to be disgusted and convinced that his desire is an indication of moral decay and vulgarity. Of course a man feels desire for an attractive woman - nature intended that he should and something would be amiss if he didn't. A girl's judgement of this man should be based only on his respect for her wishes but don't ask him not to feel an instinct as much a part of him as hunger and thirst.  The world is full of lonely people-people capable of happiness and of giving happiness and love is not a magic touch of cosmic dust that preordains two people and two people only for each other. Love can grow slowly out of warmth and companionship and none of us should be afraid to seek it."  i shall now retreat to my humble room and start my much-needed reading.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      went to a kenduri kahwin last night. my aunt's relatives who are living in london threw a wedding reception in KL. their 2 youngest sons got married last week in london, and they came back to malaysia as most of their relatives are here. what is it with weddings that give people the rights to pressurise the singletons to 'find a man quickly and settle down'? somehow jokingly, they told me 'your wedding will be beautiful. i give you 3 years- you'll find the one and get married'. is it because i'm the eldest in my family, and not to mention the only girl, that they put so much hope on me to find the 'perfect one', get married and get loads of beautiful little juniors. i'm not sure if i even believe in 'the one'. i don't know if i have met 'the one'. this is all so..pressurising. and stupid me said to my mom "well, if you think there's someone you know that would be perfect for me, then go on". DID I REALLY SAY THAT?????? DID I?? I was joking obviously. but now i'm not so sure if i was.  I really think that i'm ready to settle down. i'm getting tired of all these heartaches and depressions. i don't think this is desperation. I just want to find a decent guy, and open a new chapter of my life. or is that just the post-wedding me talking? am i crazy to think this way?  i don't know.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm so fat...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i think something's wrong with my previous template, ergo (hehe..) i have changed it to this one. but i prefer the pink one!!! tengok la nanti.. when i haven't got anything useful to do i'll check for nicer ones..   went to berjaya times square with me mom tadi. had lunch with her and her friends and went to see some people singing their hearts out for the m'sian idol audition. it was so funny- not funny haha, but funny entertaining. maybe a bit of funny haha as well. :) . there were loads of hotties but my bet is they can't sing to save their lives. (i'm so bad..)   tonight will be the first episode of malaysian idol. my mom works with tmnet, and they're one of the main sponsors of the programme, which explains why i'm still writing about it, and why i have to promote it. saw a william hung look-alike, although we didn't get the chance to hear his 'melodious' voice. and for a second i thought guy sebastian was there, but it turns out that someone with sebastian's HAIRSTYLE was there. oh well.. what did i expect? kalau he was there, i would have begged him to serenade me..sigh..:).. have i said that i'm a fool for romance? (but BEGGING him to sing a song to me would not be so romantic would it?)  I have two days to relax before one more week of bone-breaking work with Dr Salim. It's really not that tough, but it's really tiring having to stand on my poor feet for 6-7 hours. baik jadi tentera macam ni.. Anyways, I better do my reading before Sunday night comes. i procrastinate too much, too often. and i better start exercising coz I have grown even fatter now, what with everyone forcing me to eat etc.. but i'm so lazy...:( 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Saw a patient with hereditary cerebellar ataxia in clinic today. That means she has very poor balance and finds it difficult to walk without any help. Cerebellar gait is characterised as broad-based gait, and it's not surprising that people stare at her. She's only 33, and was married, but her husband left after she developed the problems. I didn't know what to say. But she's a strong woman. I guess I still believe in 'love' and that you can love a person too much that you will stand by that person no matter what. I believe that I'm that type of person and would like to think that I'll be lucky enough to find a guy who's like that. Yeah...it's not impossible.. tapi susah.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Saw a patient in coma today. he's a really young chap, probably even younger than me. Was admitted on sunday, and he was already in coma. They thought he had meningitis based on his symptoms but investigations showed another thing- he was on drugs, and they suspect that he took some ecstasy plus alcohol. Things are not looking very good for him. He is now in the ICU and ventilated. Hopefully he'll make it, but kalau tak, what a waste. Just for a few hours of 'good time'.. You can do that in lots of other ways. I have thought of a lot of things eg stuff to make me feel better, u know..to keep my mind off things. Of course la..almost everyone pernah TERFIKIR. But it's not worth it. Apa2 jadi, orang lain susah. One should not depend on anyone expect oneself. It's true. How many cases have you heard of - anak pun makan duit mak bapak. You would think that parents should be able to be dependent on their children once they are old and tak bermaya. But ye lah, shit happens. People are deceiving. Exceptions exist though, and I intend to be one (parent-child case. Me-everyone, I have learnt to trust myself more. No more expectations from anyone else. In the end, I yang makan hati).   I think it's true anyway.   How would you feel if someone told you that you only have so and so more months/years to live? And you have a family with 3 young kids. It's so saddening.  Points to ponder. Maut tak menunggu.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am so penat. Started at 9 today and finished at 6. A 9-hour day. I haven't had that since, probably..errmm...I can't even remember. Saw a lot of things today. Motor neuron disease, cervical myelopathy, lots of migraine cases, substance abuse, and a patient with a possible psyc illness. He was a really weird chap. Repeated almost everything the doctor said, and according to him, it only started a week ago. He told us that he likes this girl, and he had hurt (not physically) her or something like that, and the girl has not given him an answer ie whether she likes him too. And dia jadi tak senang pikir. Dr asked him whether he drinks alcohol and he said "ada minum?ada..kat mana?kadang2 warung.." I mean..we didn't know whether to believe him or not. But poor chap la.. It's probably a genuine psychiatry problem, but it's also possible that he was too worried about this girl that he becomes like that. Some people can tahan rejection, but some cannot I guess. I'm grateful that I'm alright. Kadang2 sakit hati, tapi apa nak buat. Buat orang sakit hati berdosa right?..Takpela..What doesn't kill me only makes me stronger..  Dr Salim told me that I need to do 5 hours of reading everyday if I want to pass with distinction. Something for me to keep in mind. He was one of the first batch of medical students in UKM, and the best student. And he's also the fifth neurologist in Malaysia. Very impressive CV. And I guess, if I want to be like him, or close to what he's like, I have to be more hardworking. And I should be able to do that now that I don't have any other commitments. Malam2 boleh la study kuat2. This is a good opportunity for me, and I should take advantage of it. It's not impossible to pass with distinction, I think. It's hard but not impossible. That reminds me now that I have to go and have my shower, pray, eat and start reading. I smell like a kambing..
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I'll work in the UK until I get my specialisation, balik sini and work with a university and become a professor or masuk private. I don't care if I won't get married. At the moment, to me, all men are $*@@#!! Professional bullshitters.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      chin up zana! It's normal to feel like this once in a while.. you're only human.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Started my work attachment at Tawakal today at 10 with Dr Salim. Spent the whole day till 6 at his clinic, acting as though I know the stuff he was talking about and panicking everytime he asked me the diagnosis. He can be a bit garang, but overall, he's a really good teacher. Saw loads of stuff today, and I'm quite impressed with that. There was this 30-year-old chap with newly-diagnosed Parkinson's Disease. Poor guy. And a makcik with a metastatic nodule in her brain. Plus loads of other stuff that I have forgotten about. Cervial spondyliosis, epilepsy, anxiety neurosis (supposed to be handled by a psychiatrist but there's still so much stigma attached to psyc illnesses. Not surprised..), Menniere's dss, carpal tunnel, De Quervain tendospondylitis?? And the list goes on..All in a day!! Makes me sound like one of those medical student in ER?? Naahhh.. Never in my life.. Tipu je tu ..No wonder I'm knackered. And you can't blame me if all I did was tercengang and angguk my kepala.. Like a stupid sheep..Oh well, this just means that I need to brush up and read some stuff tonight before I sleep. No worries..  And I saw SM Salim jugak coz he came to the clinic with his wife. And I baru realised that one of his daughters, who's a year older than me, went to BB. But I don't think she recognised me coz I look very different now. I was VERY faaa--aaaatt (ala Chandler). Am still fat, But as Neon stressed it to me, "Fat is OK".. hehehe..  And I'm pretty proud of myself coz I've learnt how to play 'the reason' on guitar. But sekarang bila dah dengar banyak kali sangat, boring pulak..But I still like it. Romantic..  OK..Better do some reading if I want to survive tomorrow.. Or he'll think I'm a real dunce. Buat malu my dad je. Or should I do that after Fear Factors??? hmmmm...  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's nearly 6 pm. We've been out since 10 am and I'm so tired. And I haven't done any reading for tomorrow. I know, I'll just ask HIM questions. Talk about other stuff. I'm sure he'll want to borak2 first.Haha...Tapi takkan sampai petang macam tu kot...sheesshh..  Am I doing the right thing by not thinking about things? With my first breakup, I was always thinking about stuff and I was  miserable  for months. Crying and everything. A miserable zana is not a pretty sight i tell you now. But now, because I'm so tired of caring about other people and issues they have, I just can't be bothered (plus, my friends kata baik tak payah fikir). But sometimes I wonder, if I tak fikir sekarang, will they come haunting me in the future? Know what I mean? On the other hand though, I really don't want to think about it, coz I feel what's done is done, it's all history and I don't want to feel down because of him. I don't want to stay unhappy any longer. I don't want to let him affect how I feel throughout the day. Why should I? But senang cakap dari buat..I'll try though..  Have migraine now. Gonna lie down for a bit. Adieu.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I 've been thinking that one day, I'll show him who he's messing with. I'll be a really succesful person, rich and happy, have a beautiful marriage and kids, and live in a big house. But although I want all those things, I don't want to work my ass off because of him. It's just not right, as one of my friends said. That's just like being a slave to him subconsciously..I know.. I'll change my mindset soon..  Off to bed now..
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Been doing some thinking these past few days.. and had quite long chats with a few people gak..and i don't know...i'm so confused..  Talked with Tok Mak, and she said a few things that made me think..but I think the one big thing she's worried about is me finding a guy.. like, NOW. or AS SOON AS POSSIBLE. She told me that "kalau tak cari sekarang, nanti susah dapat..". But I'm ONLY 23 right? 23 is young. It is. Although, I know part of what she said is true. I've thought about it jugak. I'll be working in UK for at least 2 years after I graduate, and although a lot of people, including my mom, told me that "mesti ada orang punye.." I have doubts jugak. I mean.. I've been studying there for the past 4 years, and takde pun jumpa anyone that suits me. But then again, maybe I wasn't looking for anyone pun. Hmm..I don't know. I guess I have considered a few people, but.. Again, I have doubts.   On a different note, what should I do with things that remind me of him? We were best friends in college, and we were always writing to each other (out of boredom), and I have a shoebox full of his letters. I may dislike him at the moment, but like it or not, I still have a soft spot for him. But they (the letters) will be really useless in the future, and I won't be needing them anymore. And almost every pictures I have ada his face..I'll think about this later..  And for various reasons, I'm starting my work attachment at Tawakal on Monday. No more day naps for me. Boo Hoo.. That means I have to read stuff tomorrow..Don't wanna embarrass myself in front of my dad's friend..Wish me luck, coz I'll be needing it.  And I've also become a new fan of Hoobastank's song- The Reason.. I think it's romantic.. I'm a fool for love..haha..:)..but NO, i don't think of him when I hear this song.. I'd be an idiot..;)  I'm not a perfect person Ther are many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you and so I have to say before I go that I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me, to change who I used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday and all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away and be the one who catches all your tears that's why I need you to hear  I've found a reson for me, to change who I used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you  I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you and so I have to say before I go that I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me, to change who I used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you I've found a reason to show, a side of me you didn't know a reason for all that I do, and the reason is you  SIGH...    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Something I found from a magazine. I'm not pulling your legs, don't be surprised.  "  Semen is good for wrinkles ."   What the... But apparently it's a skin myth and according to this mag, " ..it does have a temporary skin tightening effect. But once skin is rinsed all returns to normal. A mosturiser is a better bet- not to mention more hygenic".   Like DUH!! Even I know that. I have NEVER heard of this so-called myth before, and I hope I won't hear it from anyone in the future..You know, eg when moms & grandmas & aunties & cousins & sisters all gather around you the night before your wedding and give you 'advices' on what-to-do and what-not-to-do with your dear husband.. some of those old wives tales are so silly they give me headaches. Gosh..I hope I won't have to go through that..;P  And one more thing I found.. What do men really mean when they say "I don't deserve you" aka "It's not you, it's me"... This is what this writer wrote..and I think part of it is true..   " Men have realised that the old chestnut is as predictable as Britney's dance moves, so they've attempted to mask the act of bastardry which prompted it- or is about to- with a pseudo compliment. What makes it all the more interesting is that he genuinely believes that this 'revelation'- as if you didn't know from day one that he didn't deserve you- will soften the dollops of rejection he's tossing your way. This statement has the pungent stench of cowardice wafting from every syllable and deserves neither sympathy nor understanding.   ... He'd like you to believe he's looked deep into his soul and had some sort of spiritual epiphany in which he's realised he's simply undeserving of a partner of your calibre. The spin he's selling is that your continued association is some sort of travesty of natural justice and he's doing the noble thing. YEAH RIGHT"   OKAY. So not all men are like that. I agree. If it suits you better, change the 'he's to 'she'. I think it works both ways anyway.   And check out this book by Andy Riley- 'The Book of Bunny Suicides'. Damn funny. Just makes me laugh like MAD. Super hilarious cartoons. These bunnies just find their ways to..well, die.. Eg by Darth Vader's light saber, supergluing themselves to a diving submarine, hanging around under a loose stalactite, hanging around sunbathing while the rest of the animals quickly board the Noah's ark.. Get the picture now? If not, go to the website @ http://www.bookofbunnysuicides.com/   I'm evil...;)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm back, and all tanned. or rather, gelap. It was a much-needed vacation to keep my mind off things for a while. Lepaked by the beach with my mom after dinners and had some very LONG chats. It was very refreshing to see her perceptions of things, and it makes me value her more. But I won't say what she told me here. That's between me and her.  I have been watching Malay soap operas dah sekarang, and I quite enjoy them. Maybe sebab dah lama tak tengok kot. hehe..and I just realised that Jehan Miskin (one of Cleo's Bachelors last year) is now an actor. And my long-lost love, Hans Isaac, is appearing on TV more often. Like just now, I saw him in a wet suit. Yummy..  Was in the car when I heard Pizza Hut's ad- it goes something like " Show me the sausage..(and then ada bunyi zip seluar)...etc....with a creamy cheesy filling..Yummm.." It sounds SOOOO dodgy..and disgusting..   One unrelated question- What does it mean when you keep on having recurrent dreams about someone?? I don't do it purposely though..   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Was feeling shit.ty. Suddenly felt so very lonely. Locked myself in my room. Put on (yup what else) Kris' album, full blast. Drew a bath. Oil burner on one side, luxurious piece of chocolate with hazelnut on the other side of the bath tub. Cleo in hand. Took out Lush's  urlLink  Tisty Tosty Bath   Ballistics   bought at Heathrow just before my flight home. Seven real rosebuds floating in the water. Bliss. Spent one whole hour by myself, reading craps from Cleo, and not thinking about anything or anyone else.   My mind. 50% on soon-to-be ex-crush. 20% on current problem. 20% on nothing-in-particulars. 10% on this horrible horrible grammatically-challenged entry. 0% on diet. Where are my cats when I need them? If only crying helps, KL will be flooding by now.   I wish. That I can control what I think. I could probably do that, technically. But reality is, it's hard isn't it? I wish I can sieve the thoughts that go through my mind. I am tired of&nbsp;being disturbed by all these troublesome thoughts. I'm tired of straining my brain cells thinking about all this nonsense.     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "Control what you can, accept what you can't and practise knowing the difference"  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'll pay good money to get this tee shirt.      I feel like having a chick flick marathon. I need to know that good things do happen in life. They're fairy tales, I know, but it's nice to see a happy ending after the characters go through those shitty times. Happy endings calm me down.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Listening to Kris Dayanti's Menghitung Hari album.    Scared. Tired of being evil, yet not ready to be nice. Not sure how it's going to be. Will it be weird? There's a possibility that it won't. There's a possibility that things will pick up where they were left.&nbsp;Not sure if that's wanted. Mind is saying no. Heart has always been saying the opposite thing, whatever mind says. Weird.   Crush- not working. Not with capital N, O and T. Hints accepted. Duly noted. Two weeks. That's all needed. Focus on study, and nothing more. Crush will probably be forgotten. Hopefully.   Female ego. Infected. Now what do you have to say about that? Probably worse than male's.   Not loved by people. Loved by mosquitoes. Pain. Good friends coming back from the UK end of the week. Girlfriends. No more lepak-ing in Soton. Not with them anyway. Meet up with Shahrin & Leo for drinks tomorrow, no? See la how. Meeting up with friends do wonders for stressed and confused mind. That and shopping. For a few hours, problems were forgotten. Felt calm and happy. Now, they're all coming back. Slowly, but they're getting there. Yoga is probably the answer, yes?  Really really don't know what to expect. Pray. Best thing.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know what came over me. I'm very&nbsp;'de weird these days. Firstly, I jogged. As I have mentioned in my earlier post, I don't run simply because I look funny running. But I guess miracles do happen coz I actually enjoyed my jog, even though it was only on the treadmill. Tee hee.. Secondly, I had dinner (no, this is not the miracle. i do eat dinner everyday) and had like, LOADS of rice. Which, by the way, is not good for me at the moment. Limited carbo after 6, yo. Basic rule for all dieters. Thirdly,.. well, thirdly, I don't seem to be able to control my emotions these days. As I have said to some friends, I have concluded that falling in lust/love and breaking up are the same.&nbsp;They are both&nbsp;heartbreaking. No matter how you look at it, you have to admit it, the feelings you get with both are the same. Frustrating. Tsk. But as a fellow blogger said it, as long as I'm still breathing, things aren't  that  bad. Yup yup.   Nothing special happened today. Spent loads of time in the morning facing my loyal computer, exercised, showered, had lunch, went out with a friend, came back, computer again, dinner and here I am. Bought Kris Dayanti's album (the one in concert), a bit disappointed coz my friend told me that her Mencintaimu album is much better. Oh well, just my luck. There goes my RM20. Could have been put into my Gucci Handbag Trust. Will strategically cast a spell on my dad while he's asleep tonight so that he will donate a gracious amount into the trust. Current balance is only RM 2.50. Not much. Loooonnng way to go, madam.   On the matter of what-is-making-ash-crazy, I... think I.... will shut up. Keep quiet. Senyap. Not say anything, and vanish from this world,&nbsp;hoping that (s)he (oooo...scandalousssssssss) won't notice me. MUCH safer, and LESS heartbreaking. Trust me, it's  way  easier&nbsp;asking my dad for a gucci handbag (with a cheeky smile that is) than telling someone that I would like to 'get to know her/him better'. The outcomes would be the same (a firm NO! after a big big laugh that is) but at least with my dad, he would know that I was joking. (Cheit. No wonder I'll never get the bag. My parents think I am trying to be funny???)  SO , in conclusion ladies and gentlemen, I am withdrawing myself. Trying to save myself from getting deeper into this misery, with unknown final destination. My heart (oh my god, this is going to be so cheesssyyy) has just been mended, and I'm not sure if it can go through a heartache again this soon.  O -kaaay. I surrender, white flags all around. THAT was VERY corny. I'll pen (finger, whatever..) off now. Don't want to risk writing another corny sentence.   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I would like a single room for tonight please. Just for one. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "   semalaman terkenangkan dirimu  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; mengalir air mataku membasahi bibir&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;mengapa kau sanggup meninggalkan diriku  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; sedangkan kau tahu perasaan ini   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; kau berjanji aku lah kekasihmu  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; sanggup kusingkirkan semua cinta&nbsp;yang lalu  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; tidak ku duga ini akan terjadi&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;kata perpisahan yang kau pinta&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; biarkanlah biarkan aku hidup sendirian  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; tak inginku mengenangkan kisah lama  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; biarkanlah biarkan aku hidup sendirian  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; kerana hati ini telah dilukai   "        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  ~Kris Dayanti~       Going out today, meeting a good friend and having a 'small talk'. Good. At least, I'll be able to get my mind off some things that are making me crazy at the moment. I'm going bonkers. And I don't like it one bit. I am seriously NOT myself. Ain't gonna change anytime soon I habaq you now. Mega Sale ni, CDs pun sale ke? Been listening to Kris Dayanti a lot these days, think I should get her album. Lagu dah berzaman, baru nak tersangkut. I'm slow people. Hmmph :). Too many things on my mind. Some I don't even dare voice them out loud. People read this blog, and I don't want those certain people to know how I feel. I'm egoistic. I want to appear strong all the time, but deep down in my heart (gila cheeeessyyy :P).. anyway, deep down, Tuhan saja yang tau. My brain cells are all tangled up, some going towards one direction, some the other way. Seriously. I'm one very confused human being. I know what I should do though. Make myself busy. Go out. Talk to friends. Search for handbags on the Net (not that I'm going to buy one anyway. It's seasonal, really. Have always been like this. Last time I wanted a Gucci was last January, then the obsession just faded away. It's like when one of your friends let out a really stinky fart, and after a while, you don't even notice it went away. Gross, I know.) See? I'm NOT myself. I don't usually talk about fart. I just have to do SOMETHING. Work out, that's a better option. Hopefully I won't resolve to retail therapy this afternoon. My bank balance is really suffering right now. Not now.       I'm doomed.       
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Quitting.   That's what I'm thinking. Maybe I should stop blogging. It's starting to get too personal. and I'm beginning to feel uncomfortable. my fault really.   Will think about it.   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Things to do today:    Exercise . Run on the treadmill, cycling is not enough. Am still not fit enough. Don't like running on the road. Feels so tarmac-ish. Have lost 2 inches from waist, more to go, especially if I wanna get into modelling ( yeah .  riiighttt ...). Just kidding. Have to lose more if I want anyone to be interested in me. Half-kidding. :P   Pack . Moving to Subang on Saturday. Flight is about 13-14 days after that. :( Will miss friends. Looking forward to living in a new house. New environment. Have this mental image that I will be lepakking more in my brothers' room as theirs sound much cooler than my room--> ikea-ish. The room I'm going to stay in is not exactly my room. It's a guest room. Cum bridal room (hey, that's what my mom said. and she was serious. sheeeshh..). Will only be my room when I'm back in KL. And I guess when I get married, which fortunately&nbsp;for our guests, will probably be in the next millennium or so.    Sort out my room . It's messy. I don't know how Ninie survived in that room with all that mess. I'm such a bad hostess. :P It should be called the store room.   Lepak with mama . As mentioned earlier, I have been out a lot last week. I am usually quite a homey person, except when Ninie comes down to KL. Tee hee.. Gonna lepak and talk with her tonight. It's nice listening&nbsp;to&nbsp;the things she says. Very uplifting and motivating. Most of the time. :P Seriously though, MOMS- they have a really weird sixth sense. They KNOW stuff. I don't know how they do it, but they're like..know everything. Shheesshh.. Talk about black magic.    What I feel like doing today:    NOTHING . Am feeling really... one-kind today. Feel like doing nothing, absorb myself in misery, listen to jiwang songs and lie down and feel sad. NOT a good thing. But that's just how I  feel . I won't necessarily end up doing that. Honestly, I might actually do that treadmill thingie. My brother's shoes are here next to me. Hmmph.    Crying . Is it true that women have to cry like, regularly? I have to admit that I used to cry...well, not regularly, but hmmph..I don't know.. like once a month? I have not cried for at least 3 months now. My heart feels stuffy and heavy. Shit. I sound like a loser. Whatever la, I feel bleerrghhh anyway.    &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How do you know if it's love or just lust? Love is such a deep word is it not? When&nbsp;a guy friend&nbsp;tells you&nbsp;that he's in love with someone without telling the particular girl first, what does that mean? Is that really 'love'? How can you tell?  So many questions with so little answers.&nbsp;  Have you had that fear when you like someone and thinks that 'NO WAY, JOSE (s)he won't like me and will actually  vomit  if (s)he hears about me liking her/him'? It is sickening. I remember that feeling and I can't believe that sooner or later I have to go through it again. You can't sleep coz you keep thinking of that person, you can't really eat coz you're high on adrenaline and your stomach feels full most of the time (which means that it might be good for my diet. have to jot this down in my weight loss notebook. first things first though, have to get a notebook), your heart beats like there's no tomorrow everytime you think about that person (which is  most  of the time) and makes you think that it's probably a good idea to get a life insurance in case you get a heart attack, you appear  blur  and  lost  to people around you and they'll start asking you questions like 'are you seeing double?', 'how many fingers can you see?' and 'tell me again, which planet are we on at the moment?'. Sigh. REALLY? I'll have to go through all that again? Why can't things be easier?  But I guess if everything goes well and if it's meant to be, it's all worth the 'debaran jantung' and all that shite. :) Right? I mean, it feels SO much better when you like someone and finds out that (s)he likes you too. Almost like you're high on  something . NO, not almost. Definitely  more  than when you're high on  something .&nbsp;And it's a bit different when someone you don't expect to like you suddenly confesses all her/his feelings to you. I  kinda  know. I've been there,&nbsp;even though it was only&nbsp;once. :P  I have always taken the safer option. Keep quiet and let things be. Not always la. From my experience, everytime I said anything about liking someone.., well, things just did not happen. D-UH la.. I'm still where I was when I started to notice boys. :P Maybe I'm jinxed. So, that's probably the reason why I am now afraid. Since then, Plan A has always been to shut up and pretend that I don't like the guy, or he'll run away. I'm not the only one to feel like this am I?   Back to that old black number 8 ball.   &nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ninie has gone back to Penang this afternoon. And I have about two and a half week before my flight to Heathrow. not that I'm counting. I haven't been updating my blog regularly since the BTN. I guess they have&nbsp;somehow secretly installed a chip in my head to stop me from lazing around, doing nothing and make me do something productive instead. Problem is, I&nbsp;don't think I've done anything productive since..ermm...well...let's not start 'membuka pekung di dada' shall we? I guess one good thing that has happened while Ninie was here is my expanding networking. haha.. another way of saying that I've been out more than I've been at home. Pandai.. Here's the gross breakdown of what we have been doing for the past week or so:    Saturday : Came back from BTN. Knackered. Ninie slept at 7 pm!! That was how tired we were. I thought we ate A LOT. Meal times masa kat BTN were at 7.30 am, 10.30 am, 1 pm, 4 pm, 6 pm and 11 pm. Came back worried that I've gained weight. Almost everyone was like "what happened to your diet, miss? out the window?". Sobsob..Turned out I actually  lost  2-3 kg that week. Weird.    Sunday : Ninie's birthday. Was still tired from BTN. Did not sleep well that night. Had really weird dreams. Woke up extra early (was hoping for a lie-in) as I had to help my mom shop for pinggan mangkuks. Went to Chow Kit (can't remember the last time I went there), and instead of the promised "sekejap je..", we&nbsp;were there for almost THREE hours. All for the pinggan mangkuks. Aiyoo.. The things I have to learn&nbsp;to be a wife. Ni baru the art of finding good but economical pinggan mangkuks. Tsk. (NO, not that I want to be one NOW. Oh, you know what I mean...). Had laksa johor at my aunt's place for lunch. Met up with friends for coffee. Dinner with Ninie. Lepak-ed till midnight.    Monday:  Went out the whole day. Dinner at Muray's place.    Tuesday:  Went to Mid-Vally and got a new pair of glasses. I'm in a retro mood. Will post a picture with my new glasses later. Went out with Ninie, Amir and Amir's friend.    Wednesday : Went out and shopped for new clothes. Had dinner at Nine. It was classic, and really nice.    Thursday:  Met up with Adeeb, a friend we met in BTN. A cool guy, even though a year younger than my brother. Heh. :P Nah, age means nothing. Doesn't mean you're immature if you're&nbsp;younger right? Later that night, had drinks/dinner with Shahrin and Leo. Great fun.    Friday:  Ninie and I met Trabye for lunch. Had low-cal, low-sugar, low-everything gellato. Nice. Last minute appointment with Shahrin and Leo (again..hehe) for dinner. Watched Spidey 2 (again..:P) with Ninie, my cousin and her date later that night. One thing I can say now is that we're a couple of spoiled girls now. Been treated like princesses, with people buying us lunch and dinner and whatever la lagi. Today, back to reality. Use own money. :P    Saturday:  Had breakfast at a mamak's with Ninie. After sending her to the KTM station, went out with mom and shopped. It's Mega Sale, and everyone&nbsp;went bonkers. I noticed that bila tak sale, I seem to want everything, but bila dah sale, malas pulak nak mencari. Too many people, too many stuff to go through, too many&nbsp;too many! Maybe the trick is to&nbsp;go on weekdays? Ntah. Am feeling ill, I think I'm now officially allergic to KLCC. Runny nose, headache, photophobia. Had yet another one of those weird dreams. I was having some sort of a hypoglycaemic attack while driving and had an accident. Scary.   So there you go. To put it simply, I have been meeting people, old and new, and it has been fun. Been meeting Shahrin and Leo quite often now, and I can safely say that I'm probably comfortable talking about stuff with Shahrin (Leo's a bit quiet, but a nice guy nonetheless. I think he's got killer eyes. Cair..:P No weird feelings though..). He told me things that made me understand what my ex did. And if what he said is true, I hold no grudge against&nbsp;my ex&nbsp;for wanting to get out there and explore the world. Yup, I can understand that, coz that is exactly what I feel now. I'm comfortable where I am now. I'm not saying that I don't want to be with anyone at the moment. I'm just saying that I'm happy with the way things are. It's probably not a good time for me to be in a serious relationship. I think I need more time. To understand why things happen to some people but not to others, understand why people act the way they do, understand what I want to do with my life. Who I want to be. I don't think I know a lot about relationships, probably a bit more, but I'm still one confused girl when it comes to issues like "does he or does he not like me?", "what does he mean when he said so and so?".. Yup, same as every other girl. and guy for that matter i guess.   Shahrin did ask me if I'm ready to go out dating (no, he was not asking me out. was just asking in general). I guess the answer is yes. That's how you meet people right? But fact is, all this while, I've only been on 'dates' with people from my circle of friends. Arghh...Right, right. I can hear someone shouting something along the line of "WELL, it's HIGH TIME that you go meet people OUTSIDE your circle of friends! D-UH!". Good point that (sheeshh..I sound like a schizophrenic..). Another thing to consider is, where and how do I find some decent guys? Tsk. Difficult task. We're back at square one people.   My ex is pissed off with me. Why? I don't know. I should not care about this should I? Whatever la. Talked to my mom, and SHE's pissed off. Enough bullshits already. I don't want to say anything dah. One thing though: Fuck off. And that's from my mom.   Not a very happy ending to this entry. Oh well. Shit happens. For some, it's probably 'wangi-ier'. For me, it stank, and it's time for me to be able to smell the flowers and shite&nbsp;like that. Give me a break. Please.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Woke up this morning with a sore throat. Ninie was sleeping beside me. Realised I had a very weird dream last night. Been having a few actually these days. In my dream, I was having a candle-lit dinner and dancing with someone, and it was simply  beautiful . But of course, it was only a dream. Hmmph.   Blame this on last night's outing. The ten of us went out for dinner and 'jazz' (it was not really jazz. Just a pianist and a singer singing jazz songs. Okay la.. a bit jazz-ish..:P) at Nine, a restaurant at The Ascott. It was magnificant. The food was delicious, the company was fun, and the singer was damn good. To quote a friend, "Any girl&nbsp;will go all cair if a guy brought her to this place". I have to second that. It was such a romantic place to dine and look into each other's eyes, whisper sweet nothings and hoping that no-one will hear you or they will barf out all their stomach's contents for sure. Seriously, it's definitely one of 'THE' place to go for 1. proposals and 2. break-ups (okay, this is also a quote from a friend. the same friend. probably a playboy. :P).   This is definitely one of the best times in my life. I don't mean the dinner. I mean everything that has been happening for the past few months. The friendships that have been broken, made and re-newed. Meeting new people. Learning about myself. Realising that I'm capable of more things than I allowed myself to. Noticing how badly I was treating  myself . How I would not allow myself to have more than what I actually deserve. Realising that there are more good people out there who are willing to help me. Not just the people I call friends. Having that title does not mean that they will actually help you. Friends can make or break you. Strangers are usually nicer to you, haven't you realised? Maybe because the expectations are not there. You expect some things from a friendship and that might strain the relationship. Point is, you only have yourself to depend on.   I have three more weeks before I fly off to Great Britain. It's gonna be sad. I have had so much fun here, and this is where I have re-built myself, with help from my family and friends, to be this person that I am now. Stronger. Emotionally and mentally. This is where I first heard of the most shocking news in my life, this is where I knew who my real friends are, this is where I started to understand my mom more. This is where I started reflecting on the things that I have done in my life, and realising that there are more things in life than you and me. This is where I learnt about life.   Been listening to this song since I heard it again at Nine.  Mencintaimu  by Kris Dayanti. The lyrics don't mean anything special to me, but I love the rythm. It's so soothing. And romantic. :) Enjoy.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mencintai mu    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Seumur hidupku Selamanya    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Setia menanti   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Walau di hati saja    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Seluruh hidup ku Selamanya   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Kau tetap milik ku    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Hanya satu yang tak mungkin kembali   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Hanya satu yang tak pernah terjadi   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Segalanya teramat berarti di hati ku Selamanya...    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mencintai mu   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Seumur hidup ku Selamanya   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Kau tetap milik ku    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;&nbsp;  It was a complete clone of an MRSM. The food, the atmosphere, the people, the 'semangat kebangsaan', the segregation. The accommodation was probably worse than MRSM, I have to say.  &nbsp;  We went to Sungai Sembilang, Kuala Selangor. On arrival, everyone was actually a  wee  bit excited when we were greeted by a stretch of sea. Bila sampai dorm, semua orang senyap. Shocked gila. I was dumbfounded. It was probably not that bad for other people, but I have not been in a boarding school since Banting (and even Banting was way better). We were literally out of words. Like, LITERALLY. For a good 10 minutes. There were&nbsp;6 toilets for 32 people. And no showers. We had to&nbsp;bathe in the toilets. It could have been better la considering that&nbsp;they actually named the place Kuala Sembilang&nbsp;Resort and Training Center. Part RESORT tu yang tak tahan tu.  &nbsp;  There were&nbsp;7 people from my batch from banting, and we were all in the same class back in banting. Me, Ninie, Izzie, Win, Mae, Pok Nik, and my ex. The rest of them were 20-22 years old. On the last day, someone told us that no, we were not the oldest people (I seriously felt older than  old!)  in the camp.   There were a few other people who were 23 and above, but you've guessed it, they're married. One was married with FOUR kids. Tsk.  &nbsp;  One hour after arrival, I could not wait to go home. I was seriously NOT happy to be there. My ex was there, I hated the toilets, most of the people were still in that MRSM mentality, et cetera. I thought those days were over. I thought everyone is supposed to be open-mided considering the fact they&nbsp;were all above 20. I thought that sort of thinking only exists when you're being&nbsp;institutionalised, and your mind is forced to think like that. Now that we have the freedom to do basically anything, I thought people would take that chance and use it accordingly. But maybe some people are just too comfortable with the way things are?  &nbsp;  We had lectures on the second day we were there. And yes, we had to sing the warisan song. The third and fourth day were filled with LDK (latihan dalam kumpulan) sessions. Honestly speaking, I was gradually beginning to see their points. It was definitely mainly to make us vote for the current government, but when I looked deeper, there were some good points that touched my soul. Chewah. Seriously though. Ada sedikit kesedaran la. Gila. Bangga diorang kalau dengar. heh. :P We talked about politics and history.&nbsp;Is&nbsp;Malaysia really an Islamic country? Can the opposition parties&nbsp;win and&nbsp;lead the country? Can our bangsa membangun? That sorta thing. Made me think. Even for a bit, it made me think. :)  &nbsp;  One thing though. I seriously need to&nbsp;get fit. We had to&nbsp;finish a 3-km run under 24 minutes (for girls), and I managed to do it in 17, but GOD, my legs were aching for the next 3 days. That's not good. Maybe I should change the way I'm working out. More running (noooooooooo...) and less cycling?&nbsp;The good thing about&nbsp;BTN is that Ninie and I have made some new friends, and we actually went out with them and more of our friends on Sunday. It was Ninie's birthday and the time spent&nbsp;chilling with the guys (as in all my friends regardless of sex. Hey, some people are&nbsp;naive okay..:P) was priceless. It really was.  &nbsp;  Okay, I'm not gonna start bitching,&nbsp;but&nbsp;things are still the same on the issue of&nbsp;My Ex and I. Hehe..&nbsp;Don't know la. It's all in the past. I&nbsp;feel like I tak pernah pun kenal dia, and I just couldn't bring myself to look at him, let alone talk to him. It was all so.. ntah.. different . He looked different (maybe he didn't actually looked different, maybe it was just me seeing&nbsp;him in a different light), and it was all awkward. I JUST CAN'T TALK TO HIM.&nbsp;On the first day, we were talking in a group,&nbsp;and he was there. I didn't mind that coz I could talk to other people. I was talking to a girl, and he butt in. You know what&nbsp;I did? I glanced at him. I did not even look at him properly. I just glanced from the corner&nbsp;of my eye, and continued talking to my friend. I did not say anything. Felt so jahat after that.&nbsp;But what could I have done? Talk to him as though&nbsp; nothing  happened? That would have been so awkward. Since a lot of our friends (actually, friends from Newcastle. but most of&nbsp;them are&nbsp;also my friends since my second 'home' used to be Newcastle) are now back in&nbsp;good ol' Malaysia, we had some sort of a get-together on Monday night. One of our friends have a family restaurant, and his parents belanja-ed us dinner. Obviously, he was there too, but honestly speaking, I was fine. I am fine as long as&nbsp;we are in a big group of people.&nbsp;No less than 7 people. He should have understand that I think. But NO, he just had to ask a friend to give him a lift back home, all the while knowing that Ninie and I were also getting a lift from this guy. One word (well, actually, 3 words..) : TAK gentleman LANGSUNG. Tell me something I don't know eh? Hmmph.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Entah la.. Apa-apa la labu. He was pissed off with my friend and I for not inviting him for her birthday gathering. It was not even a proper gathering.&nbsp;We just met up and had coffee. Entah la mamat sorang ni.&nbsp;Mengada-ngada pun ada, childish pun ada. I can't believe I went out&nbsp;with him. For THREE years pulak tu. And did I not say something along the line of "I NEVER want to speak to you EVER?". Which part of that sentence does he not understand? I can help him&nbsp;re-screw his brain. With a hockey stick. And&nbsp;when we&nbsp;asked him to come (again, I don't mind him being there as I am not trying to deprive him of his friends) he went all egoistic and said things like "Oh, never mind", "Malas lah", "I don't care anymore. Apa-apa lah".&nbsp;COME ON MAN. Grow some balls will ya? shhhheeessshhh!! Or if you can't handle that, go run to your girlfriend. I'm sure she can do something to make&nbsp;you all happy again.&nbsp;Tsk. I can't say nothing more.  &nbsp;  Well,&nbsp;boys and girls. I don't know what you think. Maybe some of you think that I am being egoistic too. Maybe, to some extent, I do admit that. But seriously, I am ONLY asking for ONE thing.&nbsp;I am merely asking him&nbsp;not to&nbsp;bother me anymore. Is that too hard to ask? I am not asking him to choose (and that would&nbsp;be a stupid thing to do anyway). I am not asking him to beg for my forgiveness. I am not asking him to build my trust in him and be my best friend again. NO. None of that nonsense. I am just asking him to go away. Just forget about me, and go away.&nbsp;As simple as that. Things are fucked up and&nbsp;they can never be rectified,&nbsp;so just&nbsp;get on with his life, coz&nbsp; I &nbsp;am trying to do that too.&nbsp; I respected his decisions, the least he can do is respect mine. Is that too much to ask?  &nbsp;  Some people.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Arghhh...It's Monday. Which means, tomorrow's TUESDAY. And Tuesday means BTN. Biro Tata Negara, that is. Tsk. I don't know why they are making us go to this thing AGAIN. Been to one before and I think that's enough. Don't you? (Faza, you guys kena pegi ke?) I mean, I support the government, there's no need for brainwashing lagi dah (ditzy ash..heh..). Oh well, the good thing is I'll get some money as they have agreed to reimburse our flight tickets. Well, they better do, coz I'm counting on that money to help me survive the 5-day ordeal.   It's really not that bad actually. It's just that it all reminds me too much of the times in boarding school, and i hate boarding schools. Oh well, anything to help me finance my half-priced Gucci handbag-to-be (xmas sale people!!! only errr...5 more months!).   I was reluctant to go at first because one, my ex will be there and I'm not in the mood to talk to him, and I know that his mere presence would annoy me to death and two, I wanna stay home and spend MORE quality time with mom (eh, 5 days tu banyak tu. and the next few days after balik tu, I'm gonna lepak a lot with my friends yang ada kat KL. Shit. which reminds me, I have not bought anything for my friend's birthday. erghh..). But my friend ni pujuk punya pujuk, so I pun pegi la. There'll be new people to meet, so that should be good right?  Right. I have a dental appointment at 10 am, in Kelana Jaya, of all places. Jauhnye la tempat.. Hopefully everything will be fine. Hehehe..
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A short notice. Got this email from ITV, it's a series of show that was filmed when I was a third year (macam la dah lama gila..baru je setahun yang lepas..) at my medical school. I'm a bit disappointed now coz I have been waiting since last year for them to show it, but sekarang I'm in KL pulak. Should be fun to watch it since I know the guys and girls on the show. hihihi... Anyway, here's the synopsis of the first episode, in case anyone is interested. :)   "You might be interested to watch ITV1   Monday 12 July  22:00   Young Doctors        First in a new six part documentary series following third-year Southampton medical students as they exercise their new-found skills on patients out on the wards. In this edition, Jacob Lee has problems in A&E when he struggles to take blood, Sheona has to overcome her shyness when examining a patient''s groin complaint and handsome Barney proves a hit on the wards. Narrated by Ian Curtis"   And girls (actually, Irene je kan kat UK? hihi), I'm not sure what your taste is like when it comes to men (and I mean, MEN, not boys..), but Barney: He IS handsome. All the nurses suka gila dia. And I am proud to say that I once did an on-call with him. Too bad things didn't get frisky. hahahaha...  Adieu.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A friend told me that you should not expect too much from your friends. Coz they  are  only your friends. I half-heartedly agreed to what he said at that time. I mean, he has got a point, but I thought friends are supposed to 'be there' whenever you need them. And friends are supposed to 'do whatever they can' to make you happy.   Now, I know exactly what he meant. Sometimes you just can't have too high of an expectation from a friend. And that includes me I guess. I get tired at times if people expect me to do certain things, and I  feel  that I have to do them because.. because I thought that's what I'm supposed to do. When it comes to a point where you  feel  that you  hav e to do them, I don't think that is right. I'm no superwoman. I can't say all the right things at the right time. If my friends 'terkecil hati' because of what I say, I apologise. But I can't go back in time and undo all my wrongdoings. And please, don't think you're the only one on the right side. Even if you have not noticed, you might have done the exact same thing to your friend before. I guess it is good to reflect on things you have done in the past, and LEARN from them, for God's sake. Don't la deliberately ulang your mistakes over and over again and expect your friends to not EVER do the same thing to you. Tak ke tak logic tu?  I'm a bit pissed. I don't even know why I'm writing on this. Ciao for now people, have to do my makeup. Family day (yay. I'm surely gonna meet some cute single people.. heh..) Have a nice Sunday.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Parisian Kiss by Carlton Mickle    "Was it you who spoke the words that things would happen but not to me Oh things are gonna happen naturally And taking your advice I'm looking on the bright side And balancing the whole thing But often times those words get tangled up in lines And the bright lights turn to night Until the dawn it brings A little bird who'll sing about the magic that was you and me"   I was watching Oprah (don't judge me please..I'm so bored, I'm at my wit's end :P) and she mentioned  urlLink  this   website, which sells a lot of beautiful art pieces and posters. This one caught my eye, mainly because of the name and also probably because the lovebirds in the picture look so sweet together (I know, it's only a picture.. But I'm a professional daydreamer and if I get paid for every second I daydream, I'd be a gazellionaire by now..hihi).   I love  urlLink  Paris  . I've only been there once, and yes, it was with a significant other, which probably made the whole experience more memorable and special. The WHOLE thing was just unforgettable. So romantic. So lovely. We walked around most of the time, and it was in spring, so the flowers were starting to bloom. The trees were so green and the flowers were so vibrant. It was magnificant. The river La Seine, the little cafes along the river, the boat ride, Notre dame. It was still cold and we were both ill. I still remember this scene, we were on the boat, shivering and I was holding a cup of hot chocolate. Hmm... Bliss. We had lunch at one of the cafes (a typical French cafe) and the omelette was to die for!      "Cause you and I both loved What you and I spoke of And others just read of Others only dream of the love that I love"   Walked down Champs-Elysees, swooned over French men (and some American tourists. They just have gorgeous bods!), went to H&M (coz it was cheaper there.heh..), memories memories memories.. :) This Chinese lady stopped us at the end of the Champs-Elysees and asked us for a favor. Apparently Louis Vuitton is really cheap in Paris but tourists can only buy two items, so she asked us to buy more purses for her and gave us 800 Euros I think. We were so naive, nasib baik tak kena tangkap. We should have just run away with the money. Mann...that would have been so cool. Think of what we could have done with all that money!     Sigh... I can't stop smiling now. It still feels so fresh.    "See I'm all about them words Over numbers, unencumbered numbered words Hundreds of pages, pages, pages forwards More words then I had ever heard and I feel so alive Now you and I, you and I Not so little you and I anymore And with this silence brings a moral story more importantly evolving is the glory of a boy"   The Metro, and us, so bodoh sombong tak nak bawak dictionary, so the only thing we knew were 'Parle vous Anglais?' and 'Merci'. And of course, 'Bonjour'. Don't you just love French? I think it is SO sexy. I wanna learn French one of these days. THEN I can marry a mat saleh. hah! :P   And  urlLink  Disneyland  ! And that BIG, big merry-go-round (I sound like a kid now..hihi) and the parade! I mean, Mickey actually SMILED at ME!! hahaha.. I was tempted to go and join them dance. My inner child was YEARNING to be released.   We were financially challenged (i.e broke. Takde pitis orang kata..) so, for dinner we had Maggi (yeah, I was trying to be frugal). Tu takpe lagi. The thing was we forgot to bring basic things like fork and spoon, and we had to eat our Maggi with our hands.. (disgusting kan?) Anything to stay alive man. That's all I have to say. :D But of course, we had a proper lunch at a proper French restaurant on the last day and THAT was beautiful. Went to a proper bakery (what do they call it eh?) and God, the pasteries and breads were GORGEOUS. To hell with all the diets. No way Jose. I just had to have that pain au chocolat, and that small teeny weeny chocolate that cost just a bit more than Cadbury's Whole Nuts.      Well, one day lah. One day nanti I'll make sure that I visit this beautiful city again. Probably with another significant other? hahaha... Who knows kan? For now, I'll just dream away and imagine that I'm in Paris, walking along the shops and cafes, and smiling at all the Frenchmen. Of course, in my dream, one of them would wink at me, and fall head over heels in love with me. And we'll dance until the end of time.    Do not judge me. hihihihi...                                      "and it's okay if you have to go away                        just remember the telephone works both ways                        and if I never ever hear it ring                        if nothing else I'll think the bells inside                        have finally found you someone else and that's okay                        cause I'll remember everything you sang                         you and I both loved                         what you and I spoke of                        and others just read of                         and if you could see now                        well I'm already finally out of words"                          You and I Both (by Jason Mraz)  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was checking my blog and there was this thing just under the toolbar (I think my brother installed it) that basically suggests some words that I might be interested to search based on the webpage I was looking at. So, when I was at my blog, the words that came up were " Nice people ", " Fat girls ", " Boys first   tim e" (????), " Fat   women ", " Lose weight " and " Call girl ". Yeah. That pretty much sums it all up. Hihihi..  No heavy subjects today. Went out last night with mom and my 4 brothers to McD. Pictures can be viewed  urlLink  here  . I'm now in the process of filling in the job application forms. I might apply for Portsmouth. It's not really a 'pretty' place. I would definitely prefer Bournemouth or Poole, but the programmes in Portsmouth are better suited to what I'm looking for. Might want to go into neurology or dermatology (yeah, you heard me right. So keep my contact details in case you're in need of a Botox fix. :P). Plus, I think the net-working in Portsmouth is much better.   Was talking to my mom and I told her that I might come back home after my houseman years. Reason? Coz I don't think I'll find anyone there. She was cool about it and strongly advised me to stay in the UK, and complete my professional exams before coming back for good. I'm taking her advice. Besides, old (ooo....my mom would be mad if she knows that I call her OLD..hihi).. okay,  older  (which also includes you, The Neon. hahahaha :P) people know what they're talking about. Most of the time. Besides, she said "Asalkan niat baik, mesti Tuhan tolong". I guess. Life- It's all about intentions right? *shrug* And I think I know her intentions. To get me marry a  mat saleh  ("so that mama can get cucu with blue eyes" I hope she was talking about my brothers) and of course, most importantly, to give me the opportunity to get the best I can in life.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have had a lot on my mind these past few days. Been thinking too much. My brother. That issue of me being 'too nice'. My grandma. My mom worrying over my brother. My friends. Guilt because I think I'm separating 'the group'. Everything. One advice: do not attempt to 'solve' ALL your problems at the same time, or you'll be overwhelmed and end up like me. Stressed. Over nothing. There's no use worrying over something you can't control. Just let them be. And pray I guess. Sheeeshh.. there's a reason why this blog is called 'Confessions of a Twenty-something DRAMA QUEEN'.   I was chatting with some friends the other day and we touched on the issue of body image. Maybe I'm not in a place to say anything. No, wait. (STOP being too nice Ash!). I am DEFINITELY in a place to say a few things about this. It's simple. I just don't get it when those girls wearing size six or eight jeans and still have a bit of space to breath, say things like "I think I'm fat. Do you think I'm fat?" or "Look, I've got a tummy" (while pointing to this thing normal people would call SKIN).   Okay. I should not be too harsh. I've been there. Once. A long time ago. I know how they feel. Maybe they can't control it. I was once a  fanatic  (seriously, look up this word in the dictionary and you'll find my face next to it). I grew up a fat kid (like,  really  fat). At 15, I started to notice that boys only looked for physical things, like how small your waist is, how big your breasts are, that kinda thing (Huh.  Boy s still look for these things. They should grow up I say). I started dieting, and it turned to the other extreme. I was in boarding school and I started to adopt these ridiculous notions about how thin one should be, and how important it is to be able to feel your bones. I was SICK, mentally and physically. Most days, my 'To Eat' list (yes, I had one. pathetic.) would consists of, at most; nothing for breakfast, 3/4 crackers for lunch, probably an apple for tea, and a slice of bread for dinner (okay, for some readers this might be considered A LOT. But hear me out). I lost a lot of weight, and I could see my cheekbones. I was ecstatic. I can't describe the feelings. It was just.. a lovely feeling. After all those years tormented for being fat, I was beginning to feel 'beautiful'. In the space of 2 years, I lost nearly 30 kilograms. I think looking back, my friends were worried, but no-one said anything. On the last day of school, one of my close friends in Taiping wrote me a letter. She told me that 'tak baik buat macam tu. ramai lagi orang yang starving kat dunia ni'. Huh. Not a good advice I tell you if you're thinking of counselling a person who only thinks of herself and her weight. I disregarded her, and never talked to her since then.   When I went to Banting, I started eating a bit more, and of course, gained a bit of weight. So I came up with an idea. I would starve myself during weekdays, and eat all I want when I went back home on weekends. So, it became a viscious cycle. I would lose on average about 3 kgs during weekdays, and gain them all back by Sunday. By then, my menstrual cycle was non-existent. I had not had any for almost a year. My mom started to worry and brought me to see a doctor. She gave me some pills, and that helped me gain some weight and improved my appetite. I hated that. So, I came up with another plan. I started to make myself sick. It became so bad that I had to do it almost 5 times a day. I was THAT obsessed. Almost everything I ate had to come out. It went on until 2 years ago. I gradually stopped, and thank God, had not done anything like that since then. I have had the occassional temptations especially when I'm stressed out about things (eg, the breakup) but thankfully, I never did it.   You see, this is the reason why I wrote that entry on how-much-should-one-reveal-in-a-blog. I want to get this off my chest. I've never told ANYONE about this, except for three people.   My point is, it's good to be fit and healthy, but don't let your emotions control you. It's SO easy to be trapped in that I-weigh-45-kg-but-still-look-fat phase (no, I was not that light..:P). Be confident, and happy with yourself (I have a long way to go in terms of building my self-esteem myself). I'm trying to lose weight to be healthy, and hope to God that I won't fall into that state of mind ever again. That was one very unhappy time. There are more things in life.  As a friend said to me "Benda dunia ni tak permanent. Tak ke mana. Boleh hilang macam tu saja. So think about it"  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Tarzan!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Hah.. This is pretty funny because some of my friends actually call me tarzan, although I don't really know the reasons behind it. Care to explain Irene?? hihihi..  And as some of you might have realised, this is a rather pathetic attempt to 'liven things up' after a few crap entries (don't ask, i'm just not in the mood..PMS kot..huh).   I'll be back (think Arnold Schwarzenegger) to my old self in a few days. Just have to sort out a few things at the moment (my head being one of them). Ciao peeps.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I cut them all to pieces. I wanted to burn them, but it would not have been good for the environment, what's with all the haze in KL. I'm SO thoughtful.Heh. :P  I had a really long chat with one of my closest friends the other night. I am now more angry at myself than anyone else. I should have seen it. I shouldn't have been such a pushover and stayed with him for that long. I took all those shit and pretended to be happy. I can be so nice and  stupid  at times. Arghhh..              There's a restless feeling knocking at my door today           There's a shadow hanging 'round my garden gate           I read between the lines of words you can't disguise           Love has gone away, and put these tears in my eyes                                                       -Alison Krauss-  I should stop being a 'yes woman' and start becoming a bitch. People won't even dare to take me for granted that way.   It doesn't matter.  I'm not in the right state of mind at the moment. This is one of those times when my brother would call me 'The Darth Vader'. Right. But people still step on me all the time. How nice.   Ignore this.   SIGH......     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        OK. This is going to be an extra-short entry. I think.  Watched Spiderman 2 at KLCC with my brothers, as a treat for my youngest brother's 10th birthday. It was simply AWESOME. I didn't like the first one, so I was a bit sceptical about the sequel. But man... I have to give this two thumbs up *grin*. Tobey Maguire just looked so  delicious  in that suit. ERRmmmmmmmm.... I never really liked him, but girls, you just have to see this one. In one of the scenes (no, i'm not giving anything away..) he was becoming weak (biasa la all these superhero stories kan mesti ada part dia jadi lemah) and he just looked  urlLink  adorable  . I felt like walking up to him and say "It's okay baby. I'll take care of you" and run my fingers through that beautifully layered hair. SIGH.... (and a big one and that).. most of the time my heart was screaming "Take your shirt off Spidey!! Take your shirt off!!" hihihihi...  Oh, and the special effects were pretty cool too..  And for the boys, kikky (is that how you spell it?) was pretty. And she didn't wear a  urlLink  bra   either, so that's more than enough reasons to go and watch it. ;)  p.s: one complaint though.. They cut the kissing action!!! They cut it!! ARghhh..
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, before anyone says anything, no, I'm not going to give a review on the Malaysian Idol's auditions. But I have to say this after watching the last audition held in KL on 8TV.  OH .  MY .  GAWD . Some people are just STRANGE. Pelik GILA. I couldn't hold it back, I just HAD to laugh. It was cruel but man, they were just plain weird. And I don't think any of the judges were being 'one-sided' or 'harsh' or 'know-it-all'. They were just being truthful. We have all seen American Idol, and the judges were mean, okay. SO, what were they (those who auditioned) thinking? That Malaysians being Malaysians should be 'nice' and 'soft-spoken'? Tsk. But of course, I would not be too happy if I was in their shoes. :P However, I KNOW that I can't sing (hell, I can't even carry a note to save my life) so you would need some sort of miracle before I VOLUNTARILY go for an audition of any sorts (Tsk..I'm so 'adventurous', I know :P)  Anyway, just to show you how 'unique' these people were, there was:  1. A 'guy' (inverted commas to show that I'm not  really  sure if he wants people to see him as a lady or a man) who has a thing for Britney and actually tried to sing her song i.e Toxic (of all songs?). Siap dengan gerak tangan and pusing-pusing lagi. One word: Lawak.   2. A 'guy' (again, for the same reason) who was wearing a (get this) DRESS and dancing 'provocatively' to the song he was singing. *Criinge*  3. A 'guy' (err...oh, I give up) who wore a pair of yellow with black stripes shorts (no man should be aloud to wear shorts  that  short. Not unless you're Will Smith. But then again, Will Smith wouldn't be caught dead wearing a pair of Cheetah shorts. So, no. My future hubby, maybe. Coz I'm supposed to 'stand by him no matter what' right? *double criinge*). That with a tank top, dancing to Kylie Minouge's song (I don't know which one coz I'm not a fan). Like,  really  dancing. *more cringe*  4. Another guy (a Kelantanese I think judging from his accent) who thought he could sing but was rejected. This was actually a bit kesian la. But it was pretty funny listening to him saying things like "Oh, Diora tu nak ogha hensem saja. Ini la. Musim hensem. Kalu nak ogha hense, janga datang Maleysa. Ha. " He was pretty angry. Note: please don't mind my pathetic attempt at transcripting the loghat. :P At least I  trriiieddd ???  Those are just a few who I can still remember from that 9.45 pm show (it's only 11 pm. I have such bad memory). Okay, I'm being mean la this time. But it WAS funny. :P  p.s: I *think* I have lost jeng jeng jeng...one pound!! Might be because of the frequent toilet breaks though. :).. I should really stop talking about this now or people would start to think that I'm just a girl with a serious body image issue (plus an L on her forehead)..OOppppsss.. too late for that!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was sitting in front of the telly, laughing and it strucked me: I'm in a good place. This feels good. LIFE feels good. Finally. I feel.. blessed even. Hmm.. Sounds weird right? But entah..  I realised that I have nearly come to the end of my 'grieving' process. I have come to accept that this is fate, and this is how it should be. This is how God intend my life to be, and I'm taking it in with arms wide open.   But how do I know this? I'm not sure how to describe it myself. I can just FEEL it you know. Sure, maybe in the future I'll feel sad at times. But I'm not feeling that at the moment. Right now, I feel happy. I can be reminded of how we used to be back in those happy days, and I won't feel a thing. Sometimes, when I sit by myself (usually during the day when I do absolutely nothing BUT sit and stare at the telly :P) memories of good and bad times will come flashing by and some of them even make me smile. Not smile as in I-wish-we-are-still-together smile, but smile as in gosh-those-were-the-days smile. Writing this down, I feel a bit sceptical of myself, but I mean everything I say. I think this is it. This is the beginning of the end.   Of course, I'm still not on talking terms with him. :P.. I'm not THAT nice you see. As I told a friend, if i was an animal, I'd be a bitch. hihihi...   It was never meant to be. We were (still are) like chalk and cheese. It was all wrong from the start. I really think we shouldn't have even tried it out. But I'm glad that we did, because I have grown so much since then. Yeah, no regrets. Retrospectively, there were a lot of things that did not quite fit. Backgrounds, beliefs, hopes and dreams. We have different priorities in our lives. I still find this so confusing. If we were so different, how could we stand those 3 1/2 years together? Hmmm... There were  definitely  good times, and I was happy most of the time. The last year of our relationship was a bit difficult though. We started fighting and I was just miserable. I think he was as well. Like I said, i think it was never meant to be. :)  Going off tangent (like I have always done anyway), I just realised that all my friends in Southampton have started their first final-year rotation. Errrghhh... I am officially a final-year medical student. That sounds.. odd. (No, I didn't forget to go back to the UK. I'm still here coz I applied to do my first rotation in KL. Clever eh? hihihi). And the deadline for our job application is supposed to be on the 12th of July. *terrified* I am SO confused, I don't know where I want to work. It's going to be pretty stressful for the next couple of days, and I hope that I will get my first choice (Amen). Should I go for a place with a hospital overlooking the sea (bliss...) or should I go for a place that will make me look good on my CV? (hmm..the rational me would go for this one. But the sea??? Tsk.. Tough eh?)  Going off tangent yet again.. I think if I lean towards my right standing on the weighing machine, I'm definitely half a kilogram lighter. Twisted mind I have, I know. hihihihihi..  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
              You Are A BCBG Black Leather Clutch You're a modern, urban chick who's more than a little tough (Well, as tough as you can be while carrying a purse) Black leather is like your denim - goes good with everything You'd even wear it to work, if you could get away with it    urlLink What Kind of Handbag Are You? Take This Quiz :-)      urlLink Find  the Love of Your Life (and More Love Quizzes) at Your New Romance.        Trabye recommended this quiz. I would say it's 50-50 true. I wouldn't really say I am modern or urban. But I am tough. Hihi.. (Said this to our 'mentor' at BTN when he asked us to draw a logo that represents ourselves. I know.. Macam budak2. But anyway, I said I think I'm quite a strong person. He asked 'Oh, memang angkat berat ye?'. Sheeshh..)  And the black leather thing.. I hope they meant the handbag, not leather  pants . I shudder at the thought of me in leather pants.  I  would be scarred for life.   P.s: I'm going out tomorrow night! Finally!! Won a bet with my cousin, so she's buying me sushi for dinner. We're gonna discuss about men, men and men. Weee... *clapping hands*   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Do not laugh at me when I say that I look a bit like Barney. A sick Barney.  I have a blue-black spot on my right side of the face, as a souvenir from my trip to the dentist on Tuesday.  My right cheek and jaw are still swollen, although I have to say that at least right now, I look like I have  only  been through a round of boxing with my little brother, NOT Mike Tyson (you should have seen me two days earlier. People on the streets looked at me twice- for all the wrong reasons. But I guess thats Malaysia for you. Staring is a culture).  In addition to that, I have these annoying little rashes with white centers on my face, which I think is a side effect of Amoxicillin, one of the many drugs I was on to combat any potential infections.  To top it all off, I woke up this morning with conjunctivitis in my right eye.  So, Im not a nice sight to look at today. Not that Ive ever really been. Now, I wouldnt really mind all these things (okay, okayI do mind a bit.. but who doesnt? Anyone whos not a bit vain, raise your hand. You deserve a pat on the back) if I were to stay at home and not go out in the next 14 days or so. But I have only 4 days till my flight back to Heathrow, and Im supposed to have one last meet-up with my friends. I dont want anyone to see me like THIS.  Oh dear God, Im so vain. I sound like a spoiled brat.  Anyway, as I mentioned in an earlier post, I was involved in an accident. The damage done has been estimated to reach at least RM 1500. I know, I know. You could have your boutique pedal with that kinda money, The Neon. Hell, I would certainly put that in my Gucci Handbag Trust. A few months down the line, youd see me trotting down Knightsbridge with a horsebit-detailed classic Gucci. And Kudo certainly would not mind having that much money to buy yet another guitar. Right Kuds? :P  I guess I should be grateful that Im still alive. At least the other driver did not run me down, not like what happened to a lady in PJ yesterday. That was simply inhumane and awful.  I am afraid to be a Malaysian. You can get killed for anything. Bring your daughter back home from her fiances house, and you get parang-ed. Say something to another guys girlfriend and you get killed. Say some sweet nothings to your  own  girlfriend, and people beat you up to death. Basically, what you need to do now is sit down and keep quiet at home. Sheeshh.. I bet someone will eventually break into the house and rob you. If not kill you just for the sake of it.  My dads colleague told me about how her neighbours house, who is an ex-something something in Bukit Aman, was broken into. The children (thank God they werent raped or hurt) asked these thieves if theyre not scared of Allah. If they realize that what theyre doing is a sin. The men simply replied, in Malay If you know how we live in our country, youd do the same.  I guess I would understand. But I would like to think that I wouldnt resort to the same things they were doing. Im no preacher, but theres a lot more other ways to find money. Halal ways, you know?  On a different note, how can I go out without my Tok Mak making a big fuss out of it? Yes, I am an anak dara, but this is not the 15th century. And I miss my friends already.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Its nearly 2 oclock in the afternoon, and Im feeling tired. Tired of everything. The best remedy for me is probably a good refreshing shower and a nice round of window-shopping. I have friends who say all the things I need to hear and uplift my mood. And I have friends who say all the logical stuff and make me feel down. Im in need of a big hug. I think.  Does it exclusively mean Im still affected by him if Im not able to see or talk to him without feeling any hatred towards him? Maybe. But do I care? No. Let me be me. Let me be wrong. This is what I have chosen to do. Its my fucked up life, and if I think that is the best option for me, do it I will. If you think youd do things differently, I respect that. But for now, let me be. Seriously, I want to do this. Maybe in the future Ill realize that what I have done so far is a big mistake, but at least Ill learn from it.  I was packing some books to bring to the new house on Friday night, and came upon this book that my mom gave me almost 4 years ago. Some people might think that this book is pathetic but I thought it was sweet of her. In it, she wrote these few words:   Ashrah, Tread your first journey of love with compassion. Love, Mama     Truth be told, I never finished reading it. Sheeeshh..I never even read past the Introduction. However, this is an excerpt from Cherie Carter-Scotts  If Love is a Game, These are the Rules , on the matter of what authentic love really means. Read, and tell me what you think.   'Authentic love is choosing your partner exactly as he is, it is putting your energy behind your choice and causing the relationship to be magical, rather than searching for reasons why it cant work. Love is supporting your partner in her choices, urging her to fulfill her hearts desires and go for all her dreams.  
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am afraid of myself. Am not in my best mood. Feeling fat,  looking  fat. Bloated. Half of my face is swollen and blue-black. I look like a Blue-ish Barney. Get easily annoyed by small remeh-temeh stuff. And as usual, I'm blaming all these on PMS. Tee hee. I seriously need to go out. Tok Mak is here for a visit, and I've been such a goody goody and have stayed at home since Wednesday. Shhheesshh... It has only been 48 hours but it feels like a 100 years. Hopefully this swelling will go down by tomorrow morning (please God pleaseeee.....).  Not much to write about. Actually, ada jugak some stuff, but probably later-later la. Going to have some protein for lunch. My stomach is expanding like it's nobody's business. I hate hormones.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Allow me to be as shallow as I want. Just this once. I don't. Usually.  Some of the things I daydream. Stuff I observe from my people-watching hobby. Things that can make my day. Thoughts that make me smile.    The thought of me graduating. Wearing that robe, with a scroll in my hand, and  somehow  manage to avoid looking like a big dufus in the black robe. I know that my imagination has run wild when I think that I'll  probably  look a  bit sexy  in that robe. Tsk. Hey, nothing wrong with a bit of creativity. :P   urlLink  Hoobastank's   singer, and his cute little eyes. Scot-Jap breed. One word: cair...   urlLink  VJ Utt  . He has got such lean body. Not muscular, just lean. And that height. Tsk. Why can't he be one of my normal friends. I'd definitely make a move on  him . But good looking people KNOW that they're good looking, and that just spoils it. *shrug* No-one's perfect I guess.  Guys with curly hair. or wavy hair. Just make me feel like touching it. The hair i mean.  Tall men. No doubt. Tall men over anything (no pun intended).  The smell of my new Gucci Rush 2. It is just so sweet.   Old pictures of my mom and dad back when they were studying. They look so perfect for each other. Both had big hair back then. hehe..  Hugo for Men, by Hugo Boss. My dad used to love it so much. Bought one for my ex. The smell brings back good memories. I like.   That time of the year when there's a transition between Spring and Summer. Not too cold, not too hot. Everyone starts to hang out in the park. Ice cream vans everywhere. Kids running around. Uni students playing rounders. Beautiful.  Couples making out (lightly) in Hyde Park. Girl's head on guy's lap. Picnic baskets, books, sunglasses.   White clouds and blue sky.  The warmth of the sun when I'm in England. Nothing beats that when you've been in gloomy gloomy weather all year round.   A mean cup of hot mocha.  Those beautiful looonngg dresses you see on mannequins at a shop's display. The ones that you can only wear to a red carpet event. If only they make them in my size. :P And if only I have that kind of money, without having to ask from my dad or anyone else.   Carnaby Street in good 'ol London. Hanging out at this small cafe. Not franchised.   Talking with my good friends. I can sit for hours, chatting about life, and shite like that. I simply love spending time with them. I've got a few I know I'll cherish. That's more than enough for me. Normal friends and  good  friends are different. You can just feel it.    Kris' songs. :p  Gorgeous handbags. and gorgeous shoes. I don't buy them often, coz it's not easy to spot a really nice pair of shoes. But when I do, I'll go all cair. Seriously.   Confidence in men. That plays a big role. Confident men are attractive. and I'm sure other girls would agree.   Guy playing with Girl's hair. There's just something sexy about it. And romantic.   Candle-lit dinner, beautiful scenery, music in the background. Anywhere. A dance later that night.   Surprises. Good ones.  The sound of the piano. So relaxing.   The feeling after a good workout. Like I've accomplished something really important.  The guys at the gym. Two words: Drop dead gorgoeous... Ooopppss, ditzy me. ahaks! :P  Happy endings, in movies, books, songs..  Boeing 747. Touchdown at KLIA. Hugs with mom and dad. Worth the 13-hour flight, the sickness (i CAN'T stand the smell of plane food. i have to sleep the whole journey or i'd be sick) and the jet-lag afterwards.   Bouquet of fresh lillies. I can sit and smell them all day.   The Crush.  KL. Can't wait to be back here for good. I'm still in KL, but I'm homesick already. Pathetic. :P  Tempe goreng. Don't laugh. I'm just being myself here. I even bring some back to the UK every summer. Everytime without fail.   New York City. I want to go there someday. Hopefully in the near future. Anyone up for it? and don't mind a drama queen tagging along? tee hee...  Roller coasters. One of the coolest things on earth.  Falling in love, I guess. It's such a beautiful feeling, don't you think? When you start to get to know that person inside out. And noticing things that you did not notice before. Kinda like an adventure. :)  White on white on white. White room, white walls, white sofas, white everything. SO clean.  F.R.I.E.N.D.S. I'm a fan-atic. Am collecting all their dvds. I watch it everytime I feel down. Laughing at their jokes make me forget my problems for a while. I don't care, call me a loser. It helps me through those bad times. :)  Daffodils. Very nice yellow.  TGV's caramel popcorn. Sinful stuff.   Romance.  Babies' chuckles.      
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Been away since Friday. Moved to new house on Saturday. Modem at home is making some sort of a problem. Bored to death now. Using dad's computer at his office. One word: S.L.O.W.  Went out with some friends yesterday. A lot of eventful things happened. Saw ex with his new prize in hand. A friend (actually, two..) said I'm fat. Was involved in an accident. You get the drift, no? Bad day.  Went to PJ Police Station after lunch time to make a police report. Was there for 3 hours, and I still have to go at 8 pm later for them to take some pictures of my car. How I look forward to that. Policemen scare me. I don't know why. One of them asked me to have dinner with him. After which he told me about his daughter. Riiiighhtt..One word: Poyo.  Tomorrow, will be having a minor surgery with the dentist. Have to take out my wisdom tooth, as it is 'crowding' my other teeth. No more picket fence teeth. I'm a bit of a perfectionist (a neurotic obsessive person more like it..), so might think of having braces to straighten my lower teeth. I heard that the surgery will be painful. Weeee..  Oh well.. I don't know the next time I'll blog. Flight is on the 11th. Might be after I've arrived the UK. Take care peeps. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>