<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Haven't you always wondered which Animaniac is most like you?  Now you can find out!!      urlLink Which Animaniacs Character are You?      Talkative, huh?  Perhaps sing-ative would be more appropriate, actually.  When people don't understand something, it usually drives you to cutting, sarcastic remarks.  Your other extreme is bursting into song with almost no prompting, often to explain complex ideas.  No one knows quite what you are, exactly.  You have made many "special" friends, and there's baloney in your slacks.  urlLink  Click here to see my Livejournal.     

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This morning it came home to me just how large of a company I work for.  I got a request from a publisher in Portugal to publish some of our books there.  I forwarded the request to a contact in our Foreign Rights office in London.  He let me know that Portuguese rights are handled through our Brazil office, and sent my email on to a contact in our Mexico City office, who might be able to tell me who I need to contact next.  By the time this gets handled, I wonder how many countries my email will have traveled to? 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today, somebody posted on bubbs in the Bookworms folder asking for suggestions of "secular books that can promote Christian thought in the reader."  Immediately a few titles came to mind, and then I began looking at my bookshelves for others.  As I did this, it occurred to me that pretty much ANY book I read should "promote Christian thought."  Right?  Shouldn't every book "promote Christian thought in the reader" if the reader is a Christian?  Shouldn't we as Christians be thinking "Christianly" about whatever it is that we read?  Ok, so maybe some books are more apt to tie in with Christian themes, and some just don't offer any real "meat" to think about.    But really, I was a little frustrated with myself that I couldn't come up with more titles that I could list...books that I had thought about in terms of what they meant in relation to my own faith.  And yet that's (ostensibly) one of the main reasons for why I read.  I'm thinking back to a discussion in a lit class I had at  urlLink Biola , where Todd Pickett's main conclusion for why he reads was "to be a better Christian."  I think that should be my goal in reading, too.  There is a place for escapist reading, but ultimately, my grand purpose in reading should be to prompt greater thought about my faith.  Especially if I believe that "all truth is God's truth" and that faith applies to all areas of life.  I simply don't read like this most of the time.  And I should. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Right now, I'm reading  urlLink The Golden Compass  by Philip Pullman, the first book in the "His Dark Materials" trilogy.  I've heard a lot about these books, and have been debating with myself over whether to read this particular trilogy or not.  It's been praised as an excellent fantasy trilogy.  I've also heard Christian critics call it " urlLink atheism for kids ."  Reviewers I respect have noted that if Christians are going to protest a fantasy series, their time would be better spent being critical about Pullman's books rather than something as harmless as  urlLink Harry Potter .  (Visit  urlLink this link ...)  I finally decided to pick up the first one, read it myself, and see what I think.  I must say that I'm really enjoying the story, and haven't found anything so far that makes me cry "Heresy!"  Not that I'm one to do so.  But there are two more books, and I'm not finished with this one yet, so the underlying worldview/agenda remains to be seen.  I'll probably post more about this later, when I actually finish the book.  Has anyone else read these?  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Elvish    urlLink   To which race of Middle Earth do you belong?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Hmm.  Even though I said I'd prefer to serve under Eomer.  So, what are you? 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The things I learn from my Publisher's Weekly emails.  Today is National Clean-Off-Your-Desk Day, as well as National Thank God it's Monday Day.  Thank God it's Monday so you can get to work to clean off your desk, presumably.  Also, today is the birthday of Rush Limbaugh and--wait for it--Howard Stern.  Who knew they shared a birthday?  They have more in common than we thought, apparently. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, you know what totally made my weekend?  I found Return of the King valentine cards at Wal-Mart.  How pathetic am I.  These things are SO cheesy.  They're hilarious!  There's actually one that says "Have a Happy Valentine's Day--Orc else!"  I love it.  Personal triumph for the weekend: I changed my windshield wiper blades all by myself.  Woo hoo!  And,  urlLink Alias  is back to showing new episodes.  I LOVE that show!!  Life is good... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just read that Joan Aiken, one of my favorite authors when I was little, died on Sunday, January 4th.  It's odd how it made me feel.  It made me remember the books of hers that I loved as a child:  urlLink The Wolves of Willoughby Chase  (probably her most famous children's book), and my favorites, the Arabel and Mortimer books.  It made me want to go out and read all the books she's written that I never discovered: she wrote 92 novels in her lifetime, 65 of them for children.  How is it that I didn't know she wrote so many books?  That she was still writing?  These are things I never thought about until I heard of her death.  It also made me remember how I felt when Roald Dahl died...very sad that there will be no more books written by this author that I loved.  I heard someone say that when a person dies, it's like a library has burned down.  All their experiences, memories, and stories are gone.  Seems an especially fitting description today. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First item of business: I’ve been thinking about a name for this blog.  I haven’t hit upon what I want just yet.  Suggestions?  I’m realizing that I don’t have a cool internet “handle” to use.  Kristy’s got Sugar Girl and the word ubiquitous.  Heather’s got joyfrog.  Jude’s got about fifty different ones to pick from…barbie rocks, gelding, Judi-Helen…  Me?  I’ve got boring email addresses like BHillaker and BJHillaker and barbara.hillaker.  A select few call me Babs, David calls me Barbara J, Eric even calls me Elf Witch from time to time…but none of these are quite it.  Am I just a boring person destined to be without a clever web name or description?  Hey, at least I make boring sexy.  Perhaps that’s what I should call this: boringsexy.    For now, I'm stealing the title Veronica and I had for our short-lived radio show at Biola.  Only I'm deleting Veronica's name.  Sorry, V.  Better ideas?  Anyone?  And do I have a comments feature yet?  No, not yet...I'll be working on that...  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm never going to get any work done at this rate!  This is so great.  All of the EAs in the humanities wing are taking the quizzes, and we're yelling random things like "I'm China!" and "How in the heck did I get Turkey?!"     You're Madagascar!      Lots of people don't really know anything about you, making you  buried treasure of the rarest kind. &nbsp;You love nature, and could get lost in it  whenever possible. &nbsp;You're remote and exotic, and the few people who know you  value whatever they share with you a great deal. &nbsp;For some reason, you really  like the word &quot;lemur&quot;.   Take the  urlLink Country Quiz  at the  href="http://bluepyramid.org">Blue Pyramid     I like this description.  But on second thought,  urlLink Ireland  is quite nice as well. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is far too much fun.  One of my co-workers just emailed me this quiz and after taking the quiz enough times, I figured out how to come out as this:        You're  The Fellowship of the Ring !   by J.R.R. Tolkien     Facing great adversity, you have decided that your only choice is to unite with your friends and neighbors. You have been subject to a ton of squabbling and ultimately decided that someone humble is your best candidate for a dangerous mission. You're quite good with languages and convinced that not all who wander are lost. If you see anyone in black robes on horseback, just run. That's just common sense.      Take the  urlLink Book Quiz  at the  urlLink Blue Pyramid .    Early results were:  urlLink The Guns of August ,  urlLink A Prayer for Owen Meany , and  urlLink Roots .  But I like this one best, so there! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday I got overwhelmed with new people, new everything.  I left work longing for a familiar face and wanting to just go home and hide from the world.  Actually—and I told Heather this last night—what I really wanted to do was to go home and curl up on the couch I don't own with the boyfriend I don't have.  I just wanted to hang on to the comfort of someone who knows me so well.     Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words.  -George Eliot   That’s what I needed last night.  This past week has been really emotional for me.  I don't know if it's homesickness or what; I don't think I've ever been homesick before.  I'm just longing for familiarity and I'm tired of meeting new people and trying to build new relationships.  This is not exactly a good feeling to have the day before I go on a church retreat with the goal of meeting new people and building new relationships.  Sigh. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   On Saturday I had planned on going to the  urlLink Presidio  and wandering around.  I was in the mood to be outside, and I've wanted to get up to the Presidio. But it was cloudy and a bit gloomy when I woke up, and I was depressed because the weather wasn't cooperating!  It got to be 11:45 or so, and I couldn't take being stuck inside anymore, especially with the neighbors playing their loud mariachi music as they always seem to do at about 11:30am  every single Saturday .  Grrr.  I left to run some errands, and realized that the sun had come out.  So instead of taking the 101 south, I headed north to the City, with no directions in hand, determined to find the Presidio.  Miraculously, I found it, but I then diverged from my intended pathway once I got into the park.  I saw a sign that said " urlLink East Beach parking ," and turned into the parking lot.  From the parking lot, I could see the Golden Gate bridge on one side, and Alcatraz out ahead.  So I parked.    I spent about 2 ½ hours there, just walking along the beach.  The Bay was out in front of me, the Golden Gate Bridge on one side and the City spread out on the hill to the other side.  The sun was out, people were flying kites, there were dogs chasing sticks thrown out into the water…and there was this guy balancing rocks.  It sounds bizarre, but it was SO cool.  I don't even know how to explain it; I wish I'd had my camera to take some pictures of these towers of rocks he'd balanced on top of each other.  It looked absolutely impossible, but there they stood, these towers of impossibly balanced rocks, and this guy in the middle, working to balance the next set, with a crowd standing around watching.  Everybody clapped when he finished a tower.    Yeah, Saturday was a good day. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I found this personality disorder test.  Big surprise, I scored way high on the "avoidant" category.  Oooh, and look, I'm really obsessive-compulsive, too!       Disorder      Rating        urlLink Paranoid :    Moderate       urlLink Schizoid :    Moderate       urlLink Schizotypal :    Moderate       urlLink Antisocial :    Low       urlLink Borderline :    Low       urlLink Histrionic :    Low       urlLink Narcissistic :    Low       urlLink Avoidant :    Very High       urlLink Dependent :    Moderate       urlLink Obsessive-Compulsive :    High       --  urlLink Personality Disorder Test - Take It!  --       Here's what I think of the descriptions of these two disorders: stuff in italics is definitely not me.  The other stuff is pretty much true.   Avoidant  Avoidant personality disorder is characterized by  extreme social anxiety . People with this disorder often feel inadequate, avoid social situations, and seek out jobs with little contact with others. They are fearful of being rejected and worry about embarrassing themselves in front of others. They exaggerate the potential difficulties of new situations to rationalize avoiding them. Often, they will create fantasy worlds to substitute for the real one. Unlike schizoid personality disorder, avoidant people yearn for social relations yet feel they are unable to obtain them. They are  frequently depressed  and have low self-confidence.   Obsessive-Compulsive  Obsessive-Compulsive personality disorder is similar to obsessive-compulsive anxiety disorder. People with this disorder are overly focused on orderliness and perfection. Their need to do everything "right" often interferes with their productivity. They tend to get caught up in the details and miss the bigger picture. They set unreasonably high standards for themselves and others, and tend to be very critical of others when they do not live up to these high standards. They avoid working in teams, believing others to be too careless or incompetent. They avoid making decisions because they fear making mistakes and are  rarely generous with their time or money . They often have difficulty expressing emotion.  Wow.  So I agree, I really am obsessive-compulsive.  Eeek. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I came across this quote this morning in one of those publisher’s emails that I get:   "Third Place Books derived its name from the theory that your first place is home, your second place is work, and your third place is where you come for everything else. My third place was every bookstore in the city."   --Amanda Tobier, former book buyer at Seattle's  urlLink Third Place Books , now marketing manager of the Perennial paperback imprint   I first encountered this concept a couple months ago while watching an interview with  urlLink Nora Ephron , where she talked about everyone’s need for a "third place."  Ephron talked about how  urlLink Starbucks  has become a third place for a lot of people, and actually attributed the decrease of crime in New York City partly to the advent of more Starbucks.  (Starbuckses?  What’s the plural of Starbucks?)  It’s an interesting idea--that people sitting in coffee shops with large windows could be a deterrent to crime--but I find the third place theory far more intriguing.    I haven’t found a third place since moving here.  For a long time, La Mirada Park was my third place.  Here, I’m still looking. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We all know that today is the ominous Friday the Thirteenth.  But, did you know that today also marks the celebration of Get a Different Name Day?  This is the day designed to encourage those who hate their birth names to change them.  So, what new name would you choose?    And, tomorrow is not just Valentine's Day.  For those of you without a Valentine, go out and celebrate Ferris Wheel Day!  I suppose you could go on a Ferris Wheel with your Valentine (should you have one), and fulfil both of the day's celebratory activities.  I'll have to settle for just the Ferris Wheel. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yet another children's book.  I really am reading some big people books...I just haven't felt like talking about them.  Kids' books are more fun.  =)   urlLink The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle  is set in 1832 and is narrated by the 13-year-old Charlotte.  She's traveling to America from Britain, where she's been at boarding school.  Her father has made arrangements for her to travel home on a specific ship owned by his company.  There are two families booked as passengers on the same ship who can watch out for her and keep her company.    When she arrives at the dock, the other families have backed out, and she ends up being the only passenger traveling on the ship.  She's surrounded by a bunch of rough sailors, and so she's immediately inclined to trust the captain, who's refined and gentlemanly.  But a few of the sailors befriend her, and she's torn between wanting to believe their stories about the captain's cruelty, and wanting to believe the captain's stories about how the crew's all a bunch of lazy liars.  Turns out the captain really is evil, cruel, and ruthless, and Charlotte is caught in the middle of a mutiny.  At first, the captain turns her against the crew, then she realizes how cruel the guy is, and tries to stick up for the crew.  When she does this, the captain turns against her, and she ends up signing on as one of the crew.   There are all kinds of other intrigues that go on...plotting, murder, betrayal...and overall the story was really exciting and a lot of fun.  Hey, it's a Newbery Honor Book.  Good stuff.  It was a pretty quick read...yeah, well, it’s a kids’ book, what do you expect?  When I finished it, I went and watched my new  urlLink Pirates of the Caribbean  DVD since I was in a seafaring mood.  Arrrr. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wrote briefly about this book before, and said I'd write more when I finished it.  Well, I finished it a good while ago...and should have written something when it was still fresh in my mind, but oh well!  Here goes.     urlLink The Golden Compass  is the first book in Philip Pullman’s  urlLink "His Dark Materials"  trilogy.  The main character, Lyra, has spent her childhood running wild around Jordan College, Oxford.  Events conspire to take her away from Jordan, and she seeks protection from the gyptians (kinda like gypsies), some witches, an armored polar bear, and an aeronaut as she journeys North.  Her goal is to find her Uncle Asriel and deliver a mysterious golden compass to him, as well as to find her friend Roger, one of many children who've been stolen away by the "Gobblers."   An interesting aspect of this particular fantasy world: Everyone has animal "daemon," described as a physical manifestation of a person's soul.  Daemons can change form until their human reaches puberty, at which point the daemon fixes on just one animal shape.  There is an invisible physical connection between human and daemon, which keeps them always together.   The anti-religious agenda I've heard so much talk about is not overtly present in this first book of the trilogy.  But I can guess at where things are headed, from little hints at the end of the book.    A bunch of the adults in the book are obsessed with studying something they call "Dust."  It's only visible in certain types of photographs, and the theory is that Dust is actually original sin.  Very little Dust is seen around children until they reach puberty.  There’s a bunch of bad people experimenting on children to try and discover how to get rid of Dust completely.  At the end of the first book (and I don't think this is giving away the ending), Lyra and her daemon conclude that Dust must be good, since the people trying to get rid of Dust are bad.   "We've heard them all talk about Dust, and they're so afraid of it, and you know what?  We  believed  them, even though we could see that what they were doing was wicked and evil and wrong...We thought Dust must be bad too, because they were grown up and they said so.  But what if it isn't?" "Yeah!  What if it's really  good ..." If Dust were a  good  thing...If it were to be sought and welcomed and cherished...   So I can see where Pullman might take this...he’s already set up original sin as potentially a good thing, and everyone against it as evil, child-torturing fanatics.  That said, I really liked the fantasy world Pullman created.  I loved the idea of the daemons, and the armored polar bears are really cool.  There were some parts of the book that surprised me with their intensity, and a few times, with pretty graphic violence.  I'd definitely have to classify this as young adult, not children's fiction.    Though I really liked the book, I was uneasy with the ending, and not just because of the "Dust is good" thing.  The book gets you to really care about the children, and I became quite horrified at what was happening to them.  And I felt that Lyra’s response to the event at the very end of the book really diminished the importance of that.  Something that should have cut her very deeply was brushed off far too quickly for me.    I'm curious to read the next two books, but hesitant to actually shell out money for them.  Gotta get me a library card for San Mateo County. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Muppets this time, just for Heather.    You are Kermit the Frog. You are reliable, responsible and caring.  And you have a habit of waving your arms about maniacally.  FAVORITE EXPRESSIONS: "Hi ho!" "Yaaay!" and "Sheesh!" FAVORITE MOVIE: "How Green Was My Mother" LAST BOOK READ: "Surfin' the Webfoot: A Frog's Guide to the Internet" HOBBIES: Sitting in the swamp playing banjo. QUOTE: "Hmm, my banjo is wet."   urlLink   What Muppet are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    It really makes me laugh that I'm Kermit. Now I know why Heather is friends with me! And I have a prediction to make: I think Heather will be Fozzie.    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I meant to post this yesterday, but supposedly Tuesday, February 10th signaled the beginning of  urlLink International Flirting Week !  Or so said my Publisher's Lunch email last week.  What's funny is  urlLink the site  they linked to in their article.  Hmmm.  Take charge of your social life with the Love Coach!  Apparently endorsed by  urlLink Cader Books .  Also yesterday: Celebration of the date when the Utah legislature made Jell-O the "official state snack of Utah." Sometimes you just don't want to know.  But, TODAY, Wednesday, February 11, is Satisfied Staying Single Day!  I guess that's to help the single people feel good about themselves before Valentine's Day. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I came across  urlLink this article  today about objections to Shel Silverstein's   urlLink A Light in the Attic  .  Favorite quote: "The three judges hearing the case found that 'Silverstein...was apparently intending to be funny.'"  No, really?  Anyway, the article mentioned  urlLink The Forbidden Library , a site I'd forgotten about.  Read about a bunch of other books that people have tried to ban, for often silly reasons.  My favorite tidbit for today: "Four members of the Alabama State Textbook Committee (1983) called for the rejection of this book [ urlLink  The Diary of Anne Frank  ] because it is a 'real downer.'"  This stuff really makes me laugh.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I had an interesting conversation a few weeks ago with some locals about what to call San Francisco.  They advocated "the City" as the preferred term.  Pretty much everyone in the Bay area calls it "the City," and I've picked up on that since moving here.    Personally, I've had long-term contempt for the name "Frisco."  I just think it sounds stupid.  So, Yoori and I always called it "S.F."  I kinda thought it was unique to us until I heard a local entertainment reporter use "S.F." on TV this week.    Then today, I ran across  urlLink this article  on how the term "Frisco" is making a comeback.  Heaven help us all.  Another note on pronunciation: I love this quote from above referenced article: "don't say San-Fran-Cis-Co. That's the way Easterners, like Larry King, pronounce it. It's more like SanfrnSISco."  I couldn't agree more.  Look at me becoming a local.  :-)   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   While driving to work this morning, I noticed a new billboard along the freeway.  It has this big picture of Scott Peterson in ugly orange prison garb, and next to that, in huge letters: "Man or monster?"  It's an ad for a local radio talk show, and there's a phone number at the bottom for you to call in and vote.  Apparently this isn't the  urlLink first billboard like this .  It'll be interesting to see how much more media obsession is headed our way in Redwood City... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Thank you for the books you sent which connect  quite specifically to everything I have been thinking of  for the last 12 years.  How did you know this?   from Naomi Shihab Nye's  urlLink "Sincerely"   Over the weekend I bought the new  urlLink Dido  CD that I've been wanting for a while.  You know how every once in a while, the lyrics of a song exactly mirror something you've been thinking about?  Well, this was one of those times.  Track #3, Life for Rent.  It's got me written all over it.   I haven't ever really found a place that I call home I never stick around quite long enough to make it...  if my life is for rent and I don't learn to buy well I deserve nothing more than I get 'cos nothing I have is truly mine  while my heart is a shield and I won't let it down while I am so afraid to fail so I won't even try well how can I say I'm alive   This exactly connects with something that's been kicking around in the back of my head for a while—I can't shake the habit of feeling like where I am is temporary.  I realized this a few months ago, and it's been bothering me.  Now that I have a job in publishing, now that I've relocated and am pursuing a career in the field I've chosen—I am puzzled by the fact that I still have this transitional, temporary mindset.  I look at my apartment, and decide against silly, small things like buying a new curtain for the window in my front door.  Because maybe I won't be in this apartment very long—after all, it's only a 6-month lease I'm committed to, maybe I'll find something better. I'm not thinking long term as far as my position at work, because maybe I'll decide that textbook publishing is not where I want to stay.  And, I haven't yet committed to a church up here.  Mainly because I haven't yet found one that's what I'm really looking for (that's another topic for another day), but I also wonder if it's because, sub-consciously, I have a phobia about making permanent plans.  I don't know what it is that's holding me back from feeling settled where I am.  I'm still wondering. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've really become obsessed with these online quiz things.  Or so it would seem.  This week: Veggie Tales!    urlLink        urlLink Which Veggie Tales character are you?   this quiz was made by  urlLink Karen   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Check this out : one of the highest-profile cases of the year is being held in none other than the city in which I live.  Go Redwood City!  It's kind of bizarre to think that this trial is taking place literally up the street from me.  My nieces always watch for me on the news whenever San Francisco is mentioned.  And now, who knows, maybe I'll pop up in the background as the news discusses the Scott Peterson case... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So it seems that there are  urlLink conflicting reports  as to whether the groundhog saw his shadow today.  Apparently  urlLink the official groundhog , Punxsutawney Phil of  urlLink Groundhog Day  fame, saw his shadow and thus predicted six more weeks of winter.  But a rival Staten Island Zoo groundhog (more sensibly named Chuck), failed to see his shadow, predicting an early end to winter.  That's what comes of having too many groundhogs, I guess.    There would be no groundhog-shadow-observing possible in the Bay area today, if people here were inclined to such things.  It's pouring outside. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In continuation of the "All About Me" theme of the day...here are lots of things about myself!  I ripped this off from  urlLink tequila mockingbird .  (Side note: I love this blog.  For a long time, Kristy and I have joked about starting up a restaurant just so we could have a drink on the menu called the Tequila Mockingbird.  This site is cool enough that somehow I don’t even feel miffed about somebody else coming up with the name, too.)  I was playing in the archives one day, and came across  urlLink this post .  I did a little googling and found  urlLink this . Anyway, I thought I’d give it a shot myself.  It reminded me of the game two truths & a lie.  Especially since I always have a hard time coming up with the lie.  It really is hard to come up with 100 things, though.  Enjoy….  100 things about me: 1.	I believe in God. 2.	I believe the Bible. 3.	I believe in prayer. 4.	I don’t believe in evolution. 5.	I believe words don’t have any inherent meaning. 6.	I believe words can have tremendous power. 7.	I'm a book person. 8.	I devour books at a sometimes alarming rate. 9.	I've read War and Peace. 10.	I've read Don Quixote. 11.	I’ve never read Les Miserables. 12.	I’m not a phone person. 13.	I am an email person. 14.	I’ve lived in England. 15.	I used to have an English accent. 16.	I used to have blond hair. 17.	I’ve studied in Italy. 18.	I love to travel. 19.	I wish I could travel more. 20.	I've met the Queen of England. 21.	I wear glasses to drive. 22.	I love Kinder Eggs. 23.	I don’t own enough bookshelves. 24.	I don’t own a couch. 25.	Over the course of 7 years, I had 19 roommates/housemates. 26.	I lived with seven of those roommates/housemates for a year or more. 27.	Right now I live alone. 28.	I live in the Bay area. 29.	I love the beach. 30.	I am a youngest child. 31.	But I don’t act like one. 32.	I have three nieces. 33.	And one nephew. 34.	Who shares my birthday! 35.	I can say “Not if you were the last man on earth” in Italian. 36.	I rarely exercise. 37.	I don't weigh enough to give blood. 38.	That's fine with me, because I have a phobia about needles anyway. 39.	I like Trivial Pursuit. 40.	I like board games/card games/games in general. 41.	But I don't like relationship games. 42.	Sometimes I think too much. 43.	I have a hard time letting people get close to me. 44.	I'm not good at being friends with guys. 45.	I don't believe in soulmates. 46.	I make boring sexy. 47.	And, shockingly after that last revelation, I’ve never had a boyfriend. 48.	I like to tell people that the reason I've never had a boyfriend is because my obesity scares the men away. 49.	I’m  never  sarcastic. 50.	I think it's funny to take things completely literally. 51.	I'm extremely hard on myself. 52.	I hate confrontation.  Avoidance, avoidance, avoidance. 53.	I play the violin. 54.	I sing. 55.	But not in the shower. 56.	I do sing along in the car, though. 57.	But usually only if I'm alone. 58.	I drive faster when I’m happy. 59.	I don’t like cola. 60.	I love cranberry juice. 61.	I don’t like mint. 62.	I like salty more than sweet. 63.	I've never learned to ride a bike. 64.	I love Alias.  Even with Evil Lauren. 65.	I watched every episode of Joe Millionaire. 66.	And I am not ashamed of that! 67.	I've become a TV junkie lately. 68.	I'm attempting to change that. 69.	I'm not fond of facial hair on men.   70.	Or on women, either, for that matter. 71.	Indecisiveness bothers me.   72.	Especially in myself. 73.	I was home schooled. 74.	I graduated from high school two years early. 75.	I took 5 years to finish college. 76.	I have a Master’s degree in English. 77.	I’m compulsively responsible. 78.	I alphabetize my CDs.   79.	And my movies. 80.	I categorize my books and alphabetize within those categories. 81.	I’m hopeless. 82.	My name is written on a beam in the ceiling of Ely Cathedral. 83.	The story that goes with #82 is probably not as interesting as the one you’re imagining. 84.	I hate the phrase “Bye for now!” 85.	The phrase “Back in the saddle” makes me laugh.  Mockingly. 86.	I often have a compulsion to mock people.   87.	Not always in a good way. 88.	I have a weakness for art galleries. 89.	And bookstores. 90.	I don't like roller coasters. 91.	I've climbed Mount Sinai. 92.	I've gone swimming in the Dead Sea. 93.	I've eaten Belgian waffles in Belgium.  Mmmmm. 94.	I'm scared of being the one who loves more. 95.	I prize being self-sufficient.   96.	Sometimes to an unhealthy degree. 97.	I wish I didn't care so much about what other people think of me. 98.	Today is my birthday. 99.	I've been working on these 100 things for several days now. 100.	And now I am done! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There is a new boy in my life.  More specifically, a new nephew, who arrived this morning at 2:17 a.m., sharing MY birthday.  So he's gotta be a cool kid.  =)  Comments from his sisters:  Emily: "He's cute, even if he is a boy." Hannah (apparently repeatedly): "Can I hold my brudder again?" Rebekah: Had a LOT to say, as always, and I didn't catch half of it, since I was on the freeway driving to work.  Love that kid. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Happy birthday to me!  Send birthday greetings my way! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What Wonder of the Ancient World Are You?  You are the Tomb of King Maussollos!  Private and reclusive, you just want to be left alone.  Although you do enjoy good conversation, you tend to avoid confrontations and keep an emotional distance.  As the Tomb of Maussollos, you are very precise in your work and daily living and strive to keep out of other peoples business.  Youre a good listener, and you strive to find logical solutions to your own and other persons problems.  Very indecisive, you tend to analyze yourself into inactivity.    urlLink   What  Wonder of the Ancient World are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes, yes, I  know  it's Descartes' birthday.  But what  else  is on Wednesday?    No, really, guess.  I want to feel loved.  =) 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Heh heh.  Take a look at my March 16th post below.  Specifically at the words "copier battle of  2006 ."  I knew this was going to happen sometime, I just hadn't realized I'd already done it in writing.  Because of our editorial schedule, I'm constantly 2 years ahead.  Right now, we're reviewing and revising books for the 2006 copyright year.  The books I'm sending into production now are our books for 2005.  I frequently have to stop and think about what year it is, because 2004 sounds so...two years ago.  One of these days I'm going to write a check and date it 2006 without even thinking.  I can just see myself trying to explain that one to my credit card company. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been randomly browsing apartment listings today.  My 6-month lease will be up soon (can it really have been that long?!), and I'm suffering from the grass-is-greener syndrome.  Plus, I went to a friend's apartment in Mountain View last night and I'm jealous now.  For things like a patio and a garbage disposal and more room for bookshelves.  Anyway, check these out.  For only $795/month, I could rent  urlLink an apartment with "new pain."   How great is that?  Or, I could  urlLink live on a boat  in Half Moon Bay!  Seriously, the whole living on a boat thing has a certain charm.  The commute to work would suck, driving across the peninsula from Half Moon Bay every morning would not be fun.  But when people asked me where I lived, I could say, "On a boat."  And that has infinite conversation value.  But alas, where would I put all my books? 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Confession: I ripped off  urlLink this link  from my coworker, Anne, who just sent it to me with the following comment:  "is she lady macbeth? or is she just another disgruntled carroll college student?"  You decide. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Heather said something a while ago that I've been turning over in the back of my head recently: "I wish there was just one thing that I was really good at."  That really resonated for me, because I SO often feel that way.  Like I'm mediocre at a lot of things.  Like I'm not good enough at any one thing, and therefore, just flat out not good enough.    That line of thought reminded me of the first of these poems.  I looked it up tonight, in this blank book I used throughout jr. high and high school to write down poems that meant a lot to me.  I discovered that right after it, I had copied in the Naomi Shihab Nye poem "Famous."  I didn't intend it at the time, but it's a rather apt pairing.  In any case, it reminded me tonight of what's really important, especially when I feel like I'm not good enough.   "A Hot Property"  Ronald Wallace   I am not. I am an also-ran, a bridesmaid, a finalist, a second-best bed. I am the one they could have just  as easily given it to but didn't. I'm a near miss, a close second, an understudy, a runner-up. I'm the one who was just edged, shaded, bested, nosed out. I made the final cut,  the short list, the long deliberation. I'm good, very good,  but I'm not good enough. I'm an alternate, a back-up, a very close decision, a red ribbon, a handshake, a glowing commendation. You don't know me. I've a dozen names,  all honorably mentioned. I could be anybody.  "Famous"  Naomi Shihab Nye   The river is famous to the fish.  The loud voice is famous to silence, which knew it would inherit the earth before anybody said so.  The cat sleeping on the fence is famous to the birds watching him from the birdhouse.  The boot is famous to the earth, more famous than the dress shoe, which is famous only to floors.  The bent photograph is famous  to the one who carries it and not at all famous to the one who is pictured.  I want to be famous to shuffling men who smile while crossing streets, sticky children in grocery lines, famous as the one who smiled back.  I want to be famous  in the way a pulley is famous, or a buttonhole, not because it did anything spectacular, but because it never forgot what it could do.   Both poems originally taken from  urlLink The Place My Words Are Looking For .  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   They're doing this over at the  urlLink I Love Books message board , something I've recently gotten hooked on.  I think I'm actually going to send this out as one of those email surveys to a bunch of people (gasp!), but I finished it up last night and thought I'd post it here first.   1. I'm currently reading:   urlLink So Many Books, So Little Time   2. Next I'll read:  Probably  urlLink The Tale of Despereaux  or  urlLink Tunneling .  Although tonight for some odd reason I began craving some chick lit a la  urlLink Coffee and Kung Fu .    3. The best book I read in the past year was:  Definitely  urlLink East of Eden .  Disclaimer: I'm taking this to mean so far in 2004, because to go back a full year would just give me too many options!    4. The book I'm most looking forward to reading is:  the next Harry Potter!  (It's an addiction, I tell you!)  A little closer on the horizon--the next Jasper Fforde:  urlLink Something Rotten , due out Aug. 2004.  5. My favorite author is:  This is so difficult.  It's almost as bad as asking: "What's your favorite book?"  Across the board, maybe Madeleine L'Engle.  But I have a soft spot for L.M. Montgomery and Roald Dahl.  And while I'm in children's lit, Katherine Paterson and Lois Lowry.  And of course, J.R.R. Tolkien.  I love Jasper Fforde, but don't know if I can pin "favorite" on him yet.  Then there's Wilde and Dickens and George Eliot and...yeah.  Like I said, hard question.  6. My favorite book from childhood is:   urlLink The BFG , or the  urlLink Ramona  books.  7. My favorite book from when I was a teenager is:  The whole  urlLink Anne of Green Gables series .  8. The first western I read was:  I don't think I've ever read a western.  Unless perhaps I can count  urlLink Indian in the Cupboard  as a western?  9. The first romance I read was:  Probably something cheesy and young adult that was completely forgettable.  Which is why I can't come up with a title.  10. The first mystery I read was:  I read a lot of mysteries as a kid, but I totally don't remember titles or authors.  No Nancy Drew, though.  11. The first coming-of-age story I read was:  Oh, gosh, I don't know what the first one was.  I'll just go with favorite coming-of-age story... urlLink Jacob Have I Loved  by Katherine Paterson.  Man, these "first" questions are killing me.  I need to browse in the children's section of either the library at Lakenheath AFB or the City of Ely public library, then maybe I could refresh my memory.    12. The first "ethnic" writer I read was:  Maybe Mildred D. Taylor and  urlLink Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry ?  I'm not sure.  I guess it depends on your definition of "ethnic."  There was a book I distinctly remember reading at a very young age about a little girl in Africa, but I can't for the life of me remember the name of it, or even the name of the little girl in the book.  It was red, though, and it was a small cloth covered hardback, with a worn, threadbare cover.  I can remember the exact look of the book and the illustrations in it, and I kind of think the girl's name started with a K.  But that's all I remember.  Funny the memories that come flooding back!  13. The first science-fiction/fantasy book I read was:   urlLink Chronicles of Narnia , or maybe something by E. Nesbit, I don't remember which I read first.      14. I wish I spent more time reading:  non-fiction.  15. The book I think was the greatest waste of my time to read was:   urlLink The Life and Opinions of Tristram Shandy  by Laurence Sterne.   16. The person who most encouraged me to read was:  Frances Bright, childhood best friend and fellow bookworm.  Or my mother, who taught me to read so early on that I honestly can't remember a time when I didn't know how to read.  17. The book I'm embarrassed to admit I liked is:  The entire collected works of Janette Oke--cheesy Christian romances I read in jr. high/high school and totally loved at the time.  More recently:  urlLink Bridget Jones' Diary , but I'm not too embarrassed by that, really.  18. I think people could be encouraged to read through:  Movies.  Seriously.  It sounds like a travesty to say it!  But people are often much more willing to read the book either before, or right after they watch the movie version.  Also, I think recommending just the right book (and having it actually get read) is one of the best ways to get someone reading in the future.  19. My current favorite genre is:  Oh, goodness.  Whatever I'm reading at the time, if I'm enjoying it, so right now: books about reading books.    20. The one book that I'd recommend to almost anyone is:   urlLink To Kill a Mockingbird      

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...simple pleasures.  I rearranged my cubicle at work yesterday.  Well, as much as you can really rearrange a cubicle...I moved a bookshelf.  Still, it made me happy!  I even swiped a chair from the humanities conference room, since I now have room for one.  It looks much homier in here now!    And, yesterday afternoon I had to photocopy a partial manuscript.  Since our lame copier here in the humanities wing seems determined to jam every 10 or 20 pages, I had to stand there and babysit the copier.  But I brought a book and snuck in another chapter of So Many Books, So Little Time while I did my copying.  Whee! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't quite know how to even summarize this book.  It really is the story of one man's life--but it's a sprawling story.  It follows the life story of Adam Trask and his family, and interweaves the stories of the people who shape Adam and his children throughout their lives.  Can I just say--if you're gonna read it, don't read the reviews on  urlLink Amazon  that give a synopsis of the main events in the book!!  Grrr.  (That's what you get when you click on the Oprah's Book Club version of the title...not the only reason I link elsewhere...)  I went into my reading having heard people say they'd really enjoyed the book, but not knowing much about it.  And really, that's enough.  There's not a huge plot hook to draw you in, but  East of Eden  is a really, really good book.    What stands out to me is the way the main characters are so fully developed.  Yet Steinbeck does this so slowly throughout the course of the narrative, that I didn't think about it until I finished the book and realized how well I knew each of the characters.  I loved so many of them--Lee, Adam, Aron, Abra, Cal.  Often, I was frustrated with them and yet I felt like I loved and understood them at the same time.  There are so many parallels in the family relationships--between brothers and fathers and sons--and yet each relationship is very much distinct and different.   Anna (one of our assistant editors) asked me if it was depressing...classic question for a Steinbeck novel...and I have to say no very emphatically.  If I gave a run-down of some of the many horrible things that happen throughout the novel, I guess you might think it was depressing, but the book is by no means heavy in tone.  I felt like it was overwhelmingly hopeful.    Yes, there are parallels to be made between the generations of Adam's family and the family of the biblical Adam...there are themes of good and evil...but what interested me the most was the recurring idea of growth, formation, and influence--who and what a man can become, and why.  "Timshel--thou mayest!"   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   On Friday, I left work at about 2:30 and headed to LA for the weekend.  I left about an hour earlier than planned, thanks to my very nice boss, but no thanks to the idiotic copiers (count them, FOUR!!!!) that were determined to jam, refuse to copy, skew, blur, and otherwise mangle the documents I had to get copied before leaving.  Anyway, after the copier battle of 2006, I was off for a nice long 6 ½ hour drive to my parents' house.  I kept myself amused by listening to all three  urlLink LOTR soundtracks  in succession, and with phone calls from  urlLink Heather , Laurie Winkler (formerly Irwin), and  urlLink David Seruyange .     David & Dianna came up from San Diego as well, so we just had a big family bash on Saturday, celebrating my mom’s birthday, Hannah’s birthday, and my birthday.  Saturday night, Heather came over and joined my family for games, and we had a great time playing  urlLink Apples to Apples  for about three hours!  I haven’t laughed so hard in a long time.    The main reason I headed home for the weekend was to be part of the 25th anniversary celebration for Paul Krake at  urlLink Green Hills .  Church on Sunday was a great time of remembering fun Paul memories (and hairstyles) and thinking back on how much he and his family mean to me.  Because it was Paul’s anniversary, there were not only the regular church folks, but also quite a few old-time members visiting from out of town.  It was so great to see everyone!!  Green Hills really is home for me, and I really miss my church family there.  Fun stories about people’s changed appearance: -Heather looks AMAZING!!!  She seriously has lost a "small child" in weight….and she looks SO great.  What struck me when I first saw her on Saturday was that she looked skinnier than her sister Allison.  Woohoo!  (Just don’t tell Allison I said that…) -My 3-year-old niece Hannah has a mullet.  No joke.  She did it herself!  She took scissors to the whole front half of her hair, and it's now WAY short from the ears forward.  When Nancy described it to me, I was picturing much worse, as in actual bald patches…but no, it's just a bona fide redneck mullet she's got going on.  I got her a hat for her birthday, helpful aunt that I am.  Post-weekend goodies: -I got home Sunday night to find a bonus check from work in my mailbox -Yesterday, my federal tax refund arrived -My latest order from  urlLink Amazon  also arrived yesterday ( urlLink So Many Books, So Little Time  and  urlLink The Tale of Despereaux ) -Last night, I watched my tape of the new  urlLink ALIAS  from Sunday night! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today, my niece Hannah turns three years old.  She's absolutely adorable, in spite of her new self-inflicted haircut.  This is the last year that she will be the youngest child in her family, because in another 2 or 3 weeks, Nancy will have another baby! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'll post about my weekend later, when I'm not so tired.  For now, here's a random quiz.    You are the Girl Next Door.  You're the sweet one. The quiet one.  The one that he doesn't realize he's got until you're gone.    urlLink   What Type Of Retro Gal Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Is is just me, or does the picture look just a  little  too sexy for the "Girl Next Door"?  (Insert requisite boring/sexy joke here.) 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I finished  urlLink  East of Eden   last night. (Please note: the non-Oprah’s-Book-Club version.) Absolutely wonderful book! I'm still processing my thoughts on it, and will post more about it later.    I couldn't decide what to read next, and after glancing through a couple different options, I picked up   urlLink The Soloist   by Mark Salzman. I've had this book for a while but have never picked it up to actually read. I started reading the first few pages to decide if I was in the mood for it, and I got hooked. I read half the book last night. It's about a cellist who was a child prodigy, but lost his "gift" at age 18. His sense of pitch became so acute that he would be distracted during performances by any slight variations in tone.  Anyway, this excerpt really amused me & I thought I'd share:  "I told her about how my sense of pitch was so strong that if even mechanical sounds were out of tune it annoyed me. 'What do you mean, mechanical sounds? You mean machines?' 'Right.  If a blender is a little flat, or the neighbor's lawn mower is a little sharp, it's actually physically painful for me.' ... 'I guess you don't make margaritas at home that much, huh?' 'Actually, I can.  I found a blender that mixes at F-sharp.'"  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes, here we go again with the random "Guess what day it is?" announcements.  Today is supposedly Uppity Women Day.  I thought I would acknowledge it because a few weeks ago, Lee (assistant editor) called me uppity for correcting Steve's (boss) spelling of "soiree" in an email.  What made me laugh the hardest about that particular email exchange was that Lee misspelled uppity.  And then Anna (other assistant editor) came back with the suggestion that Steve should consult  urlLink this site  for help with his French.  Man, I love my team.  These people are great. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This was a good weekend.  I feel like I got a lot done, and I also did fun stuff!  -I opened a bank account up here -Jude called me on Saturday (woohoo!) -I was adventurous and had sushi on Saturday night (and successfully used chopsticks for the entire meal) -I went to a piano concert with people from  urlLink church  -I actually had people to talk to between worship & Bible study at church -I signed up for a small group Bible study -I went to my first church choir rehearsal  -I got a CD player for my car, just in time for my trip home this coming weekend -I spent a nice Sunday afternoon sitting in the sun, eating  urlLink Baskin-Robbins  Chocolate Peanut Butter ice cream and reading East of Eden -I wrote up a little thing for the memory book Bill's putting together for Paul's anniversary -There was a new episode of  urlLink ALIAS  on last night!  Oh, and this wasn't over the weekend, but I want to add it anyway: last week, two of our new books arrived from the bindery—the first ones to have my name on the copyright page under Editorial Assistant!  Ah, the vanity of seeing my own name in print.  =) 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I get  urlLink daily book reviews  from  urlLink Powell's , and today's was particularly interesting: it's on a book called  urlLink American Jesus: How the Son of God Became a National Icon , and the review is titled  urlLink The Fashion of the Christ .  The review is long, but thought-provoking; it actually covers  urlLink another book  in its second half, but it's the first half that made me stop and think.  I found it sadly correct in many ways as the early part of the article described what Jesus has been reduced to in American culture as a whole:     "The latter-day Jesus is an American optimist: good-tempered and informal, a generous Jesus sympathetic to the desires of this world."  "The amiable savior, not only personal but also personable, has pushed the traditional Father, merciful and mighty, off center stage, and with Him the formal elements of Protestant worship. Pop-inspired music for easy listening has ousted gorgeous hymns dating back to the fifteenth century; leisure wear and sneakers have supplanted Sunday best; ministerial raps have edged out liturgy."   Arguments of worship style and church attire aside, this guy’s got a point (whether we’re talking author or reviewer at this point).  The book traces the way American Christianity’s view of Jesus has changed according to cultural trends in the Christian community:    “As popular culture exploded, so did the possibilities for Jesus makeovers.”    "The savior chronicled by Prothero is not a spirit whose powers ever outstrip the culture's -- although you would think that would be a job description for any divinity. Far from transcendent, Jesus is 'more a pawn than a king, pushed around in a complex game of cultural (and countercultural) chess, sacrificed here for this cause and there for another.'"   I'm intrigued and saddened by this penchant we have for serving a Jesus of our own making:  "American Jesus is interested in the country's singular mix of whimsy, obliviousness to theological complexity, and spiritual lust that has created a Son able to serve many -- 'the man that nobody hates' in Prothero's phrase."   I know I myself am guilty of this—of creating my own version of Jesus rather than earnestly seeking who He really is.    I don't want to fall into making Jesus into my own image—of using the name of Christ to justify my own agenda.  I don’t want to serve an idea I have of Jesus, a Jesus I create; I want the real Jesus.    This all brings me back to a sentence prayed at a church I recently visited: "May we seek Your will, instead of seeking that You bless our will." 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe I forgot to mention this in my earlier round-up of random events I hadn't discussed--I went to a  urlLink Jasper Fforde  reading & signing on Saturday in San Mateo!  It totally made my weekend.  Fforde's books are like extended inside jokes for the well-read.  They're hilariously packed with so many literary references that I feel like I need to read more books just to get all the stuff I didn't catch the first time around!  His writing is incredibly clever and creative, and he's the same in person.  I had a great time hearing him talk about his writing, his books, and other random tangents.  What I love about his writing is one of the things he talked about—being intrigued with the idea of making connections between books.  He does this in so many ways—using characters from classic literature in his own stories, making references to other classic books, and actually writing material to fill in bits of other books: like writing the context for some of the Cheshire cat's non sequiturs or answering the Mad Hatter's question of "Why is a raven like a writing-desk?" (The answer being "Because there's a B in both.")   There's a passage in  urlLink The Well of Lost Plots  where  urlLink Thursday  uses the footnoterphone to try and communicate with one of the characters in a book she’s currently reading, A Dark and Stormy Night.  Fforde said that someday he's going to publish that book, and on page 200, that character will randomly say, "Did someone call my name?" and there will be a footnote of Thursday, calling his name.  I love this stuff.  Kristy currently has my copies of  urlLink Lost in a Good Book  and The Well of Lost Plots, and some bookstores are weird about people bringing in books to be signed (they want you to buy THEIR copies…), so I stupidly left my lone Fforde ( urlLink The Eyre Affair ) at home.  But at the end of his talk, Jasper (can I call him Jasper?!) said "I'm happy to sign anything you've brought!"  And, he had mentioned some of the updates he made to the US edition (including a bonus extra chapter)…so I gave in and bought the US edition of WLP for Kristy, and had it signed.  For Kristy, that is.  I then explained that Kristy had borrowed my copies, and told him I would try to get her to come to the LA signing to get my copies signed!  It was so cool, his girlfriend was standing there, and she said, "Ok, we'll have to remember that…Kristy is bringing books to be signed for Barbara!"  Kristy made the trek to San Diego yesterday to go to a signing in La Jolla, so I shall get my signed book yet.  I still have to check and see if Jasper remembered me when Kristy handed over my book to be signed!  After the weekend and being reminded of how much fun Fforde's books are, I've become obsessed yet again.  I need to re-read all three!  After I finish  urlLink East of Eden , that is... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I haven’t blogged in ages. My life has been really busy for the last week and a half, both at home and at work, so I just haven’t done anything on here! Um, let’s see. Various updates, not necessarily in chronological order!  Two weekends ago:   I had dinner with a couple of girls who were English majors at  urlLink Biola  a little while before I transferred there. It was cool to compare Biola English department stories and have some good book conversation. After dinner, I rushed off to the  urlLink YAF  Retreat with  urlLink PBC .  I went into it knowing hardly anybody, but I met a lot of great people over the weekend. It’s really a fun group of people! They'll be forming some new small groups in the coming weeks, so I feel like the timing is really right for me to jump in with this group. I'm looking forward to getting more involved, since YAF's pretty large.    Fun stuff: the retreat of course included the requisite dumb skits and opportunities to look stupid in front of large groups of people. Most elaborate of these was the YAF version of  urlLink American Idol . It was hilarious, they had a host calling himself Ryan Piecrust and the judges were Peter Abdullah (who gave everyone a score of 10), "Simone" (female, you see), and guest judge  urlLink William "Hunk" of "She Bangs" fame . The rest of us were in teams and each team had to pick a song to perform, complete with dance moves. Our team, consisting of three girls and 6 guys, did “Girls Just Wanna Have Fun” and the guys got totally into it. Kinda scary. But not as scary as the other team who stole our song…they had guys in makeup. With purses. Singing falsetto. THAT was scary.  It's funny, because my main purpose for the weekend was to get to know people, rather than any spiritual reason. Not that I didn't expect to hear from God, it's just that I didn't go looking for any deep revelations. But Sunday was really a wonderful time of worship and God speaking to me about some things that I've been struggling with for a while—about missions and what role that will play in my future, and the tension I feel between the now of publishing and the desire to serve in overseas missions at some point.    What else… The  urlLink Oscars  were fun on Sunday. Go  urlLink LOTR !! I got together with some coworkers to watch and we had fun making fun of some of the fashions as well as predicting winners. I didn’t do so well on that.  Darn documentary categories. I made  urlLink Heather’s  vacuum cleaner bars for the event, and they were a bit hit. We had some interesting conversations about politics during the course of the afternoon. They were blown away by the fact that I’m a Republican. Laryssa commented “I don’t think I’ve ever met a real live Republican before!” And Anne said, “It makes sense, though, cause you’re really Christian, right?” Hee hee. Then Laryssa asked me what my views were on gay marriage. It's funny, because my beliefs are really SO very different from theirs, and it's weird to have so little common ground to start from to discuss some of these things.  It was a good conversation, though, and it’s been good to share a bit of who I am and what I believe as I get to be closer friends with these girls.  A while ago, but I didn’t mention it here: I got the time off to go to Wales this summer with the team from  urlLink Green Hills !! I’ve even booked my flight, since I found an amazing deal on the web…the internet is a wonderful thing. I’m really looking forward to this trip. I know it’ll be a bit of stretching for me this year, since my mom has asked me to teach a group of my own rather than just co-teaching with her. Kinda scares me, but it’ll be good.  This is getting hella long. Hee hee! I had an elaborate discussion with some people at retreat about the word “hella,” apparently widely used by San Jose high school students. So using it myself makes me laugh. Anyway. Enough of this; I’m off! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Paul Buchanan told us the Milk Story in my Creative Writing Class at Biola.  I don't remember if it was originally a Tim Caron story or a Walt the Stalker story. ( urlLink Kristy --do you remember?) But anyway, it was about a guy who was paranoid about drinking milk once the date on the carton had arrived.  One night, he inadvertently drank some milk on the sell-by date and, very worried about what might happen to him, he left a note on the fridge that read "It was the milk," so that all would be clear should he die in the night from food poisoning.  But really, the question is: How long does milk stay good after the sell-by date passes?  Because if the store must  sell  it by that date, it follows that there is a grace period, so to speak, following that date, during which the milk is still good.  At least, that's the logic I have always used.  Until now.  Last night at about 9pm I got hungry and decided to have some cereal.  In the process, I finished off the milk, and threw the carton in the trash.  That was when I noticed the sell-by date: April 22.  For some reason, I thought yesterday was the 25th.  So I figured the milk was still good--it didn't smell bad, it didn't look weird, so everything is fine, right?  Maybe not.  As I went to bed later, I glanced at the calendar on my desk, which read April 27.  Urgh.  5 days past the sell-by date, not so good.  Suddenly the cereal seemed like not such a great idea.  Indeed, something didn't agree with me last night.  I didn't leave a note on the fridge, but I'm pretty darn sure it was the milk. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I found this on a blog and modified it for my own purposes.  The original instructions were to choose a band and answer only with titles of songs by that band, but, well....it's all about the books with me.   Answer only with titles of books:   Are you male or female?   urlLink Little Women   How old are you?   urlLink Now We Are [Twenty-]Six   Describe yourself:   urlLink Lost in a Good Book   How do some people feel about you?   urlLink The Long Secret   How do you feel about yourself?   urlLink A Heartbreaking Work of Staggering Genius   (I just couldn't resist) Describe your ex girlfriend/boyfriend:   urlLink Invisible Man   Describe your views on significant others and crushes:   urlLink Things Fall Apart   Describe what you want:   urlLink About a Boy   (and sometimes,   urlLink How to Disappear Completely and Never Be Found  ) Describe how you live:   urlLink How to Be Good  ,   urlLink Hey World, Here I Am!   Describe how you love:   urlLink One Hundred Years of Solitude  ,   urlLink Where Angels Fear to Tread   (or on a good day,   urlLink Great Expectations  ) Share a few words of wisdom:   urlLink Stand in the Wind   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Got this from my mom last night:   Last night Hannah was sick--fever, threw up, the whole bit.  This morning while Nancy was nursing Little John, Hannah said she didn't feel so good, got up and went to the kitchen, got a bowl, threw up in it, then brought it to Nancy.  I think that was very responsible!   When I was three, I wouldn't have had the presence of mind to go get a bowl to throw up in.  Go Hannah!  And, as of yesterday afternoon, Hannah's feeling better; saying she's "all fine."  Yeah.  I miss the kids. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I know I'm behind on this one.  Yeah, I'm behind on a lot of stuff.  I debated for a while about whether I was going to see The Passion or not, mainly because I didn't know if I could deal with the violence.  And then, the Christian bandwagon effect kicked in, which further discouraged me from seeing it.  "Every Christian should see this!" is never a motivation for me to see a movie.  I'm contrary like that.  But I talked with  urlLink Kristy  about it, on Easter actually.  We talked about how it's often hard to see Jesus as a real person; when you've heard the stories over and over, they lose their meaning sometimes.  And our conversation made me think that the movie would be something that might help me to see who Jesus is more clearly, just for myself emotionally.  It also clarified some of the violence issues for me, and with that, I decided to go ahead and see the movie.   First off, the violence wasn't as bad as I was anticipating.  Yes, it was extremely violent, and there were plenty of times when I winced and had to look away, but for the most part it didn't bother me the way I thought it would.  It was an amazing, and I would even say beautiful film.    There were so many small touches that were just artistically beautiful.  I loved the depiction of the the grave clothes at the end, the pieta that was created when they take Jesus down from the cross, and the flashbacks throughout, showing scenes from Jesus' life.    The depiction of Satan and the demonic elements was intriguing.  I felt that some of it was over the top (like the freaky demon children, for example...), but especially good was the scene with Jesus praying in the garden and Satan throwing doubts and questions at him.  I loved the portrayal of Jesus' relationship with Mary.  It was one of the aspects of the movie that really made me think about Jesus in some new ways.  So much was demonstrated through just a few scenes: his love and care for his mother, and how much she really understood what he would have to go through.  The scenes showing Jesus' relationship with his mother and his disciples were so wonderful at giving glimpses of who Jesus really was: fully God, and yet fully human.  And I think what affected me the most was the pairing of those scenes from Jesus' life with the events of the Passion.    I do wish, though, there had been more of that--that the film had taken more time to show who Jesus was before arresting him and beating him up.  I heard the movie being criticized for only portraying the crucifixion, and not depicting the whole life of Jesus.  And I was frustrated with that criticism, because after all, the movie is called "The Passion of the Christ."  It didn't set out to be a life of Christ, but a depiction of the events of the Passion.  If the movie had showed more of the life of Jesus, it would have been a different movie.  And as a portrayal of the Passion, it was incredible.    But the thing is, there's more to Jesus than the Passion.  There's more to my faith than the Passion.  The meaning of the Passion is rooted in the life that preceded it, as well as in the Resurrection.  Yes, the crucifixion is central to my faith, and yes, that is why Jesus came--to give his life--but there is so much more to who Jesus is.  And I wish that had been more a part of this movie.    There are many who will see the film who do not know the surrounding context of Jesus' life, and who won't grasp the depth of Christ's sacrifice or the reasons behind it.  Don't get me wrong, I know the movie has and will continue to offer opportunities to start conversations and answer some of those questions.  But there really was no space given to character development, and I think that's one of the reasons the movie didn't have the emotional impact for me it might otherwise have had.    All of that said, this movie was a wonderful reaffirmation of what I believe, a reminder of the magnitude of Christ's sacrifice and our Savior's love for us, and it was an amazing experience I'm glad to have had.   And being found in appearance as a man, he humbled himself, and became obedient to death--even death on a cross! Therefore God exalted him to the highest place and gave him the name that is above every name, that at the name of Jesus every knee should bow, in heaven and on earth, and under the earth, and every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord, to the glory of God the Father. --Phil. 2:8-10    Crown Him the Lord of life, Who triumphed o'er the grave, And rose victorious in the strife For those He came to save; His glories now we sing, Who died, and rose on high, Who died eternal life to bring, And lives that death may die.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I loved this movie.  I really can't say that enough.  It was an amazing movie in so many ways.  But as I started to write about it, I realized that right now I'm more interested in my reaction to the movie and the way it made me think.    I left the movie with such a strong sense that love is worth it no matter what.  That no matter how difficult the experience, it is never worth forgetting.  That even if relationships hurt and even if they don't work out, they should still be pursued, because the journey is worth it.  I've heard and read quite a few interpretations of the ending of the movie.  And I think it was ambiguous and definitely open to interpretation.  You can take it to mean that we are doomed to repeat our mistakes.  You can take it to mean that fate controls everything, no matter how hard we fight against it.  Or you can walk away from the movie as I did: convinced that love is worth it, no matter how much it hurts.  And that the experience is worth remembering, even if it rips your heart out.  I was talking to Yoori about the movie a few weeks ago, and she challenged me to put some action behind these words and go after something I'm scared of pursuing.  And it's funny, because she's right.  I believe strongly that love is worth the risk, and yet I have an extremely hard time acting on that.  I'm such a defeatist.    So I'll see.  Perhaps life will offer me the opportunity to act on these thoughts, and then again, maybe not.  There's the pessimist in me emerging yet again.  I can be such a paradox... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The following is courtesy of an email I received from the  urlLink Tattered Cover Bookstore , a wonderful place to visit should you ever find yourself in Denver.   Every year on April 23rd, Barcelona erupts in a celebration of chivalry and romance. It all began in the Middle Ages with an annual Festival of Roses to honor St. George, Patron Saint of Catalonia. A brave Roman soldier, he allegedly slew a dragon about to devour a beautiful young princess. According to legend, a rosebush then sprouted from the blood of the slain dragon and the soldier plucked its most perfect blossoms to give to the princess as a remembrance.   In 1923, the traditional Rose Festival merged with International Book Day, established to celebrate the lives of Miguel de Cervantes and William Shakespeare, both of whom died on April 23rd in 1616. Now, bookstalls and flower stands sprout up along the Rambla, a two-mile stretch connecting the city with the Mediterranean Sea. Thousands of Barcelonans crowd the streets to enjoy a festive atmosphere of readings, music, literature, and dance. And rare is the woman without a rose--or the man without a book tucked under his arm.   I must say, I'd rather have the book than the rose.  =)  Today is also Barbara's blog update day, since I did a bunch of writing last night.  Here it comes... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Something to add to the page while I'm in the process of generating my own words.   My very British name is  Margaret Gladstone .  urlLink Take The Very British Name Generator today!   Created with  urlLink Rum and Monkey 's  urlLink Name Generator Generator .   I also tried this with just my first and last name, instead of my full name.  The result was "Margaret Thatcher," which kind of scared me.  So I'm keeping the Gladstone.  Either way I remain in the British Prime Minister genre of names.  Gladstone was a PM, right?  Gonna have to look that one up.  Here is another name game:    urlLink      urlLink What Name Should You Have?  by  urlLink Lauren    I'm not too enthralled by the name Alyssa, so I went back and changed a bunch of my answers.  I got the same thing.  Hmmm. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are bits and pieces of things kicking around in my head that I want to blog about, but I haven't actually taken the time to write lately.  I'm hoping I'll have time to do that this week, so stay tuned for some of the following:  I wrote up something last week about  urlLink Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind , only to find that it was more about me than about the movie.  Then I decided what I wrote was far more personal than I wanted to post on my blog, so maybe an abbreviated version will show up here when I have a chance to abbreviate it.  On Saturday, I finally saw  urlLink The Passion .  I am really glad I went to see it, and it was an amazing film...but I'll post more thoughts on it later.  I was supposed to get my  urlLink couch  yesterday, but didn't.  Not for lack of trying.   urlLink Pier 1  just wasn't cooperative.  Grrr.  Hopefully it will be delivered (for FREE!) this week. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Jude and I have been going back and forth lately about "three months."  And, I am excited to announce that exactly three months from today, I will be arriving in Porthcawl, Wales.  Woohoo!  I'm really looking forward to a great time of ministry this summer as I get to be part of a team helping lead a Holiday Bible Club with Gilgal Baptist Church.  I know there'll be many challenges during the trip, in both ministry and relationships, but I am looking forward to seeing the ways I know God will work during my time there.  It's exciting and also bittersweet, because this will probably be my last year to be part of the team from  urlLink Green Hills .  I've moved, I have a  urlLink new church , and I know it's time for me to get involved in ministry here.  But this summer, it will be SO good to again minister alongside friends from my home church, as well as friends from Wales! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Common Errors in English .  I love the occasional snarky comments:    urlLink SOUP DU JOUR OF THE DAY   Soupe du jour  (note the  E  on the end of  soupe ) means "soup of the day." If you're going to use French to be pretentious on a menu, it's important to learn the meaning of the words you're using. Often what is offered is  potage , anyway. Keep it simple, keep it in English, and you can't go wrong.  And while I'm at it, I'll just point out an error that's one of my pet peeves:    urlLink YEA/YEAH/YAY  "Yea" is a very old-fashioned formal way of saying "yes," used mainly in voting. It's the opposite of--and rhymes with--"nay." When you want to write the common casual version of "yes," the correct spelling is "yeah" (sounds like "yeh"). When the third grade teacher announced a class trip to the zoo, we all yelled "yay!" (the opposite of "boo"!). That was back when I was only  yay  big.   Each entry has a donkey next to the error and an owl next to the correct usage.  Wise owl, dumb ass.  Hee hee. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday my computer at work automatically downloaded Windows updates.  That's all fine and dandy.  Except that now, EVERY SINGLE TIME an error message pops up, my computer emits this loud beep that makes me jump.  And I can't figure out how to turn it off!  It's coming from the freakin' hard drive itself, so even muting ALL the sound on my computer doesn't do anything.  GRRR.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    You are a  GRAMMAR GOD !   If your mission in life is not already to preserve the English tongue, it should be. Congratulations and thank you!    urlLink   How grammatically sound are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Found at  urlLink andshesaid.com , and edited just because I didn't have interesting or witty answers to all of the questions.  Not that all of these answers are witty or interesting, but there you go.  It was the first question that drew me in...anyone else care to share their own page 18, line 4?   1. Grab the book nearest to you, turn to page 18, find line 4. What does it say?   I'm at work.  I have three whole shelves of philosophy and religion textbooks to my right.  It's really a toss-up as to which one is closest...but how about  urlLink A Journey through the Hebrew Scriptures  by Frank Frick.  Because I like the author's name.  Hee. "…Tyndale in 1526, all English translations were based on the Vulgate."  2. Stretch your left arm out as far as you can. What do you touch first?  In which direction?  To the left, nothing.  Straight ahead, my computer monitor.  Up, nothing but odd looks from other EAs who see my fingers wiggling in the air above their cubicle walls.  Behind me, nothing.  3. WITHOUT LOOKING, can you guess what the time is?  Right around 3pm, because they just came to pick up the mail.    4. Now look at the clock, what is the actual time?  3:03pm.  Woohoo!  5. With the exception of the computer, what can you hear?  Trina's salsa music playing quietly.  Trina humming along to her salsa music.  Annie talking to Holly.  Other people typing.  6. When did you last step outside? What were you doing?  At lunch. I walked over to the café to get food.  7. What are you wearing?  A big comfy grey sweater, jeans, grey snowman socks, and my black t-strap docs.  8. When did you last laugh?  About 10 minutes ago when Cheryl sent a  urlLink weird news story link  and I gave a witty comeback.  9. What is on the walls of the room you are in?  Is a cubicle really a room?  I think not.  But anyway...pictures of friends and family, Shakespeare calendar, pictures drawn by Emily, and my JDE database cheat sheet.  10. Seen anything weird lately?  See #8.  urlLink News story on eyeball jewelry .    11. What do you think of this quiz?  Better than some.  12. What is the last film you saw?  On DVD:  urlLink The Truth About Cats & Dogs .  In the theaters:  urlLink Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind .  Which was excellent, I might add.  13. If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first?  A plane ticket to Florence.  And the necessary travel expenses for traveling all around Italy and Greece and eventually the rest of Europe and beyond.  14. Can you tell something about you that no one knows?  Yes, I can.  But I won't.  15. Do you like to dance?  Not really; I'm too self-conscious.  16. Imagine your first child is a girl, what do you call her?  I've always liked the name Amanda.  17. Imagine your first child is a boy, what do you call him?  I like the name Caleb.  18. Would you ever consider living abroad?  Where do I sign up and when can I leave? 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Regent College Bookstore, one of the largest Christian bookstores in Canada, has decided to not carry  urlLink Glorious Appearing , the latest installment in the Left Behind series.    From today's  urlLink Publisher's Lunch : "Manager Ian Panth says the books, 'Mix a dangerous theology with politics--and we don't want to sell it.... The book is very American-centric. It suggests the United States is successful because it has supported the state of Israel. It portrays the Antichrist as a Romanian who has risen up to take over the United Nations. It also paints the European Union as entirely demonic.' He says the faculty supports him, 'appalled by the bad writing and bad theology in the apocalyptic series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins.'"  Call me a literary snob, but right there is just another long list of reasons why I won't read these books.    Check out the Beliefnet article  urlLink here . 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This morning I got onto my blog to change my "Currently Reading" info.  And I happened to glance at the google ads at the top of the page.  Now, I have noticed that these ads are usually vaguely related to whatever is posted on my blog.    But this morning, what I found was this:   Relationships And Love Find your Soul Mate - 8 million Singles, Pictures and Profiles!  	  And this:  Affair Help Professional online counseling for extramarital affairs    And the "related searches" below:  Romance novels  Harlequin romance   Apparently that's what I get for ranting about Christian dating books.  Although, I really don't get where the "affair help" came from.  I do realize that I'm perpetuating the cycle by even posting this.  Who knows what adultery-related ads will result in the next few days.  Apologies in advance. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I bought  urlLink a couch  last night.  Or, more accurately, a loveseat.  Soon I shall have more than one place to sit in my living room.  Right now, there is a choice of the papa san chair or the floor.  Anyway, I just hope that I will actually be pleased with where I  think  the couch will fit.  My lovely friend Laryssa has volunteered the use of her Explorer to transport the thing, as well as the assistance of her husband to get it up the stairs.  Although Anne kindly offered to carry it the two blocks from Pier 1 to my apartment--a leisurely walk down El Camino-- an offer definitely worthy of mention.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My parents gave me two Christian dating books for my birthday.  I ran across them this afternoon while rearranging some bookshelves in my apartment, and for some odd reason--perhaps it was guilt over having not even cracked the covers open--I decided to take a closer look.    The first is called  urlLink  When God Writes Your Love Story: The Ultimate Approach to Guy/Girl Relationships  .  I get pretty skeptical when anything claims to be the "ultimate approach" to anything.  But, I thought I'd try to set aside my skepticism, and I took a look at the back cover.  "Bestselling authors Eric and Leslie Ludy invite you to discover how beautiful your love story can be when the Author of romance scripts every detail."  Ugh.  Somehow, talking about God as the "Author of romance" just doesn't appeal to me.  There's a bad association with romance novels hidden somewhere in that phrase.    Well, let's check out option #2, titled  urlLink  What's a Girl to Do?   and subtitled "While Waiting for Mr. Right."  O-K.  Because, you know, I've always found that to be a great mystery.   /sarcasm alert/ Oh my word, I don't have a husband!  My life has no purpose!  Whatever shall I do with myself?!  /end sarcasm alert/   I've never been the type to sit at home wondering what to do with myself until I find myself a husband, so I'm getting just the  slightest  (ok maybe not so slight) inkling that this book is probably not for me.  But the back cover didn't sound quite as sticky-sweet as most of this stuff, so, again quelling my skepticism, I opened the thing up and took a look at the first few pages.    At first, things seemed promising.  In her introduction, the author somewhat sarcastically referred to the numerous Christian dating books out there, and said, "As you may have guessed, I'm not into books like that."  Well, good.  Neither am I.  I flipped a little further along in the book, and found sentences like, "The good news is, you don't have to sit around waiting."  And: "While we're waiting for God to send along Mr. Right, we need to get in the game of life."  Yeah, genius there.  Because, you see, I thought I was just supposed to sit at home and wait for a guy to come along and marry me!  You mean, single Christian girls should actually have a life, and not just focus on finding a man?  What a newsflash!  Grrr.  I don't mean to mock these books or their authors.  I'm sure there are people who find these books helpful.  And it's not like I've never delved into the Christian relationship guide genre.  My sister gave me Elisabeth Eliot's  urlLink  Passion and Purity   when I graduated high school, and I read  urlLink  Knight in Shining Armor   in college, when a bunch of my friends were reading it.  (And when my cynicism about such books was at a much lower level.)  Both books made some good points, though I would say "grain of salt" to both of them.  But now, I guess I kind of pride myself on not being the kind of girl who reads these kinds of books.  And it frustrated me that someone would think I was the kind of girl who needed that sort of thing.    In  So Many Books , Sara Nelson talks about the impact that giving or lending a book can have on a relationship.  What do you do when someone you love gives you a book you hate?  "I should let it go, or reconsider my feelings about the book in question.  But I end up reconsidering the friendship instead" (67).  Now, don't get me wrong, I know to make allowances for difference of taste in books.  And yet, there is a lot of truth to the idea that the kind of book someone offers you says something about what they think of you.  And a book recommendation can affect your relationship with the person who recommended it.  I love my parents, but it kinda bugs me that they think I'm the sort for Christian dating books.  It annoys me to think that they see me as the kind of person who needs to hear: "The good news is, you don't have to sit around waiting."   The thing is that for me, I really don't see the point to these books.  What God wants me to do while I'm "waiting for Mr. Right" has never been an issue for me.  My concern should simply be what God wants me to do.  Why even tack on that second part?  Why make that distinction?  I don't feel like my life is purposeless or unrewarding simply because I don't have a man.  There are books to read!  Places to go!  There are ministries to be involved in, things to experience, to think about, to explore--and I don't need a boyfriend to do these things.  I never have.  Yes, I would love to be in a relationship now, but that's not my first priority.  Finding a boyfriend has never been something I've pursued.  Maybe I need a book that talks more about how I should stop avoiding relationships, instead of one that tells me to stop pining away after them.  So, for now anyway,  What’s a Girl to Do?  and  When God Writes Your Love Story  are going back on the shelf.  Between  Passion & Purity  and  Knight in Shining Armor .  I have other things to read. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Right after I finished  urlLink  So Many Books  , I got sucked into reading  urlLink  Good in Bed   by Jennifer Weiner.  Don't laugh.  I read it, I liked it, say what you will.  Yes, it's chick lit.  But it was...enjoyable.  (That was for you, Heather!)  Following is the disclaimer I feel compelled to provide because I always compulsively explain myself:  For those who've not heard of the book, don't go jumping to conclusions!!  The ex-boyfriend of the book's narrator writes a monthly column called "Good in Bed" for a women's magazine.  Thus, the title.  Get your mind out of the gutter, people!  It's not THAT kind of book. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Things have been kind of quiet on the book front lately.  I finished  urlLink  So Many Books, So Little Time   a few weeks ago, and never really wrote up my thoughts on it.  Guess it's time for me to catch up.    The premise of the book is that it's the chronicle of a year in the life of a passionate reader.  Sara Nelson set out at the beginning of 2002 to read a book a week and chronicle her thoughts on each one.  And, pretty much, she does accomplish this.  Her stated goal is to do more than just this, though; her desire was to observe the reading process and the ways books intersect with our lives.  And those observations are exactly what I liked about this book.  I really liked  So Many Books , even though I realized that Nelson's and my own taste in books probably don't intersect too much.  Nelson says, "If a particular book I mention makes you want to head off to the nearest bookstore, great; if not, maybe what I say about it will spark a memory or suggest a topic that seems honest or interesting or true" (7).  And, it did.  That's what I love about books and talking about books--the springboard effect.  Books can bring up common experiences and ideas, and provide ways for us to connect with each other personally, as well as through discussion of the book itself.  And you don't always have to have read a book to be able to have a conversation about it.  (Or to write a paper about it.  Heh heh.)  I enjoyed the way Nelson mentions various reading quirks that I often see in myself--like "double-booking," and the aversion to re-reading (when there is the guilt of so many unread books looming overhead).  Also, the way we have "public books," you know...the ones that you're proud of reading, so you're more apt to let yourself be seen reading them.  Unlike guilty pleasures like  urlLink  Good in Bed   and  urlLink  Bridget Jones' Diary  , both of which I read at home on the weekend.  So this leads me to a habit I noticed about myself while reading this book: I have to use a bookmark that matches the book I'm reading.  Not only does the bookmark have to be the appropriate size and thickness (leather bookmarks just don't belong in paperbacks), but there cannot be a thematic disconnect between the book and bookmark.  While reading  So Many Books , I used a bookmark with a picture from the Old Library at Trinity College Dublin.  When I read  Good In Bed , I had to find a completely different bookmark.  The stacks of books in the Old Library at Trinity just didn't fit between the covers of contemporary chick-lit.  Current bookmarks: in  urlLink  The Princess Bride  --one with hearts and "Be Mine" on it, a gift from a friend at Valentine's Day years and years ago.  And in A.S. Byatt's  urlLink  The Biographer's Tale  --one from Shakespeare's Globe in London, with a quote from  urlLink  Love's Labour's Lost  .     Does anyone else match bookmarks with books, or am I just an anal freak?  Maybe I shouldn't have asked that. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My nephew finally has a name!  Or, in my sister's words:    "Houston, we have a name. . . . at least it has stuck all day : )  John Michael James  I know, how could it take that long to come up with something so original?!"     Apparently, my niece Emily still intends to call him Jesse.  Hee hee.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So my sister hasn't yet named the new baby.  They're pondering both John Michael Puckett and Jesse Michael Puckett.  John Michael carries with it a family tradition; both John and his dad are called John Michael.  Jesse was my grandpa's name (my mom's dad).  This morning, John was leaning towards John Michael, and the girls were swayed by the idea that their dad would be "Big John" and the baby would be "Little John."  (Shades of Robin Hood...)  But Emily's with me in preferring Jesse Michael.   So, let's take a poll here...what do you think: Jesse Michael or John Michael?  The actual name is to be decided sometime today.  No word on whether this poll will have any bearing on that or not.  =)  Not that this blog is now or ever has been a hotbed of comments, but hey. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Remember playing MASH?  Well, now you can  urlLink play it online .  Ahh, the memories.  Come on, you know you want to know what the future will be like: where you'll live, who you'll marry and how many kids you'll have, what you'll do for a living, and what color and type of car you'll drive.  MASH holds all the answers!!  On our plane trip to Italy in '96, Melinda and I couldn't sleep, so we decided to play MASH.  I believe that the paper with our MASH predictions still lives on in Mel's journal.  And I think it predicted me marrying the guy I had a crush on at the time.  Yeah, like  that  would have been a good idea. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   While I'm on the subject of television, and because I am sad that  urlLink Alias  is on hiatus until January 2005 (How could you do that to me, ABC????), here is another quiz.    You are Marcus Dixon    urlLink   Which Member of the Alias SpyGang are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    I like Dixon.  I just wish he'd actually had a few lines this season! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Today's review  from Powell's Books is particularly good.  It's about a book by Davy Rothbart called  Found: The Best Lost, Tossed, and Forgotten Items from Around the World .  This sounds like something I'd love to page through in the bookstore, but probably wouldn't buy:   Within the span of a few pages, one can find a burnt tooth brush found in the ruins of Waco, a ransom note from a grade-schooler holding another child's binder hostage for $3.50, and a poster directed towards building residents, asking them to lock the front door in order to "prevent unauthorized people from entering the building and defecating in the washing machine."    The review draws a parallel (as well as many contrasts) between reality TV and the glimpses of reality this book offers:    But, this record of daily life is undoubtedly more "real" than most reality programming. No one in its pages is forced into staged situations, no one is over produced, highly edited, publicly humiliated, pumped with silicone or forced to drink offal and intestine milkshakes. Instead, they are captured quietly in time, the waste of their lives reexamined, recontextualized, and earnestly appreciated.   I've been thinking a lot about reality TV lately.  The reality TV addiction started for me a couple of summers ago when Suzanne got me hooked on  urlLink American Idol .  Then came  urlLink Joe Millionaire .  And  urlLink Average Joe .  I watched the last half of  urlLink The Apprentice  recently, and also got sucked into watching the last two seasons of  urlLink The Bachelor .  Man, I need a life.  But this stuff can be so addictive!    The contest type shows aren't really that bad.  American Idol, The Apprentice--people pretty much know what they're getting into, and they're the ones that are putting themselves out there to be embarrassed or showcased on national television.  But the more I think about the dating shows, the whole concept becomes more and more unsettling to me.  On shows like Joe Millionaire, Average Joe, and The Bachelor, real people's emotions are manipulated and edited down just to provide us with "entertainment."  These are real people, and their bickering, embarrassment, and heartbreak are aired for all to see.  Yeah, sure, they sign up for the shows of their own free will.  But it's sad to me that television is thriving from manipulating people's lives--even if it is only for a few months.    So, yeah.  These are the thoughts that come from my watching "After the Final Rose" last night, and I guess the above review just hit me in such a way as to bring this rant to the surface.  I gotta stop watching reality TV! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday at lunch, some co-workers were filling out a crossword.  One of the clues had something to do with a play by Tennessee Williams that had the word "iguana" in the title.  None of us could think of the correct title, so we proceeded to offer suggestions like "Iguana on a Hot Tin Roof" and "An Iguana Named Desire."  Laryssa then commented that if she ever gets an iguana, she'll name it "Desire."  That goes right up there with my wish to someday name a dog "Tim Johnson."  While I'm on the subject of iguanas, I'd also like to mention that "iguana" is a fun word to say.  Try it.  You'll like it.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     What Color is Your Brain?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      GOLD:   At work or in school:  I like set routines and organized ways of doing things. Rules and directions are a great help to me. I prefer to stay on one topic at a time. I need to know what is expected of me, and I always want to know if I am on the right track. I like subjects that are useful and traditional, such as business, accounting, history and government.  With friends:  I prefer people who are careful with their money and who make plans ahead of time. I like my friends to be loyal, dependable and on time. I am serious about love and show it in many practical ways.  With family:  I like stability and security and enjoy traditions and frequent celebrations. I like to spend holidays with family members, and I plan ahead for such gatherings.  Hmm.  That's pretty much me, other than the supposed affinity for "subjects that are useful and traditional."  I don't know if they consider literature useful and traditional.  After all, according to Oscar Wilde, "All art is quite useless." 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Maybe I should have waited on getting my own Gmail.  Check this out:  urlLink Gmail Swap .  Tons of people desperate for an account are advertising what they're willing to exchange for a Gmail invite.  This has possibilities... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have a  urlLink Gmail  account!  Blogger had been offering them before they changed their layout, and I kept thinking, "What do I need another email address for?"  Then Blogger changed their layout and quit offering me Gmail.  And then I decided I wanted it.  Typical.  Well, I just logged in and there was the offer again.  HA!  So now I have Gmail.  Just days after I told everybody to start using my Biola email.  Oh well.   urlLink Email me ! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   At our team lunch on Wednesday, my boss entertained us with his idea of walking to work some day this summer.  He said he'd checked, and it would be about 22 miles, from San Francisco to Belmont.  This is my boss.  Last weekend, he hiked Half Dome on Saturday, and ran  urlLink Bay to Breakers  on Sunday.    Last weekend, I sat at home and read books.  This is me, folks.  I don't exercise.  Like, ever.  And I'm going hiking tomorrow.  It's supposedly a fairly easy hike, pretty flat, only about 4 miles.  I'm looking forward to the promised views of the Golden Gate Bridge and the Marin headlands.  I'm not looking forward to the pain I know I will be in on Sunday.  But I'm still gonna go.  On another note, my good friend Veronica went hiking yesterday with her boyfriend and came home engaged.    So yeah, I'm going hiking tomorrow.  Wish me luck.  ;-) 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For performance reviews at work, that is.  And, I just got a very very positive one.  Yay!  Tomorrow I meet with my boss to discuss it, but I'm not worried, because I am very pleased with the written review he just handed me!  This struck me as slightly ironic, though: when he walked into my cube to hand me the review, I was checking my personal email.  Then I proceeded to read the part of the review where he said, "Barbara resists the urge to waste time on unnecessary projects.  She knows how to set priorities and spends her time wisely."  Doh!  Back to work!  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Warning: Irreverence ahead.  Yesterday at church, not in the main service, but in our young adult group, I noticed a VERY BAD TYPO on one of the overheads.  Here is where we discover why being correct is VERY important. I was appreciating the fact that we were singing a hymn, and then this line appeared: "See Him prostate in the Garden."  My eyes went very wide.  I managed to quell the laughter and channel it into coughing.  But away went any hope of sincere worship from me for the rest of the morning.   Prostrate .  Not prostate.  There is a second R, and it makes a BIG difference, people.    Also yesterday, this time in the main service, we sang "Better is One Day."  I really like this song.  But I cannot sing it without thinking of a comment we once received in the church office at Green Hills.  After complaining about the song being too fast, the person claimed that "even Jesus couldn't have sung that fast."  Far be it from me to comment on how fast Jesus can sing.  But yesterday at PBC, as we sang a slower version of the song, I thought to myself, "I wonder if this is a better tempo for Jesus."  I honestly think that God laughs with me when I think things like this.    Along these same lines, I've been following a blog entry and its subsequent comments on the topic of " urlLink Top Five Worst Worship Songs ."  Favorite comment yet: "Isn't it ironic that if God really answered me when I sang "Trading My Sorrows," we would never sing that song again? Yes, Lord. Yes, Lord. Yes, yes, Lord. Amen."  Indeed.  All of this started me thinking about worship songs that have been ruined for me by some association I have formed with the music or words.   Shout to the North:  Melinda commented once that the rhythm of this song reminds her of a German drinking song.  Now, whenever I hear the chorus: "Shout to the North and the South," I picture sweaty bearded German men sloshing their beer steins in time to the music.  Thanks, Mel.   Let Everything that has Breath:  When I was working in the church office at Green Hills, Jamie once told us a story about a pastor's mis-reading of Psalm 150.  With a triumphant final line, the pastor shouted out, "Let everything that has breasts praise the Lord!"  Call me juvenile, but I've only recently been able to get past the urge to giggle when we get to the chorus of this song.   We Want to See Jesus Lifted High:  My first issue with this song was that it made me think of Alice, a blind lady at Green Hills.  I'm not being cruel; she tells more blind jokes than the rest of us.  But when it repeats, "We want to see, we want to see," well, I think of Alice and laugh to myself.  And then, thanks to Eric's performance of Heather's VBS choreography on this song, I have a hard time keeping a straight face at "Strongholds come tumbling down and down and down and down."  Unfortunately, the image of Eric shaking his butt on those lines is permanently burned into my memory.  (ACH, MY EYES!!!!!!!!)  And a hymn:  He Touched Me:  Ok, go ahead and tell me I have my mind in the gutter, but the title just sounds completely inappropriate.  Either that, or it sounds like little kids fighting: "Mo-om!!  He touched me!!"  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This morning on my drive to work, I saw a bumper sticker that read:  "Don't pray in my school, and I won't think in your church."  It made me defensive, a little indignant, and finally sad.  I'm sad that the world at large perceives the church as something that is mindless.  I'm sad that many think religion is something that requires you to turn off your mind in order to believe.    I'm a pretty logical person.  I believe what I believe because I have logical reasons to believe it.  My faith is not a blind faith.  I believe the Bible is true because there is evidence that supports it.  I believe in creation because the evidence simply does not support evolution.  I could haul out my notes from J.P. Moreland's apologetics class and go on about arguments for the existence of God and the historicity of the Gospels, but I won't.  Though I believe that Christianity is true and reasonable and rational, I'm sad that the church often lives up to the perception that Christians don't think.  The reactionary American Christian sub-culture fuels that perception, with Harry Potter book burnings and the like.  I think that alienates many who just might be open to faith if they were offered a reasonable defense for the faith.    So, I invite the skeptic to come and think in my church.  Examine the faith, and judge for yourself whether it is reasonable to believe.  1 Peter 3:15 – "sanctify Christ as Lord in your hearts, always being ready to make a defense to everyone who asks you to give an account for the hope that is in you." 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Something I discovered just now: when you kill a fruit fly in midair above your computer keyboard, and its dead carcass lands between the keys, don't despair.  If you are careful, you can extract it using the sticky side of a post-it note.    Don't laugh.  You might need that information someday. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   One of the editorial assistants here, Anne, works with an author whose last name is Damschroder.  I just can't resist using the author's last name as a curse word.   Damschroder!   Brings back fond memories of my days in the  urlLink Biola  Chamber Orchestra, when I would take my stand partner's name in vain.   Dan Bennett!   It also reminds me of one of the letters in the  urlLink Ted L. Nancy book , where he claims to have a form of  urlLink Tourette's  that causes him to bark out men's names.  I love creative exclamations like these.  I taught Jude "Oh, for the love of bald men" last summer.  I recently heard someone use "Oh, for the love of  urlLink Google " and found it also quite amusing.  Anyone have others they'd like to share?  C'mon, people, make me laugh and expand my vocabulary.    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today did not get off to a great start.  When getting out of my car at work, I managed to spill juice in my lap.  In a very bad place.  So I spent the first couple hours of the morning with my sweater tied around my waist and my jeans uncomfortably wet.  But things are looking up.  I got the phone calls I was dreading out of the way (almost) first thing, and I have only two items left on my list of things to do today.  Ok, so they're big things, but it still makes me feel good.  And, as the title says, I'm feeling reclusive.  I don't know if it's due to my overly social weekend or what, but I so want to just hide from the world today.  Instead, I'm going to be social tonight.   urlLink Drinks & dinner  to celebrate a friend's one year anniversary of her return from the  urlLink Peace Corps .  Tonight will be fun, but tomorrow night I'm gonna determinedly park myself on my couch with some books and maybe my DVD of   urlLink Harry Potter  and the  urlLink Chamber of Secrets  . 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Even though I'm really not fond of Blogger's new commenting feature (Why the heck must you log in to leave comments?), I'm going with this new template.  For now, anyway.  I finally got things kind of how I want them.  If only I could figure out how to still use HaloScan with this template instead of the Blogger comments.  Because of the new commenting feature, all previous comments are now sadly gone.  They still exist at HaloScan, I just can't get them to appear here.  Bleah.  Not that there were that many comments anyway, but still.  They made me feel at least mildly popular.    But look at the template!  It's new and shiny! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, so with the launch of a new look to  urlLink Blogger , I started looking around a bit.  I found they've got a ton of new, cool templates up.  But I can't get the one I like to display all my stuff like I want.  I can't get the comments up and working, and I can't get the currently reading where I want it.  Grr.  I WILL figure this out, dangit.  Tomorrow, perhaps, when I can stay late at work. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This weekend was the busiest one I've had since I was in SoCal for Easter.  Check this out:   Thursday:  Friends finale party with my small group  Friday:  coerced into going to a party by friend from small group  Saturday:  lunch & movie & ice cream with work friends; birthday dinner for Kelly from small group  Sunday:  fulfilled my introvert need of a low-key afternoon alone--reading, doing laundry, and running errands.  Oh, and calling my mom to say Happy Mother's Day.  =)  I feel so...social.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Check out  urlLink this article .  A music student at the University of Texas at Austin has been charged with killing a professor.  With a meat cleaver.  I heard about this from Anne this morning.  One of her current reviewers is a music prof at UTA, and he emailed to let her know he wouldn't be able to get his review in on time.  Because his colleague had been murdered.  Anne consulted me on how to respond to his email.  Because, really, what do you say?  "Of course I will extend your review deadline, and I'm sorry to hear that your disabled colleague was killed with a meat cleaver by a student." 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Which theologian would you be?        "God will not suffer man to have the knowledge of things to come; for if he had prescience  of his prosperity he would be careless; and understanding of his adversity he would be senseless."         You are Augustine!   You love to study tough issues and don't mind it if you lose sleep over them.  Everyone loves you and wants to talk to you and hear your views, you even get things like "nice debating  with you." Yep, you are super smart, even if you are still trying to figure it all out. You're also  very honest, something people admire, even when you do stupid things.        urlLink What theologian are you?   A creation of  urlLink Henderson    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So  urlLink Kim  sent me this email yesterday about  urlLink Friendster .  Some friends at work had been talking about it recently, and so I decided to check it out.  The concept is really cool--basically you register yourself and link yourself to all your friends and then you can meet their friends, and their friends' friends...and so on.  Cool people linking to cool people.  So now my latest time-waster at work is to log on and see if I can find people I know on Friendster.  According to Friendster, I only have 3 friends.  Sad.  Though I do have two friends pending.  And I must say, it was fun to get emails saying "Cheryl is now your friend!" and "Anne is now your friend!"  So, anybody else out there on Friendster, let me know!   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Came across  urlLink this article  yesterday--it's a preview of the book LIVING WITH A WRITER.  In this book, the families of authors (including William Golding's daughter and John Updike's son) share what it's like to--well--live with a writer.  Reading this reminded me of a passage I love from Calvin Trillin's  urlLink Family Man :   "I have a simple rule of thumb that I offer to my fellow scribblers.  I call it the Dostoyevsky test: If you have reason to believe that you're another Dostoyevsky, there is no reason to be concerned about the effect what you write might have on the life of some member of your family.  Your art is considerably more important than any such consideration.  Readers a century or two from now should not be deprived of the prose you fashion out of, say, the circumstances leading to your conclusion that your oldest son simply didn't have the guts to stick to junior-varsity football and thus set a pattern for a life of drifting.  You have the right--the responsibility, really, to future generations of readers--to mention your mother's private confession to you, in a moment of stress, that she never truly loved your father, even if putting that conversation in print causes some awkwardness in their life at the retirement village.  If you have reason to believe that you're another Dostoyevsky, you can say anything you need to say.  If you don't have reason to believe that you're another Dostoyevsky, you can't."  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "It really gets me when the critics say I haven't done enough for the economy. Look what I've done for the book publishing industry."  --President George W. Bush at the White House Correspondents' Association dinner 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The real title of the sixth Harry Potter has been released, and it's  not  HP & the Pillar of Storge.  And I'm glad.  From  urlLink Publisher's Lunch  again...   The rumor/hoax about the title of Harry Potter 6 took on a lot of momentum before being denied, and then the real title was indeed found on JK Rowling's web site. The book is called HARRY POTTER AND THE HALF BLOOD PRINCE. (The prince is neither Harry nor Voldemort.)  The CNN article is  urlLink here .  Rowling's response to the "leaked" title:  A "rumors" section of the site had included a post from fans Monday that the new title would be "Harry Potter and the Pillar of Storge" but Rowling dismissed that idea on the site, saying, "I am trying very hard not to be offended that anyone thought this was possible."   Another posting in the rumor section said that the title would be "Harry Potter and the Toenail of Icklibogg" to which Rowling responded, "Well, if you believed the Storge one..."   Heh.  Toenail of Icklibogg.  Thanks to  urlLink Kristy , who texted me to ask if I'd heard about the title...and prompted me to read today's Publisher's Lunch.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   From today's  urlLink Publisher's Lunch :   Harry Potter fan sites are vigorously debating whether a "hidden" posting on J.K. Rowling's site reveals the true name of book 6 or is just a red herring. The posting from the author, dated July 1, says, "The book is growing so fast, I could swear Filius has put an Engorgement Charm on it; an editor's nightmare! I promised myself not to exceed the length of Order of the Phoenix, but every day that passes makes that undertaking more difficult." It also proclaims, "The title of Book 6 is: Harry Potter and the Pillar of Storgé."   Read the article  urlLink here , and info on why the leaked title might be a hoax  urlLink here .  I hope it's a hoax.  "Harry Potter and the Pillar of Storgé" sounds kinda dumb to me. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   An email I just sent without carefully proofreading:   Hi Julie,  I'm filling out an ISBN request to ass the website for Environmental Ethics.  Do you have a pub date for this?   Thanks! -Barbara   Yes, folks--I said I'd like to ass the website.   Ass ?!?  I think I meant to type "assign."  Moments like these make me glad I have a sense of humor.  And glad that I was emailing someone on my team, and not an author or a reviewer. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "I also believed, with Aldous Huxley, that it takes just as much work to write a bad book as a good one, and that whoever made the effort deserved, at least, a kind word--even if the kindest words one could muster were 'please learn to spell, punctuate, construct a sentence, think coherently, find some other way of making a living.'"  --Rayanna Simons, "Slush," in  urlLink Editors on Editing    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here's a  urlLink particularly entertaining review  of Mitch Albom's  urlLink The Five People You Meet in Heaven : "...sportswriter-turned-pop-religionist Albom has one more cute little lesson for us unenlightened masses to gobble up and gag on."  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You who live in heaven Hear the prayers of those of us who live on earth  Who are afraid of being left by those we love  And who get hardened by the hurt   Do you remember when You lived down here where we all scrape  To find the faith to ask for daily bread  Did You forget about us after You had flown away  Well I memorized every word You said   Still I'm so scared I'm holding my breath  While You're up there just playing hard to get   You who live in radiance  Hear the prayers of those of us who live in skin  We have a love that's not as patient as Yours was  Still we do love now and then   Did You ever know loneliness  Did You ever know need  Do You remember just how long a night can get?  When You were barely holding on  And Your friends fall asleep  And don't see the blood that's running in Your sweat   Will those who mourn be left uncomforted  While You're up there just playing hard to get?   And I know you bore our sorrows  And I know you feel our pain  And I know it would not hurt any less  Even if it could be explained   And I know that I am only lashing out  At the One who loves me most  And after I have figured this somehow  All I really need to know   Is if You who live in eternity  Hear the prayers of those of us who live in time  We can't see what's ahead  And we can not get free of what we've left behind  I'm reeling from these voices that keep screaming in my ears  All the words of shame and doubt, blame and regret   I can't see how You're leading me unless You've led me here  Where I'm lost enough to let myself be led  And so You've been here all along I guess  It's just Your ways and You are just plain hard to get.  --Rich Mullins, "Hard to Get"  I first heard that song when I was in college and I loved how honest it was.  Often when I ran across a song that resonated with me like that, I would think about maybe singing it at church the next time I was signed up for a solo.  And I remember thinking that this particular song wasn't "appropriate" for church.  How sad that is--somewhere I unconsciously absorbed the idea that public worship had to have all the questions answered, all the doubts assuaged, and be tied up in a nice shiny happy package.  My public Sunday morning reality excluded doubt and sin and being less than a "perfect" Christian.     The pious fellowship permits no one to be a sinner.  So everybody must conceal his sin from himself and from the fellowship.  We dare not be sinners.  Many Christians are unthinkably horrified when a real sinner is suddenly discovered among the righteous.  So we remain alone with our sin, living in lies and hypocrisy.  The fact is that we are sinners. --Dietrich Bonhoeffer, Life Together   Oh, for an honest community of faith where we acknowledge that sin and pain and hurt are real, that people will disappoint us, and that sometimes we will even be disappointed in God.  Doubt does not mean denial, and questions are a part of faith. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Take a look at my new desktop  urlLink here .   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     You're a Speak & Spell!!  You nerd, you.  Just because you were disguised as a toy doesn't mean you weren't educational, you sneaky bastard.    urlLink   What childhood toy from the 80s are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I know very little about Kathryn Harrison, described in the  urlLink Seattle Post-Intelligencer  as "the leading literary self-exposer in this tell-all age."  I did, however find the following quote very amusing:  "The reader response with Harrison no longer is: We're With You Through Your Traumas. It's more: Get on With Your Life and Keep Something Secret for a Change." 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Anyone out there want a  urlLink Gmail  account?  I just got three more invitations.  Send bribes my way.  If anyone's even reading this... 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   That's pretty much what my weekend consisted of.    On Saturday, I went to a birthday party for a friend from work, where I spent most of the afternoon hanging out with a bunch of married couples.  I was literally the only single person in attendance for the first half of the party.  That was kind of interesting.  After the afternoon of snacking & playing games, we headed to Palo Alto for bowling...with the lights out and the disco ball and blacklights on.  Very fun.    I must say that I am proud of myself for going bowling and enjoying it.  Usually, I hate bowling because I really, really suck at it.  My scores were 44 and 67...look at how I improved!  I did not, however, win the prize for lowest score of the evening.  If there had been a prize for most entertaining bowling style, it would have certainly gone to Anne.  More fun to watch than words can describe.  =)  And as to the reading...  I finished reading  urlLink Confessions of an Ugly Stepsister , and I really enjoyed it. I was worried that it would be cartoonish, more of a spoof. It isn't. It's much more serious and really pretty good. There was a focus on art that I didn't expect, and I liked the way Maguire used the artist and the paintings in the tale to mirror the obvious themes of beauty and appearance.  The theme of art and the Dutch setting reminded me--oddly enough--of Vreeland's  urlLink Girl in Hyacinth Blue  and Chevalier's  urlLink Girl with a Pearl Earring .  I also started reading  urlLink Purple Hibiscus  and I'm loving it.  Powell's had a  urlLink review  of it a while back, and it caught my eye, so when I came across it at the library last week, I had to check it out.  On Saturday, there were times when the conversation lagged, and I found myself thinking longingly of  Purple Hibiscus  and wishing I could be reading it at that moment.  It's narrated by a young girl whose father is an obsessively strict Catholic.  He holds the family to impossibly high religious, academic, and personal standards.  The father refuses to associate with "heathens"--a category which includes his father.  The book reminds me a lot of Achebe's  urlLink Things Fall Apart --it echoes a lot of the same themes, exploring the conflict between Christianity and the Igbo culture and traditions--but it's told from the opposite perspective.  It's making me want to re-read  Things Fall Apart . Though I don't agree with some of the undertones that suggest all religions are equally valid, this is an excellent book and offers a lot of material worth exploring. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday marked the 10th anniversary of my high school graduation.    Not disturbing, but worthy of mention: yesterday was also my sister's 12th wedding anniversary.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We had a fire at work on Monday.  No, really.  The hillside next to my building caught fire.  The hillside that's literally right next to the corner of the building where my desk is located.  The power went out, the fire alarm went off, and we all got evacuated from the building and eventually sent home early.  We even made the  urlLink newspaper !  Well, sort of:   The South County Fire Authority and the California Department of Forestry on Monday battled a half-acre grass fire in the Belmont Hills, at Davis Drive above Water Dog Lake and behind Ralston Intermediate School.   South County Fire Battalion Chief Dan Belville said the fire started at about 1:52 p.m. when wind caused two electrical lines to touch, resulting in a spark that ignited the vegetation below.   About 1,600 PG&E customers lost power. One business was threatened, but saved by fire crews.   One business = my work.  We were threatened, but saved!  Woo!  Also of note: I'm moving.  Not far, and not till August, but I'll soon be packing up my belongings yet again.  I went to look at a house in Palo Alto on Sunday with Julie F. from my small group at church.  She's moving there in July, and they need one more person.  I decided Tuesday night that I was gonna go for it, and the girls let me know yesterday that they want me to move in.  I'm excited about the possibilities of what I can do with the $300/month I'll be saving on my rent!  Though I'm a bit reluctant to give up the independence of living alone, I think it'll be good for me.  And Julie and I have plans to decorate.  This is gonna be fun!  What's not going to be so fun: moving all my stuff just 4 days after I get back from Wales.  Heh. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I came across a link to  urlLink this article  in a recent  urlLink Publisher's Lunch  email.  The fifth author to be discussed is Jerry Jenkins, co-author of the Left Behind series.  There are so many comments to make about this excerpt that I'm not sure where to start.  But here we go:   Speaking at a seminar on Christian fiction, Jenkins struggled to explain the phenomenal success of the series.   Yeah, well, I struggle to understand the phenomenal success of the series.   "I like to think it's the great writing," he said, laughing.   I'm laughing, too.  But probably for different reasons.   "It continues to astound us. Because it's so many millions, we're way past the point where we feel like we should take any human credit for it. I mean, I don't want to sound too mystical, but we feel like God is in this, and it's a message that we feel like he wants out there."   Ok, back the truck up there.  Because the book has sold so many copies, God  must  approve of the message?  Wha--?  God's behind the success--and the message--of all best-sellers, eh?  That makes  perfect  sense.   The most challenging thing about writing Christian fiction, he said, is balancing the desire for realism against the expectations of religious readers.  "I don't use foul language myself, but I hear it, and I think I could reproduce it, and it might be realistic," Jenkins said. "But you weigh that against a hundred stores that say, 'We're not carrying that because it's got this word in it,' it's just not worth it."  Then there's the problem of keeping the standard of quality that readers of the series have come to expect.   I can't imagine that it's difficult to maintain the standard of quality that the series has demonstrated so far.  Mainly because "quality" is not the word that I would use in reference to the series.   "You try not to think about the fact that a certain number of millions of people are waiting for the book," he said. "The pressure is, I could write a mediocre book and my career could be over tomorrow. I could sell two or three million because people are waiting for it, and then they go, 'I thought this guy could write.'"  Or, you could write a mediocre book and sell tons of copies.  Like you've been doing for the  entire series so far .  Ok.  That's the end of my literary snobbishness for the day.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmmm.   Ms. Winfrey's selection of "Anna Karenina" was notable in several ways, not least because she has not read the book.  Read the article  urlLink here .  And then there's  urlLink this , from the Literary Saloon.  They quote a rather scary description of  Anna Karenina  from Oprah's site:   An extremely sexy and engrossing read, this book tells the tale of one of the most enthralling love affairs in the history of literature—it truly was the "Harlequin Romance" of its day.  Please excuse me while I go away and scream at the idea of comparing  Anna  to a Harlequin Romance. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Soon after I got to work this morning, our Editor in Chief came around all the EA's cubicles and let us know that there were free leftover bagels outside the Executive Board Room, if we wanted some.  Mmmmm, bagels.  Now that I've enjoyed a cranberry bagel with cream cheese, I'm settling into the morning with a nice cup of tea.  And...I will be seeing Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban at 6:30 tonight.  So, SO excited. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There's a great post at  urlLink Jeffrey Overstreet's blog  about  urlLink rating churches .  Go read it, then come back here.  Go on!  What's that? You're back?  Ok.  So that post was kind of a springboard for a lot of thoughts.  Having written what's below, I feel like there's so much more to say that I didn't even touch on--about the balance between reaching people and at the same time not losing track of the church's purpose of worshipping and serving God.  But anyway, that's a digression for a later date.  Here we go.  I wholeheartedly agreed with what Overstreet had to say.  But I found myself thinking, "But what about when you  have  to evaluate a church?" It really got me thinking about the process of finding a church.  Because when you're looking for a church, you have to evaluate; you have to come up with some sort of selection criteria--whether consciously or not.  Now, let me preface this by saying that I'm not the church-hopping type.  I've always been pretty committed to my home church.  If there was something I felt was lacking, I got involved and tried to make things better, rather than packing it in and moving on to another church.  I've gone to a total of four churches in my whole life.  Del Mar Baptist Church: the one I was born into.  Sedge Fen Baptist Church: my family changed churches because we moved from California to England.   urlLink Green Hills Baptist Church : we changed churches because we moved from England to California.  And now,  urlLink Peninsula Bible Church : because I moved to the Bay area.    Church-hunting didn't sit well with me when I first moved here.  For one, I didn't like going alone to new places where I knew no-one.  But the other thing that bugged me was that I was church-shopping and not really worshipping.  I would enter every worship service or Bible study with a critical eye; looking for what I did and didn't like: were the people friendly, did I like the style of worship, how good was the sermon, and so on.  I felt like an outsider on most of these church visits--in part, because I was new--but also because I felt like I was standing back to evaluate and, yes, to "rate."  I don't know if you can look for a church and escape this, but it bothered me.  Maybe it's my own personality--I often fight against being too critical.  But looking back, I wonder if one of the reasons I settled on PBC was that I was tired of being an outsider and a critic and I wanted to be a worshipper again.    I have loved the teaching at PBC.  Pretty much every pastor I've heard speak has been excellent--challenging me as they offer Biblical truth.   urlLink YAF  is a great group of people, and I appreciate that PBC has a ministry focused on people in my own demographic--something I felt I was really lacking at Green Hills.  At first I wasn't too enthralled with the worship at PBC, and that's actually one of the things that kept me visiting other churches when I first moved here.  But the teaching brought me back and the fellowship got me to stay.  When I moved here, I needed to find a church that was right for me--a church that fit my church background, my stage in life, the type of teaching I connect with, the style of worship that was comfortable for me.    Yes, the point of going to church should never be self-serving or me-oriented.  That's not what the church is about--it is about God and  His  pleasure--not our own comfort or preference.  But I can't help but think that some kind of honest evaluation of various churches is necessary--especially by those who are genuinely looking for a place to worship and learn and fellowship.    However, I agree with Overstreet--I should never evaluate a church based on the quality of its snacks.  Cute single Christian guys, perhaps...but snacks, no. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This morning, I got a call from our production manager, who was wondering where a certain preface was.  I hadn’t seen it, so I emailed the authors to see if they’d sent it to our assistant editor, who’s on vacation this week.    Thus ensued the following exchange, edited to protect the not-so-innocent:  From author to me:  Barbara, We didn't do a preface!  Simply forgot, I guess.   How's about I take a shot at it today and tomorrow - send you a draft asap, and we aim to have it done by Monday?  From me, to production manager, with a forward of the above email:  Well, whaddaya know?  They forgot.  From production manager to me:  Preface?  Oh, golly.  Well, maybe there should be a preface.  How about a preface?  Gee, OK.  Have I mentioned how much I love the people I work with? 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was initially very intrigued by the concept behind  urlLink this book : the idea that you could figure out people's problems by examining the song lyrics that run through their heads.  It ends up being more than just that idea--there's more of a story here than I expected.  And in the end, I really enjoyed the story Tucker built around the concept that drew me in.   The characters were well developed--especially the teenage narrator, Leeann, and her older sister Mary Beth (the "song reader").  The story of their family drew me in and kept me reading.  It did feel like a first novel in places--there were times I felt the imagery or situations were a little too obvious.  But overall, it was a quick, good read.  Kristy--I think you'd really like this one.  And a side note: I'm trying to be better about blogging on what I'm reading.  Maybe at some point I'll double back and write about  urlLink Girl in Hyacinth Blue .  I definitely recommend it. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe I'm blogging about Oprah's Book Club.  Apparently  Anna Karenina  is the  urlLink latest pick .  I must say I'm pleased to see she's selected the  urlLink Pevear/Volokhonsky translation .  When I studied Tolstoy at  urlLink Chapman , this was the translation we used.  My professor said it was the first time he'd taught  Anna Karenina --he'd been reluctant to do so because he hadn't found a decent translation until this one was released.  Of course, the skeptic in me wonders whether Oprah's Book Club selected this translation simply because it's the most recent.    Here's what makes me laugh, though.  The  urlLink cover  of the book--thanks to Oprah's nice thick self-promoting book club wrap--looks to me like it's been censored.  When I was reading this particular translation of  Anna  for my Tolstoy class (before Oprah slapped her logo on it), people were always commenting on the cover.  It's actually a woman's bare knees, but at first glance, it appears to be either breasts or buttocks.  This confusion in the image is no doubt intentional.  But the placement of this new purple wrap promoting the book club is just so handy.  Covers that flesh right up so no-one has to give it a second glance.  Way to go, Oprah's Book Club.  If you check out  urlLink Oprah's site , you can see the "uncensored" version of the cover image. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm fighting the urge to take a nap. It's Friday afternoon, and almost everyone else is on summer hours. I have a contract addendum to prepare, but the office is pretty much empty, and I just want to sleep. Instead, I offer you:    urlLink 20 questions to being a better person     Your score as a human being is  84.1 .    You are close to ideal. So close, and yet so far. Amusing, really, to watch someone squirm so close to the vaunted ranks of perfection and still remain so very, very ordinary. It is all one can do to keep one's ingratiating smile from polluting one's perfect face.    Actually, one recommends you take the quiz again and lie a little.   Because I'm such a good person, I'm going to go prepare that addendum now. Whee.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When I have  plenty  to do, but no desire to do it.&nbsp; And so, for your reading enjoyment, I offer you:    urlLink 20 Questions to a Better Personality     My results:    Wackiness: 52/100    Rationality: 72/100    Constructiveness: 50/100    Leadership: 22/100     &nbsp;   You are an  SRDF --Sober Rational Destructive Follower. This makes you a  font of knowledge . You are cool, analytical, intelligent and completely unfunny. Sometimes you slice through conversation with a cutting observation that causes silence and sidelong glances. You make a strong and lasting impression on everyone you meet, the quality of which depends more on  their  personality than yours.     &nbsp;   You may feel persecuted, as you can become a target for fun. Still, you are focused enough on your work and secure enough in your abilities not to worry overly.     &nbsp;   You are productive and invaluable to those you work for. You are loyal, steadfast, and conscientious. Your grooming is impeccable. You are in good shape.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   You are kind of a tool, but you get things done. You are probably a week away from snapping.       &nbsp;    Addendum, 2004/07/19 : this fits me 99%, there is a slight inaccuracy however. We are not necessarily completely unfunny. If we have a sense of humor (I do) it surfaces on the occasion with well-timed, completely dry, very sarcastic, wit. - Chase    I wholeheartedly concur with the addendum.&nbsp; I am  not  completely unfunny.&nbsp; I got complimented on my sense of humor just last week, thankyouverymuch.&nbsp; I'm definitely not in good shape, and I think I'm probably far less than a week away from snapping.&nbsp; =)   Another note: Since I'm right at 50/100 on the Constructive scale, the following is likely also accurate:    You are an  SRCF --Sober Rational Constructive Follower. This makes you a  White House staffer . You are a tremendous asset to any employer, cool under pressure, productive, and a great communicator. You feel the need to right wrongs, take up slack, mediate disputes and keep the peace. This comes from a secret fear that business can't go on without you--or worse, that it can. If you have a weakness, it is your inability to say "no." While your peers respect you, they find it difficult to resist taking advantage of your positive attitude and eagerness to take on work. You depend on a good manager to keep you from sinking under the weight and burning out.     

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    I know you all missed me terribly.   It was a great trip, and there's so much to tell.&nbsp; But I know I will be FAR too long-winded if I try to give an overview of everything.&nbsp; So, here are my favorite and most memorable parts of the trip:    Being greeted with "Welcome home!" by my host family    Staying up till 11:30pm the first night there, enjoying frozen Twix (or is it Twixes?)     Hot chocolate at   urlLink  Verdi's    and walking along the beach at the   urlLink  Mumbles        Worship—singing "Reign in Me Again" somehow never got old     Horseback riding along the beach (but not so much the sore bum afterwards)     Going to a chip shop in the largest caravan park in Europe at midnight    One of the kids in my class, Jack, who told me I was the best teacher he'd ever had     The kid in my class who guessed that San Diego was a country in Africa     Wandering through   urlLink  Hay-on-Wye    with my Welsh host family     Sunset at Rest Bay in spite of the freezing wind     Hanging out with Jude, my Welsh little sis     Finding out that I can fit under Jude's bed     Hanging out with Eric, the annoying little brother I never wanted (who doesn't label his CDs!!!)    Getting a whole lot of lovin' from Rachel    Butt jokes & cannibal jokes (you really had to be there)     Ok, now my list is just degenerating into inside jokes...   It was really sad to say goodbye to everyone--to my Welsh friends at the coach station in Cardiff, to the mission team at the hotel in London, and then to Heather at Heathrow.&nbsp; It was weird to travel home alone!   I came back to find a ton of changes at work--two co-workers have gotten promotions, and another quit while I was gone.&nbsp; Changes at home, too--I'm moving to Palo Alto on Saturday, and I am now immersed in the craziness of final packing and cleaning.&nbsp; I can't wait to be done with the move so I can unpack and know where everything is again.   And I'm still thinking longingly of Wales and wishing I was there instead of sitting here at my desk catching up on the last two weeks of work.&nbsp; Sigh.  One of the songs we did with the kids at the Holiday Bible Club keeps coming back to me, and it really sums up my feelings about the trip.&nbsp;   Come and see what God has done, All the wonders under the sun Come and see what God can do, He’s alive in me and you  This trip was a time of stretching for me in many ways--I was doing more leading than I had done in the past.&nbsp; When I'm leading, I so often get caught up in the details of getting everything to work just right.&nbsp; But God is good at sending me reminders--and it's&nbsp;amazing to see what God&nbsp;can do&nbsp;when I take the time to pay attention.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, I will be in an hour anyway.&nbsp; I'm leaving work at 4:30 to head to the airport, and then I'm off to Wales!&nbsp; I'll be reachable by  urlLink email  if anybody wants to harass me while I'm gone.&nbsp; Don't know if I'll have a chance to blog, but I will email some updates as I get a chance. &nbsp;  Following are some thoughts I pulled together for an email that most of you probably already received.&nbsp; Figured I'd post them here anyway--seems a good way to leave off here before I go.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  He made from one man every nation of mankind to live on all the face of the earth, having determined their appointed times and the boundaries of their habitation, that they would seek God, if perhaps they might grope for Him and find Him, though He is not far from each one of us.  -Acts 17:26-27   &nbsp;  God has brought these verses to my attention many times over the past few years, and this passage is especially meaningful when I consider missions. &nbsp;It is amazing to me to consider that God has determined the time and place where each one of us will live. &nbsp;God places people where he does, when he does, for a reason—and that reason is so that people will seek Him.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;  I leave today for a mission trip to work with children and youth in Porthcawl, Wales.&nbsp;&nbsp;I know that God has a purpose for the young people we will meet on this trip. &nbsp;These kids come from largely unchurched homes, and live in a community that for the most part sees Christianity as irrelevant. &nbsp;And yet, God has placed them where they are for a reason, and God will orchestrate events so that He will be found by all who seek Him. &nbsp;I am excited for this trip and all that God will do through this time of ministry. &nbsp;I know God has a purpose for our team and our time in Porthcawl and I look forward to seeing all that He has in store!  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      My life is rated PG.  What is your life rated?   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I leave for Wales in just over 3 days.  Can't wait.    I'm SO not getting any work done.  At least nobody's playing the email game with me this week.  (Ahem--Julie Farmer!!) 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Note: when playing mini golf with friends, and it is sunny out, it is not such a good idea to wear your long hair in two braids.  Cute, but not a good idea.  Ouch.  My neck, it is purple. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Over the weekend, I read  urlLink Sixpence House  by Paul Collins.  It's sort of a memoir-ish account of Collins' move from San Francisco, California to Hay-on-Wye, the famous "Town of Books" in Wales.  I visited Hay-on-Wye in 2000, and found the place delightful.  I have fond memories of browsing for books in the shadow of Hay Castle.    The book was great fun.  Collins incorporates references to obscure books throughout his narrative, as well as observations on life in Britain.  A favorite passage involves a meditation on water pressure in British showers.  It will be quoted as soon as I can locate the book...currently it is somewhere in my future home in Palo Alto, packed in one of a myriad of book-filled boxes.  But for the time being, here is another of my favorite passages, helpfully quoted by one of the reviewers on Amazon.com.   If a book cover has raised lettering, metallic lettering, or raised metallic lettering, then it is telling the reader: 'Hello. I am an easy-to-read work on espionage, romance, a celebrity, and/or murder.' To readers who do not care for such things, this lettering tells them: 'Hello. I am crap.'  You may be interested to note that Sixpence House has no raised lettering, metallic lettering, or raised metallic lettering on its cover. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Could you pass the  urlLink U.S. Citizenship Test ?  I got 10 out of 11.  Pesky amendments to the Constitution.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I remember seeing  urlLink The Patriot  in theaters when it first came out, and I was really annoyed at the way it irresponsibly demonized the British.  I still am annoyed by its portrayal of British soldiers locking an entire village of "traitors" in a church and then burning the church down.  It sounds vaguely historically familiar because it did happen.  Except it was WWII, with Nazis locking Jews in a synagogue.  Historical revisionism, anyone?  The Patriot was an exciting, entertaining movie, but I still walked away from it with an overall feeling of how pointless war is.  And of how movie-makers will wildly elaborate on the truth just to give you a good show.  I watched it again on TV this weekend, and this time, there were other things that bothered me.  I came away from it with what felt like a very un-patriotic reaction--especially on the Independence Day weekend.  The Mel Gibson character is portrayed as a man of faith.  He is shown praying at quite a few points during the movie.  He initially objects to the war, advocating peaceful methods of resolving the issues.  But then his family is attacked, and he is drawn into the conflict--because it becomes personal.  It becomes vengeance; he goes after the evil Brits who threaten his family.  I am always uneasy at the mixture of faith and patriotism.  It gets too easily muddled.  Yes, our country has a wonderful heritage of faith, but being American does not equal being Christian.  I can't stand it when people apply scripture to America that refers to Israel.  America is not the new Israel, and Americans are not God's chosen people.  But that's another rant for another day.  The elements of faith in the movie got me thinking about a discussion we had in Bible study at Green Hills about Romans 13, and how Christians should respond to the government and its leaders.   In the historical context of Romans 13, Nero was the head of state.  It's kinda hard to find a more anti-Christian leader than Nero.  Yet Christians were asked to pray for and show respect to their leaders--even when that leader was someone like Nero.  We are called to do the same.  Whether the leader is Nero, King George, or George W. Bush, Romans 13 advocates submission and obedience to the state.  Yes, yes, I know--duty to God always has priority over duty to the state.  And submission and obedience do not mean blindly accepting everything you're told with no critical thought.  But neither do they mean supporting the overthrow of governmental control because of "taxation without representation."  If Paul asks the Romans to demonstrate submission and obedience to  Nero , then how in the world is the Revolutionary War justified from a Christian perspective?  So in looking at the Revolutionary War, I can't help but think that anyone who champions it from a Christian perspective is sadly wrong-headed.  I just can't reconcile it with Romans 13 and the attitude Christians are called to have toward the government.  I guess it really doesn't matter that much, since the Revolutionary War is over and done with.  I'm not advocating a return to the British Empire.  And I'm still processing these thoughts.  But it's unsettling (and kind of amusing) to me that this is what was kicking around in my head over the Fourth of July weekend. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have bruises right above both of my hip bones.  It's weird--I really don't know how I got bruised there.  Unless it's because of all those boxes of books I moved yesterday.  Oh, yeah, that might be it.   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I guess I haven't been blogging much lately.  Last week was Harry Potter and nothing else.  So, here you go:  Last weekend (as in June 25-27), I went home to visit family.  I wanted to see my nieces and Johnny before I go off to Wales.  Johnny's so big now!  That's what happens with babies over the course of three months, but still!    I also got to spend a little time with Heather (we ditched Sunday School together), and it was fun to say goodbye to her (and other Wales team people) by saying "I'll see you in Wales!"   urlLink Breakfast  with Kristy in Uptown Whittier was great, too.  This past weekend: we got a half-day on Friday, so I caught a matinee of  urlLink Spider-man 2 .  It was SO much fun.  Saturday, I alternated between packing, reading, and watching the audio commentaries on my Season 2  urlLink Alias  DVDs.  Then Saturday night, I ended up watching  urlLink The Patriot  on TV, thinking it would be a fun Independence Day thing to do.  More thoughts on that later, but let's just say that I'm probably not the poster child for patriotism this particular Fourth of July.  On Sunday, I helped out in the Sunday School class I'll be teaching for the summer--3rd through 5th graders.  Since it was a holiday weekend, there were only 6 kids, but it was a good group and hopefully things will go well next week.  They're using  urlLink Gospel Light's VBS  material as the first half of the summer curriculum—and that's exactly what we're using for the Holiday Bible Club in Wales in a couple weeks.  So I am already quite familiar with next week's Sunday School lesson!  Handy.  Sunday evening, I went to the  urlLink YAF  barbecue, which was good.  After things wrapped up there, some of us headed out to find a spot to watch the fireworks at Shoreline.  We ended up watching from a freeway overpass, which was interesting, but fun nonetheless.    Then yesterday I moved a carload of books over to the house in Palo Alto, and stood around in what will be my room, figuring out what will go where.  I also went to see  urlLink The Terminal  with Julie F, and it was pretty good.  Tom Hanks is great.  And now the weekend is over, and it's back to work! 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Theory trading cards!     Handy and fun information on prominent thinkers and concepts, presented on pocket-sized collectible cards for your trading enjoyment.  Download and print the  urlLink online set , or buy the higher-quality  urlLink published set  for the low, low price of $12.95.   You can put them in your pocket, and refer to them secretly during seminars or pretentious dinners. You can play them as a card game, or just admire them as art.    My personal favorite:    Jacques Lacan  Strengths: Highly influential among many theoretical schools Weaknesses: Often unintelligible, bordering on nonsense Special skills: Requires subtitling in his native language   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If you're interested in seeing some pictures from my trip to Wales,  urlLink Heather  has some posted  urlLink here  on her  urlLink Wales update site .  Or, get together with me in person and I'll be happy to share more.  =)  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     You speak eloquently and have seemingly read every book ever published. You are a fountain of endless (sometimes useless) knowledge, and never fail to impress at a party.  What people love:  You can answer almost any question people ask, and have thus been nicknamed Jeeves.  What people hate:  You constantly correct their grammar and insult their paperbacks.   urlLink  What Kind of Elitist Are You?     
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am blatantly plagiarizing this list from a co-worker who shall remain nameless. She's actually received all of these excuses from textbook reviewers during her time as an Editorial Assistant. Enjoy. You couldn't make these things up if you tried.  10. Unfortunately, I got a horrendous flu-like cold while at a conference, and this knocked me down for about five days.  9. After reading the "profiler" attachment necessary, I have decided not to do the review. I don't feel comfortable giving out all of that personal information.  8. Every single time I had a block of time to do this the last couple of weeks, the computer thwarted my attempts.  7. In my head, I had thought that it was due by May 15th, but Saturday would be an odd day for a deadline.  6. An hour and a half at the dentist slowed me down this morning.  5. Best-laid plans o' mice and men gang aft a-gley, I'm afraid. I'll send it either tonight or tomorrow morning. Company's coming over. Sorry!  4. Between classes, my car has broken down and is in the shop and the tax return deadline, I may need an extension of a couple of days.  3. My air conditioner went out at my house and I have spent the day having it looked at, which has delayed the completion of the review.  2. Last week and this weekend brought unforeseen fires to put out in my life as a composer. I did not want to rush a review of your work, so I did not finish.  And everyone’s favorite...  1. I am afraid that I will not be able to meet today's deadline for review of the text. We have recently had a faculty member murdered by a student which has slowed things down here a bit. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The move is complete! Things actually went very smoothly this weekend...huge thanks to my moving help: Karen helped me move boxes on Friday, then Josh, Kelly, and Anne helped me move furniture on Saturday. And I wouldn't have been able to assemble my bed without the help of Anne and the handy socket wrench from Target.  Though the move may be complete, the unpacking most definitely is not. My room (and the rest of the house, sadly!) is strewn with various boxes, bags, and what I affectionately call "random crap" that all needs to find a place for itself. This is gonna take a while. Somehow I never feel at home until my books are settled, and it's gonna be at least a couple of days before I can put all my books where they belong. Sigh.  

						
</post>


</Blog>