<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow!  Its like all of a sudden I feel sad.  I don't know what it is.  Maybe because I've had this happy high for about a month.  Or maybe because I feel like I'm growing apart from a certain person.  I see him everyday when I walk to Biology.  He's always talking to this one girl.  And sometimes I think if only we were in the same grade.  But then I run into Jacob and Jake and they're both sophmores and have always taken time to say hi or comment on my hair.  I dunno Jake told me my hair looked nice once.  But why the fuck cant he ever say something nice during school.  On the weekends and on trips I think could you flirt anymore,  but then like a meathead he can't talk to me in front of other girls in his class.  It sucks.  But I did tick him off the other day.  I was walking to class and I saw Matt Grimes and he was walking in front of Matt and I said hey to Matt and I talked to him a bit, because he never talks to anyone.  Plus I think it gave him an ego boost because he despises him.  But I blew him off like he blows me off.  That showed him.  And Matt would never act in a weird way if I said hello.  No telling what the other person would do.  He does come and talk to me in the hall though sometimes.  Michael is becoming a closer friend.  I can tell because he will smile at me in the halls.  He never used to do that.  Huh.  Well I feel a little better.  Maybe things will look up at Gatlinburg.  Three days of competeing, fun, flirting, and him.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Day.  I was told I had it goin on.  But by someone who couldn't flirt to save their life.  And I saw Jake.  FINALLY!  I haven't seen him in a week.  But all is well.  I had another happy day.  Til Tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would just like to say all of this is bullshit.  We should argue about all the petty things we may say about each other and we should not make statements that may be taken the wrong way.  We should try to make it so that what we say doesn't offend everyone we know.  This is a place to express our feelings, but if it is any need of concern we should be able to talk to each other.  And I know I'm one to talk because you guys have been friends for as long as you can remember and I'm just the fifth wheel, but I'd really hate to see you four stop getting along over something that was written.  Anyway I won't stop writing my blog.  This has helped me though all my family, love, school, and friendship struggles.  Even though it seems as though I say nothing it has helped me to open up to people or a person at school.  Liz knows what I mean.  I plan to continue to write.  Well we got out of school early today.  Yeah!  Snow!  And I don't have to go to practice.  But now I don't know what to do for the rest of the day.  Oh well I'll find something.  Until later, BYE!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would first like to say that writing in this blog has helped me immensely.  I had so many emotions bottled up inside.  I was always happy in front of my friends and never showed any sign of how I actually feeled.  But writing has helped me to feel the way I was acting.  And for Liz and Jenessa, I didn't do this because I thought it was cool.  Or because I wanted to take something for you.  It's because I'm not good at keeping a diary and I really needed a place to put my emotions.  I had no one to talk about my feelings with.  No one knew.  At least you guys had each other.  I still have no one.  But this is just an aid for me.  Anyway lets just say someone said something mean and it got me really mad and I wanted to cry my eyes out because for about two hours I couldn't help but thinking he hated me.  But anyway,  I have this huge tournament in Gatlinburg coming up.  It's three days long.  Now I was chatting with Lindsay George and Sara Fon last night and we're the only ones that know, but it is know among upper classmen that Gatlinburg is known for the initiation of freshmen girls.  But we thought it would be funny if we pulled a prank on Jake and Ferrell cause Michael won't be there.  I have it all planned out.  MATERIALS NEEDED  tampons  condoms (lubricated) thongs  bras camera   STEP 1  Practical Jokes like: 1) sticking tampons on their door  2) putting bras and thongs in their luggage or "carry-on" 3) condoms everywhere they look   STEP 2  MESS WITH THEIR HEADS 1) flirt with them 2) make good eye contact 3) act hard to get   STEP 3  THE MESSAGE Send a message to their room that reads something like two young women would like to meet you somewhere but only if they bring a thong and a bra.   STEP 4  THE FINALE When they show up Sara and Lindsay will come out and greet them and ask them what they're doing out.  Or they will be the two waiting for them.  When they have the thong and bra.  I'll be hiding and take a picture.  Or maybe in the note say that they can come only if they wear the bra and thong outside their clothes and then I take a pic and show everyone what idiots boys can be.  Anyway it'll be fun and Lindsay knows who I like and I can't tell Rachel because she hates him to death.    Ta Ta For Now       
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recieved this e-mail from Matt Grimes today and almost wet my pants with laughter: From:  To:  Subject: Ferrell: The Lying Menstrual Cycle Man/Boy- Trophies, Knives, and Feeding Us "Crud" Date: Tue, 20 Jan 2004 19:27:42 -0600   PLEASE BEAR WITH ME- I CUT AND PASTED THE PREVIOUS EMAIL AND SENT THIS ONE TO YOU. I MADE MINOR CHANGES, BUT DON"T BE SURPRISED TO BE READING ABOUT YOURSELF IN THIRD PERSON.   MATT   Yes, Ferrell was at it again. Surprise, surprise.   Let's recap- there are two aggravatingly annoying people on the Forensics team- one is a guy name Michael Honig who is the horniest freshman you will ever meet in desperate need of some Ritalin. Then there is Ferrell Armstrong, a gangly, lying excuse of a sophomore who grates SO MUCH on my everlasting nerve that he is likely to pop one of my capillaries with his illogical, perverted brain (however little that brain may be) or send me into a yawn-inducing coma with all of his cock-and-bull stories about how he is "such a chick magnet. I can land any girl I want."   I'm sorry, but I could land thirty women before even one would be wooed by his elementary charms.   Now, I'm sure you knew everything that I listed above, but I thought I'd remind you anyway.   It was a consensus at our dinner table at Ruby Tuesdays that we needed to teach Ferrell a lesson. You see, it all started when Mr. Armstrong received third place in extemporaneous speaking. You know Ferrell well enough to know that he was full of himself, but imagine his overblown ego when he realized that he had beaten Jake Poteet AND when he touted his plastic trophy at the restaurant, plopping it dead center in the middle of his booth, blocking any views he had of any of the people in front of him. But why should that matter? The only people he'll have a conversation with will be himself and that stupid trophy ("So, how beautiful am I today, Mr. 3rd Place Trophy Winner? Dashing, if I don't say so myself.")!!! Oh, he'll be unbearable for weeks, I thought.   Then he decides to give Honig some encourage insight(never a good thing) about the ups and downs of life in Forensics. But what he said to Honig I shall never believe. You see, I have diagnosed Ferrell with CLS, otherwise known as Chronic Liar Syndrome. After Honig complained of not doing very well, Ferrell responded:   "Don't worry, Honig. It's not about winning all the time. It's about the experience."   Bullshit, Ferrell. Normally I don't curse, but Mr. Armstrong evokes passions within me that I would like to suppress. Jacob Hamburger (who, by the way, won fifth place in Duo) explained to me that he likes Ferrell occasionally, whenever he ISN'T lying. I compared Ferrell to a feminine cycle- whenever women experience their period once a month, their estrogen levels soar and make those female individuals unbearable for one whole day. Likewise, Ferrell lies for thirty consecutive days, has a day where he doesn't, and then lies again after the brief period of time subsides.   Make sense? Okay, keep up with me now.   Okay, so our table, which consisted of Amy Thomas, Paul Higgins, Lindsay George, Rachel Romeo, Mrs. Eckstein, and myself, concocted an ingenious plan after a rather unfortunate prank. During the course of the evening, Ferrell convinced sweet, innocent Josh of the Overton team to go over to Rachel Romeo while holding his fork and Ferrell holding his knife. Now, you are aware of Rachel's phobia of knives, strangely titled aichmophobia (go to http://www.hypnotictapes.com/premade/pg-fearsandphobias.shtml and find a hypnotic tape that will help to cure your fear!), and the two of them spooked the heck out of poor Rachel. Josh had no clue what was going on, but Ferrell instigated it all and chuckled deeply. MWA-HA-HA went his chuckle. GWAGWAGGWA!!! went Michael's cackle, his large, gaping mouth held agape by his un-hingable jaws of death and destruction. It was then that we came up with the Ferrell Plan.   There really was no basis to the Ferrell Plan at first. Jacob, Rachel, Lindsay, and (I think) Paul had decided that Ferrell deserved to be punished and wanted Mrs. Eckstein to distract Ferrell or at least create a distraction so that they could pull some sort of prank. This is when the gears in my head began spinning crazily, and I suggested that we steal Ferrell's most prized possession of the evening- his dinky, breakable 3rd place trophy sitting center stage at his booth. Rachel and Lindsay agreed to hide it in the women's restroom, and Mrs. Eckstein called over one of our regular servers to call Honig and Ferrell up to the front, saying that there was a phone call for the two of them.   The waiter went one step further, obviously reading Honig like a book- he told the two of them that there were two pretty women up front looking for them. As soon as they left their booth, Rachel Romeo bolted with the trophy, and she and Lindsay George intermittently checked on it in the women's bathroom. Ferrell didn't even realize it was missing until fifteen minutes later, and BOY, was he fuming!   We finally gave him his trophy back, but I was pleased even more at what else we gave him... a run for his money. He has now caught on that we are not his most ardent fans, and he will have to cut back on all the BS he feeds us. Either that, or find a place that sells medication for his CLS and Michael's "Viagra Reducer."   Funny, funny day. I must say, the freshmen girls are giving Sarah Wellbourn and Elisa Lutz a run for their money. Rachel Romeo, Lindsay George, Caitlin Eckstein, Rebecca Bennie, Divya Narala, and Ashley DiGiorgi are all pretty cool, if I don't say so myself. I also found myself warming up to Becca Weller's sometimes sardonic humor, Amy Thomas's easygoing attitude, and Lindsey Reid's pleasantness. And, when Mrs. Eckstein asked if I would rather room with Honig or Ferrell, I found myself saying Honig. I'd rather room with a psycho who will listen and tell the truth than a vain, shallow guy who won't tell me that an apple is red if he can lie instead.   I detest liars. Ferrell needs a dose of the movie "Liar, Liar" and not be able to tell a lie for one whole day. But, then again, I guess that is why he is Ferrell: The Lying Menstrual Cycle Man (if you can call him a man...he really fits the profile of Britney Spears's "I'm not a girl, not yet a woman...")   Matt  Now you have to understand he detests Ferrell.  But my mother thinks he's jealous because I enjoy the company of both of them. Anyway another good day.  I spoke with Ferrell about Ted Turner and Goodpasture and Gatlinburg.  Said hello and talked with Jacob and Jake and Michael line danced in English today.  Funny Shit. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week is off to a good start.  A few set backs but great so far.  To start we did not have school on Monday and it snowed.  Yeah!  We went back to school Tuesday and I had fun presenting my Geography project to the class.  Imagine last year I was completely stagefright.  In second period we had a review game in Wellness, it was girls against guys.  There were seven girls left and one guy left and coach Waggoner asked the girls a question and they got it wrong and Kevin got it wrong now if the next girl go it right Kevin was out and the the girls got three extra points on their test.  But if she got it wrong Kevin was still in.  Now someone asked whose next and I timidly raised my hand.  And you hear guys say oh god she knows it.  And girls say yes.  I was like you don't know if I know it.  Then Coach Waggoner says now be quiet she knows it.  And then I answered and he said correct.  And because of me all the girls in our class got three points added to their test.  Later that afternoon we had practice and a meeting.  Now for the National Qualifying Events Competition our team was allotted two Public Forum Teams that did not count against our total allotment of entries.  Ms. Then comes into practice and said I want Lindsay and Sara on a team and on the other team I want Michael and Caitlin.  I'm thinking oh shit.  What the fuck am I going to do.  It will be really fun, but two whole days of Michael.  Nonstop Michael.  OH MY GOD!  But then I figured we'd make a good team.  I'm prepared he's not.  He has tons of knowledge.  I don't.  We're going to kick butt.  Whoo!   Ta Ta For Now
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll try to sum up everything that happened.  It started on Friday and Lindsay, Michael, Ferrell and I were in the car together.  That ride was pretty tame, considering who was in the car.  The competition was fun, I won two and lost one.  And everyone drank my lemon juice.  When we left I tripped when coming out the door and Ferrell kept imitating me and making fun of me.  Then on the ride home Ferrell asked if we could go to McDonald's so we did.  But before we got our food, Michael took my lemon juice and ran with it.  Then he threw it at a tree.  It was dented on the bottom and balanced on its side.  Then he took it and ran with it again this time he threw it over the fence.  Ferrell had to go to the bathroom then so he pissed outside of McDonald's.  We went inside to eat and then these two white gangsters came in and we thought they were going to rob the place.  We were like oh shit so we left.  Now we had to go to Kroger.  Why you ask?  Duh!  Michael threw my lemon juice over the fence.  So we get in there and Michael leans on me.  I tell him not to touch me so he rubs my back.  Then Ferrell tells him that he will give Michael ten bucks if he feels me up.  We bought the lemon juice and left.  We then went back to the school.  Ferrell left his large coke on the back of my car.  So I put it on his.  He threw it on the ground.  I picked it up and threw it at him from maybe a few yards away and hit him.  He picked it up and started chasing me.  I was in a skirt and heels and he could not catch up with me.  I slowed down though cuz it was killing my feet especially after chasing Michael in the McDonald's parking lot.  He was then about a foot away and he threw it and missed me by a mile.  I picked it up and threw it at Michael and hit him.  Then my mom drove Lindsay home and I got home.  Then Saturday came and Saturday was better than Friday.  We left Saturday morning and I talked to Matt and Lindsay on the bus.  When we got there Ferrell told me to watch my step because I tripped the night before.  We got in and Matt, Jacob, Lindsay, Paul, and I played poker.  Then we went to our rounds.  I didn't really see anyone until after third round.  So I got in their and Ferrell, Jake, and our HI people were in finals.  Then when they got out we had to wait about 2 hours in the cafeteria for awards to start.  Ferrell and Jake broke the 3nd place sweepstakes trophy but it was funny watching them try to put it back together.  Ferrell and I broght down the rest of the trophies and he put his arm around me and made a joke about something that had to do with masturbating and his left hand being stronger than his right with his left arm around me.  I backed off and yelled at him.  Then Jake came over and said that Ferrell was turning me into a guy.  Then Ferrell said so she's a guy but she likes guys but she's still a girl so it is okay.  And then Jake said so she's a gay faget.  Then I went to talk to Wes and Paul and Jacob.  Becca Weller and I were curious about what the big deal with breasts were.  Long Discussion.  And Becca suggested that Michael and I do a Duo next year about a saleslady who goes to this guys door and wont go away.  After he repeatedly trys to tell her to leave.  In the end she shoots him in the leg.  I thought it was appropriate.  Then when I spoke with Jacob, Jake, Ferrell, Michael and Paul.  Ferrell said that he bet Michael 500 dollars if he would have sex with me.  I pulled him aside and told him that sometimes he thinks his jokes are funny but this time he went over the line.  He was sorry and told me it wouldnt happen again.  And that he would think before he would say anything.  We then had to go back to school.  Ferrell, Lindsay, Jacob, Paul, Michael, and I al sang songs on the way home.  Ferrell said I love you Caitlin will you marry me and i said go to hell.  Then Jacob said he loved me.  It was so corny but it really felt great to be the center of attention.  When we got to Ruby Tuesday Ferrell, Michael, Jake, and this kid from BA walked over to Starbucks with me.  They got ice frappachinos (SP?).  And Jake asked me how much I weighed and then he and Michael called me bulimic.  The nerve.  And then they pretended to vomit in the bushes.  We were then seated at Ruby Tuesday and I sat next to Jake and across from Ferrell and diagonally from Michael and we sat in a booth.  We all got burgers but ever since I had a colossal burger it makes me nauseas and I cant eat their burgers.  We had fun at dinner but Michael offended the waitress and he put his mouth all the way around his cup.  Rob came later and got the four of us two tallcakes  he shared with Michael.  Ferrell, Jake and I had the other.  Ferrell let me have the rest when their was one bite left.  Jake turned to me and asked if he had anything on his tie or shirt.  He had chocolate on his shirt but he couldn't see it cuz it was by his neck so I had to wipe it off.  The others though had the waiter call Michael and Ferrell to the front desk because 2 girls were there for them.  When they left Rachel took his trophy and put it in the girls restroom.  He realized it was missing fifteen minutes later.  I told him I saw it at the front desk cuz they moved it and he covered for me cuz he was mad about them stealing it and gave me a hug.  I made alot of new friends this weekend and Rob told me he was proud of the work I was doing and Ferrell said he was too but that was only because I was prepared ahead of time and able to help him with his case.  wow my fingers hurt.  gotta go see everyone Tuesday.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I FOUND OUT HIS FAVORITE BAND.  ITS RED HOT CHILI PEPPERS.  IT WAS HIS BUDDY ICON.  MINE IS COOL.  YOU SHOULD CHECK IT OUT.  MY SCREENAME IS TROCHJR218.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh Shit!  In English today Ms. Medlin told me that for Goodpasture the bus was canceled and now my mom has to drive Michael, Lindsay, Ferrell and me to Goodpasture.  YES, IN THE SAME CAR!  It will be an incredibly interesting ride.  My mom is pissed though b/c she has difficulty driving in the dark.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a flex day.  I went out to eat and well that made the day special.  Oh Ferrell ticked me off today.  I went up to him in the hall after school to tell him that Ms. Medlin said that we had to be at the school at 6:30 on Saturday instead of seven, and do you know what he said?  Bullshit.  My god of all the nerve.  Well he isn't getting any of my lemon juice this weekend.  That is if he shows up on time.  Anyway I saw him today.  Wow he got a new jacket and it makes him look slimming.  Very nice.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I ran into Jake and told him I finished my aff.  He was happy for me.  Later he came up to me and was again excited (as always).  At the forensic meeting this afternoon, I got my gold sticker for degree of honor there were 8 of us so we posed the Can-Can.  Then at practice rob had me read the first paragraph of my neg to check speaking skills.  He told Chris he was boring and then people critiqued me.  Lindsay, Sara, becca, and Chris liked my SKILLS, but autumn said I was too forceful and flowery.  Then rob said and this is a direct quote, "that some judges might not like it and, as they did to autumn once, write 'Caitlin you're being a bitch'."  But then rob said when I was a debater I was known for my speaking skills and I spoke like you and when you spoke it was pleasant and I wanted to listen.  I felt special.  Then he had Michael try.  And as you all may know you cant look at Michael without laughing.  So he can't even speak because everyone even rob just cracked up when Michael started to speak.  Oh god.  This was a good day and also they have Ted turner at Gatlinburg so Sara and Lindsay might do that and that opens up some spots in LD so I probably will get to triple.  YEAH! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another great day.  I would like to say though that I did not appreciate my friends at lunch making fun of my stupidity.  And also sanitary napkin is called that b/c apparently it is made of some of the same fibers that dinner napkins are made of.  INTERESTING!  I finished my aff.  WHOOPEE!  I am done.  Jake bugged me today, but he's not as irritating as he used to be.  He cracks me up.  I had a salad for dinner and rode our exercise bike for 30 minutes, I'm really fulfilling my new year's resolution.  YEAH for me! Buh Bye
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I talked to him today on the phone.  We are going to meet in the library tomorrow morning.  I cannot wait.  He read my neg case and loved it.  Especially my evidence on Yugoslavia's 8 year international isolation..  I did a lot today.  I went furniture, treadmill, and foosball table shopping.  Boy this has been a terrific end to a spectacular week.  And watch next week will probably suck.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omg you would not believe who just imed me, "george".  im so happy we have been talking alot latly.  just now out of school.  got to get back to working on hw 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woo!  i had a stupendus day.  rob emailed me and said my case was excellent and maybe even varsity quality.  Yah.  i went to the mall to pick up a skirt and i looked at those new foam pillows but they were forty bucks but then later i went back and my mom lied and said she spent like 600 dollars there for christmas but she only spent one hundred and they knocked 15 bucks off the price.  this has been another happy day.  oh he who shall remained unamed lets call him george emailed me today.  he wanted me to help him with something but i can't say cuz it would give him away.  ta ta for now
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a great day.  I had forensic practice and my coach loved my selecton for prose. Yeah!  And also he who shall remain unamed stop me today to tell me somthing that happened to him.  It was really funny.  This has been a great week.  I got back from babysitting tonight.  It was my first time with these kids.  They were probably my best so far.  Extremely obedient.  Never had to ask them twice.  And I got forty dollars.  This week should be called SPECIAL CAITLIN WEEK.  WEE
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hurt my friends feelings today and feel terrible.  The worst part was I hadn't even realized it until i read their blog.  But for them, I know exactly what you're going through with him.  I feel the same way for someone too.  But his name shall never be disclosed.  It's a wonderful feeling though, when I see him in the hallway.  He even smiles at me and a few times caught up and talked with me.  The problem is I sometimes feel like he treats me like a sister.  And thats okay sometimes, but when you just want more it starts to kill you inside.  I struggle with myself though because I don't want to say that I'm in love with him.  What do I know about love?  But I really think I'm almost there.  We talk all the time and all though we may not be close now I must say I think that day will come.  And other times I think what the fuck am I doing wrong, but I suppose for now I will just live everyday as it comes.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so sorry for Ferrell.  I asked him yesterday where he was taking Annie on their date and he said he hasn't been able to talk to her.  She's been with her friends or just walking away.  I know she doesn't like him, and I know she is avoiding him.  Even though it's Ferrell that's just mean.  To accept an offer for a date and then try to shaft him.  That's cruel.  Well they had swim today.  There's no way to avoid him there.  So she'll get what's coming.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a good day today.  At practice I did my story telling piece and people laughed again.  Sondra said it's starting to flow and mush together.  That's a good thing.  And I found out that at Gatlinburg, we perform in the hotel.  Meaning our rounds are in the hotel rooms, now this trip will be even more fucking awesome!  I am pumped.  Too-ta-loo!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got chocolate today.  Yeah for me.  I would like to start by sending my sympathy to the Mock Trial team for your loss today.  Yesterday I did really well at practice and found out some juicy news.  Ferrell asked out Annie Dawson.  Hamburger said he will dump her soon though.  I don't know what she was thinking.  I think she just wanted a date for Valentine's day.  She doesn't like him anyways and she seems to be a desperate person.  But Jacob was funny about it.  Ha I love his name!  I got a lot of stuff today.  And I'm going to go see 50 First Dates.  It's going to be great.  Catch Ya Later
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I GOT MY EARS PIERCED TODAY!  I am so psyched.  I really have nothing to say today.  Well, Friday is tomorrow.  That's it.  Cya
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aquarius (January 20-February 18)  It's almost like you're a teacher today, Aquarius. You can be terrific at helping someone else with a problem at school or work. But what your real talent is today is speaking your mind in a way that's so clear and understandable that even the densest person can get it. Complicated issues are made simple because of how carefully and precisely you're able to talk about them.  It's like the twilight zone.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's really funny what can make a person respect you for the person you are.  Today was interesting.  We had practice today.  Swim is over so Ferrell showed up.  He lies all the time and it really does take a toll on me.  It was driving me away.  So before we actually started anything I asked Ferrell if I could talk to him in the hall.  I explained to him how everyone felt about his lies and all that.  Of course he tried to defend himself.  But what was really awkward was when he couldn't make eye contact with me anymore and never has not been able to keep eye contact with me.  I knew I had embarrassed him.  I thought to myself I really screwed that up.  I went to go back into the room and he grabbed be my waist and asked me how the party went without him.  I told him how Matt imitated Britney Spears the pole dancer and how Honig became aroused.  But he was very touchy feely with me the rest of the day.  I don't know if he respects me more for speaking with him or if he was aroused by my being direct.  I'll go with the idea of respect.  Well I'll wait and see what happens later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a few days.  I've started a diary for extremely personal moments so I don't think I'll write that often.  I had an okay day.  I spoke with Ferrell about five times today.  He was being a little perverted, but then he got serious when I asked him how he was.  He looked miserable.  He had a long face and looked really tired.  He smiled when I asked him and I really sent a rush of glee through me.  He made some funny jokes, but I don't feel like telling them.  Jake was acting weird.  He thanked me for inviting him to the party and then asked me if we missed him after he left.  It is so weird, he is such a ladies man and no one knows why.  Then I spoke to Hamburger.  He still tried to mess with me and I told him how I enjoyed the conversation we had when he thought I was Chelsea and how he asked me if Liz, Morgan, and I fell for their joke, thinking that I was Chelsea.  Chelsea confessed when I told her what happened.  Ha it was funny.  She's great.  It was cool today.  Walking down the halls today I found that there was always someone at my side from class to class.  On my way to 4th I was in between both Hamburger and Ferrell.  That felt satisfying because I've always been the weirdo and to have two sophomore guys on my arms felt nice.  And I was scary, Ferrell actually did that clingy thing where you hook your arms.  He grabbed my arm.  It was a really different side of him.  Huh.  I'll leave on this note.  Until Later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so pumped about my party tomorrow.  It is going to be so much fun.  I just hope it doesn't get too out of control.  I've picked out two movies to watch,  one is Best In Show and the other is The Ring.  Sounds stupendous so far doesn't it?  And for food we will have chips and dip and pizza and for during the movie we will have popcorn and tons of it.  Then for entertainment we have a couple games if we get around to it,  one is MADLIBS otherwise known as the best game in the world, and then a game called Balderdash.  Another word game and it is really funny.  It is going to be soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrreeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaattttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttt!  As you can probably tell I'm really excited.  Ta Ta For Now
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't feel like putting a title today, if no one minds.  I had another good day.  School let out early for flooding!  And thats great because I didn't finish my homework for biology.  And there was that occasional disgusting thing that happens to me almost everyday.  Ferrell ran into me in the hall.  He has to compete at a Regional swimming tournament tomorrow so he had to shave his legs last night.  Ewww!  But he came up to me and asked me to feel his leg.  Even more disgusting.  But besides that I had an okay day.  It was fun when I got to watch Christmas Vacation in spanish class.  Oh I have to get the phone.  It's Ferrell.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MEDIOCRE!  I hate those kind of days.  Well I got a 101% on my espanol exam.  Go me.  But I don't know how I did on the Arthropods exam in biology.  Who knows.  I don't have any homework and Chelsea asked me to go see a show at the something theater.  Can't remember.  But I bet my parents will say no.  You know why, because they wouldn't let my sister go out last Sunday night.  But don't they always give you that crap about how you have more responsibilities because you're older and that you get more privledges also.  Well, please tell me when does that come into effect?  When we move out for college, "Oh by the way you can go out with your friends now."  Yeah that was crap, I know.  Well, anywho I have to go ask my dad.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't posted in a while.  Well, to start we swept up the District tournament.  I broke for my first time ever.  And Interp Theater is going to State.  It'll be awesome.  Well, really nothing is going on.  I have a huge Bio test tomorrow and I know absolutely nothing on it.  So I guess I'll have to study my little hiney off tonight.  Oh well, So long.  Farewell.  And the rest of the sound of music song (to the melody).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did you ever feel so completely overwhelmed that you just want to cry your eyes out until you feel you have no responsibilities in the world, except to take care of yourself.  I feel tied down at home, at school, and anywhere else I can think of.  I'm extremely excited to perform on Friday and Saturday, but after all my hard work this whole year I can't even go out to dinner on Saturday after the tournament.  That is partially my fault, but I really don't see what it is with my father.  I hate my family.  My mom is fully supportive of Forensics, but she hates to do anything.  She is always trying to get rides for me because she doesn't feel like it.  That is so embarrassing when I see all these other parents who don't mind to take their children places, but now it makes me feel bad when they are equally responsible for getting me places now.  And this has nothing to do with her surgery, I can understand that,  but this is all the time.  Then my dad.  He just does not understand and he won't take the time to listen.  Sometimes I just cry myself to sleep wishing he didn't pressure me so much.  I have so much to focus on at the moment and it all just adds up.  The reason I don't like to help around the house, isn't that I'm lazy, it's that I am so tired, stressed, frustated, angry, and just all around overwhelmed and all I want is some time by myself to cool off and simer before I join my corruptive family.  The reason I forget to call them is that deep down I don't want to call them.  I want to be out for as long as possible so that I can just be away from them.  And on Saturday when all my friends are out to eat, celebrating, I'll be at home with the worst people in my life right now.  I love them, but they are horrible people to be around, I guess that is why I have an "attitude" as my dad calls it.  And I guess that is "what's wrong with me" which is what both my parents question.  I wish sometimes I weren't here for them to complain about.  Maybe then Courtney wouldn't look so perfect in my dad's eyes.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Practice went horribly today.  I couldn't talk or act and forgot everything we did on Saturday.  I have three huge tests tomorrow.  I'll have to do a whole lot of studying tonight.  Which I really don't feel like doing because at the moment all I need is rest.  hasta luego
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like doggy poo.  I came home from practice yesterday and slept until 7:00.  Then kept waking up in the middle of the night.  But I did have one awesome time at practice.  That is besides the loss of power and the being smacked in the nose by Sarah which wasn't as bad as when she clutched my head to her chest so I couldn't breath and then Chelsea trying to shove a tissue up my nose for fear that is was bleeding.  It was pretty funny.  Well, anyhwo I'm sorry I couldn't make it last night to the Miss Guardian Angel Pageant.  But for now I must get well for Districts are on Friday and I can not miss school for rehearsals and whatnot.  I will see you all later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was good for me!  I had an excellent time warming up with Becca.  And I downloaded Ice Ice Baby on my iPod....finally.  But I have awesome news from Erica.  She spoke with Darren today in Spanish about things.  It's hilarious.  You'd have to talk to her about it.  Scott was so giddy today.  He is so excited....it was so cute.  Oh, funny thing.  I got in the mail today an application to enter the Miss Tennesse Teen Jr. pagaent.  Later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH MY GOODNESS!  OH MY GOODNESS!  OH MY GOODNESS!  Do I have the best news or what!  Scott Lemons asked Christina Lordeman to prom!  I know. Contain your excitement!  I can't.  Oh more good news,  Mrs. Medlin actually liked our Interp Theater!  Bad news, the theater was not available to practice on. Dag Nabit!  Well, til tomorrow!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, my day was...okay, average, long, tired.....blaa.  Well, Erica is feeling better. Yeah!  Ooo!  I told Lindsay how we thought it would be cool if Michael played Juliet for Shakespeare with Medlin.  I think she wanted to be Juliet.  Oh I have good news for those who care.  My foot is healing, it's itchy and I think scabbing.  Oh man I am so tired!  We have shortened classes tomorrow for a suckey assembly on bullying called Bang Bang You're Dead.  Sounds Oscar worthy. Well that's about it for today.  sea you guys tomorrow  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for the title.  It was more like a comment and has nothing to do with this entry!  Anyway....Interp practice today rocked my socks off!  We have our music and learned from now on we are practicing on the stage!  How exciting!!  And....that Friday on the 26th we get to miss the whole day of school!!!!!!!!!  I am super psyched.  We will be practicing at Elisa's that morning and compete at around 1:00 at Ravenwood.  Whoo Hoo!!  As you can see I am super super excited (doesn't that sound like an Elle Woods line).  Ha! I crack myself up with my exclamation point rampage!  And I going out tonight to get my hoodie.  I am a blessed person!  Well enough for now!  If you read comment, Pleeeease!  P.S.  Becca you should really start your own blog.  Since I have refused to read Jenessa's and Liz's I only have Erica's to read.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      READY FOR LOVE: You're sensitive but no pushover, active but not manic. In short, you're a great girl/guy who's ready for a relationship. If you're not already involved with someone, it's only because you want a guy/girl who's worthy of your love---you just haven't met him/her yet. That's cool. You've got plenty of other interests to keep you busy. When you do meet ''Mr. Great/Miss. Great,'' chances are you won't abandon all the other impotant stuff in your life for romance. In fact, your independance and spirit will be part of what attracts him/her---and keeps him/her. Would YOU PLEASE rate my quiz? YOU surely don't have to, but i'd apreciate it more than YOU could imagine if YOU would! Thanks! Peace out yo'!        urlLink Are YOU ready to have a BOYFRIEND/GIRLFRIEND? For the OLDER GALS/GUYS!      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    M&M'S: Just like the candy. you're soft on the inside, but have a protective shell so you don't melt for all things sentimental. While you're not going to forget what's important to you (like friends, school and the cool activities that make you such an interesting girl), you're also open to romance in whatever form it might take. You'll have an amazing V-Day, whether you spend it with a cute boy or have a girls night out. Would YOU PLEASE rate my quiz? Thanks a whole bunch!     urlLink How ROMANTIC are YOU? For the LADiES!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    THE FREETHINKINER: I like you, and I don't even know you. Who wouldn't? You have your own opinions---and are confident enough to voice them---but you're also willing to listen to the other side. And you're not afraid to try new stuff even when your friends aren't interested. For example, if you were dying to see Linkin Park in concert and no one else wanted to go, you'd still be there rockin' out. Basically, you rule.     urlLink How INDEPEDNDANT are YOU? (For the LADIES!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had the greatest day today!  Towards the end of the day I had no hateful feelings because I really don't give a damn anymore.  For those who care, I changed my sn.  Now it is Meshgurl218.  Becca will understand.  I had the greatest lunch also.  Tomorrow is bound to be better.  I have practice, which is always fun with Sarah and Elisa.  Which by they way, they definitely stole the show.  It is such an honor to be working with them.  Anywho, guess I'll see you guys tomorrow *notice how I refrain from using the term ya'll*.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You just don't get it, do you?  I don't care if you like him or not.  I'm over that.  Every time I tried to expressed my feeling about your "love" for him I get bitch-slapped.  And that pissed me off.  The fact that no one can have different opinions about him other than the ones you have set out for us.  I really don't think he's that bad.  Christina and Chelsea have told me some hilarious stories.  And he actually seems kinda cool.  But do remember the other day at lunch when I was talking to Erica and Becca about how for Les Mis they wanted him to cut his hair and he refused.  You caught on to what I was saying and made everyone shut up so you could hear.  That is what ticks me off.  The only way I can communicate with you and actually have you pay attention is if I mention him.  But now that you don't want to talk to me about him, I guess you don't need to hear about all the hilarious things he did on the set during rehearsals.  I got the stories so I could possibly talk to you, but as that isn't going to happen I suppose I'll just keep those stories to myself.  And Becca has offered an invitation to Erica and I to eat lunch in Mr. Millers room with her and her friends.  Maybe there I won't have to worry about people taking offense to everything I say and I could possibly carry on a normal, interesting conversation, in which no one hypervenalates (sp?).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided that since Hamburger got me into this www.quizilla.com thing I might show you guys my results.  I had a lot of fun in my extra spare time.  Check this out.   your shit.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Gay Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla        My inner child is sixteen years old!    Life's not fair! It's never been fair, but while adults might just accept that, I know something's gotta change. And it's gonna change, just as soon as I become an adult and get some power of my own.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Your: Happy eyes! Your cheerful, bright and always want to try something new. Your inquisitive and quite lovable. You have many friends and will succeed in life.    urlLink   What type of eyes do you have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Just so you guys know, this is not a pic of my actual eye.    footsie - you like to goof around and laugh with the people you care about.    urlLink   What Sign of Affection Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      schizotypal    urlLink   Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're just the happy go-lucky type. You might have your pet peeves, but other than that, you're mainly calm. Blending in with your surroundings, you're the type of person who everyone likes. Usually it's you who cracks jokes at social gatherings - after all, laughter is the best medicine. Sometimes you pretend to be stupid, but in all actuality, you could be the next Einstein.    urlLink   What Type of Soul Do You Have ?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Sneakers- funny, laid-back, and goofy, you love to make people laugh and have a good time.  You enjoy comfort and don't care to much about what people think of you.  You like to hang out with your buddies and just have a good time. [please vote! thank you! :)]     urlLink   What Kind of Shoe Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are Woodstock!    urlLink   Which Peanuts Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're bubblegum!!! You love to have a good time, and enjoy being around others who feel the same way.  You tend to be the life of the party, and people like to be around you as much as they can.      urlLink   Which kind of candy are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You should be dating a Virgo. 23 August - 22 September This mate is known for his/her ability to work with the helpless, to evoke strong feelings of empathy and to keep a household strictly organized.  Though the virgin can sometimes be scathingly critical of others, cranky and irritable, he/she will seduce their partner with finesse, charm and subtlety.    urlLink   What Zodiac Sign Are You Attracted To?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Hey that is so funny the guy I used to like was born on August 31.  I know that b/c it's the same day Princess Diana died.  He told me.  Isn't that weird.    Your Heart is Red    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You feel happy, and loved. Nothing could be any better for you....you may even have a love one in your life....go you. (Please Vote)    urlLink   What Emotion Dominates you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Morpheus    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're Element is Light. You are friendly, happy, social, bubbly, and can brighten up any one's day. You are very kind and a real people person because you have several friends (or at least should). You're cheery nature makes you lovable and your stunning looks are sweet and stand out.    urlLink   What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     Okay! Still awake?  I think I'm done now.  If you didn't know much about me before you certainly do now.  Hey I'm going to be intuitive for a moment and say that I think the fact that I posted about 7 billion quiz results reflects on my personality.  Ha, imagine that.  I can be intelingent and retarded at the same time.  Muhahaha (evil laughter). 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been a while and a lot has happened.  Gatlinburg was cancelled...fuck the school transportation system.  But I'm over it.  I had a good day today though.  I went to Kohl's with Chelsea.  We each got a new suit and decided to do a duo next year.  So my new suit is kick ass, but you will have to wait to see it.  Then I went out for Starbucks with Ferrell and some other peoples you guys wouldn't know from BA.  That was...interesting.  Then I had Interp Theater practice.  I am tired out.  I have practice tomorrow and I'm babysitting on Saturday so I'm going to see Cinderella on Sunday with a few people.  It'll be awesome.  Sarah and Elisa will steal the show.  I've been to some rehersals and they are unbelievably good.  Sarah has to be the most talented person I have ever met.  Rachel and I were talking about how she inspired us to do well in Forensics.  She is amazing and I guarentee she will become famous someday.  I have a jam packed schedule for the next three weeks.  It's nice to have things to do.  I hate sitting and just have nothing going on in my life.  That would be an incredibly sad life.  Yeah *sigh*.  Oh I do have good news.  The guy I used to like, I don't like him like him anymore.  Our friendship has bloomed and I don't want anything to change.  It's a really nice feeling.  To know that my crush is gone simply because something more has developed...hint of smile.  Sorry Becca, I definitely stole your "beautiful people" line.  Oopsie Daisy.  Ha when was the last time I said that............yesterday *bashfully*.  Okay I can't hold it in.  My new suit is a lilac purplish color.  It kicks hiney (butt).  I'm so excited.  I'm wearing it to districts.  I hope it doesn't piss Medlin off.    Oh well.  Districts will be fun. Well,  I have to go wash my hair *notice the typical dating excuse, meaning I have better things to do*.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I only have one thing to say today...........I DROVE FOR MY FIRST TIME EVER!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IT'S MY PARTY AND I'LL CRY IF I WANT TO!  Seems as though everything is coming to an end.  I have to say, this has been the best school year I have ever had!  I think I have finally realized the person I really am inside.  I have come out of my shell, I speak my mind, and I really don't care at all what others think of me.  Sorry Erica I'm copying your entry.....almost.  I have more going on in my life and discovered hidden talents.  But enough about me.  I have really made some strong new friendships.  And I've lost some friends also, but not to hurt anyone.  It was all in my best interest.  I did it to help myself not to hurt anyone, despite what they may think.  I didn't feel like I really belonged and that at times I was completely unwelcome.  I'm really quite upset this year is almost over, but then again I'm looking forward to next year also.  It will be twice as much fun.  We know now to go with the flow and not get caught up in mess of things.  Work hard, but enjoy it while it lasts.  Next year will be a time to make even more "special friendships" and hey, ya never know, we could also find our "special someones"  *if ya know what i mean*! OMG!  I am so excited for spring day this year!  That'll be another first.  Oh Well enough of that.  I'll see you dudes later.  YOU WOULD CRY TOO IF IT HAPPENED TO YOU! (that song is stuck in my head....there's plenty of room up there)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everybody!  Nothing much going on in my life at the moment.  I just recieved the invite to showcase.  Fun stuff!  And on a darker note I lost my spiral notebook which contained my Bio notes and packet, all my Geometry and Romeo and Juliet stuff.   It really holds just about everything of academic importance.  It sucks.  So tomorrow I'm gonna figure out what has happened to it.  If I can't find it I'll get all the notes from Mr. M and fail Geometry for the quarter.  I choose not to sink into a depression over this and I am determined to be upbeat about life.  Even though it does suck.  Hey Becca and Erica when do you think we can see Home on the Range?  Talk to me later.  Tomorrow is a focus day! Whoo Hoo!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So we watched our video in Miller's room during lunch today.  Let me just say we are all going to look like stupid shits tomorrow, but I am okay with it.  A lot has happened lately, but I really don't care to type it.  One last thing, I spoke with Ferrell and apologized for cussing him out on the phone and he seemed relieved.  Apparently he felt like he had done something wrong.  I'm glad I apologized, made me feel better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry the title sounds like something a depressed person would say.  Obviously I'm not depressed.  Well anyways......spring break sucks.  I've had fun I guess, but it just hasn't been as fullfiling as hoped for.  Well so far I've gone to the rec center everyday to do laps, gone to the movies twice and I might go again today.  I want to see The Whole Ten Yards.  I love Matthew Perry.  I've gone to the mall (my least favorite place in the world) twice.  I've gone on about 5 bike rides through Crockett Park.  And yesterday to make some cash I weeded my whole front and back yard.  Holy Cow was that a nightmare.  Good thing though, I got sun tanned.  Whoo hoo! Oh yeah and I got my own cell phone.  It's a sony ericsson and it is so cute.  I need your opinions though, I'm ordering a face plate for it and I can't decided between a bubblegum pink one or a hot pink one (not neon but a darker hot pink).   Well that's all for now.  Sorry I Haven't posted in a while.  I just didn't want to, I guess.  P.S. To make your easter even more specialer check out the Rapping Easter Bunny (under links). Enjoy the rest of spring break! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing to do, nothing to say.  I'm rotting in my room and my house.  Talk to me.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It stinks!  I can't leave the house.  What am I supposed to do?  I miss you guys already.  It also sucks because my parents secretly favor my sister so when she gets all C's and an F and is grounded it doesn't even last a day.  It stinks.  Becca I got the pics.  They didn't come out stupendous, but they are pretty funny.  And I got doubles sos you get half.  Call me or something and I'll get them to ya.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry guys, no perkiness today.  I feel like all my limbs will fall off and I just slept for 4 hours and about to sleep some more.  Well for tomorrow we're meeting at the soccor fields of crockett park at 6 or 7 to gel out.  pick your best time and we will comprimise.  becca will bring the frisbee.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So many parties and I have about five more this month.  Hey guys we should really get together at least once a week.  It would be so great!  Becca- we could get together and just like ride our bikes to crocket park or whatever.  "There's trees need to be fell".  Oh do I love great quotes.  I'm just rambling.  We should have another water fight too.  That was so much fun!  Oh Becca another awesome thing about next year is we get to help with orientation. Next year will rock my thighs off!  Just going for something different there.  WE WILL HAVE THE BEST TIME EVAAAAAA!  Ok, I'm done.  Well see you guys later.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has now officially come to the end.  Only half a day left.  What will I do with out you guys.  What can I say, it's been great.  Well I guess I'll see you guys on Friday and Erica on Saturday.  Man you guys we cannot lose touch this summer.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I felt like several of these answers suited me so I took it twice.  My first results were:    Gay Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    My second results were:    Raver Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    And there it is.  You take the quiz it's got some dirty outcomes if you're not careful.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay!  I got it all figured out!  So what we do is have the water fight this friday at say 11:30 am.  Then grill some stuff, eat it.  Don't forget dry clothes.  And then we all just hang out like a Starbucks get together.  Ferrell is coming when I told him that Asscraft, Holkum and Honig are all coming.  So we have a party.  Tell me what you think 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GYPSY COW-TIPPING IN HOLKUM, MISSISSIPPI 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had an interesting time tonight, I won't go into detail, but it was fun.  My mom is staying at the hospital all weekend.  To tell you the truth I'm kinda happy.  I don't want her to come home and take the risk of hurting herself again.  All's well though.  ttyl.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today was Spring Day!  ASSCRAFT!  I'm as red as a cherry.  You guys'll see me tomorrow.  I had a lot of fun, but when I got home I found out my mom had a heart attack at 9 am this morning.  I didn't know what to do, so....I called Ferrell.  He understands the relationship between my mom and I more than anyone else.  I couldn't stop crying.  It was so embarrassing.  I don't know what to do.  I'm going to Starbucks tomorrow, but I'll need a ride to and from there.  And I apologize in advance if I'm not my Speed-y self, but I feel the need to get out.  But Spring Day was fun today, but I still can't bend down.  Erica just in advance, that is how people act at away tournaments.  You only get a couple hours of sleep in 2 days and you just go crazy.  Well now off to put lotion on my face.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is just a little quiz I took today.  You can see the results plain as day.  U are as clean as the clean spring air.     urlLink                                    ?Are u a durg addict?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Catchy title, eh?  There's a lot behind it and I believe the only person capable of explaining it best is Mr. Eric Asscraft Ford.  All I can say is the napkin is the device used to record everthing embarrassing and hilarious stated at Starbucks.  I will now turn it over to Eric.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have nothing better to do so i am blogging.  i cleaned out my basement today.  i moved out anything glass or porcelain and moved out the end tables and coffee tables which have glass surfaces.  i cleaned that bathroom too.  man that was a lot of work.  now all i must do is air it out and vacuum the floors.  and then stock up of napkins, plates, etc...so guys i was thinking starbucks on friday.  i want to be with my dad on saturday because i miss him when he's away.  Erica I love you too.  I really need to tape my hands to my hiney though.  I'm going to kill someone one of these days.  i hope i'm not annoying in any way, if i am tell me to shut up. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today was the discovery of a whole new flavor....VANILLA NUT CREME.  Seems as though 'hazelnut' isn't the only coffee she's having with Miller.  Man O Man Bella, you sure do get around.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm still pretty mad, but I'm learning to get over it.  "Shovels and bricks will kill, but words can't and will not hurt me."  Like how I made that up.  I think we should all vent at Starbucks this weekend.  Laugh and cry like an old eighties movie and I'll be the pregnant star who dies in child birth after the discovery of my breast cancer.  "goin to the chapel, and we're gonna get married.  gee I really love you and we're gonna get married, goin to the chapel of love."  Gee what ever happened those good old oldies songs.  I miss 'em.  Man I feel like listening to the gay musical stylings of The Producers.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I changed my template and I lost all my comments.  But isn't it pretty.  So for all that care the party is at my house 6-10 on May 22.  See you all later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      COTTON CANDY AND MONKEY RACHETS
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bella- I went to Starbucks in Cool Springs this morning with my mom and guess what I got!  I pink water thingamabob.  I'll show you on Monday!  Happy Mother's Day everbody.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have discovered that I scare people with my awkward behaviors.  For instance, I talk with my hands, laugh like a madwoman, and I'm on Speed (inside joke, NOT LITERAL).  And well I've decided that I need a behavior makeover.  Also I need to not make stupid inferences that no one understands and leads to others thinking I'm completely insane.  Starbucks was fun.  I appreciated it (nodds head).  I'm one of the 326BCs.  And Becca, Bella and I will do something extremely crazy on February 28 at 11:30 pm on my front lawn.  And probably invite some people over for Hazelnut (Klingon quotation fingers) Coffee.  Sounds fun, doesn't it?  And just for the record the trash can fell on me, I did not jump into it.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So a lot has happened lately.  I'm driving, I helped some friend of mine, I have been doing more stuff socially, I'm going to Starbucks saturday and Becca's b-day party on friday.  It'll be fun.  Tomorrow is the Friends season and series finale.  It seems as though everything is coming to an end or just beginning.  It's a nice but upsetting feeling.  My friendship with Bella is growing.  We were so giggly this morning.  It was fun.  Just so much has happened.  There's not much time before we all leave for summer vaca.  Happy Hump Day and Happy Cinco de Mayo.  ttyl
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!    My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  My braces are off!  Ok thats enough of that, but they are off....FINALLY!!!!  But b/c my gums were so swollen they couldnt take molds for my clear reatainer today I have to wait a month for my mouth to get used to not have braces in but in the meantime i have another retainer which is really hard to get used to.my teeth are soooo white too.  with braces my obsessive compulsive brushing didnt show but now it does.  It's kinda scary but at the same time cool.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I had a lot of fun this past week....saw a bad movie, went to Kentucky Kingdom, had tons of Karyoke fun, and went out to lunch.  Erica and I had a cool idea for something to do next week.  We can all meet at my house at around one o' clock and play some flag football and make t-shirts.  Tell me what you think.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I had a lot of fun this past week....saw a bad movie, went to Kentucky Kingdom, had tons of Karyoke fun, and went out to lunch.  Erica and I had a cool idea for something to do next week.  We can all meet at my house at around one o' clock and play some flag football and make t-shirts.  Tell me what you think.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I think the party went okay!  I hope you enjoyed your party!  Well nothing much to say about it.....any comments?  Please make them.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok....so I am now ungrounded!!!  Whoopeee!  Such a great feeling to get out of the house.  Ford, I hope this isn't too pitiful.  I fixed my bike.  What happened was the brake pad was bent and the brake was constantly on.  You try pedaling with the front brake on and up a few hills.  Not so easy, but it is fixed.  I miss Starbucks.  It's so much fun.  I'll see you guys tomorrow.  Adios mis amigas y amigos.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Temporary post for Asscraft.  Full-length one coming later.  I keep to my word.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a joy ride, but a few things I never realized....there are a whole lot of pedestrians!!!!  Holy crap!!! I could have sworn I was gonna hit one of them.  My mother is a lot less....nervous?  And doesn't yell as much or well...yell as much.  It's slightly more relaxing.  Well everyone watch out for me on the rode!!!  And Good Luck!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like a complete dumbass.  I failed the permit test.  I'm going again tomorrow so if there were any questions that you got stuck on please inform me.  I'm seriously scared shitless to go back in there.  Oh guys we need to do something.  What are you guys doing Monday?  And what are you doing the 8th, 9th, and 10th of this month.  Footloose is playing at Pull-Tight.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I must say it is good to be back.... now is it just me or are there more options for blogger now? Anywho I was curious is anyone was up for starbucks on wednesday at noon. And here is my name acronym....I don't think it's a too right about me.         C     Cuddly       A     Appealing       I     Influential       T     Temperamental       L     Lively       I     Insane       N     Naive         http://www.go-quiz.com/acronym/acronym.php">Name  / Username:      urlLink Name  Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>