<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I caught the  urlLink Nick and Jessica Variety Hour  and I watched Jessica sing with Jewel. That girl looks like she's having a seizure when she sings! She spasms and jolts, and her lips purse and protrude oddly, and she curls her lips in unfortunate ways. I can't watch her with out wincing. I think the only time I find her acceptable is on  urlLink Newlyweds . Then she seems whiny and ditzy, but at least she seems like someone real. I swear she's trying way too hard when she sings, and it's absolutely painful to watch. It's especially noticeable when she sings with a normal singer like Kenny Rogers or Jewel. Less so when she sings with Nick, who seems to come from a similar school of smiling, singing and spasming while moving your hands about in a supposedly emotional way. Ick. It really creeps me out.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I for one am glad the whole super straight hair look is on its way out. My hair is naturally wavy and big, and has never been willing to cooperate with my desire for straighter hair. So I'm thinking I'll try  urlLink the hot roller method  next time I actually do my hair. I must admit, most mornings I just flip my head over, work a little smoothing cream in (from back to front, concentrating on the ends), then I finger comb and blow dry quickly. I've been trying to wear it down more lately, because I've been abusing the ponytail, mostly because it's finally long enough to all stay back. Very exciting to get my hair out of my face. But the exciting thing is that my hair naturally hangs in big waves, so I might be able to get away with my old method for a while longer. Until I get another short haircut that needs special styling again.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so I'm killing time waiting for a response on my  urlLink IGETC  bullshit, so here are some of the things I've been contemplating lately:    1. The  urlLink Bachelor  final rose ceremony is just cruel. I've watched three of them at this point, but I think it's so awful to take two people who think they're in love with another person, and at the last minute completely crush one of them, while establishing a quasi-relationship with the other. I just don't get it. Yes, it's good entertainment, sort of, but it's also painful to watch people's hearts broken by reality televison producers. They really are going to hell, and soon.  2. I am getting way too caught up in blog world. There are people I've never heard of who are way to popular... mostly they're club kids and DJs, and they remind me a lot of my sister-in-law's friends, who are only different because they're in San Francisco and not New York. Check out my blogroll, and you'll see what I'm talking about. It's kind of bizarre.   Okay, off to quit screwing around. I'm likely to drive to my old school to sort this mess out, so no posts for a while. Ta-ta!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As a devotee of both history and reality television, I really enjoy  urlLink Colonial House . But I have a few issues with what I've seen. It really bugs me how easily the people on the show forget why they're there: it's the history, stupid! Quit whining about how hard it is, I imagine it was worse in the 17th century. Remember Roanoke? They ate each other and everyone died anyway. Living in close quarters and having to work your butts off is not the worst thing in the world. In fact, it would be such an adventure to actually live as people really lived then. I can't imagine how difficult and yet amazing it would be. Of course, the producers probably are editing in the sections that are most dramatic and crazy, I bet they were normal and content for at least some of the show.   Also, what's up with the women's hair being everywhere? I mean, they're doing a better job with the clothes than the people on  urlLink Frontier House , but it's so not period to wear your hair down and in your face. And doesn't it drive them crazy? When I do reenactments for just a weekend, I'm so thankful for period snoods and caps that keep my nasty, greasy hair out of my face and out of my way. Even touching my hair is too much when it hasn't been washed in a while. But those are just my nitpickings. Has anyone else been watching and have any opinions?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why  urlLink Harry Potter and Left Behind  are more alike then you think. I've read the earlier books of Left Behind (I was a little Christian during my teenage years), and all of Harry Potter, and I can honestly say that Harry Potter's better. They're just less cheesy, more originial books. Left Behind reminds me of Michael Crichton for Christians: very mass produced, very "action packed" yet not nearly as satisfying as a good old Harry Potter book.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jimmy Fallon's  urlLink leaving SNL ! Now who's going to make Tina Fey look so brainy on Weekend Update? They had the best chemistry. And there aren't any other good cute funny guys on SNL besides him. Horatio Sands is not gonna make up for the loss of Jimmy Fallon. I'm so depressed. Honestly, the only thing that'll keep me watching is Tina Fey, and she's branching out into movies. Did you see 'Mean Girls'? Brilliant stuff. She has a career ahead of her, a very witty and clever career. Yay for smart, pretty girls with glasses!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the horror of Abu Ghraib&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been doing a lot of study about colonialism, and it's very upsetting how relevant all of it is to current events. This  urlLink article  looks at how Iraq compares to Joseph Conrad's "Heart of Darkness" and the Congolese ivory and rubber boom. Another good book if you're interested in more of this is  urlLink "King Leopold's Ghost"  by Adam Hochschild. This tells the history behind much of Conrad's novel, and discusses the actual horrors and extermination of the era. Again, frighteningly relevant.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read this  urlLink article  about the life-long benefits of breast feeding, and then maybe you'll know why I'm so freakishly healthy (knock on wood). 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      New and improved, I've decided to try to classify my blogging: commentary here, ranting/personal stuff at the confessional. I've decided to go with a whole ambivalent theme, since that's my favorite word, along with "Alienated" and also "Authentic." Funny how they're all "A" words. I'll have to think about any other words that I'm into. Oh well, now I need to look for stuff to comment on. Shouldn't be hard, considering the state of the world lately!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and you end up getting all riled up about the world. Last night I caught the end of Frontline's  urlLink "The Way the Music Died"  about why the music industry is faltering so much and why their sales are down. In a nutshell, MTV+corporations=singers who only look good and music that sounds like crap. I thought it was fascinating to watch, and it reminded me of why I absolutely love Frontline. It's a documentary of the news. It's always so current and so relevant, and really gets you thinking deeply about an issue. If they replay it on one of the  urlLink PBS stations , you should really try to catch it. Or just watch Frontline and PBS as often as you can. It's usually worth it, but who knows, I'm just a pinko liberal who loves thinking about the world around me. You might not feel the same.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you're looking for something to do in Davis area this weekend, go across the causeway to  urlLink Sacramento  to see the Jazz Jubilee. Earlier this week,  urlLink Melissa  and I heard  urlLink Fat Sam's Band  while getting dinner at Pluto's, and I heard an interview with the band on KXJZ this morning. It looks like a lot of fun, and I bet there's more to do than at the  urlLink Stockton Asparagus Festival , the town sponsored event that I grew up with. It involved a lot of beer and deep-fried asparagus, and a lot of cheesy vendors. I assume the Jubilee is much the same, but there'll be music to watch and listen to. Could be good times, so I might talk the boy into going.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been reading  urlLink Greg the Boyfriend's ideas about men and women  and it's getting me  urlLink thinking  about male/famale relations in general. Or maybe I've been reading too much  urlLink erotica . Anyway, single or not, we are all confused yet fascinated by the opposite sex (sorry for the heterosexual bias). Why are they so confounding? Aren't we all just people? It's real question that I don't understand. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I have issues I'm dealing with  Posted by  urlLink Hello    I'm trying to figure out this whole photo hosting dealy. I'll probably take this down eventually, I'm just working everything out for a bit.  I think I need to get HTML for Dummies. I'm good a figuring things out with help, but I sure am clueless about a lot of internet stuff. Good thing the boy is good at it or I'd be screwed!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An interesting  urlLink article about bloggers . Makes me feel better about my posting habits. I think I only post once a day on average. I'm like most of these bloggers because NO ONE reads this! It's kind of weird, but I feel like I'm keeping a record for myself of what I think is interesting on this blog, and on the other I record my personal drama. Lately I've been more verbose in the confessional, mostly because I've been going through more drama and spending less time being transfixed by world events. Next week should be light all around because it's PAPER TIME!! Yay. :(
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks Melissa; another time waster. I must say, this is a great test, because Merry always was my favorite--          Merry Brandybuck   If I were a character in   The Lord of the Rings  , I would be Merry, Hobbit, heir of the Brandybucks and a friend of Frodo's.  In the movie, I am played by  Dominic Monaghan .  Who would  you  be?   Zovakware Lord of the Rings Test      with  Perseus Web Survey Software       
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay a small flash of insight: I watched  urlLink Gilmore Girls season finale  last week, and it was an absolutely awesome episode. Reminiscent of the first season. Really, this and  urlLink The O.C.  are the only non-reality shows I follow. Really. So anyway, I'm of the opinion that Dean totally came on to Rory, and he's the one who should feel the worst about it, not Rory. I mean, Dean showed up at her house and came into her room proclaiming his love for her, and how much he hated Lindsay. Poor Rory is all I have to say about it. And it irritates me when people say she's the slut... everyone always blames the woman. What about the man who toys with women's emotions to get laid? I ask you. These people. Check out the TWoP forums. The venom is amazing.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I hate going too long between posts, but I used up all of my daily ration of analysis on creating a presentation for my Colonialism and Culture seminar. It was a really interesting reading which I outlined and summarized, but I'm not sure I'll go too much in depth. Let's just say that one of the articles noted that S/M is a violation of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights which says the "No one will be tortured, nor subjected to degrading or humiliating treatment." No where is there an exception for consenting adults. Interesting, huh? Think on that next time you think religion is barbarous. "Consenting adults" doesn't just apply to sex and the eroticization of pain.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent way too much time at  urlLink The Oracle of Bacon at Virginia  trying to find an actor with more than two degrees of separation. All I found was Cheryl Tiegs, Tina Fey, and  urlLink Melissa  found Mike Meyers. Really a great time waster and a tempting challenge. I had to finally give up!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've always had this odd obsession with flags and the meanings of national symbolism. This  urlLink article  shows some of the tensions around the junction of design and politics. Especially interesting is a proposed EU flag, which I think is beautiful, and graphicly stunning. I'd take it over the lame blue field with a circle of gold stars. It's just so P.C., and I generally prefer controversy.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Though I don't think anyone actually reads this, I just wanted to put it out there that my posting will be very light in the next week because of finals and impending graduation from school. All of my snarky brain power is currently being diverted to papers about the dehumanizing aspects of the colonial project, the meanings and conflicts in the myth of the west as compared to the actual history of the west, the evolution of the Republican party from one of principle to one of money, and last but not least, the role of race in Spanish America in the 16th century. Yes, I've been spending way more time worrying about the past than I have been worrying about the present. I'm trying to keep myself abreast of any big news, but that's the extent. After graduation: more time than I know what to do with! Plenty of time for blogging.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Though I don't think anyone actually reads this, I just wanted to put it out there that my posting will be very light in the next week because of finals and impending graduation from school. All of my snarky brain power is currently being diverted to papers about the dehumanizing aspects of the colonial project, the meanings and conflicts in the myth of the west as compared to the actual history of the west, the evolution of the Republican party from one of principle to one of money, and last but not least, the role of race in Spanish America in the 16th century. Yes, I've been spending way more time worrying about the past than I have been worrying about the present. I'm trying to keep myself abreast of any big news, but that's the extent. After graduation: more time than I know what to do with! Plenty of time for blogging.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad and I were talking about  urlLink this  and it really is fascinating. How to survive the Spanish Inquisition: go the the furthest outpost possible, go to New Mexico! Amazing.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so he was old and senile, and I didn't agree with his politics, Ronald Reagan was the president of my first eight years of life. When Bush was elected, I wasn't sure if the world would still continue to spin. My eight-year-old self was a bit concerned about this change in continuity. But my 23-year-old self is somewhat perplexed at feeling sad. After learning so much about his atrocious policies in the world, I'm still a bit nostalgic for my youthful feeling that he could do no wrong, because he was the president of the United States. I think at that point I wasn't even sure about political parties, but I knew who the President was. He was the only political figure I knew by name, and it's kinda sad that he's dead. The end of an era.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know you're a closet ABBA fan like me. I did a little dance to Chiquitita when I played Lane the butler in  urlLink The Importance of Being Earnest  in high school. Good times.    Your song is: CHIQUITITA! You are sentimental and honest ... and really boring.      What ABBA song are you?     brought to you by  Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Omigod, I finally found  urlLink Bumble & bumble  online. Now I just have to figure out a way to justify the expense. I really want to get Brillantine, or maybe the styling creme. I used some of my sister-in-law's and my hair was fabulous. Hmm....
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh no she didn't. I just can't abide by this.  urlLink Madonna wants to be called Esther?  I mean, it's a little weird, and kind of an old lady name. Is this how Madonna...er, Esther, is making is clear that she's old? I mean, she is old enough to be my mother (they're the same age), but you don't see my mom embracing matronhood like this. That's my theory: Modonna's trying to make the shift to old lady easier by adopting an old lady name. Esther isn't your grandma's rock star. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Daily candy  has this  urlLink swim cap  featured, which I must call a bathing cap. I'm not sure why, but it makes me think of my grandma's white flower cap she used to wear when I went swimming with her when I was a little girl. She was a PE teacher, and she taught me how to swim, and I learned all my strokes from her too. She was my special grandma, and because of that, I have a deep affinity for all things grandmotherly, and I feel the need to own that swim cap, even though I rarely go swimming and not really much at all this summer, so far.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the opening night of  urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11 , and it was awesome. I feel all kinds of fired up and angry. It really is a film worth seeing, especially for those of us who are sick and tired of being berated and harrassed by the right. The movie is really well done as well. Though at points heavy handed, I cried, got angry and laughed. I think watching the film in Oakland with a large group of fellow liberals worked to make me feel very validated about my beliefs. Also, I felt like all of the reviews I read were way too careful. This is the kind of movie that will get you really pissed off at the scam the Bush administration has pulled. Human lives are at stake, and yet people still want Bush to continue. Are they ignorant of the atrocities and lies of Bush and his cronies? I can't believe people can be so blind.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    hmm...do I really have to grow up?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is is just me, or is  urlLink Bill Clinton  way too pervasive lately? I've seen him on Oprah, listened to him on NPR's Fresh Air, and I've seen ads for his interviews all over the place, notably, Larry King Live. Last week, it was all about the '80s and how Reagan "won" the cold war, and now this week, it's all about the good old '90s and our friend Bill. Remember how everyone had jobs and we had an economic surplus? Oh, and my favorite part of the '90s: complete ignorance about the rest of the world. America was a nice place where the concerns of places like Bosnia, Uganda and Kosovo were very far away and didn't concern my everyday life. I've been feeling nostalgic for then, although I must say Clinton has an unfair advantage over Reagan considering I was born the same year Reagan was elected, so I don't really have a clear recollection of his presidency like I do of Clinton's. I remember 1992-2000 quite clearly on the other hand. That would be my entire adolescence, and try as I might to forget it, my memories are still intact. Oh yes, I was in high school during the Clinton administration.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bush can't even get his cliches right. But when I heard that they'd  urlLink transfered power in Iraq  I sat straight up in bed. I'm really not sure at all how I feel about this, but I know I'm skeptical, and I don't think that Bush has succeeded at any of this. It seemed more like a surprise retreat, as Jon Stewart put it. I always know I can count on the Daily Show to put it all in perspective for me. 
     
    
</post>


<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love entirely non-productive Saturdays spent cuddling with Jerm and watching home improvement shows on PBS. It's been a nice day, but I'm beginning to feel guilty about not reading. Eh, I just do stuff tomorrow. I really need to get the tree down and Christmas things put away.  Now Jerm is looking over my shoulder disapprovingly. Clearly, he doesn't read his email regularly. Jerm now wants me to clarify that he was merely confused, not disapproving... I must leave to help make dinner, so I am properly contributing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate driving home to Oakland every weekend. It's so much goddamned driving, and I hate having two houses with two different sets of stuff. It's so aggravating. Now I need to figure out what books to bring home so I can feel guilty about not getting it done. It's raining and I'm in a bit of a black mood. I think I need to listen to Outkast or Coldplay for the drive. Or I'll just listen to NPR, which makes me feel smarter when I'm home.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My Dad just sent me this comment, which makes me feel better about my whole blogging escapade:  >>BTW, just keep in mind the quote from Ambrose Bierce:  "Egoist: a person of low taste, more interested in himself than in me".  I decided to drop my Medieval Studies class last night after reviewing the reading list, and actually setting my alarm for 7am. And considering how much trouble I had getting up this morning by 8:30am, I think it was appropriate, especially since I barely made it on time to my 10am seminar. I ended up taking way too long drinking my coffee, eating cereal and chatting with Lisa (this has become our morning routine), and had to rush with everything else. I didn't get on my bike until 9:46, and partway to class realized that the quickest route to the Social Sciences building is under construction. Damn! So I had to ride my bike all the way around the quad in the midst of mid-class rush. It was a small seminar of 16 people, so I felt especially conspicuous breathing hard and sweating. I peeled off all of my jackets and sweaters, and spent the first 15 minutes of class recovering, having gotten quite out of shape over winter break. My sits bones and my quads are so sore.  This seminar sound really interesting, though. It's about memory and war, post-1945. It deals especially with the Holocaust, but also with the after effects of totalitarian rule... I think I'm really interested with European and American views of colonialism, and totalitarianism and imperialism often intrinsicly linked. Hopefully I can explore something of this in the class with one of my papers. And it's my New Year's resolution not to half-ass my way through class work this year, and actually take the time to get really into the assignments and enjoy being in school and thinking about such far reaching topics.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Those of you with Salon should read this article... I've wrestling with envious feelings myself lately, even had a few dreams about it. It's just not healthy, and I really like the advice Cary Tennis gives about simply admiring beautiful and gifted people as forces of nature, rather than as someone to compete with. Of course he puts it more gracefully than I ever could.  urlLink Salon.com Life | Ugly duckling   --I want to clarify that I am not envious of my sisters, but rather of beautiful, successful people in general... I had a discussion with Lisa yesterday and wondered why she was asking about my envy of my sisters. It took a few days, but I realized that this post could be misinterpreted. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This website has the snarkiest reviews of tv shows. I just love them. It's awesome.   urlLink Television Without Pity 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm now fully regretting this whole blog thing, but there's something ego stroking to imagine other people reading my words. Soon I may add pictures. All in a further ploy to avoid cleaning my room or doing school work. If I read now I'll be ahead, but somehow that just doesn't feel right. I got a 3.82 GPA without working very hard at all last quarter. This doesn't encourage me to work my butt off for a few more points. But maybe I'll try. Who knows.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Indiebride 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Erm, okay, I guess I've decided to add another mediocre, vain and whiny blog to the world, but what the hell... I've realized I might not mind posting a public journal and share some of my exploits.   I've just started classes for winter quarter... history, history and more history. May sound tedious to some, but actually, this quarter ought to be gratifying. I hope. I'll wait to pass judgement until midterms, when the reading has gotten overwhelming and I walking to exams feeling like a complete ass because of how poorly I've studied. I did that in a few classes last quarter, and then felt like I'd really pulled one over on the TA when it came back with an A-. How the hell did that happen? I didn't even read one of the books. It was so amazing, and I was intensely impressed with my prowess....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm done with the presentation, and since we went first, I'm done for the quarter. Now I can just be a normal class member. I'm not sure how I felt about our presentation, people said we did good, but I felt a bit lame, and somewhat disappointed. I wish we'd had more group cohesion. I think it could have been better.  Now I'm off to the RMS winter encampment. After I posted earlier about not really wanting to go, Jerm got a bug up his butt and got all excited and enthusiastic about going. He even built a rope bed this week, which I must admit I'm a bit nervous about. Apparently it's an old Byzantine design, and is quite clever. I think Jerm has found his niche in the history world: historical engineering. People have been clever for a long time, and came up with some inventive solutions to design and stuctural problems. But now we're going to sleep in it, so we'll see how well he followed the design!  Thanks for the few emails of those of you who've checked this thing out. At some point I'm going to move this to Jerm's server and add some more features, like a comments section. I'll be gone all weekend, I'll write again on Monday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I must admit that I've been following the Paul O'Neill story rabidly. I'm glad that more in the Republican party are admitting that Bush's policies are harmful to our country and that these are scary idealogues, not policy makers. Now the moderates that Cheney fired are fighting back, and the press is loving it. I'm hoping for a Clinton-sized scandal here, but what with the conservative media, who knows. Luckily, I try to get news from the liberal media.... :)  Christie Whitman:  urlLink Op-Ed Contributor: The Vital Republican Center   Paul O'Neill:  urlLink Salon.com: He Cannot Tell a Lie 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate stressed out attempts to meet people. I never get stressed out like this when I work by myself. I can count on me to work hard, at the last minute if need be. The third member of our group is really stressing me out. Of course, she's sick all week, and of course, she's busy all day today... this whole experience is really making me HATE group projects. When and if I am ever an educator, I will never assign group projects. They just drag the everyone down. And of course, her whole excuse is that she didn't think we'd "want to be around a huge walking germ." I would assume that being ill doesn't fully preclude one from emailing! Please. Really.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another foggy day in the valley.... Last night I worked on my seminar presentation with other Liz, but first I spent some of my birthday money at the Gap. After Liz and I had decided that our 3rd member had died and must not have wanted to help, I got a message on my cell about how she had sick all day, but still wanted to help out. This still didn't explain why she neglected to respond to any of my emails, and wrote to Liz once... it's called REPLY ALL, people. When communicating with more than one person via email, you should talk to all of them at once, it just saves time. I really think she had no idea which Liz was which, but come on, we have completely different emails and last names. Is it that hard to tell the difference between F and H? Anyway, I'm just pissy, because Liz and I had our presentation all worked out, and now we have to figure out how to add one more person. If she had just responded in a timely manner, than this wouldn't have been a problem. I sent out the first email on Sunday, and the first response I got was on Wednesday night, after I sent a barrage of pissy emails. If you knew you had a project due on Friday, and that your group had agreed to get in contact over email, wouldn't you check more regularly? Bah. Dumb people make me mad.  And after all the stress, I got a migraine after Liz left. I took a bath and some excedrine, and felt somewhat better, then watched the Bachelorette. I went to read in bed, and felt ill, so passed out promptly... so I had to get up early to work on an assignment, and now I'm behind on my reading. I'm going to try to catch up through the course of the day. Blech. And it's super foggy and cold. My bike will be cold!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have to do a presentation on this book by Primo Levi, and what do you know, it isn't at the bookstore! I'm just beginning to freak out, and it's due by Friday. Ack! I'm also meeting with the study group this afternoon, and I have no idea what I'll do. I guess I should go to the library and see if it's on reserve, and spend the rest of the day reading. That sounds so logical. I guess I should go do that. I think I'll make myself some lunch first, and then head back out.   BTW, I really am hating this bicycling in winter thing... I am freezing on my bike, then the moment I step into the building I am suddenly overwhelmingly hot. I end up peeling down to my t-shirt, and with my current layering technique, that's a lot of peeling! Oh well, it beats being entirely cold all winter, right?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This sounds very intriguing:  urlLink Salon.com Arts & Entertainment | Will Jake and Heath shatter Hollywood's taboo against gay sex? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been a seemingly long day, and I didn't get everything done that I had planned. I'll spend tonight getting a bunch of reading done, and that should relieve some of my stress. I'm going to finish Elsa Morante, Benevolent Assimilation and Under a Cruel Star tonight (extremely over-zealous of me), and then I'll read all of Primo Levi tomorrow morning at the library.   Jerm and I are having angst about ren faire and reenacting again. What makes me reticent about the whole affair is how embarrassed I am to talk about it. I rarely even mention that I do it, and when I do, I'm very vague and go on about how dorky I am. I think if something I do embarrasses me that much, maybe then it isn't the right hobby for me. Besides, it's expensive, and I really want a break. There is so much oddness and sleaziness at faire. Although I must admit that the people I hang with are a fairly wholesome and cool bunch, comparative to your average boothie. It was really fun when I was younger, but it's beginning to lose a lot of it's appeal for me, even though Jerm and I met at faire, and probably wouldn't have met ever if not for the easy social atmosphere of after hours at faire. This weekend is the RMS winter encampment, and I'm conflicted about whether or not to go. It isn't a faire, so should be more fun in some regards, but last encampment I went to was extremely clique-y. There was apparently some drama between some parties (about which I attempt to remain oblivious), and the camp was divided into 3 groups: the hardworkers, the harpies and the borderers. The hardworkers are those that do all of the cooking, get the gear out, and generally organize the event. These are often oldtimers as well, but not always. The Harpies are the funny, catty and somewhat bitchy women who have always been kind to me, and generally give me little to complain about. But they tend toward drama, and are a self-declared clique (disclaimer: if somehow, for some random reason, a harpy happens upon this, I love you all, and appreciate the ferocity you display in sticking up for each other). At the bottom of the hill is the camp of the borderers, who dislike the confines and structures of the traditional RMS encampments, and tend to do their own thing. I call them borderers not because they are in the middle of anything, but because the majority of the group portrays Scots-English Border Rievers, a hardy bunch, from which those of Appalachia, Oklahoma and good old California descend (This is the ethnic group with whom I most identify. I have to admit to my Okie roots.). Then there were those of us who moved between groups, some more easily than others. I have to admit that I often find it difficult to insert myself into social groups, and find it quite uncomfortable. More often than not, I'd rather be in my own group, and be a loner. I hate to be a joiner. It doesn't feel right to me. And it is because of this complex and disorderly social situation that I think I need to take some time out from faire and RMS, until I feel more comfortable about myself and what I have to say. The blog is kind of nice for that. Hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been looking for a pair of knock-off uggs, but those are as back-ordered as the namebrands. Why do I want a pair of these so bad? They would go perfectly with my mini-skirt! I've been taken hold by consumerism! Ack!  urlLink Ugg 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Uh-oh, I think I've found a new show to be addicted to. I love me some Survivor: All Stars!    urlLink CBS Survivor 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is too wonderful. Real life, right here.  urlLink Yahoo! News - Group Points Out Wacky Warning Labels 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Poor Britney. When I first heard this news story I thought it was a joke, but being the media whore that I am, I have enjoyed this entire sad saga far too much. Besides, I really think Britney's pulling one over on us and tricking us to think she's hot.  urlLink Yahoo! News - Mrs. Britney No More 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blech. I have to go to the library to read, but if I go I should really go to the bookstore too. I truly hate college bookstores at the beginning of term. I just can't deal with the insanely disorganized mass of people who don't know what books they want, and where the line is. There are just too many people in too small a space trying to do too much. I attempt to only go very early or very late, to avoid as much of the crowd as possible. Damn you, bookstore!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm and I oversleep every weekend. I didn't even know I could sleep so late before we started dating. We sleep in til 1pm fairly often. That's so late!  I finally got the Christmas stuff down, and I feel good about that, but now I need to go back to Davis and get my room together and go grocery shopping. I'm also thinking about dying my hair darker. I'm getting tired of mid-color brown hair again. Oh well. Got to go, I'll probably type more this evening, though I doubt anyone really reads this at all!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I find myself caught up in our raging consumerist culture more and more these days. I notice when people wear designer clothes, and I covet. I really am desireous of a pair of tall Ugg boots, even though these are terribly faddish and trendy. I want all things designer, but I can't abide by paying full price, and further, I don't have the kind of disposable income to buy all of those sorts of things; I also cannot allow myself to incure debt that isn't for my education. So, I think my goal when I "grow up," is to own a house with a hot tub, and be able to by select designer pieces to augment my discount wardrobe. Right now my wardrobe is almost entirely discount, which should be what a college student should have, but this is not in line with the current styles at my school. I tell myself this: girls who wear designer clothes are either rich, in which case I am both envious of their wealth and sneering since they go to state school, or they, or their parents, are deeply in debt to afford such an expensive habit. It gets me through my day, and makes me feel better about myself. It's good for my ego to feel superior.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm and I had an adventure last night trying to get dinner. We were hankering for some sushi, but Farmer Joe's, on the corner, had pretty meager selection. Normally they have super fresh stuff, but all the good stuff was gone, it being Friday night. So we went out to Whole Foods in Berkeley... that was meager too... so we decided on tempura and teriyaki up at Sparky burger. Yum, fried food.  I rented the Bicycle Thief at Global, and I'm planning on watching it this weekend. Last night we watched Pirates of the Caribbean, and Johnny Depp is so wonderful. I loved it. Tonight we're gonna watch special features since it's not due back until Tuesday. That's all of my boring life.   So far today, we've eaten breakfast, bathed and had coffee. I did some reading and watched some Saturday morning cartoons, and then caught a little of Weird Science. Classic '80s teen movies. I love it. Now we're planning on running errands so we'll actually leave the house this weekend. Should be fun. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't have to got to school today because today was a monday and I have no school on monday... so I came home to Oakland. I've spent the whole day listening to the radio, doing laundry and catching up on TiVo. I need to get on top of my reading next, and write some outlines and plans for upcoming essays. It's been a relaxing day, but I'm sure I'll regret it later. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out what this google search finds:   urlLink Google Search: miserable failure   Then read:   urlLink NY Times: Engineering Google Results to Make a Political Point 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I covet these pants... but the price is too steep; $100 less, and I'd buy them now.   urlLink "A" Pocket Pant Non-Stretch, Pink - shopbop.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After last night's embarrassing internet drunkenness, I spent this morning in the reality of cleaning my messy room. Not only did I tidy, but I vacuumed and dusted, making me feel much better about myself. I've decided that there is no point to living in a messy house: it's harder to find things, I get panicky if people come over, and I don't get to enjoy my lovely decorations and knick-knacks. So I am attempting to be tidy. It's somewhat more difficult over at Jerm's, because we tend to be messy together, and I hate cleaning up after other people (something that I  will  get over when I have kids). When I finish with my room, I'm going to get over my weird issues over dealing with strange people and go to the grocery store and the water store. And I'll spend this evening reading, with a break for either the OC or the Bachelorette... I'm not sure which right now. Damn the TV programmers!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not really sure what I want to say, but I've finished two big martinis and felt like spilling my guts... or maybe I'll just yak on about the weird shit that I'm interested in as of late.   The O.C.: I didn't think I'd like it, but Alexa went on and on about it, so I TiVo'ed it. Now I'm sold. It's like 90210 but less melodramatic and lame. Everyone is so beautiful and shiny, and I can't take my eyes away from their fabulous clothes and hair. And there's the witty banter that has always been a selling point for me, especially since I got into Gilmore Girls. I think it may actually be more interesting than the Bachelorette. That show has too much lame build up and pretend excitement. I don't know if I can do another rose ceremony. But I do rather enjoy Meredith, and think she's much less annoying than that freak Trista. That girl is so done up. It's weird.  Queer Eye: I'm always a sucker for make-over shows, but this show is getting old. It was fun at first, but I'm thinking that the American attention span is over gays and into the rich, i.e. Paris Hilton and Donald Trump, as exhibited by their new reality shows. I think the next big thing will include hot people trying to get famous... oh wait, I think that's the common theme with reality tv. Huh.  The Tracy Morgan Show: Good old situation comedy at it's finest. Consistently funny, without lame plots involving characters getting out of an embarrassing fix. Makes me feel like I can enjoy sitcoms again. I was beginning to lose heart completely, then along came Tracy Morgan. I loved that guy on SNL, and now he's even funnier. And the kids are genius, comic gold. Oh yeah.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back from MLK Jr. weekend, and I didn't get much done for myself. I'm behind on reading, laundry and cleaning, but I had a lot of fun hanging out in costume all of Saturday and Sunday. Jerm and I got up to Camp Tamaracho at dusk, set up camp in the dark, then drove down the hill to get fast food. I always forget how cold it is to camp in modern clothes! My wool dress, gollar and cloak are much warmer than my blue jeans and a jacket, oddly enough--the skirt of the dress does a lot to keep my legs and backside warm! I probably drank too much, but it was fun, despite the Sunday morning hangover. I got up just in time for lunch. Eek.  Then on Monday, Jerm and I went up to Monte Vista to help his folks finish staging the house for all of the realtors coming through today. I cleaned a bunch of construction dust and carpet bits off of a lot of things. Hard work, but very satisfying. I could really see what I was accomplishing. Since I stayed so late finishing up, I cut class this morning, but made it to my afternoon class. I went to the drug store and spent the rest of my birthday money on frivolous things, like hair dye and this cool kohl powder eyeliner, among other things. Kind of a dull post, but I'm feeling a bit lethargic today.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I decided to take a break from my self-imposed suffering and type a little bit. I have three papers to get done by Tuesday, and I'm somewhat screwed. I was supposed to get the paper for Russian history done today, but so far, I've been reading the book it's about all day, because it's longer than I thought. I guess I'll stay up late tonight and get it done, I can turn out 6 pages, right? It's about the Turgenev's  Fathers and Sons  and using it at a primary source to examine the social upheaval of the 1860s as evidenced by the intergenerational conflict. I just need to figure out my structure and I'll be on my way. Then I have to write an editorial for 20th century European history about legacies of WWII, which should be easy, since it's only three pages. After that I'm writing a compare/contrast essay between US Foreign Policy in Latin America and Asia between 1898 and 1920. It all sounds very interesting, and I probably should have put more time into it, but I didn't. It's important to me to get it done on time, so I'll just work my butt off now. At least I didn't put it off to do on Monday. I'm hoping to only have one paper to write and some editing by then. I just need to work hard tonight to get  Fathers and Sons  done. It's only six pages, I can get through it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm really liking John Edwards right now, mostly because he's fairly mainstream democratic and is mildly pro-gun... or maybe he's just not fervently for gun control, because he's from North Carolina. I heard his response to a question about guns, and he emphasized gun safety, which won me over. I gotta get my absentee ballot so I can be relevant.  urlLink John Edwards: Edwards For President 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is pretty cool, worth trying out, and a hell of a lot faster than a lot of other internet quizzes.   urlLink World's Smallest Political Quiz 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think I'm going to write my essay about the EU as a reaction to WWII and the humiliation of the Marshall Plan--it helped Europe a lot, but it also forced the "grand" countries of Europe to see the Americans as saviors and bringers of wealth, harbingers of luxury and style. The EU is the attempt of Europe to regain some of its former cultural, economic and military supremacy. I think I have myself a thesis. Hoorah!   urlLink Europa - The European Union On-Line 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      More for Liz:  urlLink BBC - History - Churchill and the Holocaust 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For Liz:  urlLink NATO Faces Afghan Test, General Warns (washingtonpost.com) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      An interesting article. I've always been a little obsessed with the Olympics, so this caught my attention.    urlLink East German Steroids' Toll: 'They Killed Heidi' 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just looked at my calendar, and my brain is a few days off. I had dinner with Melissa at Dos Coyotes (very tasty, I might add) and I haven't been so spacey in a long time. I've been feeling frazzled all day today, might have to do with that lack of iron that goes hand in hand with my "special lady time." I should probably take my vitamins. But I got a voice-mail from Shannon that I should call her sister's cell, and Regina was all, "why did Shannon tell you to call? She's already in Humbolt." So something happened with my voice-mail, and I didn't get it for a few days, and I feel lame about missing Shannon and Annie again. But that's why you don't rely only on one voice message to communicate with someone. And I had plans with Melissa, so I got all flustered worrying about having to see Shannon and maybe missing Melissa, and in addition I'd agreed to study with Liz in the morning, forgetting about plans with Melissa. Driving home from Oakland in the morning always throws off my day in Davis. Maybe I'll blame it all on that. Although Jerm made a good coffee this morning. It was somehow different than normal, and better. God, I'm such a space-case. Time to work on my essay about a lingering unresolved issue of WWII. Gotta find some sources tonight, and write something tomorrow. This means much blog venting about WWII, I'm sure.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've kind of had an uneventful weekend. We did stuff, talked a lot and got a little drunk. But nothing of note. Oh, Jerm and I figured out that I need new tires. That'll be fun. And I went thrift shopping can bought $3.00 in glass collectables, and Jerm bought a pasta maker. Yep, we lead riveting lives.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Beatlemania Turns 40  That sounds interesting... I love the beatles with a 14-year-old's passion. They make me want to dance and scream and faint, all at once. Oh yeah, they make me want to sing.  Last night I went with Lisa to the Law School Prom and had a good time, but I'm now suffering the effects of dancing in high heels and drinking too much Jack Daniels: my feet hurt like a bitch and I'm a bit twitchy and ever so slightly hung over. Nothing that can't be fixed by a day of reading and a good breakfast. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, it isn't Friday yet, but I wish it were. I spent all of Monday writing my 3 papers, spent Tuesday morning finishing them, spent the day going to classes and turning the papers in, then came home in time to register for classes next quarter (equals cold sweats about my future). After I finished that, I decided/felt guilted/wanted to go to Oakland on Tuesday night because Jerm is spending the weekend in Irvine visiting with Jason. Then, Wednesday was a rush out to Stockton, then hang out and chat with Dad day, then drive home with Jerm having panic attacks (which happens when he doesn't eat) about how he was never going to get all of his tasks done before Thursday. We went to Pleasanton Safeway (which is almost like a costco--gas and everything), and watched two annoying yuppie ladies have a traffic dispute waiting in line for the gas station, one an older lady in a tan Volvo, the other a very well-dressed lady with crazy eyes in a Mercedes suv. They honked a bunch at each other, as the lady in the suv tried to cut in front of the lady in the Volvo. Then the suv stormed away, presumably to park. Then the suv lady walked up to the Volvo lady and told her something (we had our windows open to eaves-drop, but couldn't hear), and the Volvo lady completely ignored the suv lady. Then she saw Jerm and I watching the drama, and looked exasperated. It was awesome. Then we saw the lady in the grocery store, and she was buying healthy choice frozen dinners and wine. Interesting, right? It's almost as good as reality television...oh wait, maybe there's a reason people love reality television, because since we've closed ourselves off from our neighborhood gossip and intrigue, it's our only avenue towards satisfying our inner voyeur. Oh, and I came home this morning and realized I have another paper to write, a ton of reading, and I forgot my essential toiletries in Oakland, so I may well spend the evening driving to and from Oakland. I'm tired of it all, and can't wait for some restfulness... I forget this thing is so public, because I have some scathing analysis of some of the people in my life, but it's never good to publicly display short-term annoyances in a long-term friendship. Or in the case of family, they'll just make your life miserable for a while if you cross them. Oh well, off to school work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, no liberal ads at the Superbowl, but this is allowed?  urlLink Political Cartoons / Political Strikes 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's a real picture, courtesy of open-minded Australians:  urlLink Herald Sun: Janet and Justin get hot [02feb04] 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is so awesome! I watched this yesterday and wasn't sure of what I saw. This some serious scandal and I love it!  urlLink Yahoo! News - Justin & Janet: Out of Control 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate writing thesis statements. Teachers want you to be so clever when you write them, and whenever I start writing a thesis, I sure don't feel clever. And I hate writing a history paper with literature. I get my tenses all confused. What's wrong with a history book? If I'd wanted to write lit papers, I'd be an English major, dammit. Poop. I feel so exasperated with myself and my teachers, and I hate being creative. *sigh* It's okay, I just need to be calm and write... since Jerm isn't here to vent at, I decided I needed to vent here, I promise, as soon as papers are done I be witty and clever again. If I ever was.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Valentine's is such an enigmatic day, with so many expectations. I have to remember Jerm's present and not leave it here, which is likely. That'll be lame. Oh well. Interesting to have Friday the 13th the day before Valentine's day too. I hadn't even realized it until I read Liz's away message. I think I need to call Liz something else... since she's an Elizabeth, I feel like I can get away more with weird nicknames. What about Liza? Or Betty? Bessie? Libby? Lizard-Breath? I always liked Eliza. It's such a cute nickname, with so much more personality than Liz. Liz is a boring, run of the mill shortening of Elizabeth. When I was in second grade I went by Beth. On the first day of school, the teacher asked if we had any nicknames to go by, and I surprised everyone, including myself, and said I liked to be called Beth, even though no one had ever called me that before in my life. I'd only been called Elizabeth, Lizzie-toes, and Lizard-breath. Oh and my dad called me Bob-tot. Not really sure how that evolved, but he still refers to me as Bob... that's right, Alex called me "Bof-boss," which was because of my mother trying to get her to call me Beth-beth, to be cute. Must have evolved from that. I always called myself "Ebis" when I was little, and I guess I still think of myself as Elizabeth. It's such a weird thing, what people call you, it becomes such an important part of how they identify you, but you are able to respond to so many different variants and combinations of your name. In track, everyone called me Liz, and once I was wearing an initial necklace with the letter "E" and someone asked me what it stood for. Elizabeth!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so proud of myself. I just figured out how to add comments to my blog. It was actually very easy, and makes me want to figure out html more. It's not as scary as I thought.  Another good thing: I was freaking out about getting all of my reading done tonight at the library, because the book I need is on reserve, but if you check a book out at night, it isn't due back until the morning... so I ought to get reading now instead of fucking with my blog. Also, now I need to get to the library by nine, but that shouldn't be too hard if I'm devoted. Now you can tell me what you think, although I'm sure no more than 3 people read this. Hee.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink American Apparel  is where I want to buy my next set of basics from. They're completely sweatshop free, and I already own a few shirts of theirs and I love them... I'm going to pay off my credit card this month, then think about getting some new t-shirts and tanks for the spring... and maybe a pair of shorts too. Hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm spent the day with me here in Davis, and I got nothing done, except that we figured out that Shane's Disneyland firefighting discount isn't valid on president's day weekend. Way to research. And I'm not referring to Jerm who discovered this small, but costly issue. So Valentine's Day for Jerm and Liz will include a long motorcycle ride, followed by take-out sushi and a bottle of saki. This will hopefully ensue in good loving and not a migraine, which happened to me once when I had too much saki. We're looking forward to a quieter and cheaper romantic weekend. I admit that I'm sad about the Disneyland mix-up, and only slightly bitter at Shane and Ursula. I know they feel bad, and they're being really nice to get us these super-discount tickets, but I've grown increasingly grumpy with them. It all started with the oatmeal incident. If you're not going to eat something that someone makes for you, tell them when they ask you that you don't like breakfast food. That's all I ask. I hate wasting food so needlessly, and I ended up using all of my organic oatmeal, which I really like, to make a pot of oatmeal that no one but me and Jerm ate. Shane managed a few polite bites, but I seriously wouldn't have made so much if I'd known they didn't like it. I like them and think they're good people, but they can be demanding and picky, two things I try hard in life not to be. Anyway, enough of my rant. It all makes be feel apathetic about life in general, especially school. Oh, and I missed dollar pint night because of my apathy. I'm in the blahs.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink If You Knew Sushi  you were wrong. Check out chocolate sushi. Really. It's amazingly detailed and looks tasty, oddly enough.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoo-hoo! Jerm came over to Davis and told me where we're going for Valentine's Day: Disneyland! Just as I guessed. I'm so excited, and we're going for 3 days with park-hopper passes, which means we get to see California Adventure too. Although you may not know it, I'm a complete Disney-freak. I seriously want to go to Disneyworld for my honeymoon. Really. I even know that I want to stay at the Polynesian Resort, and I want to go for the first week of December--this is giving me ideas about what date to set for the wedding whenever Jerm gets a job and I can make plans to settle down and get my MRS.  Shane, Ursula and Hayden (Jerm's best friend and family) will be going too, which I'm not sure about, but we'll see. They can be a little bit picky, which gets on my purposely easy-going nerves. Hmm. They can be a whole lot of fun though, and hopefully Hayden won't be to shy so we can jump into being silly. He's a fun kid when he's comfortable with you.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm depressed today. I don't know what on earth I'm going to do with my life, and, sorry Mom and Dad, but I don't want to end up like my parents. I'm already too unmotivated and I don't have any job skills and I'm probably just going to be a lazy bum housewife and that sucks. I don't want to be that, I want a grown-up job in the real world, but I just don't know anyone and can't do anything, and I can't see why anyone would hire me. I'm too shy and lame about getting a job, and I am frozen with indecision. I hate looking at my future. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have had two cups of super-strong coffee and I'm feeling twitchy... I'm having trouble even typing, but I'll muddle through somehow. I was supposed to meet to study for a midterm this morning, but I totally slept through it. I should call the girl, but I'm feeling socially phobic and I don't wanna. So there.   This has been one of the first weekends I spent in Davis, apart from Jerm. It's kind of sad. I have a lot of fun spending time with him, and he really rejuvenates me. Hmm. He's so much my best friend, and phone calls aren't enough for me to really discuss our problems, and stuff.... Oh well, enough mushy stuff, I need to study for european history.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just finished watching the grammy awards, and I was quite impressed with the talent of the performers. It was very powerful at times, but maybe only because they honored the Beatles and Johnny Cash and June Carter Cash. Also my two favorite modern artists did well, Outkast and Justin Timberlake, though I'm sad that 50 Cent didn't do as well. He's so authentic.   I'm a little drunky-pants now, but I spent the day meaning to read and generally fucking around. I finished knitting another scarf, this one for Jerm, and I'm getting inspired to try another project, but they don't have the colors I want at the Davis yarn shop. I want hot pink! I spent too long on the internet trying to decide where Jerm is going to take me for Valentine's Day... he's going to surprise me with something, and all I know is that we're going somewhere in SoCal... at this point I'm guessing Disneyland, because he knows how much I love it there and how romantic I think it is. I spent so many angsty teenaged years wishing I had a boyfriend on Valentine's day, and my teen experiences at Disneyland were often painful as well; I remember observing couples my age in lines holding hands and cuddling, waiting to get on Mr. Toad's Wild Ride, and feeling completely unloved and ugly... I had serious self-esteem issues then, and I'm so happy to be with such a wonderful, supportive, attractive and intelligent guy like Jerm when I think back to those years. I want to tell my past self about how much better it gets and how guys are mostly attracted to confidence, and that looks are secondary to feeling good about yourself. I dunno. I had forgotten how easy and fun flirting was until I went to the law school prom. It's fun getting drunk and yakking at guys in random drunk situations... I haven't had so many fairly cute guys just talk to me in a while. It's fun to have that kind of no-strings-attached flirting. I need to be less shy and do that more. Who cares if a guy thinks I like them? It's their issue, not mine, right? God, I'm so rigidly in control of myself sometimes, it's difficult to relax and just not worry so much about how people perceive me. That's really my big issue in life. Mostly I try not to care, but sometimes it really inhibits me, and I won't even go out in public. Thank goodness I've found my future husband, because I don't know if I could be as open and free as I was when I was 19 now that I'm 23... getting too old to party like that any more. If I like you, I'll tell you more about that year in person. For now just know I really grew up that year.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I totally cut my seminar yesterday, probably because with all of my emotional bull, I didn't get enough of my reading done. I was trying to write my response paper for the class, and I looked at the clock: it was 9:50. There was no way I could make it to class on time, and I was literally exhausted, both from lack of sleep and lack of coffee, so I just said "fuck it." I called Liz, called Jerm and went back to sleep for another hour, until Jerm came and picked me up. No car for a week is just dumb. It's not that I go anywhere, I just hate feeling so limited. I needed to go grocery shopping. I think most of my issues were due to lack of caffeine and food.  Today Jerm and I are going to a reenactor's dinner thing called Emperor's Birthday. It's a chance to hang out in costume, eat and get drunk with old-timey faire friends. Jerm is now frantically sewing up his doublet, and I, despite my best intentions, am going to wear what I already have, because I'm super lazy. Who really cares?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's amazing what a few glasses of whiskey and a good meal will do for one's mood. I feel much better than I did at the time of my last posting, and I wanted to let everyone know that it's all good. I have love for the world. Now, I'm going to read in a relaxed and calm manner--hopefully I won't fall asleep, but it's the price I pay for being happy. Ah.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm am seriously having an emotional break down today... maybe I just need to eat, but we don't have any food and I don't have a car today. Oh wait, a flash of inspiration: we have bacon, eggs and toast. That sounds like dinner to me. I need to eat so I'll stop fucking around and feeling so sorry for myself. It's a bad day when I start with the self-loathing and self-pity, but it's full force today. God, every noise Lisa makes sets me on edge. Clearly I'm in a funk. Maybe I'll think about yelling. Hasn't happened yet, though.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out this article about the design behind the  urlLink TiVo remote . Considering how often I've used it, I must say that it's a pretty good design... my only complaint is that it's too easy to hit the channel buttons when watching a buffered show and lose everything you've been watching. It just makes sense to record anything you want to watch.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a midterm this morning, and I got up early to work on it. Last night and this morning I was really grumpy. Then I had to call Jerm and vent. Sometimes have the most uncontrollable rage, it surprises me. I should probably just tell people when they piss me off, but it's too hard. I'm too worried about hurting people's feelings until I snap at them and say really snotty things. So I've decided to go back to bed and get caught up on my reading, so as to avoid my negative emotions. Hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Liz and Jessica came over tonight to study for our history midterm tomorrow, and I think we went over a lot of good information. I'll clarify my position in the morning. But the whole meeting was a little weird. I don't think Liz and Jessica get each other (I know Liz'll read this, but I'm sure she's aware). Liz was in a weird mood that I don't quite get. It's always so weird to me how I can really like two people, and then they have no means for connection. It's like my sisters. Alex and Catherine are such interesting people, and I have an easy time talking to both of them. But they have nothing to talk about. They don't even fight, they just don't understand each other at all, and don't really care to try. It kind of upsets me that I'm the sister they both get along with best. It secretly strokes my ego, I admit, but I so rarely don't get along with people, it just confuses me when people can't just get over it and try to empathize more. I dunno, I probably try to hard too make people feel good, I always look people in the eye, and try to really listen when people talk to me. It just seems like the way to interact with people. It's not even so much as wanting people to like me, it's me wanting people to like themselves. Maybe I'm too supportive, but I try so hard to buoy the self-esteem of my friends. Maybe that's Jerm rubbing off on me, but I like it, and I like giving--as long as it doesn't take away from my happiness. It can just be exasperating sometimes.  Oh, sidebar: for my list Melissa, I remembered: nice(ish) lotion and face care, pens and notebooks, wrapping paper and bows... that's what I can think of now, but I'll keep you posted if I notice any new trends. ;)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is my dad and his company--makes my obsession with history a little more understandable, right?  urlLink Military Specialists for the Film and Television Industry 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've spent all day watching Sex and the City, and last night I watched Queer Eye for the Straight Guy, and it all makes me want to live in a urban setting. I think I should go to law school. I really want to be a young, successful professional. I was thinking last night about it, and it seems like the best option. I finish up with the history degree, start working on the LSAT, and apply next year while I have some weird job. I might be able to talk my mom into helping me find something (she works at a temp agency), or I can look into finding some kind of entry level job, not tell them I'm going to law school, then leave after a year, with more experience under my belt. Hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I've done something that may be scandalous, I've posted links to Liz's and Melissa's blogs--they are my two vaguely tech savvy and internet interested friends who actually are as vain as me and think people would like to read their online journals (I'm interested, but I'm a little bit of a voyuer). BTW, if either of you read this, feel free to post links to my page, even if it isn't "Xanga," which sounds like some weird Brazillian underwear anyway.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Rain and a bicycle do not mix. Ever. If I had it to do over again, I would have worn contacts today, because let me tell you, glasses, which have long been my means of overcoming Darwinism, in fact are a hindrance in the rain. And there was rain today. And thunder and lightening. It was a little bit terrifying. I felt the wrath of God, which is normally something I like to avoid. Maybe tomorrow I'll take the bus. It'll save me some wrath.  Melissa invited me over for dinner today. Very tasty, and good company. Melissa always leaves me feeling more centered. It's nice to hang out with someone who I'm not holding back from... or at least mostly. I don't let most people to get very close to me. It takes a lot of long term bonding for me to feel secure enough to let leash some of my more biting criticism. I'm actually a very judgemental and critical person, but I try to work on that. I'm also easily cowed by people who I think are judging me, and I'm often hyper-aware of being seen by people around me. It's a little weird. I just need to get over it. But often it causes me to spend more time on my outfit and outward appearance than you may think. Interesting to think about. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had kind of a weird weekend. I think I must be too stressed out and dehydrated, because I had migraines on both Saturday and Sunday morning. I felt better by the evening and was able to hang out with Jerm, but it really sucked. Pretty lame. Migraines are so weird and uncomfortable that I can barely describe them. It's like all of your senses are heightened, except for vision and touch. I get weird missing spots in my vision and sense of touch goes numb in my right hand, usually. But then all sounds and smells are overwhelmingly upsetting and nauseating, as is bright light. It's some bizarre sensory malfunction in the brain, and I just don't understand why it happens when.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night after my unsuccessful trip to the store, Melissa called me, and I went to her house to lend her a necklace for her Unitrans prom thing... Liz and Dave eventually made it over and after Melissa shooed us away so she could prep for Mike's impending arrival, we headed to my place for pizza and irish car bombs. I'm still recovering. I haven't been so drunk in quite a while... I seem to get pleasantly buzzed fairly often, but I don't drink like that very often. Anyway, we adventured around Davis a bit and talked a lot... I made overly frank, candid comments about nearly everything, and apologize now for any offensive things I might have joked about.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried to go the the water store and the grocery store, and the water store had suddenly moved. So I decided to go look for it, because I knew vagely where the shopping center it was supposed to be at. I finally got there, and I drove around the center and I couldn't find the water store. And instead of parking and shopping at the grocery store at that center, I suddenly had this horrible feeling of dread and I didn't want to force myself to go in. So I just kept driving until I got home, and throughout the drive (which was rather long), I got more and more freaked out, and I got into my apartment and nearly cried. I'm freaking out. It's really scary, and I feel like a big moron to not feel able to interact with normal people in normal settings. I know I should just go and face my fears, but I think I'll just wait until Jerm gets here tonight so I can go to the store with him and feel less vulnerable. Sometimes I just get so freaked out about going outdoors and running errands. It's really weird, and I probably need therapy. But the idea of calling to make appointments freaks me out even more. God, I'm such a freak.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow. What an utterly unproductive and enjoyable evening. Except for an hour long phone chat with Jerm, I spent the whole evening by myself. It was awesome. I watched what ever I wanted without apologising, and I realized that I really like my own company for the most part. After too long, I get freaked out, but the occasional evening alone is nice to get my bearings and just think my own thoughts. Oh well. I'm going to bed now, and I'll get up early to type out the assignments for the seminar tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Lisa left for Irvine tonight, so now I have the house to myself. Kinda weird, but I dig it. Right now I have my laptop out in front of the tv so I can watch the Bachelorette Reunion and type stuff up. I need to write a paper propsal tonight, and a response for my seminar--for the first time ever I did the reading ahead of time, so I don't have to stay up all night trying to get through the reading. But I might have been more into the reading this week because it was a comic book,  Maus  by Art Speigelman, and it was awesome. I tell you, this was the most interesting and easy reading I've ever read.  So I'm going to start a bigger knitting project than I've ever attempted before, and I think I'm going to do a project diary of it... I'll keep you posted!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is my new blogchalk:   United States, California, Davis, UC Davis, English, 21-25.   :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of my favorite reviewers hated it. I think I'll avoid it, but I'm really not into violent movies anyway, and I don't really think of myself as a Christian. If I ever do, it won't be the kind obsessed with the death of Jesus. It's always seemed like his life was kinda important. Anyway, read this:  urlLink Jesus H. Christ - The Passion, Mel Gibson's bloody mess. By David Edelstein 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's nice to have a day off mid-week. Except that I always plan to get a lot done, and end up getting nothing done. Well, I checked a few things off my to do list, but not much. I really need to figure out what the heck I'm writing for Von Henneberg's classes. I have a pretty good plan for 146B, just need to do a bunch of research, but I'm a little bit mystified by the 102E class. Not sure which prompt to work on, but I'm leaning towards the last, analyzing how films and books deal with responsiblity. Not sure I can milk 8-10 pages out of that topic, but we'll see. Oh well.   The weather was weird today. Aparently we're in for more: Jerm called and said that in Oakland, they had a massive thunder and lightening storm, and while we talked it started hailing sideways, hitting the windows. Sounds exciting, and should hit here in the middle of the night, just in case we wanted to be asleep. It'll be interesting. I hope the power doesn't go out and kill my alarm. I better set my cell phone just in case. That reminds me: Liz, I read that your cell doesn't work, but I don't have your home number... but I usually talk to you by IM, so it probably won't matter. Whatever.  Melissa and I went to the Clinique counter so she could buy some foundation. I almost got some, but it was $24. I thought my Neutrogena tinted moisturizer was expensive at $12, but I guess you get a free gift with Clinique. I'm not sure if it's worth it, but I'm contemplating going there after class tomorrow and getting some for myself. I need think about, because I'm not sure I really need it. What I've really been thinking about getting is a straightening iron and also maybe a diffuser. I'm sick of my hair doing this wierd almost maybe wavy but kinda sorta straight. Or maybe I just need to get better at styling my hair. I'm having hair issues. Maybe I need a hair cut, though I'm not sure at all who to go to. Never again will I go to Suzie. I'm done with lazy, old-lady hair cuts that start off bad and take weeks to settle down, and which I actually never like. Yesterday I actually tried to style my hair and tried to make it lay smooth, but it got all big and voluminous, like anchor woman hair. It's upsetting. I am really considering chopping my hair off again, or letting it get back to pony-tail length, so I can just leave it back all the time. I have really good pony-tail hair. It looks so good and smooth and the tail flips out nicely and everything. I'm so close, but the hair around my ears is still a bit too short, which is annoying.   Nice how much more passionate I am about my hair than about my homework.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got sick of my old title and I'm trying out something more creative... what do you think? Should I go back?   On the weather: you know it's windy when you have dreams about doors blowing open and trees falling down. I woke up this morning to the loud and crashing storm outside, and it was impressive. I went outside later and the parking lot is flooded. Makes me want to stay inside cuddled up near my computer! I've got to get moving on reading and writing today for classes; you'll be able to tell how much work I get done by seeing how much I post here today. I've taken to tagging a link for this site at the end of selected emails and I'm curious how many friends end up here. If you came here by way of an email, type in a comment, I'm interested to see how many people are as nosy as me! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Salon.com | Crashing the party once again : "The Republican Party marches lock step in a campaign against the environment, working people, the poor, civil liberties and world peace"
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a nice evening. After a rather mediocre day, Lisa left to go to the mall, and I thought that I'd have a quiet evening in with a self-made dinner of cous-cous. As I was cooking, Melissa called and asked if I wanted to go to Woodstocks and that sounded so much better than my crappy meal that I said I'd totally come. It was nice to hang out with people I don't really know or really miss seeing a lot. Her friends Ian and Leah were really nice and cool, and it was nice to see people I barely knew. I've also been really stoked about seeing Melissa a lot lately, because earlier we... okay, I, was really bad at keeping in touch. I'm looking forward to going to a makeup counter tomorrow with Melissa too. We won't let the makeup ladies bully us! Oh well. After a beer and two manhattens, I probably shouldn't be writing too much more. Update tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw my old friend Diana at Emporer's Birthday this weekend, and in the course of telling her about how Alex was doing and how upset I am at her, she suggested I write a book about my family drama. I'm thinking this is the next great American novel. It's brilliant, and I can "fictionalize" it all. I need to start writing out ideas about how to write it and what to say. Is this just crazy? Do any of you want to edit it when I get into it? Hmm. I need to brainstorm this more. Also a good excuse to put off school work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Before I go to bed, I want to express guilt to Rosalyn, Holly, Liz and Alex, all of whom I intended to call tonight, but got caught up in bad television. I'm not sure why, but I have a mental block about calling people. It freaks me out a little bit, even though once I get on the phone I talk for hours. I'm just spastic. I miss all you guys in varying degrees, and I'm sorry I'm flakey and have such deep issues about telephones. They just make me uncomfortable. Very uncomfortable. Panicky uncomfortable. I don't like to feel like that, so I avoid the whole issue. It's how I deal with shit: by not dealing with it. It's really healthy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you guys seen that crazy  urlLink Quiznos ad ? I haven't laughed so hard at a commercial in years. Seriously, the screaching spongmonkey in a hat is freaking awesome. And I'm a big geek who reads articles about ads. Go figure.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back to the world of school. Yesterday Jerm and I went to the farmer's market with his sister and we bought a lot of cheap organic food, then got lost driving around Oakland looking at houses, then we tried to find a crepes place downtown only to find it closed. We ended up going to crepes-a-go-go in north berkeley, which was a drive, but yum! I had a banana and nutella crepe. Yummy.   Spent the morning being lovey-dovey cuddley with Jerm, and finally got back. I spent the drive contemplating myself, and almost got hit my a madman in an explorer. I hate those bastards in SUVs. They just want to kill the rest of us while using up too much fossil fuels. Ass-faces. Now I'm hungry and deciding about when to go to the grocery store. Lisa's roasting a chicken, and I want to make cous-cous and salad to go with it. Sounds tasty, and healthier than Lisa's normal offering of mashed potatoes with half-and-half.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night Jerm and I went to his sister's house and had a get together with his sisters and some friends. We finished an entire bottle of kettleone among 6 people all in cosmopolitans, plus wine. I haven't been that drunk in quite a while, but I somehow managed to avoid the hangover. It must have been the massive amount of coffee and breakfast I had this morning. Tried to get some reading done this morning, but I wan't too successful, even though I have two papers due next week and need to get to work on so I'm not completely screwed. I also need to catch up on Elsa Morante, I'm like 200 pages behind and need to read at least 400 to finish the book. At least it's a good book, but it can be depressing to make so little progress when I actually open it up. Oh well. Best intentions for a productive weekend!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't looked forward to a Friday like this in a long time. Except for the stressful drive home, It's really nice to be here, except Jerm and I have been on the phone with Holly for the whole time we've seen each other. And in other exciting news, I switched out my earings for the first time since the December piercing experience. I think I want to get another hole in my ears, and I've been contemplating the belly-button. Any comments/ideas for non-creepy piercings?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent all morning finishing my paper, went to the class for which it was due, came home, had dinner (and the first food all day), then went to see a film for my seminar called "Melena." A movie worth seeing, but some really harsh scenes in there. Now I've got to do a ton of reading before tomorrow, and I'm so behind on the long book that we're supposed to read throughout the quarter. I have to read more than a book a week per class. In 10 weeks, it can get a little out of control, and I am way too into reality television. And my eye is totally infected and red and swollen. I can only hope that my thick lenses cover some of the horror of it. So, long story short, I'm pissy, hungry, tired, and misfigured. Who said college was the best time of their life? I'm glad it's only 4 years.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm nearly 25% done with my paper, but I think I won't relax until the whole thing's written and I have some time to edit. My goal is to have 5 pages done by 9:00, so that way I won't feel too guilty about taking a break for The O.C., which is the most addictive show ever. It's so much better than 90210 ever was, everyone is hotter and wittier. Not sure if wittier is actually a word, but I mean "more witty" when I say wittier. Hmm. Maybe I can begin a new word. Only I need your help! All you gotta do is start using the word wittier as often as possible. Just think of how much wittier you'll be. Oh yes. It's totally, totally good. I'm feeling wittier than I was 10 minutes ago. So many uses. Start now.  Okay, just ran spell check, and wittier didn't even faze it. It's not a new word, and I don't feel wittier any more. Just lamer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I've been to the library, I have research, I just need a clear and concise thesis. It's coming to me, and I may try to write my paper and figure out a thesis after. Sometimes it actually works better, only I need to make sure I stay focused on a single theme, and then come up with what the point is. I'll need to do some serious editing, though. Hopefully, I'll get done early enough to get Liz to read it. We'll see. It always takes longer than I expect. I'm sure I'll keep you posted.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm pretty sure I have a topic nailed down for my paper, so that's starting to look better. Mostly, I'm exhausted from reading too late last night (a school book, even!), and getting up a bit too early. Add in a few glasses of sherry, and I'm ready to pass out. I'm getting up early to make up for the missed late night work. Good night all!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I absolutely loved the  urlLink Chronicles of Narnia  when I was younger, so I'm just hoping this turns out well, like "Lord of the Rings" or "Harry Potter." Anyone else love the books and nervous about the prospect of a movie? It has to be better than the 1980s Wonderworks/PBS version with those horrible centaur effects. I wonder if they'll make it through the entire series.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Dick Clark Sued for Age Discrimination 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once again, I'm feeling ambivalent about this paper and about life in general. I'm just having real trouble discerning a real pattern in any of the research I've done. I don't think I want to watch a bunch of movies by Thursday, so I think I need to pick a better topic. I'm too stuck in WWII. This quarter has been altogether too much about that damn war. Too much synergy--everything I learn in school is so freakin' relevant to current events, it can get aggravating. I love history, but I've gotten so obsessed with the present. I need to know what is happening in the world, like I can somehow predict an outcome to it all. And who even knows? Big themes in history are interesting and all, but then something wacky and terrible makes it all seem pointless, like that 1918 influenza outbreak that killed more people than any of the horrors of WWI. Will it matter if George W. or Kerry or Edwards is our president when the coastal cities begin to flood, and mass chaos ensues? Who knows. I'm sick of analyzing it all, but that's probably the end of the quarter talking. History is my love, I cannot leave it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh Lord, I hate it when my research doesn't go well. I was inspired by analyzing weird comedies about WWII, especially children's movies set in WWII, like Bedknobs and Broomsticks. But I can't find anything else, and I'm freaking out... I have no idea of where to go with this idea and it's horrifying. I know I can pull it together, but it'll be a lot of stress until I get there.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm has been harrassing me about this lame paper for European history since for once he actually read the assignment sheet and freaked out for me. I'm not sure he's comfortable with the idea of me writing massive papers in one day, and of course, he can't mind his own business. Not that I would mention the fact that he's been unemployed since August of 2002, and only just now has started to apply for jobs. If we're going to compare procrastination, I think he's got me beat. He's such a know-it-all busy-body.  But despite his nagging (or perhaps because of it) I'm trying to get to work. Lame, I know. It'll probably be something about the memory of world war II, probably something involving war movies and novels, and how they change depending on the era they were created in. While I was typing, Jerm called, and I may go ahead with the movie theme, and spend tonight and tomorrow watching movies, and tomorrow night and wednesday writing my paper. I hate to cut class, but I suppose this is the time to do it. I need to think hard about that. Any comments about my impending truancy?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday and today have been rather lazy, though very enjoyable. It was really nice to hang out with Jerm this weekend on my turf instead of at his house. It's interesting the differences between the things I take for granted and enjoy here and those in Oakland. The house there is so small that if I watch tv in the living room, I can hear it in the entire house. Here, I can't hear anything from the living room to my room. That means that here I can watch tv and be sort of loud in the morning while Jerm is sleeping. That boy sleeps so much... I feel like an early bird with him, and I don't even get up until 11:00 on weekends. He can sleep til 1:00 pm easily, and this is when he goes to bed at the same time as me. Sometime when he goes to bed late, I get up hours and hours before him... we try to have the same sleep schedule when we're together, but it can get awkward and tiring. But he's so sweet and cuddly in bed, I can't get aggravated.  The Oscars were kind of emotional at times, and I am convinced that Renee Zellweger has sold her soul to the devil, aka the Weinsteins of Miramax. I've never seen someone so smug about an award before. And she looked totally bitter when Lord of the Rings won best picture, it was awesome. I'm totally stoked that Return of the King did so well, they very much deserved it after all that work. It really is the masterpiece of our time. It's better than Star Wars. Amazing stuff.   Overall, a good weekend spent entirely in Davis. I think I have to do it more often. I especially had a great time seeing Melissa, Liz H., and Dave. It felt like old times. Good times. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so tired, but content that I have an entire weekend left ahead, only one more paper and a few finals to write. So minor studying this weekend, and I hope to get work done on my paper. I'm debating whether to bring the computer or leave it and write the paper by hand to force myself to edit. Hmmm.   Also, had a nice time wandering around Davis with Melissa after my long week. I forget how much fun Melissia is, and how I feel like I've dealt with my issues more. She's such a therapist. She's great.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so sleepy. I need to get a lot of reading done for my seminar tomorrow, but that's restful. I need to eat first, and I'm thinking that after a week of homemade quesadillas and grilled cheese sandwiches, take out is in order. Maybe even dos. I haven't been there for weeks, and I'm craving a good old fashioned border burrito. I'm hungry now. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow. I haven't stayed up this late sober in a very long time. I usually manage to get to bed by 2 or 3am when writing a paper, but I usually don't start so late. I need to write my conclusion on this paper, and then I guess I'll go to bed, so I don't go crazy. I need a few hours of dreams, and something to divide one day from the other. Oh well, gotta write the conclusion. It's going to be awfully confused and full of bull, I can tell you that now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm starting to get tired, and I'm only at 4 pages. I just need to keep chugging along, and not let myself get sidetracked (guess what I'm doing right now). Just an update. Hope to post a triumphant post in and hour or less. Hope is key here. Goddamn it's late. It's almost early it's so late.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, now 3 pages into the 6 page paper and I'm doing much better. I've had two cups of coffee, and I'm taking a quick cereal break now. Should be done before 4am, so I may be able to catch a few z's before class. Luckily, I'm so hyped up on caffeine that sleep doesn't sound like a possible activity. Back to work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm freaking out. I have no idea what to write, it's 11:30, and I think I might cry. I know I did this to myself, but oh lordy, this is bad. I don't think I've been in such a bad way for a long time. I just need to breathe, breathe some more and just start spewing out some bullshit. I got an A on the last paper, and a B on the midterm, I can afford a mediocre grade on this thing. It'll be half-assed, but it'll be fine. I just need to chill the fuck out. It's cool, I'm cool, and I can get through this just fine. I just need to establish a plan of action and I can get through it just fine. Whew. I just need to breathe steadily and write, and read it in the morning. I'm fine. I can do this. I've gotten As on papers written in less time and with less preparation than this. It's cool, I can do. Whew. I'm feeling better after my little stream of consciousness self-help talk. Now you know how I'm so calm. I just soothe myself regularly. And breathe deeply. All the time. Also helpful is the slow countdown from 10 to 1, following my heartbeats. Very calming. Okay. Now to write the worst paper ever, but it'll get done, and it'll get turned in on time. That's what counts.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm a little bit freaking out about this next paper I need to write. Luckily, I managed to finish my paper on Vietnam at 7pm, so now I just need to get to work on this next one. Last time, I got an A on the paper, but that time I read the book, this time I don't think I can get through it. Ugg. Well see. I've gotten through harder topics in less time before, I will just have to do the same again. Hmm. May need to do some grade calculation to see how badly I can do and still get a B in the class. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, maybe only American History buffs get the reference, but I thought of it last night when I was wasting time contemplating my knee. Even though I absolutely HATE getting injured, there's something obsessive about dealing with the injury itself. I always want to show people, and I am such a baby! I never nurture myself as much as when I'm injured, which happens more than you might think. The last big injury was the coffee maker incident, which resulted in a very bad scalding burn on my right hand. It sucked big time, but it was an amazingly impressive injury. I wore a gauze hand wrap for a few weeks. But damn, it sucked happening. There's this point while you're healing where the injury kinda hurts, and is still gross, when it is best to show off the injury. I'm already at that point with the knee, so it clearly wasn't the worst injury. But what's worse than the skinned knee is the deep bruising beneath it. I took the entire fall on my knee. Ouch.   Okay, time to stop wasting time thinking about my knee and get to work writing my two papers due tomorrow. I hate that shit.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night Melissa and I agreed to try a "agnostic non-denominational vegetarian thingie" for spring quarter. I basically entails giving up meat, but making some exceptions for fish and poultry. And there will be no giving up of eggs or dairy, as neither of us is really into that. I'm all for only getting free-range, super organic stuff too, and I'm sure that will limit intake due to cost. The main goal is to dramatically increase consumption of fruit and vegetables, and to make those kinds of foods the main source of calories. I'm looking forward to it, because I think it'll be good for me. And it'll be easier to turn down meat that seems questionable in origin. My only worry is giving up bacon, which holds a special place in my Saturday morning breakfast itinerary.   You may have wondered about the nature of the title above. As you all may know, Davis is a bike town, and I don't mean harleys. I've been riding my bike to school with no problems all school year, even in torrential rains, and freezing fog. But my eyes must have been dazzled by the sun on this first nice school day of winter quarter, because I finally had a bike inflicted injury. I'm riding along, minding my own business, and in the course of avoiding people, I run over some of those yellow bump things on the side of the traffic circle. I totally bit it. I land on my knee, everyone around me stops and looks at me and I leap up and say, "I'm okay!" as reassuringly as I can. I roll up my newly torn pant leg, assess the damage, and limp towards the bike racks. I wanted to cry, but worked really hard to maintain control. My knee is tore up. It bled all through class, and then I gingerly rode home, terrified I might do something dumb again. But I made it home, washed my knee and changed. I took the bus to my later class, and inspired by Liz's example, I walked back. It was all very nice, but damn my knee hurts. It's super bruised. I mean to post a picture of it tonight if I can figure out my camera phone thing.   Also, I'm freaking out about all of these damned papers I need to write. I'm going to see how much I can skim the book for Russian history, and then I'll write out a strictly structured paper about Viet Nam. I'm sure I'll whine a lot about it here, so hopefully all will be well. Okay, I need to outline both papers tonight and see how much I can get written ahead of time. It would be amazing to get enough sleep before the due date of a paper.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been having trouble coming up with clever titles for my posts... but I'm sure I can keep it coming. The wit just never ends. Uh, yeah. So I dunno why I'm even posting, just felt the urge to type out my emotions and drama. I should be reading, but I'm distracted by the idea of blogging. It's actually an interesting book, just got to get further into it. It's Tolstoy's Resurrection, for my lame "Fall of the Russian Empire" class. That class can really blow. Not really sure why, but I think it has a lot to do with the aged history professor. He's such a cliched stereotype, it's not even funny. Normally I really dig history professors, because they're a lot like me, only more devoted. But this guy is seriously from a different generation and it's very apparant in class. He's such an old man.   I think my main weight loss plan is to eat smaller portions and drink in place of candy and desserts. And if I only drink mostly hard alcohol drinks, there'll be less chance of beer gut. Also, I think I'm going to try to ride the old bike on more errands, and start rationing my tv time. It's a huge timewaster and butt grower. Seriously, it's a bad scene: it robs me of momentum and makes me forget that I'm not interacting with human beings. Also, I need to limit my internet time, but I'm fully addicted. I'm waiting for the day when wi-fi covers the world and we all have hand held, *cheap*, or even free, access to the web always. It'll be creepy, but awesome. Then I'll never have to cut my umbilical cord of the plethora of information.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know it isn't actually the best thing to have two papers due on Thursday, but I'm stoked about one of my papers getting postponed. Now I can spend tonight reading like I should, and I can figure out what I really want to write and not pump out some crap thing. Yay. Now I'm going to make something interesting for dinner... I'm thinking mexican food.  In other news, I spent this weekend feeling overweight: Jerm's already excessively thin sister lost 15 pounds going vegetarian. She's like a size 2 now, and she's my height. I used to be so thin, and ate whatever I wanted, and now that's catching up with me, especially my terrible lack of physical activity. I just need to work out more and eat better... easier said than done, I know. And please don't tell me that I'm too thin anyways, because I don't feel as healthy and strong as I used to, I'm not as connected to my body anymore, and I think once I regain some of that, I have a much healthier body image. But damn, that girl's weight loss is enough to give me an eating disorder. If it weren't for my lack of will power, I would totally be anorexic. Except that whole not eating thing sounds uncomfortable. And I have enough issues with vomit that I think bulimia just wouldn't work out. I think I might have to go the obsessive exercise route, which sounds better, because people won't think I'm sick, and I can feel superior to the weaklings who don't eat, right?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm and I have made up and I'm amazed at how angry I was earlier. We had a big fight right after I posted my thoughts, all about our time management issues and how he tries to control me and my time too much, and I get too lazy and unmotivated about papers and then get sick when we have time together. But we washed my car together, which was covered in crow shit, and we both felt better about getting something productive done. Now he's gonna go for a run with his brother-in-law, and I'm gonna work on my lame-ass paper that I'm conflicted about. I'm just going to pick a topic and outline the entire thing tonight, and then we'll hang out with Kier and Trina and have fresh pasta. Now to work....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow. It is such a beautiful day, and it made me happy when I got up, but Jerm gets all conflicted and guilty on nice days because he thinks he has to be outside to appreciate it, and then thinks about all of the things he *has* to do, and ends up making me feel like shit. I was just looking forward to hanging around the house with all of the doors open and working casually on my paper that's due tuesday and hanging out laundry on the clothesline. Why does Jerm always have to make lazy days into this huge fucking ordeal? Who the fuck cares? Why do I have to feel guilty and bad because he can't fucking make up his mind? Sometimes he's can be so damned dramatic and pathetic and it pisses me off enough to swear in writing. And since doesn't care enough to read this, he'll never know how much I rant about him.   Sorry, end of my bitching and moaning about my relationship, which is generally very good. I'm just having a particularly bitter moment, since I was just made to feel guilty for having some "alone time" and taking a freaking shower. I mean really, WTF? I'm sorry I don't drop everything to be selfless the moment Jerm wants me to. Okay, really, I'm done. Anyone else want to rant about their significant others/dating in general?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After I dropped Lisa off at the airport, I drove home to Oakland. There was traffic in Berkeley, as always, but I got though it and came home before Jerm. He was at his mom's house, and they got me to pick up Jerm's sister and we all had dinner there in Orinda. It was pretty tasty, but I was so tired after my night of 3.5 hours of sleep (all in daylight), that I was pretty woozy. Jerm and I came home and went to bed by 10:30pm, which I think might be a record for us. And then we slept till 10:00am. It was awesome and I feel well rested. Jerm and I read and screwed around for a while, then we went to a park in Alameda and just laid out on the grass and ate and talked. We watched the sailboats out on the bay, and I realized how lucky we are to live in such a beautiful part of the world. I really do love northern California, especially the bay area. It's just so pretty and pleasant. I need to do some laundry and tidying around the house, then I'm going to make a chicken soup for dinner. I'm feeling very happy and domestic today. Maybe it's all the knitting. I think the only thing that would make me feel more domestic would be if I were knitting baby clothes. But that's a while off. Jerm and I were talking and I think 26 is an ideal age for that. Oh, fat little babies, with pink cheeks, blue eyes and baby breath. Babies smell so good and sweet... I just need to hold out for a few more years. Hmm. Speaking of which, I need to go take my pill. Eek!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I stayed up way to late last night, or rather early, since I saw the sun rise. I know. Way too freaking early/late to be awake at all. I finished my paper, and it's all turned in and everything. I'm just going to pack my bag for the weekend, take Lisa to the airport and go home to Jerm. I think everything will be okay. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The sprinklers are going, the crows are cawing... it's early morning, and I'm still up. I've hit a road block in my writing, as I wrote down a quote and forgot to put the page number, and now it seems like it never existed and I hallucinated the whole quote. But it's really good and I need to cite it, damn it! Crap, and I need another movie quote... whew, just need some food and another cup of coffee, I can get through it, I got nothing to do today but sleep like a crackhead who stayed up all night, except replace the crack with coffee. Okay, just a few more hours till sleepy time. Oh, and who knew there were so many trains in Davis at night? I've heard so many, and I think the tracks are fairly far away. But I think sound travels better at night. Oh, the crows are getting loud, I think the sun might be rising. Weird. Ok, back to writing....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Methodists Put Minister on Trial for Declaring Herself a Lesbian  Hmm. Need to email this to my mother, as she is a Methodist. And, if you don't know much about me, in high school I was *very* active in the UMC Youth Fellowship, and even went to a convention in Knoxville, TN. I almost decided to become a youth minister. Oh, and I was pro-gay marriages and pro-choice even then, before you think I was a crazy Christian coalition girl. Those people scared me even then. I'm all about liberal Christianity that's about love. I always thought that was the point. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My back hurts, and I'm tired, but it's what I get for procrastinating. My solace is that I don't have to do anything but turn this paper in, drop Lisa off at the airport, and drive to Oakland, have a drink and go to bed. Heck, I'll probably throw a nap in there somewhere, just to mix it up a little bit.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's what I'm writing my paper about, it's moving right along, I've selected quotes and scenes. All I need to do now is write the paper and try to ignore the screaming baby next door. Ah, the joys of married student housing. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just trying to cram in a few last facts before my final exam in European history 1945-present. I just need to outline some more and it should all come together. After the exam I need to write my 10 pager for the seminar, which shouldn't be too bad, considering I'm very familiar with both of the sources I'm analyzing and I already have an outline. But still, we'll see how it goes. I'm sure I'll post often in despiration.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In honor of my favorite drinking holiday, a few  urlLink facts and misconceptions  about the weird Irish holiday. And yes, I'm a little bit Irish, even though my birthday isn't anywhere near this day. But, oddly enough, this is Melissa's birthday, and she isn't Irish. How can it be? Happy Birthday Melissa!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know you wanted to know the  urlLink history of car cup holders . It's more interesting than you might think. Really, I think you might like it if you try it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i had a nice time hanging out for Melissa's birthday. It was fun, and I was glad to spend more time with Dave and Lisa, two people who I sometimes neglect. Also good to see Liz, and attempt to comfort her in the face of her burglary. That's so scary that it makes me paranoid. I checked all the windows before I went to bed. Also, in other scary news, there was a spider on the dashboard of my car and I almost had a panic attack. It was so big and white and I just could feel it crawling on me. That spider heeby-jeeby thing has been getting worse lately. Or maybe it's just the whole driving/trapped thing that terrified me about this spider. Thanks to Lisa for calming me down. Man, I was freaked out. Okay, I'm sleepy now, so off to bed. Have a good dead day to all of you approaching finals!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm and I just had a big talk about "the future" (in quotes, because as far as I'm concerned it's an imaginary place created to scare us to join in the alienation called work), and we talked about our future, and what we want to do with each other and our careers. I just don't know how I'm going to graduate and join the workforce and be a grown up. I have no fucking plan, and I don't know what the point is. This whole college thing seems like another vast holding pen to keep an entire age group out of the work force. And thanks to the loverly economy we live in, I'm not going to get hired immediately out of college and into a high paying bullshit dot-com job. Goddamn you late 1990s! Why did you have to leave us poor kids in 2004 with such beautiful visions of what would happen if twentysomethings ruled the world? Well, we saw it, people lost a lot of money, and you can bet your ass that wall-street won't let it happen again. So, lately it's been looking like elementary school might be a good place to teach. Hell, I'd get paid more and get better benefits than some poor adjunct professor in history with a Ph.D. It makes 2nd graders seem more appealing somehow. And if they act up, I'll be bigger than them, unless there's some poor hormonal kid. But the kid'll be a freak anyway, I won't have to deal with him. He'll go to the tough but nice special ed. teacher that everyone secretly fears because no one wants to be a special ed. kid. There was always something a little off about the kids in his class. They were weird, and would scream for no apparant reason sometimes. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent this weekend watching movies for my various classes (yeah, sometimes it's good to be a history major, especially when movies count as "sources"), and hanging out with Jerm. Nothing too exciting, no big fights or anything special. Just nice sunny days, some knitting and some studying. Oh, and a lot of sleep. A whole lot of necessary sleep. Man, last week killed me. This week ought to be somewhat more relaxed, despite a final and a paper. It won't be too hard to get through.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this looking for booze recipes, and it's pretty cool. I need  urlLink help  transistioning to that post-college thing, though.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One last post before I disappear for a while during my trip to Disneyland. Holly and her weird friends came by for breakfast before they left for Seattle. That was nice, though brief; I'd have liked to spend more time with Holly. After they all left, I sat down to watch Arrested Development (awesome show). There's been construction next door, so I haven't been as atuned to weird noises as normal. I thought I heard someone at the door, and I was all paranoid, so I wasn't sure if there was really anyone there. I look out the windows and out front, and I don't see anything. But a few minutes later I see some guy going in the back gate and going past the backdoor. And then I get brave and open the door and ask "What's going on?" Of course, this is through the screen gate, so I have bars in between us. I'm all ready to yell at some guy prowling around the house, but the landlord hired him to look at the tree in the back that needs pruning. Sounds fine, but he gave me a seriously creepy feeling. I mean, my eyes are up here. Please look at them, not other parts of me. So he's creepy, and I called Jerm, and he's totally dismissive of me. I honestly closed the door after talking to the guy and I was shaking. I haven't been so scared in a long time. So I'm still bitter at Jerm not comforting me or even trying to make me feel better. He just treated me like I was a fool for even getting scared that some strange, creepy man was wandering around our backyard. He made me feel like a dumb woman.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm has a job and now we can celebrate! He starts the Monday after I go back to school, so timing is perfect too!! I just gotta take my final, then I can call everyone and share the good news. So happy! And he didn't have to take a pay cut, he's making the same as he was at Tut. I'm engaged to a senior engineer at ... hmm, I have no idea what the name of the company is. All I know is they make some kind of weather computer things and they're in Hayward, so Jerm won't have a horrible commute. He's very relieved that he didn't have to get a crappy job in San Jose. That's a sucky commute. Whoo-hoo! Jerm has a job! It's really nice not to be engaged to an unemployed engineer anymore. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm studying for my last final of winter quarter, "Twilight of Imperial Russia" or Russian Rev as I refer to it, even though we only studied the actual 1917 revolution in the last two classes. The thing is, I've been an incredible slacker in the class. Like, I never bought the reader, nor have I gone to the library to check out any of the reserve books we're supposed to read. And both of the papers I wrote at the absolute last minute, and on the 1st I bamboozled the TA into giving me an A. I love it when the history TAs appreciate my skills of an artist. I have bs down to an amazingly fine art. Thank you ISIS (integrated studies in systems); those three teachers and their full on bs taught us students some impressive skills of bs. I don't think I would have done so well in college had I done traditional high school... hmm, maybe I should go back to the high school and visit those teachers and tell them how their bs class made me a better college student. Except I might say it nicer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm just got a call from the place he just finished interviewing and they told him to come in so they can make an offer. They want to hire him! I'm so proud of him, and I'm really glad that we'll be able to afford rent next month. Whew!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just don't care. It's awful. I copied out my final and I could have cared less about what I wrote or what grade it will get. I just want to be done with finals and I want to go to Disneyland and start a new knitting project. I need to knit a scarf for Fi, and after that I want to make a pink and black striped scarf for Holly. At some point I want to make a pink scarf for Liz too, so I'm getting mighty back logged. I also want to make myself a poncho. Here's a  urlLink link  to the pattern. I think I want to make mine in either hot pink or maybe something more off-white and pale blue, to be more summery.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      An awesomely hilarious excerpt from this article all about the awkwardness surrounding breastfeeding and looking at hot boobs that happen to have a child hang off them.  urlLink Salon.com Life | Breast intentions : "'I had the hot-mom fantasy thing going for a while,' says a friend who prefers to remain nameless for reasons that will become clear in the next sentence. 'When my wife got prego, my fantasy turned to lactating breasts. I waited nine months, then finally convinced her to let me try it. I started sucking and at first didn't get anything. I put all I had into it and -- bam! -- milk started streaming like a small hole in a hose right to the back of my throat. It startled me -- the taste was super dry and didn't taste quite like the milk I was expecting. There goes that fantasy.' "
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate that damn class. I want to take an honest to god test, not some cop-out cheating paper. I don't think that should be the point of a final exam. Exam being the key word. If Oropeza wanted a paper, she should have just assigned one, and then graded us in her super non-specific, un-forgiving way. I like her as a lecturer, as a person, but the woman cannot write essay questions worth a damn. And the sad thing is that she thinks she's giving us a super juicy, interesting topic. I'm sorry, but if the entire class doesn't follow your line of thinking, maybe it isn't the class's fault. You know? I'm just saying.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Read this: urlLink Salon.com | New rule    Now we can all agree that Bill Maher is both brilliantly hilarious and a complete and total a**hole.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today's sort of been a waste. I flaked on two Jessicas in one day, but I feel like I redeemed myself slightly by emailing an outline of the essay to Jessica #2. I've said it before, and I'll say it again, I'm such an a**hole. Really.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My belly hurts and I don't want to study. I want to go to Disneyland, and not suffer through anymore finals. I'm a huge flake. I hate interacting with people. Oh, and did I mention my tummy hurts? I'm grumpy and stessed out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And  now I look into the terrifying propect of a second week of finals. Somehow taking a weekend off between finals has made me dread the next batch. I'm ready for vacation, not more intense work. Belck, I hate final exams.   I'm planning on getting up early tomorrow and heading out to Davis to be a good student and study. I think I may go to the mu with a blanket and study in the sun all day. Sounds lovely.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blech, my head cold has gotten worse. I guess Jerm and I are going to  urlLink the Crucible  with Fi, which should be interesting, then we're talking about going yarn shopping and then going to a swap meet with Kier and Trina, or maybe  urlLink Urban Ore . Hopefully my illness won't make the whole outing miserable.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a decent first day of classes, and I met Jason and Lisa's friends Zeb and Carlyn who were very nice, but I still can't get over the Alex pregnant thing. I'm seriously on the verge of tears about the whole thing. Luckily, she called me back tonight, so even though I was out, I know she's alive and I can still get ahold of her. Melissa suggested this may be an elaborate April Fool's joke, but I highly doubt that, since my parents are really disorganized, and too nice to pull that kind of shit. I'm sad though. It's just not right.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Back to school in the morning, and the quarter begins with some seriously upsetting news: my Jerry-Springer-worthy sister is pregnant. My younger sister. She's twenty and living with a 48 year old man who betrayed our entire family. And that's not even all of the drama. Although this might seem like something I made up for a good blog story, it's appallingly true. To add to my astonishment, I'm also indignant that I won't have kids first. My plan was perfect, but clearly that was the problem: it was planned. I'm seriously sick. Oh, and to make everything better, that dickwad she lives with is constantly on the internet (probably cruising for 20 year olds, now that he's gotten his fat and pregnant), so I can't even talk to her. Why is she so horrible? Why can't she just be rational and normal? Why does she have to be so frustratingly self-destructive? It's called a condom! Use it! WTF!?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have a more postive outlook on life today, though I'm not sure why... everything's still in the same crappy situation it was yesterday. Oh, I know, I slept in an extra half an hour and had some awesomely vivid dreams, one part included Jerm which I won't describe in detail. Suffice it to say I miss the guy, and I'm looking forward to the weekend. It's amazing how dreams can set your mood for the day. When I have stressful dreams (like about how lazy and unmotivated I am), I tend to have stressful, upset days. The other night I feel like I had a dream that is helping me deal with my sister. I was in the shower with Jerm, and then Alex tried to push into the bathroom. I was upset because she had just walked into our house, and wouldn't even wait until we were done to demand my attention. I had to tell her to go away, and that I would deal with her later, then I shut the door. I think that's exactly how I'm dealing with Alex in my head: she upset me for a while demanding my attention, but I've put my stress over her pregnancy aside for the time being, and I'll make it wait until I'm ready. And I think that is the best way for me to deal with all of this now. I can't cry anymore, or I'll get even sicker. And I really don't think telling her how disappointed I am and how horrible I think James is will help at this point. She won't listen anyways, and she'll probably think I'm being vengeful or something. She never listened to my advice or opinions before, so I can't believe she will now. I'd like to have a real heart to heart with her sometime, but we rarely see each other alone anymore, and I don't like talking that deeply over the phone. We need to meet sometime on neutral gound, because I'm uniquely uncomfortable at her house, and I'm not sure that either of my residences are any better for her. There will be a family event this weekend for easter, so maybe we can talk then. Although if James is around, I doubt she will be alone at all.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been spending way too much time watching  urlLink Star Trek: Deep Space Nine  on Spike. Man, I love that series. So much political intrigue. I love it. I wish Enterprise weren't so cheesy. The horrible rock ballad intro makes me want to wretch, but the pictures are cool; I think that's the trouble with the show. Some things are terrible, but there are still a few remnants of Star Trek coolness that makes you want to check in on the crew. Damn them! I want my fully obsessive, addictive Star Trek back.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've written a few research papers on the LSD culture of the 1960s, and my "anecdotal research" confirms a lot of this  urlLink article . It's really interesting stuff, I might have to actually forward it to some friends, instead of just relying on the blog to pass it around.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My nose is still running and my eyes are all teary, and every so often I have overwhelming coughing fits. To add to all that, my ears are plugged up and I can't yawn it away. It's gross, and I haven't been feeling the whole blogging thing so much... just to explain the short, germ-infested posts. I'll post more when I feel better.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now off to some drug assisted sleep... no more coughing, no more runny nose. And maybe my ears will unplug, and the sneezing will take a rest. Hopefully, knitting tomorrow, but I've been disorganized with this whole sick thing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm still working with this cold, but I think I'm getting somewhat better. Jerm started his first day of work today, and I hope he wasn't late! Alex and James dropped by on Saturday night, which was rather awkward, and now I'm feeling even more judgemental than I was before of their whole relationship. Then Mom came by before her accordian class on Sunday, and we chatted about what a nut Alex is, and about Easter plans. My Aunt Jeannette is coming up from LA to visit, and I'd like to see her, so I may be driving to Stockton next weekend, or there may be a dinner thing at my Aunt Rebecca's house in the Bay Area. Now off to class.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm toying with the idea of getting a pack of these  urlLink anitpantis . I get so grossed out when I see thongs hanging out the back of girl's lowriders, so this seems to be another great option, and more sanitary than going commando!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was so brave today that I went to the History Department, Kinko's and Navin's all in one big errand. Even though I put it off all week, I finally did it and now I'm exhilarated and just a little bit proud. I think I just need to make one excursion a day, and I won't feel so freaked out and sorry for myself. I think I'm really working on this whole fearfulness thing. It's really pulling me down, I just need to push myself and challenge my fears more regularly.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dunno. Feeling vaguely unhappy and down, and I have been all week. But at least I put on a vague semblace of happiness to the rest of the world. Christ, Jerm barely knows how down I am... or maybe he does. I talked to Holly for a long time on the phone last night, and we had a great talk, bitching about the various misdeeds and mistakes of Alex. I don't know anyone nearly so self-destructive as that girl, and she's in such intense denial about it all. It seems like she has no concept of how her actions affect other people at all. Oh well. I just need to tell her again that I don't like James, I think she's wasting her life with the son of a bitch, and she really needs to get over her whole "I'm a victim" bullshit. I will not listen to her talk about how poor she is any more. For Christ's sake, she's 20! No one has a ton of money when they're in school, but I suppose she'd have more if she didn't have an old man leeching off her. Okay, enough.  In other news, this weekend's picnic day, and I hope it doesn't rain. Jason is already back and it sounds like he and Lisa are having a "serious discussion." It's kind of a weird time to be a roommate. Jerm's coming tomorrow, and I'm really looking forward to seeing him. I've been really clingy lately with this whole sister thing, and he's finally starting to see that maybe Alex isn't just making a short mistake with her dating choices. I think he now understands and appreciates the family's horror about it all. My mom and baby sister are coming on Saturday, and I'm really looking forward to having them see the campus and my apartment more. They came to Davis last year when Catherine went to sections with her 100M hurdles. Apparently this year she's even faster and doing better than ever. She even knocked my old track rival, Jenny, off the record trophy. I'm glad Catherine's better than that snobby twit. It's also good to be in college and not high school anymore!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My aunt was totally into these  urlLink shoes , and now it looks like they're back... too weird. I remember thinking they were so dated and wishing she would move on. I wonder what she would think about this? Hmm. The only trouble is that they're super weird pseudo-Native American, and that reminds me WAY too much of my childhood summers in New Mexico. And not in a cool way, but in a "let's move past this southwestern theme thing" kind of way.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got motivated about graduation after talking to Liz, and though I'm not sure I'll be completely ready to graduate by June, I will for sure be done by Summer, so that means I can participate in the commencement ceremony. So I've applied for both, but I need to get my IGETC sent in to the right office, so I'll need to see about that. Anybody else have commencement anxiety?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm just tired and out of it today, and I don't really have much to say about things. Maybe later I'll post something worth reading. But I'm still around.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes it pays to blog. I get to be one of the first to try out google's email system. It's kind of interesting to use, and completely different format than other email systems. I'm really digging it so far, although there are a few bugs that need to be worked out. I just need to tell them the things that are annoying, so they can be fixed!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just found this  urlLink awesome site . I think I may need to set my hair and get the pompadour going!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, you know you're a geek when you can read an entire  urlLink article  exploring the theories behind the shift between Klingons in the original series and in Next Generation. If you weren't sure before, I truly am a super geek.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There were too many people here this weekend, and my room was a sarcophagus for all of Saturday... well, if you you want to know, maybe you should ask.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm looking forward to going home and seeing Jerm this weekend. I have a ton of reading to catch up on though! But should be a good weekend regardless. Be back on Monday.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so I'm a dweeb and decided to look up what the hell a  urlLink dirty sanchez  was. And now I know. I think it sounded cooler before I knew. Ew. No, I mean, I would kick a guy's ass if he ever pulled anything remotely like that. The whole idea of it makes me violently, maliciously angry and vengeful; I think I won't go into detailed possible reactions. Ew, ew, ew.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I wrote a six page paper this morning. It came together amazingly fast, although not fast enough to go to my first class. Liz! Help me! Okay, I'll email you or *gasp!* even call you. So I used to be able to write a 3-4 pager in like 2 hours, and my record for a 5-6 pager is about 5 hours... okay, did the math, not counting reading, I wrote it that fast. It doesn't really beat my old record: last year, spring quarter--the paper was due at 4:40, but first I had to go to section that morning at 10-11. I got off the bus, came inside and started writing, having only mildly skimmed the reading. But the best part is that I got and A- on it, and the TA totally used my paper as an example of how to write a well organized paper. I'm telling you, organization will get you by when you've fucked off on everything else. Really and truly. Either I'm a great writer, or my TAs are shmucks. And since I like all of my TAs (except for the ones who give me Bs) I'd like to thing that I'm a great writer. Makes me feel better about myself at the very least. Well, until I get the paper back!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been talking a lot to my dad about the whole drama, and while we agree, I can't help but feel more and more depressed about Alex and her idiocy. My dad forwarded me an im discussion the two of them had (he asked if this was alright first, and I agreed), and I am just amazed at how self-righteous and illogical she is. She basically told my parents that they couldn't see her baby if they don't accept James. And my dad is right, he knows it will not be a good scene if they were all in a social situation together. I completely agree with my parents, but I feel so pulled at by Alex to take her side. And when I'm hesitant or uncomfortable with anything, she refuses to acknowledge it. I'm really unhappy about feeling stuck in the middle, and I feel like I've given way more than I've gotten.  Oh well, had a long phone conversation with my dad, and I'm feeling better. Hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man. I just can't get over what a fuck up Alex is. I just can't. Why does she insist upon disrupting the lives of everyone around her, including herself. I just don't understand why she has to be such an ass all the time. It is really getting to be a hassle, I can't deal with having to pretend everything is all right with her or something.   I've been thinking more about the argument we had about politics the other day, and I'm thinking, maybe it wasn't just about politics. I think it was the only thing I felt free and justified about calling her on, and the only thing I felt right about having a conflict with her. I think I need to tell her how I feel, in person! I haven't seen her for so long, and all this is weighing way to heavily on me. I wasn't a jaw clencher like this until recently. I think I hurt myself last night in my sleep, because my jaw still hurts. I just don't know. I'm terribly upset and distraught about everything, because I love her and I hate to see her be such an ass. It's really getting harder and harder to deal with every day. Ow. My jaw hurts. I just need to use more of those relaxing, mind-numbing substances... oh booze. You are my best and closest friend that makes me feel better when I'm sad. And that other stuff is nice too, because then I'm at least more philosophical about the whole thing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      But I'm working on not being so flakey. In fact, I'm working on a paper due on Thursday, but suddenly it's gotten very warm in Davis, particularly in our apartment. So the work ethic is not so much for the moment. But I have to finish the book, then write a paper... the plan is to get the book done today and the paper done tomorrow, and hopefully I'll have time to get through the book about Spain too. But first, Black Elk Speaks and his impressions of Americans... hmm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's an interesting article about my new favorite web thing:  urlLink Gmail . I'm really liking it so far, although I'm still working on getting all of my email transfered from my old yahoo address... for some reason yahoo groups doesn't like my gmail address and won't verify it so I can switch my lists... poopy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      How do you sleep at night? No, not that, but this  urlLink article  about the different ways people sleep is intriging. I most often sleep in the starfish and fetus positions, myself. What about you?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, now I've put off everything all week, and I told myself that it would all get done today. But I'm not doing it. I got up and watched some of the Rumsfeld hearings, which were enlightening and disheartening at the same time. I was glad to hear that old bastard Rumsfeld give an unequivocal apology, and I also enjoyed watching McCain and Kennedy scold him for being unclear and secretive. While I was zoning out into deep political reverie, Lisa came back from her final way too early. Apparently she upchucked in the middle of the exam, and they sent her home. Hmm. After she went to bed, I went to class, only to discover class was cancelled. That happens so rarely at the UC that I was somewhat disbelieving. But I can't complain. I went home and watched some more of the Rumsfeld hearings, and mailed a letter (and I think our neighbors are all bastards. I smile at them, and they just look at me like I'm nuts. Shiteaters with screaming kids and nasty garbage on their step. And they leave their shoes all around the front door. I'm quelching an urge to steal a pair and put them in the trash heap across the parking lot.), attempting to scowl at the neighbors who I hate. Okay, so I'm dealing with a lot of rage today, and I have for the past few days. I think I need some alone time. I might make a drive out to Vacaville and shop or something. I'm just tired of being home and not getting stuff done. I think it's that I make myself a little crazy when there are other people around. I'm just feeling sorry for myself. I need to finish a reading and tidy the house before Jerm and Trina get here tonight. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I'm still dealing with my deep ambivalence about growing up and having to begin a new part of my life. I know I need to be ready for it, and I'm really lucky to have Jerm support me through trying to find the right career and life path for myself. See, I feel really comfortable and confident about my personal life, and I feel like that's all in order, but I am completely lost when it comes to my professional life. I'm thinking that after I graduate, I'm going to focus on taking tests, like the LSAT, the CBEST, the GRE, and the civil service exam; I'm going to take language classes (Spanish, and maybe Dutch? I dunno) to broaden my skills and make me a more desirable job candidate in the fields I'm interested; and I'm going to get a part-time or even volunteering position at a local library, look for some kind of internship, and just get myself moving forwards towards a goal, so that I can accomplish it. It feels better to know that I have some kind of plan besides being depressed about crappy job prospects.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...ought to be  urlLink fake.  I saw Mean Girls this afternoon, and I was looking at some Lindsay Lohan pictures, and that girl is  urlLink ORANGE . Way too much sunless tanning. She's a naturally pale girl, but this is scary... I want a tan, but not like this! I hear the key is exfoliating, and starting as light as possible. But I'm still toying with the idea of spending my Sunday evening tanning myself. If I come to school wearing long sleeves, you'll know what happened!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I did my two midterms today, and they seemed, well, passable. I just don't know. I can't analyze myself like that. I don't enjoy the self-doubt, and since there is absolutely nothing I can do about it, why worry? I've had some quality study sessions with both Liz and Jessica, and it's been nice having friends in all of my classes... I need to hang out with Liz and Melissa more. I've been bad about that; but after this week, things should be less hectic. Although, I think I need to get in some serious pool time, though I may just go to the rec pool or something. Makes me nervous to go alone, but it'll probably be good for me. Maybe I'll go tomorrow after class.... anyone want to go to the pool with me tomorrow? Eh, I probably should just go alone so I can lay out and study.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      An article I need to read about how to clean and get rid of all of the accumulation of materical culture... or how to throw out my crap!  urlLink DigsMagazine.com | lounge: CULL BABY CULL: KITCHEN 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now the slacking of the early quarter is catching up to me. I have to read 6 books by tomorrow. But only 4 are directly necessary for an assignment, so I will probably only skim those and skip the other books entirely. I'm not really sure why professors think we will read so much, because I'm only barely getting by on the reading that I do get done.   So, about my weekend: accordions in the cemetery, and barbecues with homeowners. Yep, a truly surreal and strange experience--and that was just the homeowners. My mom has revived her love of accordions and as such has joined an accordion band. Who knew that she was so cool and alternative? They were hired for their first gig to play for this modern dance troop in the Mountain View cemetery in Piedmont; the music was entrancing and beautiful, and fit the surroundings well, but the dancing was, well, weird. The most painful moments were when they danced without music and embraced mausoleums. The best was when they ran around the fountains with flags. But mostly, it was weird, so I zoned out and looked at the amazingly cool surroundings of the cemetery. A lot of really cool architecture and sculpture, and there were even some famous California families buried there. Like the Ghirardellis and Charles Crocker, one of the "big four" who paid for the transcontinental railroad and got stinking rich--one of the four founded a university. You might have heard of it. Can you say Stanford? Yep. Stinking rich.  So then on Sunday I managed to get very little work done as well, because we went to a barbecue held by Dave and Alexa, with some of their neighbors. It was weird, because they talked a lot about their houses: improving their houses, how much their houses were worth, how weird their neighbors could be, and many other equally bizarre topics that renters just don't talk about. I'm not sure if I want to join the homeowners cult. It's a little too intense and exclusive these days. It costs a lot of money to join that club!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I didn't post that Jerm's mom, sister and I were planning a surprise party for Jerm on the off chance he might read it, but he really was surprised! He only started to suspect when he saw John's car out front, then wondered what the heck was going on. It was awesome. As we left, he said it was the best party ever. Sweet.  Now today I need to write a paper and email it in when I'm done. Hopefully that will all work out well, I just need to get writing! It's a very theoretical topic, and I'm having a bit of a hard time getting it going. But I have a clear outline, so I think I'll start writing and then write my intro. That seems to be where I'm confused, so I guess I should just write it after I know what I mean!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been pondering the idea of starting a media blog that would keep tabs on things I find interesting in the media; I told Jerm about it, and he said "you'll just be one mediocre blog among many." Then I scolded him for only doing things if he was the best at it. No one reads this anyway, but ideas? Opinions? I'm not sure if it's a good idea, but I will probably need to actually publicize my site or something. We'll see. I just think it would be interesting to write exclusively about history/politics/media/television, and keep my personal rants here. I also think it would be good practice for writing and journalism, if I really want to pursue that at all.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Very exciting news: Jason has been hired by Utica College in upstate New York. So that means that Jason and Lisa can live grown up lives in a lovely college town. The sad part is that they're going to live in New York, not California, and are now a plane ride away instead of a car trip away. Oh well, we will all have to make efforts to visit a lot. And apparently there are cheap flights between Sacramento and Syracuse, so it might be more affordable.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For some reason this morning I didn't feel like drinking a lot of coffee. Something about it didn't sit right with me, and somehow that hyper-caffinated mood just didn't hit me. Something about Lisa's general avoidance of life lately has been affecting my energy for the worse. I feel lethargic and unmotivated; or at least more so than normal. I think that's why I had a migraine today, but a very minor one. Migraines are like warning signals from my brain that I'm not taking proper care of myself. So I took some aspirin and drank a ton of water, and I felt better within an hour. Later Alex called me because I had a depressed away message on yahoo messenger (I only have it to talk to her), which was unusually compassionate and kind of her. But then I realized the only reason she called was to talk about her. She's having a boy, which actually depresses me, because now I know she's going to name him SOB Jr. which freaks me out. I don't want that child to have to symbolize all of what is wrong with Alex's life for me. But I already feel like he does. Weird to gender classify an unborn child. Also, Alex told me that SOB and she are going to move to Humbolt, so SOB can get a second bachelor's degree. First of all, like they need more debt, second, I bet he just wants to go so he can keep an eye on Alex around all those college boys. Come on now, we all know she doesn't like boys that young. She wants 'em old enough to work with her daddy complex. God, she's so creepy. Oh, and I'm her only friend. She doesn't know who else to invite to her party besides me. It makes me feel sad, because we aren't that close anymore. There's a barrier between us that I'm not sure will dislodge anytime soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not sure how I feel about this new template. I might have to switch back, because this is a little bit too pink! What do you think?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To add to my ad hoc community, my roommate  urlLink Lisa  has decided to begin a blog as well; should be interesting to get two points of view to each story at the apartment. Anyway, check it out.  This was an intriguing weekend and Monday--I spent Saturday at a Cavalry Clinic, though I was there mostly for the theory part of the class and did not ride any horses. I hung around with some of my old-timey ren faire friends, and I forgot how cool they can be. I try to be all embarrassed of reenacting, but there are so many cool and interesting people to hang out with, it's hard to cut myself off completely, so I don't think I will.  Got home from the class in time to take Mommy out to dinner at Grasshopper, a chic restaurant in Rockridge. I think Mom had a good time with Jerm and I. We sat at the bar because it seemed lame to wait for a table, and it was nice. I think I'd sit at the bar again. Mom and I had good conversation too, it was a very nice grown-up thing to do.  Sunday morning Jerm and I went to a Mother's Day brunch at his sister's house, with was nice. I probably should have gotten my family to go, but I'm still feeling anxious about being around Alex socially. I get really tense when I'm around her, and it's just hard to deal with my emotions in general around her. Then I skipped out on the old-folks home to get my reading done, and something miraculous happened--I got my reading done before the last minute! I had time to do other stuff before my seminar. I need to keep doing this reading on time thing. It's really nice to not be so stressed out!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is an odd day. I didn't stay up too late with Jerm last night, instead I stayed up too late with Liz and Lisa. Usually I drink more than I eat with Jerm, but because it was a girl's night, I ate a ton of food. And drank a fair bit of wine. After watching the Big Lebowski and doing the dishes, I started to feel really full. I mean,  really  freaking full. When I climbed into bed, I almost barfed, ran to the bathroom, didn't barf, climbed into bed, almost barfed, ran to the bathroom, and didn't barf. Finally I decided I was fine, but put a plastic bag near my head in order work with the Murphy's law that seemed to be going--place to barf equals no barfing.   I had bizarre and interesting dreams, as always, and then Lisa knocked on my door and said, "Waffles and coffee!" I think I mumbled something about, "Mwah? Just a minute. Ugh," and promptly fell right back asleep. I hear Liz and Lisa talking, and then the door front door shut and I woke up. It was like 9:30, which was a little bit earlier than I meant to get up, but reasonable. I ate my waffle and drank coffee, while watching E! News live. Now I'm probably going to Woodland with Liz to order grad announcements, though I made a list and I have like, 6 families that I for sure want to send announcements to (my grandparents and various aunts, uncles and cousins... Oh! I forgot my dad's side! Make that 8.) I'm contemplating getting creative on the computer with some fancy paper and a printer. I might have to make a visit to Papyrus this afternoon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it took me a while, but my IGETC should be in the mail as we speak. I spent yesterday morning cutting class and freaking out that DVC hadn't received my request for my IGETC, I tried to call, and couldn't get through, so I finally sent an email asking what to do... but the response took long enough that I decided to leave for Pleasant Hill anyway. So I spent the drive freaking out and being nervous about what I needed to do, and the fact that I didn't know what the records people had to say about what I wanted. I drove into the DVC parking lot, felt a lot of deja vu from my 1.5 semesters there, and I couldn't get out of the car. I literally had a panic attack about being so unprepared and having to deal with people. I'd forgotten the address I needed to IGETC sent to, and I didn't even know what I really wanted, so it was an entirely bad scene. So I drove on to Oakland, berating myself for being such a spineless wimp.  But the day got better. Holly called, and the first thing she said was, "Are you sitting down?" I'm picturing something terrible, like Holly has VD or she's pregnant or something similarly full of personal crisis. But no, Holly isn't pregnant, it's her brother Ben's girlfriend, Monnie Rose, aka "the beast." I, in all of my sensitivity, burst out laughing when she tells me this. Oh, the ironic twists of fate, that both of us now have impending nieces or nephews from each of our siblings that are with the worst person on the planet for them. Why to all the people who shouldn't have kids get pregnant? It's called birth control, people. I've been having sex for years, and yet somehow, I've never been pregnant, I don't have a kid, so I feel like I can be self-righteous about judging people who are not as responsible as me.   I checked my email in Oakland, and got a response that they'd never received my letter of request, so I decided I'd just go in the morning on my way. Jerm had to get up early to take BART in a complicated series of rides so he can go to the airport tonight to see Jason, so I dropped him off down at Fruitvale, came home and got together my junk and headed back out to DVC. This time I got out of the car, armed with all of the information that I needed, and went straight to the admissions and records office, where they were very helpful, and I got my IGETC sent. Hooray! I might just graduate!   I raced to Davis, and barely made it to class on time, then I came home. I still have to go the pharmacy to get my pills (see, responsible about *not* getting pregnant!), which will probably set me back a bit, because I want to get the rest of my packs until November, because I probably won't have health insurance for a while next year. But after that, I'm thinking about getting off the pill and reexperiencing my own hormone levels again. After 5 years, I think it might be a novel experience. Back to good old condoms.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           urlLink Which John Cusack Are You?      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I'm having panic attacks about my IGETC. I thought I'd taken care of it, but I got an email from one of the counselors at the dean's office that it's not in. So now I need to go to DVC in Pleasant Hill to get this damn thing straightened out. I've tried to call the offices and it's all information that I've read on the website, no real person. When I pushed the button to talk to a real person, it put me back to the beginning menu. I sent an email, and so far no response. I sent them a letter months ago requesting, in writing, with my signature and everything, that they send the certificate to the dean's office as soon as possible. And apparently nothing happened. I gave them all of my contact information and nothing. I guess I need to be more proactive about this, but it's hard. That isn't the way I work, nor is the way I was raised. I know I'm way too go with the flow for my own good. But all I want is for people to do their job without causing me so much undue stress! I cut class today, just so I could deal with this bull-oney. Crap. I'm probably going to drive to DVC, park without a permit and pray I don't get a ticket, wait in line at the admissions office to have them tell me it won't work and I'm screwed! Ack! Ok, maybe I'm catastrophizing, but I'm terrified about all of this not working out for the best. And it's probably my own fault for procrastinating and not wanting to deal with lame ass counselors. Ack!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so depressed about school. This just hasn't been my quarter--yet another low B on an assignment, and once again, I thought I did pretty well. It's upsetting and unexpected. I'm not sure what's going on at all. I guess I'm going to go talk to the TA on Friday to talk about where I went wrong, and what I can do in my next essay to do better. This is starting to be a pattern, so I'm beginning to think it has something to do with me and not just my TAs. I guess I'm just not working as hard as I have in the past... I miss von Henneberg. I could always write clever, thoughtful essays and tests for her. She had a really approachable and well organized style that I miss in my teachers this quarter. After 4 years of As, getting a big patch of Bs is really disheartening. But I just need to work harder and not give up completely, which is what I'm tempted to do at this point. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Kinda freaks me out, but hey, I often think I know better than him when I watch him dress those poor straight men. Huh. Who are you?    You're Shop till ya drop CARSON Kressley: Fashion Savant. Get ready to max out your credit card on madison ave.    urlLink   What Fab 5 member from Queer Eye for the Straight Guy are you?(with pics)     brought to you by  Quizilla   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I've been having trouble with my grades this quarter. I swear I'm writing the same stuff I have been all year, but these TAs this quarter have been really nitpicky over stupid details. And the teachers have been unclear and inconsistent with what they want from us. I hate this stupid TA in TransMississippi West, he marks me down for the lamest things, and I feel like I wrote a clear and well written essay, and he picks out these lame details that I didn't mention enough. I can't write about everything, I have to pick and choose, we only have an hour for chrissakes! I hate getting a B when I felt like I wrote a good essay, and I felt good about what I wrote and what I knew. It's so fucking arbitrary, it makes me sick. Maybe next time I'll just ramble on about who knows what and I'll get an A. It works for other people. God I'm pissed.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I decided to go ahead and start a commentary blog, and keep this about my issues and journal stuff. But you should bookmark both... at some point I'm going to post a link to each on the sites, but I need to get around to it. Sounds like a project for tomorrow afternoon! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thank goodness I'm done with the hard part of Monday! I got up this morning with Jerm, and our bed with the new high thread count sheets is just way to comfortable. And they were freshly cleaned, so it was a little bit of a snooze button morning. We showered and grabbed coffee and left as quickly as we could, and I was only slightly later than expected. I got home and read a bunch for Colonialism and Culture seminar, and then ran to American Political History. We talked about the election and presidency of Zachary Taylor. The funny part of that is when I was little my dad's friend had a dog named Zachary Taylor, and for the longest time I didn't really know that the dog was named after an actual historical figure. I just thought it was funny that the dog had a last name. But that dog had the temperament to be named for a general/president. He was a gruff old dog!  Anyway, finished the reading, wrote up my response and went to seminar, where I actually talked and said some stuff about the topic. Next week I present, so I need to email the girl who I'm supposed to work with. I'm sure we'll just divide it up and make sure we both know what to talk about, and it'll be great. I think I'll make up some discussion questions and maybe look up some kind of visual--we're talking about hook swinging and sati, so maybe it'll be more intriguing to see images of what the British were so offended by. Hmm.  Then Melissa called and we went to the grocery store together. It was just like old times, except we didn't have to steal a cart from across the street and go up the elevator with it like at Lakeshore. Oh well. We then got dinner at Dos, which is always tasty. Now I need to have some alone time with the bathroom... bye!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I actually worked on my Western History paper, and I finally found an inspiring topic. I realize now that my issue with papers this quarter is that I wasn't excited about the topics, I didn't have any flashes of inspiration or insight, and I was writing papers as bored as I was. So I figure to get through this next set of papers, I really need to start early and get inspired to write something that I care about. I really do well when I compare and contrast, just because I'm good at weighing two sides of an idea or argument and picking a side by the end. It comes easily to me, and the structure and organization is easy to work out. Did you know that I'm a structure nazi? I bet you can't tell with this blog and the free flow of ideas, but when I write a paper, I can't just blindly write, I have to have a goal, an intention and an inspiration. I have to outline everything in detail before I'll even begin to write, and often that takes longer than the actual process of writing. I usually feel good about this, because one consistant comment I get on papers is that I have good organization. One the last paper I got back, the teacher wrote, "I especially liked the way you organized your paper--which I thought was particularly elegant." Yay! Elegant. That comment made my day.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Disclaimer: This post may be a bit more graphic than normal, and you should avoid it if it might freak you out, or if you don't want to know. Continue at your own choice! And don't say I didn't warn you!    Good grief I need to get laid. I know I normally don't talk about my sex life with, well, anyone, but the midweek visit with Jerm threw me off my schedule of only weekend sex... that was nice. We were too sleepy when I arrived after visiting the sister, but whoa, some lovely morning sex after a night of sexy cuddling. Very nice stuff. But now I'm wanting more, again, and a few more times after that. Maybe it's the new pill. I haven't felt this randy since I was 19 and hooching it up, except now I'm actually getting off and I know a little bit better what I'm doing. All I have to say, is if these are the side-effects of the generic pill, I'll take it. I think ortho-tricyclen was inhibiting my desire a bit. It was part of why I wanted to get off the pill. But this is better, because increased horny-ness tends to equal pregnancy if you aren't on the pill. And in light of recent events, I've been feeling even more paranoid about the pregnancy demon. No little bastard babies for me! No thank you. Or my increased libido is due to getting some mid-week... I swear, the more often I do it, the more I want to do it. If I don't do it a lot, I forget how much I like it, and tend to be lazy about it. Thank goodness I'm going back to see the Jerm tomorrow... I can get Jerminated. Hee hee. I've been meaning to make that joke for a while, it just never seemed appropriate. Oh well, lucky you to read this, I'm likely to delete it later from embarrassment. But now I feel no shame.  Oh, and to add another idea I've been pushing about in my brain: sometimes I miss sleeping with all kinds of interesting people. Or at least making out with random guys/girls when drunk, etc. I kind of miss exploring my hetero-flexibility. I know some girls aren't into lesbian/girl-on-girl action, but that stuff is more exciting then seeing guys in porn. It's probably because guys in porn are nasty and frightening, at least more so than girls in porn. But anyway, I love Jerm, but sometimes I miss the freedom of being single. Maybe it was just the situations I was in, but it was so easy and fun to see if I could get a guy into bed. It's probably because I was 19. Guys just wanna do you when you're 19 and all naive, yet legal. It's weird. I guess it's that I still wonder if guys find me as desirable now as they did then. Now I put out that whole "not interested" vibe, although maybe this is coming up because a cute guy who says smart things smiled at me and I smiled back. It was an old-timey, high school kind of feeling. He was one of those smart, dorky, cute guys. I'm such a sucker for that; brains are hot. Good thing that's what Jerm is, or I wouldn't be happy at all (don't forget, engineers do it better). When I was in high school I'd have the deepest crushes on the loud, brainy, cute guys, and my friends would tease me about not liking the asshole jock. I'm sorry, I've never liked jocks since they were assholes to me in elementary school and middle school, and I have to get to know a jock before I'll let my guard down. Now they're all frat boys, and I still hate them a little bit. Oh well, way too much deep reverie for now. I better get back to work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sorry for the gap in posting... yesterday I overslept--something I have not done since I started taking later classes, but I guess I stayed up too late for my 10:30am class, because that was what time I got up at! The problem was that I thought it would be a good idea to stick the alarm up in the loft bed with me, instead of down below on the desk where it's been all year. The result was the volume was turned down by my pillow, and then at some point in the morning I knocked the clock down to the grown. It was pretty bad. So now I've missed two classes in a row for Spain and the Americas class. I'm doing so badly in that class. I need to do the reading and write well for the term paper.  So, I made it to my 2nd class, Western history, and wore my new silk shirt from the Gap. It's bound to become one of my all time favorites. You know, the shirt you wish you could wear a few times a week, and if you think you might be seeing different people you'll try to wear it, even if the last time you wore it was yesterday? It's pale teal, button up, silk. For $12.99. I just can't get over Gap sales sometimes. They can be so awesome that it's hard for me to want to pay full price for anything there. I'll just wait until it's on sale.  I rushed to my sister's house in Manteca, because it was her 21st birthday, and I said I'd be there. I totally crapped out on her present, but I bought her a dress at Walmart. I wanted to take her some place nicer, but she refused. She's a stick in the mud like me, only less amiable. And it's only been two weeks since I last saw her, but she is PREGNANT. I mean, there is no mistaking it anymore. She is clearly pregnant. And I'd forgotten how loud she is. Maybe that's where my sensitivity to loud noises comes from. Hmm. We had a nice dinner that I felt guilty about them paying for, then they took me out to see Shrek 2 (good movie, I might add), and I tried to pay at least for myself, but they insisted. I always feel weird accepting hospitality when it's like that. I'm not sure why. And it's not like I'm rich, I'm just living a cheaper life, so I can afford a few luxuries sometimes. I always feel like the rich one when I'm with her, except I never feel like that with anyone else. I feel like a farce. I just spend money on clothes so I look nicer, I guess. And it's not like any of my clothes cost more than $20 bucks. I have one pair of Gap jeans that I bought full price that cost $50. But that's a lot of money to Alex, who seems to be supporting a lot more than she can afford. Those are choices she's made, and I shouldn't have to feel guilty because I've made different choices, such that my life is easier and maybe even better. What can I do?  Then I got anxious (a little bit stressed by being excessively diplomatic for too long) so I came home to Jerm for a night. It was lovely, and made today seem better. Also, I watched the Big Lebowsky again. An awesome movie. Okay, I'm going to bed or I'm going to read, or a little of both. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I picked up my cap and gown today with  urlLink Liz , and it was amazingly painless. I talked to some other people and they said it was a mad house this morning, but that was probably because of the people trying to score extra tickets. I have to remember to keep my mouth shut about the possibility of having an extra ticket! I let it slip in front of my presentation partner, but I told her that I wasn't sure yet if it really was available. I think maybe Jason can go with Lisa, so that'll take them. So it's Mom, Alex, Catherine, Jerm, Lisa and possibly Jason. My dad'll be on a cruise to Alaska so can't come. I'm still a little bitter. I need to find out who is where when. And I need to get my announcements out. I bought the sticker seals today that I'll use as a decoration on the pages. I think it should turn out nicely. Oh, and I need to remember that I owe Liz money for the paper and envelopes! I'm not sure how much, we need to do some math together.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished my outline of what I want to talk about in my presentation today in seminar. It's about torture, and of course, I have the section on S/M and what it means to accept some forms of pain in the realms of personal choice, versus others, blah, blah, blah. I'm just hoping I won't giggle when I outline the definition of S/M, or when I talk about some pretentious artist who pierced his head to look like Jesus. So angsty, so full of ennui. How writhing for me! I kind of hate performance art, but hopefully that won't show while I'm talking to the class about it all. Everything else is very serious, as you might imagine, but I'm still anxious about the one risque part. Sadomasochism. My favorite thing to talk about in front of a group of people trying to be serious about torture. Oh well, at least I wasn't the guy who had to talk about masturbation last week. Who knew colonialism was so dirty?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I sure do enjoy sleeping in on Sunday morning. I got up at 11:30am, which was  so nice . I really feel okay this morning. Yesterday was fun-ish, but tiring. I was glad to show Liz the Rockridge neighborhood and take her to Christopher's, which is like the only place I ever eat cheeseburgers. Organic beef, you know. Very tasty, especially when hungry.  Last night I did my own thing, I watched a little  urlLink Adult Swim , and watched some other lame television. I think I even caught an episode of  urlLink Trading Spaces  that I hadn't seen before. Then I crashed, probably staying up later then I needed too. A nice time, though. I forget how much I like my own company late at night. I had to be quiet though, because Lisa was sleeping, but that wasn't so bad, because I'm usually awfully quiet late at night.  So, I slept in, had weird dreams about being at fair and trying to keep a baby rattle snake from biting people at Renaissance Faire, then having to save the chickens from being eaten by a cat, all this after being squirted in the face with liquid LSD. A strange dream, I know. I woke up as my dad was trying to get us a better camp situation at the faire. It's refreshing to wake up when my body is just done sleeping. Then I had some coffee, IMed with my sister, and Melissa dropped by because she had a brunch in my complex. Then I called Alex, and we talked for 45 minutes, which was nice. Now I'm putting off reading, but I better get back to it, I have to present it tomorrow in class. I'm more ahead on my reading than I normally am on Sunday afternoon, so I'm a bit complacent.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I can go to bed now. I finished my paper for Latin America class, then I went to Stockton to see Catherine's graduation. Too much happened to really talk about yet--I'm still processing. But I'm still alive, though I'm trying to figure out my weekend plans.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's times like these when I actually look forward to graduating, unlike my normal mindset of complete terror at having to get a job and be a grown up. As I sit here looking at the jumble of crap I managed to write on my screen, I realize that I hate staying up late writing crappy papers. Maybe it would be better to work eight hours a day, then go home and screw around. Of course, that's unrealistic too, because when you're a grown up, you have to do things like paint your house, pay your bills, do the dishes, vacuum your carpet and eat healthy grown up food that you had to push through the always crowded heathfood store to get. I suppose I just have to get used to the idea of working a lot for money, spending said money on a crappy house that needs a ton of work, and not having enough time for the good things in life, like sleeping, drinking and smoking that unmentionable stuff that'd I'd never do because it's, like, illegal, man. That's the good life, as long as you can do it all on your own property and not have to worry about being a renter. I'm sick of being a renter, so maybe I have to make the move to adulthood soon. Weird. Look at me, I'm rambling again. Back to the role of the mestizo in Spanish colonial society. Oh Boy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I'm trying to get through this paper about race and social mobility in 16th century Spanish America. Yeah, a little bit dense, but I'm working my way through it. What I'm really beginning to freak out about is my paper tomorrow about the development of the republican party... I have to go to Catherine's high school graduation in the evening, which promises to be awkward. I'm just going to go early, get Catherine a present, then spend the afternoon sitting at my dad's writing... why won't I ever learn to give up procrastinating? I'll start tomorrow, really.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Memorial Day weekend turned out much better than I'd expected for an unplanned series of barbecues and get-togethers. Jerm and I spent Friday night cuddling and being happy about having a whole weekend together, but Jerm was really tired from working to much, so I made chicken barley soup and tried to get him to take it easy for the evening. I wasn't entirely successful, but we had a tasty dinner and went to bed by 11:30, much earlier than normal.  We woke up very late, at about 10:00, but it felt so nice to get so much sleep. I made coffee and breakfast while Jerm slept later, and then we decided to go to Target and Ikea, to get a soap pump for the bathroom and to look at entertainment consoles to replace the black behemoth we have currently. On the way, we saw Dave and Alexa getting into their car after getting breakfast on Macarthur, and Jerm called them and asked if they wanted to come. After some initial waffling, they met us at Target in San Leandro that's I'd never been to before. There was just way too much stuff at Target, and Alexa and I looked at shoes and clothes until Dave got impatient with all of us and we had to go back home. We traded cars so we were all in the WRX and went to Ikea, which was a madhouse as always. Jerm and I looked at so many different tv tables, and through various misunderstandings and miscommunications had a fight, so we decided to eat. Yay, Ikea cafe! I had the manager's special and ate way too many meatballs. Yum. I should have gotten a lingonberry soda though. That would've been tasty too. Then we wandered through the rest of the store and no one ended up buying anything. Oh well. We all went back to our homes and then reconvened for dinner--this time barbecued apple chicken sausages, veggie skewers, and a big salad. Oh, and a lot of sangria. Whenever the four of us hang out, you can count on booze!  Sunday was devoted to cleaning and reading. Or at least, that was our intention. Jerm and I read the newspaper and had breakfast first, then we finally got going. Fiona and I had made plans to hang out at some point during the weekend, so we decided Sunday night would be good. This was of course not without angst, especially on Jerm's side, but I agreed to make dinner again, and I'd pick her up at BART at 7pm. So as Jerm is emptying the contents of the garage into the driveway, he decides that what he needs are shelves, and Dave is the one to help him. At about 6pm he leaves to meet Dave, Alexa and their truck at Home Despot so he can buy lumber... and I can't leave the house while he's gone, because someone needs to keep an eye on all of the stuff in the driveway. So I start cooking dinner, and getting that in motion, and by 6:45 Jerm calls saying Fiona called, and he's going to pick her up... oh, and Dave and Alexa will come by and hang out tonight too. So I add more food to the stew, and suddenly I'm descended upon by starving hoards. But it was fun. Fi, Alexa and I watched The Big Lebowski while Jerm and Dave built shelves in the garage. We drank a lot and stayed up too late, and I got up early to take Fi to Orinda... but I'll tell you about Monday in another post. Too much good stuff to tack onto the end of this post. Good times.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I've been intending to finish my essay before the due date of midnight on Sunday. I've been working a little bit to casually and I took an awfully long break for a barbecue over at Dave and Alexa's. That was a good time, thought I started to feel overwhelmed and worry about my paper when everyone started talking about going for a hike. Maybe I'm just lame and lazy, but I just felt like I had to finish this paper, and going for a hike would eat into my working time too much. Taking a few hours for a meal seems okay, but I feel like I need to devote more of my energy to this paper. Of course, work is slow going, but I'm getting going.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finished my first final this morning, and I'm so relieved that it's over. I wrote the weirdest, longest essay, but I think I might have gotten a B. I can hope. We'll see.  Next I'm going home to Oakland, and I'm going to write up my paper on colonialism over the weekend. I'm kind of into it, so I'll probably begin it earlier than Sunday, the due date. I was going to take a shower, but Lisa beat me to it, and it's probably for the best, since she's been working so hard yesterday and today getting sweaty (I'm just teasing, Lisa). I'll probably get a shower at home in a few hours.   I'm guessing everyone's really busy with finals and doesn't have time to comment on my graduation clothes quandary. Maybe later.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Liz  and I made an expedition to the  urlLink Galleria in Roseville , and I got  urlLink these shoes  except in fushia and I paid $20 less than the shoes are listed for on the website. I'm super excited, and I love Aldo. Now I just need to figure out what to wear. Although it may be time for another black dress, I'm also contemplating nice black slacks and white button up shirt, neither of which I own, but would come in handy for interviews, etc. Ideas? Opinions?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm feeling much better about life in general after a cathartic lunch with Melissa. She and I have so much fun yakking away about three different things at once. And I always feel like I've worked through my issues, and I understand myself better after I talk to her. We're totally going to Disneyland for graduation. It'll be awesome.  Gotta rough draft/outline a paper today, meet with the teacher about the paper, and go to exit counseling. Then I'm going to go shopping with Liz and possibly Melissa in Roseville, and I spend the evening studying with my classmate Jessica. And Friday I take my final and I guess go home to Oakland, I suppose. I have to talk to Jerm.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm exhausted. Physically, emotionally and intellectually. Mellow, sleepy day at school (after writing a crazy paper in the morning) followed by some TV watching and general time-wasting at home. Liz came over to get announcements going, then Dave and Melissa came over and we all went to Woodstocks. Despite some general awkwardness, I had a reasonably good time, then Liz and I talked about deep stuff. I drove her home, then came back, watched weird TV with Lisa, and then took a long needed shower, though I neglected to shave. I think I'm going to go to bed now, since I was up at 5:20am this morning. Oh, my best friend sleep, how I've missed you. I'm sorry that drama queen homework took me away from you all this time. Homework really is a needy, demanding kind of friend, who really isn't a friend to me all that often. Stupid homework. Oops, I hope she doesn't read my blog. She'd be pissed, but I'm totally blowing her off when I graduate. Really, sleep, I promise, I won't neglect you any more.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yikes, what have I gotten myself into? I need to write the last paragraph of my essay, only the book I need to use is fiction, very dense, and I have no idea how I'm going to find the quotes I need to write my paper and get my thesis across. I'm tired of this whole song and dance, only one more to go after I finish this baloney.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm still reeling from the terribly depressing readings in my Colonialism and culture class. I'm having a lot of trouble processing all of the horror, and it makes me feel weepy. Maybe it's just the lack of sleep and the new pill (BTW, my boobs have gotten HUGE. I can't understand it, and it's kinda uncomfortable. Though I admit, it's a little bit okay.), but I am feeling weepy about everything in my history classes.  It's "crunch time," in the parlance of our times (as the Dude would say): tonight and probably tomorrow I write a paper for western American history, I believe 5-7 pages. Next I'm going to get a rough draft done for seminar, then I'm going to meet with the prof. to discuss my outline, etc. And either tomorrow or Thursday I have to go to the exit loan counseling, which I meant to do with Liz, but I'm way too busy today (how did it go, Liz?). Thursday I need to study for western American history final, and write up a reading journal, which won't be too bad, because the books are what I'm writing an essay about tonight. Sunday is the final due date of the seminar paper (10-12 pages, expanding on an existing essay, which I got an A on. Yay!), which I'll email in. Then I have my American political history final on Wednesday, Spanish America final on Thursday, and COMMENCEMENT on Saturday. Wow. How did it get so close to the end? Weird. Next step: the real world and a JOB.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Honest, last quarter I spent way too much time thinking about and studying the Holocaust and how it is remembered. I remember feeling vaguely numb and clinical, but I just finished reading  urlLink "Things Fall Apart"  by Chinua Achebe and I seriously cried. My god, the self-important arrogance of colonizers. The mindset is so appallingly unaware and uncaring. They had no sense of the tragedy they were creating, they just arrogantly assumed that their way was the best way, and it would benefit everyone. But it didn't, it hurt everyone, and no one came out of the colonial system without being seriously, deeply affected psychologically.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I talked to Holly, who has been out of touch for the last week, and she and Roz and Roz's boyfriend aren't coming until tomorrow, and I'll feed them brunch with all of the other masses of people. I've decided to try a little bit of a  urlLink gourmet meal , which I'm kind of stoked about. I can do most of the cooking tonight, and I'll just make some scones tomorrow morning. Along with coffee, OJ and mimosas I think I might be okay. I just counted, and there will be 12 people to feed. Might be exciting. But that grocery store trip was a little scary. I bought too much expensive food, and I still need chocolate and orange marmalade. Cost plus, here I come.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometime word.a.day just captures my whole frame of reference in a single word. I'm feeling this word more and more now that my crazy LA/Santa Cruz friends are decending on me tonight--and get this, not a single phone call to me since the interupted call from Roz last week Thursday. Weird, right? Read below, and you'll see even the quote captures my mood. Too funny and bizare, this confluence of events.  gauche (GOsh) adjective    Lacking grace; tactless; awkward.  [From French gauche (literally left-handed, awkward), from Old French, from gauchir (to turn).]  Today's word in Visual Thesaurus: http://visualthesaurus.com/?word=gauche   "And, no, it wasn't another gauche instance of a designer cherry-topping   a banal performance with a celebrity ..."   Cathy Horyn; High Concept, Multiple Meanings; The New York Times;   Mar 10, 2003.   "The little gesture of respect to Robson's team was not just a matter of   etiquette. Newcastle may have been gauche before the interval but there   is gusto about them that is hard to balk over an entire afternoon on   their own pitch."   Kevin McCarra; Football: Premiership: Arsenal Keep the Chasing Pack at   Bay; The Guardian (London, UK); Feb 10, 2003.  This week's theme: words to describe physical characteristics of people. ............................................................................ One of the hardest things in life is having words in your heart that you can't utter. -James Earl Jones, actor (1931- ) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm still feeling crazy, but I'm a lot calmer than I was last night. Sleep does that for me. I mostly shouldn't even be posting, but I wanted to talk about what a nice time I had with Melissa and Liz last night, since last night I was too busy freaking out about my insane family and friends. Melissa fed me a fatty and delicious dinner. She has a good description of the meal  urlLink here . Then Liz came over and we talked a bit then walked to downtown. I probably shouldn't have worn flip-flops, because my feet began to hurt, but everything seems to be okay now, so no worries. It was nice to be out in the warm Davis night. Good times.  This morning has been about not studying for the final I should study for. I think I'll make sure I know the IDs, and that I know enough of the books to fake something, but the TA'll probably give me a B- anyway, so why put in an A effort, you know? Oh well, off to eat and study.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been feeling really put upon lately by my family, mostly because of their inaction. They barely seem to notice that I'm graduating, while everyone else's parents are all excited and doing cool things for them since they've finally finished college. And my friends Holly and Roz are showing up, but I have no idea when or even exactly where, and one is out of touch for the week, the other said she would call me back in an hour last Thursday but never did, so somehow I feel like it's her obligation to call me. Maybe I'm just a flake, but I think she should call me. I've decided that if people want to see me and do things with me, maybe they should call me, and include me in their plans. Seems simple, but it rarely happens in my life. I'm worried about this whole thing being a clusterf*ck mess with crazy people and no where to sleep. If this is any kind of repeat of picnic day, I will honestly pitch a fit. If I have to step over people to have breakfast with my mom, I will start yelling. I'm not sure where the rage and panic is coming from, but it's rising quickly, and I need to start organizing this boloney before anything crazy happens. Maybe it's just that I'd prefer something smaller and lower key on Friday night, and the insanity to happen on Saturday night. I don't mind small get together, I do mind drunken sleeping all day. I don't know, I feeling crazy and out of control lately, and my head and balance have been off. I feel like something's wrong with me. Oh, I know, I'm graduating.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I'm about to go to bed, but I thought I'd type in a quick note about what a weird day today was. Good part: Driving to Roseville with Liz and finding the perfect graduation dress. It's really perfect. Very me. Maybe I'll post a picture of it later. Also, I watched Sex and the City on TBS because I never had HBO to watch it before. It's happy. Bad part: low level headache basically all day, crazy idiots at both Safeway and Dos, and mild graduation planning crap. Also spent the day mildly irritated at the world (no, not you Liz), because of my inherent laziness and inability to plan or take care of things ahead of time. It's always the damn last minute with me. Why do I continue to be a moron?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've officially finished my last paper ever. Or at least my last undergrad paper ever. It was kind of intense and awesome. Now, to celebrate I'm drunk (Liz, I'm totally thinking of you--we need to repeat this joy after Resendez. Fun, fun, fun!). We went to Ben 'n' Nick's with Dave and Alexa and had amazingly intelligent discussion about the increasing conglomeration of our world. Now I'm having an gin martini with Jerm's new expensive gin. Yum. I'm drunk and done with papers. It's totally the way life should be always. Next step: announcements! I have to get those out this week.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ever wonder what the weather is like at my house? Jerm got a weather station from his company, and now you can see  urlLink the weather at our place.  I really like not needing to look online to see the temperature of my own home.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, so clearly I've spent too much time writing history essays, because somehow titles with a colon work well for me. Today I woke up with Jerm and drove out to Davis to do some packing. I got all of my books and notebooks packed, and most of my bathroom crap, and now they are sitting in the car waiting for me to unload them. But the neighbor's son is sitting out front in his car and sometimes I'm too shy. Seriously he's just sitting in his car. Earlier he was blasting loud music, but now he's just sitting and making me feel bad about not doing my work or straightening out my car for Jerm who will be grumpy if there isn't a good place to park. Oh well.  Thanks to Lisa for the grad pics, I totally copied a bunch of them onto my computer. I'm glad to see that your camera works well. All I need now is my own digital camera, and this whiny blog might turn into a picture blog and you all won't have to read about my sad life any more. Speaking of my sad life, let me tell you more of it: this week I hung around with Roz and Holly, but mostly Holly. That was the main reason for no posts, because I actually had a human being to entertain and talk to, rather than all of you imaginary cyberspace folks. Not that I don't like you, but sometimes you can be a little distant, you know? But what can you do? Okay, I should probably just unload my car despite the  large man sitting in his car in front of my house. Or maybe I can get Jerm to help me with the lifting later on. Books are f**king heavy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The future? Are you sure?&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I guess I'm done. It's pretty weird, and I've been feeling apathetic and I've been busy with people over. But I thought let everyone know that I'm alive.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know I bitched a lot about school, but I'm beginning to miss it a bit. I liked going to lecture and taking notes and learning new things for a few hours everyday. I need to renew some of those learning efforts. I meant to go to the library today, but somehow the momentum wasn't there for me today. I'm not even really sure what to make for dinner tonight. I made cookies this morning and then spent a long time on the phone with both Holly and then with Alex. We decided that she needs a baby shower soon, and I'd always planned on hosting it, so I am. Now we just have to see who will come and who cares.  So I've been living the drunken housewife life, except I haven't been as drunk as I ought to be, and I'm not legally married to my "partner" or fiance or whatever I should call the Jerm. But it's like we're married. We've been contemplating eloping, but that would put to waste all of this lame wedding research I've been doing, and I think that a lot of people would get all butt-hurt about it. It's weird how much emotion people put into other people's wedding. I was hanging out with Alexa and Dave, and a friend of their's was going to have a tiny wedding, family only, and they were all talking about how lame and selfish it was. It makes me even more anxious about the idea of a wedding. It's funny that marriage itself seems perfectly natural and I think I'll enjoy it, but the wedding sounds very weird.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    lovely jcrew dress as possible wedding gown--very simple, very pretty, and only $260. I like it.&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The bridesmaid dress I'm considering--David's Bridal, only $110, and it ought to flatter everyone. I like the color too--celedon, but there are many other colors if I change my mind.&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I've been enjoying my time off (though next week I'm going to get into gear) and I've been doing the wedding planning thing. I already posted a possible  urlLink bridesmaid dress  from  urlLink David's Bridal . But I'm still not sure about the ethics of getting a dress from such a mass market place, but compared to a lot of what I've looked at, it seems so affordable. I probably won't buy my gown there.   The  urlLink other dress  that I really love is a little bit too expensive at $318. The website won't let me copy the image of the dress, so you'll have to go there to see how lovely it is. It's a similar style as the other dress, but so much more style. I like how it's patterned and not just one color. But based on how appealing these two dresses are, I'm really leaning towards a spring green and white wedding. Everything will go with white flowers and their green stems. It seems so simple.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have never been so angry with Jerm in my life. This weekend we're going to go camping with Dave and Alexa, and last night we went over to their house for dinner with another couple. At first, it was kind of silly and funny how Jerm wouldn't stop talking about camping, and it seemed like he was just trying to be prepared. But as Alexa, Dave and I all told him to calm down, we'd take care of everything the next day (all of us are home on Fridays), he got more and more tense and crazy. Finally we had to leave, because he was really anxious about getting all of the stuff together. When we got home, he and I argued about his behavior, and he got all mean and passive aggressive about how "you said you'd do it all, I'm not going to help you at all." Finally I just stopped arguing and stopped speaking to him for the rest of the evening. I put some stuff together, then I went to bed. He stayed up another hour or so being loud and packing, playing the martyr. The thing that pissed me off the most was that throughout our fight, I tried to end the fight and get him to relax for a minute, but he couldn't let it go. He couldn't keep himself from adding in one more rude and snotty comment. This morning he was soft and quiet, but I'm still somewhat irritated that he thinks I'm not competent enough to pack and take care of things. He always assumes that I won't be able to do anything, and anything I do seems to surprize him, like he didn't think I was capable. I know we have a lot more tension because I'm living here full time, but this lack of trust and faith in me is getting bad. I suppose we'll have a "talk" tonight in the car.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I talked to a lot of people today via phone and IM, but I spent the morning feeling crappy with a migraine. Maybe it was the coffee, or the drinking last night, or the stress about the shower or all three, but it was a lame crappy morning, leading into a lame lazy day. I didn't get much done at all, but tomorrow will be better, I'm sure.  I need to get a job, but first, the resume!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm going to host my sister's shower, though whether or not we should be celebrating such an ill-advised move isn't clear. But it seems to be the right thing to do, and Alex is going ahead with registering for expensive things that I hope no one really feels obligated to get her. It's a little bit offensive really. I think I'm going to tell her to get some more lower priced items for other friends, because she seems to have a lot of big ticket items. The way I see it, all she needs is a car seat and diapers. She can carry the kid in her arms, and let the kid sleep with them in bed, and feed him breast milk, which is free! And of course they're moving to Humbolt, and whether or not they have financial aid is beyond me. It's all a big cluster fuck. If you aren't aware of my intensely bizarre family drama, it's probably explained in the archives, or you can shoot me an email and I'll let you in on it. It's just to ridiculous and complex to discuss now. Bleh.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jerm and I got back last night from visiting my Aunt Nancy for the 4th of July. We experienced small town patriotism, and it was a lot of fun. I haven't seen my cousins or my aunt since my grandfather's funeral, so it was really nice to see how much everyone has changed and to see where everyone is in their lives. It was also fun to reminisce about old times and to introduce everyone to Jerm. They really liked him, and I think he really liked them. It makes it more clear how important family is, and I'm realizing that I need to spend more time reconnecting with all of my aunts and uncles who my mom has lost contact with. I'm looking forward to this.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This week has been devoted to me cleaning the house and trying to get Jerm to deal with his crap when he gets home at night. He has amazing ninja powers of persuation and procrastination, because we've hardly gotten any of the things done that we've set out to do. My friend Holly and her friend Michelle are crashing here tonight, and we have yet to set up the loft bed in the guest bedroom. I'm supposed to be cleaning up the rest of the house, but I hate vacuuming when it's hot, which it is today. All the rest of the week it's been cool and comfortable, but now, crunch day, it's hot. Oh, crazy bay weather. Actually I can't complain, considering I'm from inland where it's probably in the high 90's while it's only 82 here today. So--I'm putting off vacuuming and am instead writing here and concurrently watching BBC News, which I find to be less creepy than American Network news, all owned by media conglomerates. Anyway, I need to vacuum then start thinking about dinner.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a massively non-productive day today, and I'm making up for it now. When Jerm got home last night we went to get groceries and grabbed a to go package of premade sushi along with our veggies. When we got home and ate, it was so good that we decided to go out to the sushi place on Lake Merritt. We had a couple of beers and ate yummy sushi, except for one that we didn't like. I remembered that I like flying fish roe better than salmon roe. It was like a date or something, and we chatted and held hands and were generally romantic. Very nice.   Now I'm trying to clear out the front bedroom, but I keep moving in fits and starts, doing a job, then going to another, not really finishing everything. The good thing is that Jerm cleaned out the closet, so I finally have a place to put all of my clothes, which is very exciting. Next we need to build the bed and set up the computers and get my dresser in and we'll have a functioning room! I think I might turn it into laundry sorting central to allievate the burden on the back bedroom, which is really overwhelmed with stuff.  Oh well, back to work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I a little bit love  urlLink these Angel Sanchez Wedding dresses , though they are somewhat out of my price range. I think I may use them for inspiration if I decide to get a dress made. I'll post my favorite in a bit.  Also, this weekend was a lot of fun--full of beer drinking and meat eating. We went up to the high sierra, and camped right on the shore of a lake. We brought our kayaks, and Dave and Jerm did a lot of fishing, and we ate trout for dinner. Alexa and I took out the boats and sunned ourselves, and also checked out all of the cool islands in the lake. My biceps got a nice workout, and I think I could get into kayaking. It's really satisfying and fun.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        You're Betty Grable!      What Classic Pin-Up Are You?     brought to you by  Quizilla  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On Tuesday I drove down to Santa Barbara, and I got on the road by about 10 am. I stopped for a snack in Gilroy, and then stopped again at the rest stop south of King City, and made it to Melissa's house by 4pm. 101 really is a pretty drive. I even enjoy the Salinas Valley. It makes me feel all Grapes of Wrath. Of course, Tuesday was a beautiful day, and getting to Pismo Beach and seeing the ocean was stunningly distracting. I had trouble focusing on the road the water was so dazzling. When I arrived at Melissa's we chatted for a bit then went over to her mom's place to enjoy the view. That neighborhood reminds me of a more beachy Oakland hills--everything is really nice, but still a little bit funky. I finally met Melissa's mom, sister and stepdad, who were all super nice and charming. Melissa's mom, Kathryn, treated us to dinner at this sushi/fancy chef japanese place in downtown Santa Barbara. That town is a little too trendy for me, and I understand why Melissa identifies more with Goleta after the visit. Melissa showed me around, and I even saw IV, which seems like an odd place to live. I like Davis better as college towns go.  Melissa and I got up early to go to Disneyland, and it was a pleasant drive despite LA traffic. We analyzed issues in our lives and with our families, which was interesting. Disneyland was somewhat more crowded than I'd expected, but it is July, so I probably shouldn't have been surprized. We went on most of the big rides, had a tasty lunch in Frontierland, and had a very pleasant morning and early afternoon. Then it started to get very hot, and I started to feel more woozy and out of it. I was having trouble focusing so we decided to "rest" in the enchanted Tiki room. That probably wasn't the best idea, because by the end of the show I could only see half the room. Yes, a migraine hit. The rest of the evening was a blur, but I can't thank Melissa enough for being so understanding about my discomfort. I still feel bad about cutting the evening short. I think I might need to go to a doctor about my migraines, because this is ridiculous. It really kills the rest of my day.  So after sleeping the whole way home in the car and then passing out soon after we got home, I woke up kind of early, shower, and read my Us weekly I'd bought in case. I wanted Melissa to sleep in since she stayed up late driving me home. My drive home was fine, and I stopped at the factory stores in Gilroy to avoid some of the San Jose traffic, where I bought some undies at the Jockey store. I also got back to the bay area at the same time as Jerm left work, and we ended up driving together on the freeway home. It was very funny. We had dinner at Dave and Alexa's so Jerm could help them put up their new ceiling fan, and I took the old one--I'm starting a project to modify it and put it up in the bedroom because it gets so hot. I'm going to paint the front bedroom next week, and then I'll attack the back bedroom.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tomorrow morning I'm driving down to Santa Barbara to see Melissa, and then on Wednesday we're going to Disneyland! I'm excited about it, and especially going with Melissa (my old college roommate) who is super-mellow and super-cool (I'm pretty sure she reads the blog). Then I'll spend Thursday driving back, thus taking advantage of my non-employed status fully. No more posting for a few days. I'll report on the trip when I get back.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The shower was a success. Despite all of my angst and last minute insanity, I had a blast, and I think everyone else did. We played just enough shower games to be funny, but mostly everyone sat around and talked, ate, and cooed at adorable baby clothes. Thanks to everyone who came, and especially to Alex, who really came through in the last minute food prep that sort of freaked me out. I'm really glad that everything turned out so well. It was a lot of fun. See the silly pictures below as proof. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Trina and her bum foot--stupid bees, stinging people in the foot&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    No way! Babies do what? Why didn't anyone tell me before?&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    somebody said something embarrassing!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Alexa and Valerie looking pretty--I'm marrying into a good-looking family!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Holly, Lisa and Fiona all looking pretty for the shower. Thanks for coming guys!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Yay! A car-seat-stroller-thingy!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    oh! cute little baby clothes!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mom and Catherine looking pretty, smiling at cute baby things&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Stylish and preggers: the new hot trend my sister is better at...&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Baby carrot cake; or, my twisted sense of humor.&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Lisa's ring and talk of diamonds inspired me... plus I got a new digital camera! Yay!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The landlord has been talking for years about cutting down the beautiful redwood in the backyard, and after sending over random guys without notice to look at the tree (one of whom scared the hell out of me, because suddenly a man was walking into the back yard), the landlord came by yesterday to tell me that they were going to trim the tree, and that they were coming at 8:30am. Well, thankfully they didn't come quite that early, but there sure have been a lot of loud and crazy noises--and I have no idea were they moved our tomato plant to. This more any more makes it clear that I want to own my own home, and it sucks to be at the mercy of the landlord. Now we've lost a great deal of privacy that we gained from the trees out front and the tree in back, and now we really can't walk around naked as much anymore... Also, I need to be less shy about talking to the landlord, but I've been feeling lame and withdrawn today, working on weddings and such in the office. Bleh. Oh well, at least when I type I feel like I'm getting something done and I probably look like I'm working and doing something productive. I guess I ought to work on my resume to actually feel productive.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really like  urlLink this set up for the alter ; it's just simply drapped tulle that we can do ourselves cheaply. Also, I really love the  urlLink bridemaids' dresses , or at least the color and cut of the skirt. I think my girls will all need different tops, but hopefully I can ask for knee-length A-line skirts like this. I really like  urlLink these bouquets . More brainstorming to come.  edit: it looks like the bouquet site won't let me post specific pictures, but if you click through, the wedding cake is lovely too.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went over my Birkman with Jeremiah's uncle Roger today, and I learned a lot about the way I operate and why I act the way I do. But I also feel emotionally drained, and not so talkative...that's because I have low activity needs, and I need to take time to be calm after times of stress.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I know I shouldn't since the diamond is a family heirloom, but   urlLink this article  makes me feel guilty about my engagment ring. Oh well, I can justify it because the stone is antique and the ring was created for us by Fiona... and though my wedding band is diamond, it too is an heirloom. So here's the question: Are diamonds ethically okay if they are old? I tell myself that I'm much better than girls who wear gigantic rocks from DeBeers, or am I just a hypocrite? At least my ring is small.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been suffering from intense existential crisis because I have no clue what I want to be when I grow up, and since I've already finished my degree, I really ought to have that figured out soon. I'm beginning to realize that I need to pick a path and follow it, because I'm not going to get anywhere just sitting around waiting for things to happen. I have no skills.  Other than the massively depressing state of my "career," Jerm and I have set a date for our wedding, so we can now begin the countdown: June 25, 2005. Yay! Mark your calendars people. Maybe soon I'll send out save the date emails and notes. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm really hankering after this  urlLink flower tee  from Fred Flare. Also, I've been getting all bridal, and I really like these  urlLink blue shoes  to fulfull my "something blue" requirement. I've been also obsessed by the idea of a dress like  urlLink this one  from Vera Wang, but clearly it costs way too much for me!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been trying to catch up on housekeeping because of my busy week. Yesterday I drove Catherine back to Stockton, and just as we got into town I got a call from my mom asking if I would be willing to work a temp job next week (my mom works at a temp agency and has gotten jobs for the whole family, just not me yet). Because she and Catherine are going to Florida next week, her office needs a little help covering the front desk, answering phones and basic data entry. I told my mom the I was in Stockton, and so I went on in to fill out applications and go over a basic interview with my mom's co-worker, Marisol. This morning their manager (whose name I can't remember!) called and asked a few basic questions, and basically seemed to think I could do the work since I was a college graduate. Now it looks like I'll have a low level clerical job like Melissa, but it's only for a week, and I'll be spending the week in Stockton, visiting with my dad and Neb, and staying in the pool house. I think it ought to be an interesting week, and I'm glad I've been working on my blog and writing a lot of papers so I can type pretty competently.   So today I've been trying to catch up on the laundry that I fell so far behind since we had all of the guests last weekend. Tonight I'm going to Jerm's mom's for dinner, then I'm going to head out to Stockton once again to take my mom and Catherine to the airport in Sacramento for their trip to Florida. Then on Saturday, Jerm and I will work on my car and hopefully get a present for Alexa for her birthday party on Saturday night. I'm looking forward to the party, because it will give me an excuse to dress up and look pretty. Yay.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent all day yesterday with my dad and Neb, which was really pleasant. I had lunch with Mom, Dad and Catherine at El Senor Frogs (the mexican place at the end of the street). Then after taking Catherine to Delta College to get herself enrolled and take her assessment test, I spent the afternoon yakking with my dad and Neb. It was really nice and nostalgic, and I'm glad to see Dad and Neb making the house a home.  In related news, the cats are driving me bonkers. Judy is such a wimp! She won't defend her food against the kitten (I'm thinking Estella now...) and she won't just put the cat in her place. It's getting really frustrating, because I really want Judy to eat. Ack!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent today helping my sister and her baby daddy move stuff. See, pregnant ladies can't lift ANYTHING, so because I'm a selfless sister, I offered to hurt my back and fill in on the heavy lifting. Fortunately for me, but sadly for them, I can't go up to Humbolt with them to help with that end of lifting.   Also, in the course of helping them move, I met their new kitten they were taking care of, and I decided, after much consideration, to bring her home. Right now she and Judy are coming to some sort of kitty agreement, and I kind of want to name the kitten Pantelones, or maybe Pam. I'm just not sure, but it does need to be slightly ironic and weird. What about Iris? I'm feeling the old lady names....  As to the previous post; I had so much fun hanging out and chatting with Liz H. I really missed her, and visiting reminded me of how lonely I am for close female friends. A boyfriend is nice, but should not replace girlfriends at all. Discuss.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so this is the other Liz here typing on Liz's blog while she is busy typing on mine.  We decided that it would be a good idea to change blog entries while we were semi-drunk.  I'm at Liz's house in Oakland right now.  It's the first time that I've been here in the almost two years that I've known Liz.  It's been a good time so far...I don't really know what to say since I feel awkward typing on someone else's blog...esp since Liz is so smart and correct that I really feel like I might be fu**ing this up.  Wow...Jerm is doing something funky to the bed which is shaking the desk.   Something just fell off the bed and it caused a large comotion...can I spell in this state?  Can I spell anyway?  Jerm just said something about the slice about Liz'z johnson...the johnson that I don't think that she has...Jerm has now promised that he will be cool and suave...there goes the desk again.  Liz now feels the need to download pictures...  Which brings me to my next point...why do people feel the need to take pictures all the time?  Can't we all just hold the memories in our heads?  Why do we need pictures to tell us that we are uglier than we are...  Hmmm...what is Liz putting in my blog?  I really don't have anything smart to say at this point. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    still figuring out the haircut, but I like the earrings&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    the new kitten being fiesty in the doorway&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My dad isn't looking so good since he had to take a flying leap off of his killer horse, Twister. That's a broken wrist, and look at the bruising on the other arm!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>