<Blog>



<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today at my church we had communion and there were little pieces of bread nicley cut, not crudely.  So who does cut up all those pieces of bread?
     

        
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      How much wood would a wood cutter cut if a wood cutter could cut would?
     

        
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      what is the average size of a clam?
     

        
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      the cow jumped over the moon, why?
     

        
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Why do they make overpasses different heights?  I mean Some are 15'9" and others are 16'9".  why not have a standard size.
     

        
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If you drained Boca Resavouir(however that is spelt) how much money would be there.  How many Pennies?  How many nickels?  How many Dimes?  How many quarters?  How many 50 cent pieces?  How many dollar pieces?  How many Susan Bs?  How many cows?  How many gold coins?  How many sunken ships?  How many pesos?  Well that was just a random thought I had at Boca today.  
     

        
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I dont have any randomthoughts at the momment other than a funny pick up line from Juanna  You must be a parking ticket because you got fine fine fine written all over you.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well today I went to help Timmy with his car.  His battery died.  I went in there with the battery and was going to act stupid.  And say  Hey can I get a refill, do you just refill it with joules or calories, or does it really matter.  Which would you perfer to fill it with, it sure doesn't make a difference to me.  So what ever you want unless one is cheaper.     
     

        
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      have have ever wondered why we wash bath towels arent we cleaned when we get out of the shower.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Toucan is spelled toucan not tucan so ha I win.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      How do you spell toucan?  The bird.  Is it tocan,  tucan, two can, toucan, toocan, twocan,  hmmmmmm the world may never know.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My bro and I were walking along and we saw an ostrich take flight.  THen we saw a bear with toucan on its shoulder.  It was cool.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      One day you are sitting in a car on a nice sunny day and all of a sudden the sun burns out.  What do you do?  How long will you live?  
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      “You know, you look really hot. You must be the real reason for global warming.”  “Is there an airport nearby or is that just my heart taking off?”  “If I could rearrange the alphabet, I’d put U and I together.”   "Did it hurt...when you fell to Earth from Heaven?"   Do your feet hurt,... cus you have been running through my mind all day
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My fried Paul brought it to my attention  You are in an area that says no smoking.  YOu see a hottie you go over and say  Hey there is no smoking she replies I'm not smoking you say from my point of view you are.  I know that there are many more like that one but hey its funny
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I change this sign because my boss told me too.     Aint that hilarious
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There was this guy at camp and he said  DANIEL DANIEL WANT TO SING A SONG?  LETS SING OH MY DARLING!  You had to have bean there to find it funny.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just can't think of any random thoughts.  hmmmmmmmm
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Translate that! HA
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tommora I will be going into  Texas which I have never bean to before, and I will go into 4 other air spaces I have never bean.  I believe that would be NEw Mexixco. Texas, Kansas and may be Misoura!  YEah   Piece of Pie out  ALex
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is awesome there are so many people on blogger from Reno.  WOoo HOoo!! 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>