<Blog>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's Tuesday. Tuesday is supposed to be happy. But it's not.  Yesterday Boots ran to my house to give me a hug. RAN. A mile and a half! And I got grounded for it. I can't go to Fantasy Shop Friday, no biggie, I wasn't going anyway, but the fact that I got grounded really pisses me off.  I have a presentation tonight in Ethics. I hate ethics. I just went over the rubric again and found out I'm missing a bunch of stuff. Yarr.  I still think Dave and I have some issues. He's too uptight sometimes. I wish he would just sit back and chill for a while. He needs a break. Badly.  I started watching GTO yesterday. Got through the second episode, then Boots showed up.  I accidentally deleted my massive hangman game project. I worked fripping hard on it, and my teacher had just fixed all the bugs yesterday too. Crap on a stick.  I talked to Sez, she's going to make an overhead for me tomorrow for my Spanish side-project. I want to start painting it now, I'm so psyched about having my poster done.  I'm absolutely exhausted. Took those allergy pills this morning before school, and they kicked in during Algebra. In the middle of a problem, too. I'm so drowsy. I'm hungry too. Had a bagel for breakfast, but I guess it didn't fill me up.  Yarr, everyone keeps taking my computer in the spectra room. I don't know how I'm supposed to work on CSI if they keep using it. I'm so incredibly hungry I think I'm going to explode.  Stuff sucks. I hate it all. I feel Dave is mad at me for some odd reason. I wouldn't blame him. I'm a mean person like that. I want to crawl into my hole, but someone filled it in with cement. I should kill whoever it was. Yarr.   Current Mood:  Angry   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I’m such a mean person. I can’t stand it. I hate who I am and how I act. I keep getting these sparks that say “HEY ASSHOLE, BE NICE FOR ONCE!” I’ve never been able to though, and it hurts. Sometimes I wish everyone would go away and leave me alone. Lane, Ginny, Boots, Noodle, Dave,  EVERYONE . I wish I could move away and start all over, and be that friendless girl who goes out of her way to assist the people who pick on her. I may not have any friends that way, but at least it wouldn’t be from the fact that I’m mean.  I hate being mean. I get a lot of respect that way. People fear me. And the people who don’t fear me and still manage to become my friends won’t open up to me. Some friends I have. They can’t talk to me about how they feel. And all I do is cry over it. I’m so weak. Everyone hates me. Some just do a damn good job of covering it up.  I’m starting to doubt my friendships. I don’t think they really even exist any more, and they’ve just become facades to keep from hurting my feelings.  I want to break up with Dave. I’m hurting him, I can tell. He won’t admit it though. He doesn’t want to hurt my feelings. I don’t even know why he cares. Nobody else does.  I’m such a liar. I lie to everyone. It’s become a habit. I don’t blame anyone for not believing what I say. Why would anyone care what a liar says? I even lie to myself. It disgusts me.  I want to dies. I want to stop hurting others. Especially my little brother. Oh, how he  hates  me! He’d throw a party commemorating my death and all of my “friends” would attend. I suppose that being a gifted middle class child means I have real potential, but I’ll never live up to it. I might as well just die.  I wish I could cut myself. But I’m a weenie, so I can’t. I pulled a muscle in my thigh the other day. It hurts when I walk on it. So I walk on it. I pinch it and poke it and hit it. It feels so good. But it’s not enough. I’m still waiting for that thunderstorm to strike down the tree that falls over and kills me. No one will miss me in the long run. Once my friends marry, their memories of me will disappear.  I can’t stop the pain. The tears won’t cease from flowing. I cried last night for two hours. And I’m not talking about moping around and tearing. I cried. But of course I had music on so no one could hear me. I want to be left alone. I’ve never felt this kind of pain before. Not even when I went to the hospital last Memorial Day weekend. That wasn’t real pain. But this is.  I have so many regrets. They outnumber the things I don’t regret. Life has lost its luster. I have no purpose any more. I’m perfectly expendable. My friends can get new friends. My boyfriend can go back to that girl in New Jersey. My family won’t miss one member.   Told someone not too long ago that I found happiness in the experiences with my friends. But they don’t find happiness there. So the experiences are meaningless now. I have to find a new way to become happy. Somehow I don’t think it will happen.  I want to bleed, but my heart is so cold that blood doesn’t even flow through my veins. If I cut myself, thick black tar would ooze out. The mirror shrivels up in disgust with one look at me. It eyes me with impending regret.  I laugh at myself. Even though I have a heart of stone, I call myself soft. It makes my hysterical.  Are these feelings real? No. I don’t love anyone. Not even Dave. I’m living a lie. I’m such a liar. But he doesn’t love me either. If he did, he would tell me what’s bothering him when I ask him, not hours later in a faceless email. If he loved me, he would defend me in a fight if he supported my side. But instead he takes the luxury of standing back and watching while my world rips me to shreds for thinking independently like a rotweiler rips up a baby squirrel. He doesn’t love me, and I don’t love him. But of course I can’t say that to his face. I’m weak like that. Besides, if he can’t tell me how he feels, why should I?  I just wish everyone would go away...   Current Mood:  Cold   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       …Well, not really washing so much as “pre-soaking.” Let’s start with yesterday afternoon and work into the evening and night.  I met Matt-type person. He’s cool and stuff, and he’s the only one I know that can make Shippo remotely cool and not want to squish him.  Adam dragged his group over to “repay the favor” of Boots, Ryan, and me visiting them last week. They played Dustin’s game (well, started making characters anyway). Dustin and I are apparently “cool,” since most of the time we lash out at each other, but we didn’t. I guess he earnestly accepted my apology after all.  The other group’s arrival made Dave really stressed. I hated not being able to comfort him. And Lane came, who we were not expecting to come until our next meeting (and apparently neither was she). That really added to his stress since he was totally unprepared.  Dustin was originally going to talk to Dave at the end of his game (or so I was told), but that never happened. I don’t think either of them has any intentions in resolving their problems, and I think if something doesn’t happen soon, all hell will break loose. Not that it’s any of my business. Somehow I feel I’ll get stuck somewhere in the middle…  So then the end of the night came and I noticed Boots had some scratches on her arm. I looked a bit closer and saw they were worn-out letters she had cut. It said "Just a Phase" (I didn't know it at the time that it was exactly what it said, my guess of "just a while" was close"). I confronted her about it at least twice and she kept dodging me. I felt terrible that she couldn’t tell me about it. I tell her about everything about me (well, 99.99% anyway, there are some things about me that no one knows, and I intend to keep it that way), and 97% of the time she’s the first to know (2% goes to Dave, .5% to Ginny and Lane each). But even still, a lot of the things in her DeadJournal were totally new to me, I mean she’s REALLY good at hiding her emotions, but this was just ridiculous. It makes me feel terrible that my best friend can’t tell me about her problems. Sure, I’m not good at giving advice, but a make a damn good sympathetic ear, if there is such a thing. I wanted to cry for her when I went to bed, but I didn’t know what was going on with her life, so I decided to save my tears for a rainy day. I just hope it doesn’t come for a very long time, if at all. Her friendship is important to me, and I would hate to loose her.   Current Mood:  Worried   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, I'm grounded from the internet. This week and possibly next week, starting yesterday. I'm at my computer apps class now so I get internet anyway.  I think I'll start with yesterday, seeing as it came first. I got grounded and stuff, then Noodle knocks on my door and decides that I should be kidnapped. So I get to the church and Boots decides we should bring Dave along. So we walk a mile to meet him halfway at QT, then walk a mile back. We go to church, stuff happens, Dave nearly drowns in the drinking fountain (twice, hee hee), and I go home.  Next day! It sucks! 'Cept in programming class I logged into blogger real quick to see if I could squeeze in a quick post (which I never did) and I got an offer to join Google Mail (GMail, apparently). I heart Google. Drew tried to cheat Google and sign up for an account and he failed miserably. It was funny.   Then in Spanish Mrs. Wunderlich gave me a proposal to make a HUGE hall poster, which I worked on whilst at home. I'm going to give her the rough draft tomorrow. Pa says he might get me some paints to work with on Saturday, depending on when I start working on the actual poster.  And now, I'm in "Advanced Computer Applications" class, and hating every minute of it. Yarr, boring stuff. I just can't wait till it's Friday though, but I fear it will be a short one and the weekend will be VERY long. Homework on Saturday, family on Sunday, school on Monday (ick). School is boring. Only three more weeks of college though, thank goodness. Although I've been needing to get in my registration stuffs, I've had it ready but I have to pester the guidance office at my high school still.  I think that about covers everything, I'll be playing Mortal Kind (a screwey version of a cross between modern d20 and d&amp;d) tomorrow so no blogging until Saturday, assuming I find the time. And no blogging Sunday probably either. I'll see you all whenever. Or not.   Current Mood:  Blah.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well apparently I can't go to Dave's to help him rearrange his room cause my great aunt (grandma's sister) is coming into town on Sunday. Crapola. Like crayola, except not.  I saw Puni Puni Poemy today. It burns real good, like jalapenos. If I were a dude I'd totally whack off to it. But I lack the equipment, so no whacking off for me.  It feels like Friday. It should be. At least MAP blocks are finally over. Ugh, an hour and a half around people I don't like. I took some antihistamine and it made me super-drowsy. I could barely stay awake in class. Sleep is good... But naturally, I'm not tired now. Go figure.   Current Mood:  Frustrated   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yay, me and Dave are back on good terms with each other! Too bad he and Dustin aren't. Oh well, it's not my problem anymore.  I felt really good today when Adam said he liked having members of my group around. Apparently we make the game fun. Too bad all of them are going to die, bwahahahaha... Yes, I shall kill them all with my toaster of doom! Anywho...  I can't wait for Saturday. All I've been told is that it involves duck tape. Kinky.   Current Mood:  Curious     
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hate my ethics class. I love the teacher, and I love the students, but the class is boring. I just finished three surveys on the school and class and my future plans and ugh this is boring. I hate having to go to college, it eats up free time. I don't mind the summer classes though, since they provide me with the excuse that I can't take a whole week to go to my mum's down in Dora (four hour drive, evil). However, the wire bends the other way since I can't take a week off to go down to Arkansas, and thusly have to wait until early August. I'm looking forward to it though, I'm supposed to get a suprise from Dave...   Current Mood:  Curious   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think it's time to introduce you all to Lindsay. She is a bad person to be around. I used to be her friend, until I got sick of her crap and she showed my kid brother porn when I told her not to, and even when he said he didn't want to see. What a great friend. She did apologize, but she starts so much crap that I'm not one to forgive her that easily. She told Dave that she had changed and accepted Jesus into her life to help lead her way, but that's just a load of bull. I caught her lighting up at the bus stop after I was dropped off. Way to be Linz, breaking the law. Fyi, being seventeen does not mean you can do whatever you want. She harasses people, does drugs, drinks, gossips, and sleeps around. She breaks numerous rules (both at home and at school), goofs off constantly, lies, and gossips. Did I mention she gossips? She tries to fit in, and that's about it. She's not worth another minute of my time. I try to surround myself with generally good people, and she is, was, and never will be someone I want to be around.  Here's to you, bioch.   Current Mood:  Pissed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Adam told me this morning that Dave was having cable problems so he wasn't mad at me or anything. Thank goodness.  Ugh, sitting in Programming II and I'm starving! We have third lunch at 11:40 and I normally have 4a lunch which starts at 10:15 so yeah... it's not a good combination. Today has been exceptionally long. It felt like 7th period last block and I wanted to go home soo bad! I really can't stay on task, like I have ADD or something. I would say ADHD, but I'm not the least bit hyper today.   Current Mood:  Hungry   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So what am I doing on my computer at 6 in the morning? Well, I checked my email and Dave didn't even email me. So I have to assume he died. Which somewhat worries me. If he's still alive, there's a slim chance he'll be online tonight since he has his Tuesday game. And yes, even though I'm more worried, I'm still incredibly pissed.   Current Mood:  Pissed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Pa decided to kill a spider which happened to be located on the lampshade. He swatted at it with a rolled up magazine, killing the light bulb. There was a big flash and a pop sound and then sudden darkness. He turned another light on and said, "hey, at least the spider died." Smooth. Way to go, pa.  Dave hasn't been on all day. I'm kinda worried, since he's always on, minus Tuesdays, occasional Thursday afternoons, and Fridays. But today is Monday. So I'm worried. There's a million and one things that could have happened to him, and naturally all of the causes point to me, cause I'm like that. Stuff always seems to be my fault. My mum always told me that. What a self-esteem booster. Here's to you, mum.   Current Mood:  Too fluxuating to pick one emoticon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, apparently today is my brother's eleventh birthday. I've been remembering all week. Except today. Well, it's not like he cares as long as he gets his Yu Gi Oh cards/money. Mum's birthday was Saturday, but she didn't come into town until yesterday. I hate my mum...  I had to help mum pack her stuff yesterday. "Lift with your legs, not with your arms." Well now my legs feel like they'll give way any second. Right thigh and left calf, both sore as heck. Stuff hates me like that.   Current Mood:  Indescribable   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I thought I needed to share this. I remember those cows. They were popular in 8th grade. They had piggies too. Mmmm poopy....   urlLink CLIKIE!    I'm fucking pissed. And Dave not being online isn't helping, I really need to talk with him, but not before beating his ass into the ground for LYING to me.   Current Mood:  Amused    Pissed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well Drew got lucky, we wound up doing a lab in biology instead of presenting.  I talked to Nick at lunch, he backed me up on the Dave vs. Dustin fiasco. I talked to Boots after school, and even though she hasn't known them as long as some of the other guys, she too agreed. I want to strangle Dave. Yet for some reason I can't find it in my heart to leave him. We have some good things going for us, but now I'm getting mushy so I'll shutup.  Two boys (and I emphasize the word "boys") jumped out of the second story window of the A Building at school today during my last block. The window had broken so they decided to defy the teacher when she told them to not jump. Ah, ignorance must be bliss...  Except it's not. Don't even get me started on that, ugh.  Also, there was a snake on a desk in first block. Everyone was scared. I would've taken it outside myself since it was only a garter snake, but Mr. Davis had already been called to come get it. He walked in, casually grabbed the snake, chatted with Mr. Branson (my driver's ed teacher), and walked out. No one knows what happened to the snake. Well, not me anyway.   Current Mood:  Bored   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome to my journal. As you can tell, it has died. Right now I'm at school. I'm in the "gifted and talented program," also known as "Spectra" and "Seznak's Room of Hell." More on that later.  Yes, I realize this layout is ugly and sucks. My "friend" Drew is working on it for me. I'm lazy so I don't do my own work. We have a biology project we have to present next hour and he forgot his stuff. I'm mad, but at least it wasn't as bad as last night. No, it wasn't that you perverts. Besides, I have a boyfriend.  Dave (my boyfriend) and I got into an argument yesterday. It was about Dustin, one of his alleged friends. I told him that from what I've heard they've both treated each other like crap since they met, but he begs to differ. I talked to Adam at the bench this morning, and he told me I was right. What a liar! I really hate it when people lie to me, especially when they go without lying for so long. Now I doubt all the other things he says. Especially since a while back he sent me an email telling me to break up with him (trust me, it wasn't the first). Then he sent me two more apologizing and taking back what he said cause he didn't mean it. So what does he mean? When am I supposed to believe him? I think I'll consult Monica. She's like my Deadjournal. This is like my Deadjournal too, except I don't have a Deadjournal and I've been using Monica as a Deadjournal longer than this blog. Yarr, Sez of Hell is pestering me, I'll write more later.   Current Mood:  Annoyed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       KER-LAYOUT CHANGE!!! I heart the spots. And now my Guestbook is dead. I ate it. Blogger lets me have my own spiffy direct comments now. Schuiite.  Back to the topic of this post: I drew this super-spiffy picture of my intepretation of death a while back and I thought I'd share it with you. You can see it by clicking  urlLink here . I never finished her feet, but I don't really care.   Current Mood:  Artistic   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw Forrest Gump for the first time today. I cried at the end. Not for what happened in the movie though. It got me thinking about how mean I am. Movies like that tend to do that to me. I cried because I did a horrible thing yesterday. I played with someone's emotions like a toy bulldozer. I'll never forget the look on his face when he found out it was a joke. He looked angry, like he wanted to hit me. I wouldn't have blamed him if he did. I kind of wish he did though. I deserve it. When I looked him in the eyes, I was so afraid. Not for what would happen to me, but what would happen to him. I didn't know what he was going to do, to me or himself. I thought he didn't want anything to do with me ever again. It wouldn't suprise me if that had been the case. We worked it out and called it even since he had played a joke on me too, but I still feel so bad since I had played with his emotions, and his joke was much more shallow. I'll never forget yesterday. I don't think I'll ever be completely over it, either. He forgave me for what I did, and I forgave him for what he did, but I still can't forgive myself. I never will. I don't know how he can be such a forgiving person. Or how he can put up with my dishonesty or selfishness or how incredibly ill-tempered I can be. I don't think I'll ever forget his kindness, either.   Current Mood:  Sad   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm dispicable. I'm a lowly creature that doesn't deserve what she has. I got mad at someone for something they didn't do and wasn't their fault. I got angry for no reason and took it out on them. They probably didn't even notice, which makes me even more mad. And I shouldn't be mad for that either. I'm dispicable.  Today when I went to FS I felt neglected cause I couldn't be around Dave. I shouldn't go anymore when I'm not playing, I take it personally like he's ignoring me. I know that he's playing with the other group, but for some reason I still have irrational neglected feelings. Not to mention that none of the other players like me. Except Dave and Adam, Dave cause he's supposed to, Adam cause he's been around me a lot and is used to my absolute annoyingness.  We did talk here and there to each other, but not much. And once he winked at me, but I was still irrationally mad so I just glared at him. I tried to avoid eye contact with him as much as I could unless I was glaring. I'm so despicable.  So when we got bored (we being Monica Ryan and me), we left. I didn't even say goodbye to him. What the hell is wrong with me? I simply stood up, gathered my stuff, turned around, and left. No hugs, no waves, no words. I'm so arrogant.  I still don't see why the hell I was mad at him for something he wasn't at fault for and couldn't even control. I have an awful habit of taking things out on people who are irrelevant to the situation which caused me whichever emotion. I disgust me.  And furthermore, I met another guy. Well, not really met, I already knew him, but I think I might have feelings for him. I don't want to though. I can't see myself being with him. Even with Dave out of the picture (past and present), I don't think I'd let it happen. He's not really in my taste. And he's not serious about enough stuff. He's cute and that's about it. I don't even know how I could consider having feelings for him. I don't think my feelings are serious though. I sure hope not. But it wouldn't suprise me if I left Dave only to screw myself over. I'm arrogant and selfish and dispicable like that. I think I need some time to myself for a while. Too bad I'm busy this weekend and the next week and Friday night and Memorial Day Weekend and fuck it. I just don't get time to myself anymore. I guess it's a price I have to pay for being me.  Btw, no, I won't tell anyone who the guy is. Don't pester me about it. End of story. Period.   Current Mood:  Turned Away   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I drew this and I thought it needed to be shared with everyone. Now all you stalker-type people know what I look like. Sortof.   urlLink Click to see the pretty picture!   Btw, for those of you who can't read the note for whatever reason, it reads as follows: "Dedicated to all my friends: Thanks for making everything worthwhile"  And the chibi says "Nyao!"  Yes, I actually have a shirt like that (see link at end of post). The grayish ring is my hematite one, and I usually have it on a chain, but it didn't work in the picture like that. The other one is my graduation ring, which I'll eventually get pictures of. Maybe. And don't ask about the black X on my hand. Only the members of the Cult of the X would know what that's for.  YAY FOR STUFF!  You can get a shirt like the one in the picture  urlLink here .   Current Mood:  Artistic   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We watched Spongebob Squarepants in biology today since we were studying invertebrates. I just thought that needed mentioning.  Boots drew me this prettyful picture that you can looksie at by clicking  urlLink here . Boots is the one in the apron, I'm the one with the Chinese-style shirt.  I'm sick of school. Is it over yet? At least my college classes end next week. It's a shame I can't say the same about high school.  I got my prettyful class ring today. All bow down to the engraved dragon. The stone has this shiney stuff behind it that makes me dizzy from looking at it. It was funny. And the ring came in one of those fuzzy box thingies. I proposed to three people. Only one said yes though.   Current Mood:  Ditzy   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think I'm seeing a pattern in the titles of my posts...  For possibly the first time in the memorable history of my life, my brother showed that he loved me.  After he got home from school today, he did his homework, I was typing a report, it seemed like any other day (except most of the time he comes in screaming and all hyper-like, I like the quiet so I didn't question it). Then he got the bright idea of playing his recorder. In the kitchen. Which he has known to be against house rules since I started band in fifth grade. Me, being the easily irratable person I am, step in and tell him to take his musical mojo elsewhere. And, big suprise, we fight, he winds up overreacting like the drama queen he is and cries.  Then it hit me: I was going to go to Dave's tomorrow, so if I want to keep my ass from getting grounded, I'd have to fix it, and fast. Running out of ideas, I suck up my pride through a straw and apologize. Sincerely. Well, enough to fool him anyway. He's gullable like that. Anywho, it turns out he had a super-crappy day, bullies and such, and we both wind up crying on the kitchen floor. Ok, I wasn't crying, but I felt like crying. Sorry for having a heart of stone. But the bottom line is that I know what it's like to be bullied in school. (Off topic: anyone notice how it's bullying in elementary school but it's harassment in middle and high school? it just occured to me...)  So after a long discussion on what he had done and what he should do about it, I take a stroll down memory lane, pa comes home and voila! I'm saved from Grounded City. And then Zack defended me from pa about something, I don't know.... but it seemed like he really cared.  I guess it was bad since I was only trying to keep myself from getting grounded, but hey, it's a win-win situation. And for once my brother shows that he cares.   Current Mood:  Appreciated   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just realized the other day how much I take Monica for granted. She does so much for me, and even though the things she does may seem small or take little effort, they mean a lot to me, and she has really changed my life on many occasions.  Take for instance, anime. Even though it was Abby who introduced me to this genre of entertainment, Monica was the one who really inspired me to draw. If it weren't for her drawing alongside me, I probably wouldn't be as good as I am. Heck, I probably would have given up on drawing completely.  Then there's me and Dave. She was the one who got us together (Nick gets no credit whatsoever, he got us to meet but he never followed through, so no biscut for him). She was the one who beat the true feelings out of me, then beat them into Dave so he'd ask me out. She's lectured him a lot for me too. If it weren't for her, I don't think we would have lasted this long.  Not convinced yet? How about the time she rand a mile and a half to my house just to give me a hug? We've had some good times together, and for that I'm grateful. I really appreciate her being there for me, and for being my friend. Thank you Monica, for everything you've done for me. You're like a sister to me, even when you're at school trying to strangle me. I love you Monica, don't you ever leave me.  (For all you perverts out there, I'm straight, so don't get any wise ideas)   Current Mood:  Loved   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so I know I was going to get asked about this quite a bit, so why not just explain it here and provide a link? Less typing for me. Anyway...  I was supposed to go to Noodle's birthday party yesterday. I went, but I also said I'd stay the night there, which wasn't quite what happened. Frankly, I'm bored by talks of God and Jesus and church from people I don't know. I'm not comfortable around Christians or strangers, let alone Christian strangers. So anyway, Monica said she was going and probably dragging Ryan with her. When I show up, there was no sign of either of them. When I finally get ahold of them, Monica said she'd stay the night with me so I wouldn't be on my own.  When her and Ryan get there, we decided to ditch the party. We wound up hanging out in my backyard since there was no way for me to sneak into my house without risking waking up my dad. After an hour of getting eaten by bugs, we concoct a better plan: sleep in Ryan's car in front of his house so I'm technically not home and no one else can track me or Monica down. And, we came up of plenty of excuses for various situations during one of our discussions.  We (me and Ryan) wound up talking until 3:30-ish in the morning (Monica fell asleep an hour earlier) about a lot of different stuff. I can't remember the details of any topic in particular. But anywho, I found out his car isn't very comfortable, but I wasn't complaining since he slept with us out there, despite his house being across the street. I think I only got 30 minutes of solid sleep, the rest of the time drifting in and out whilst tossing and turning every once in a while. Ryan and I got up around 5:15 (and neither of us knew how that happened), while Monica got up around 5:35. We sat in his car until 6, then drove to my house since my dad had left for work by then.  And, well, that concludes the sleepover part. The rest of the day was me entertaining (or at least attempting to entertain) Mon and Ryan until about 4 p.m. since Ryan had to go to work.  Man, I wish I could have interesting sleepovers like that more often...   Current Mood  FWEE!   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dammit, I hate drama. I'm sick of it. It makes me want to lay down and die. I seem to have unbeknownstly dragged Monica into it too, and I feel really bad for it. She said she was tired of being the moderator and had her own problems. I feel so selfish now. I told Ginny about my problems, and she seemed a little resentful about me pouring them onto her. Mon and Gin both have their share of problems, they don't need mine. *sigh* The ones i need to care the most don't care (although I can't say I blame them), and the ones i need to care the least wind up caring too much. I hate people who try to fix things that aren't broken. If I don't ask for help, then I don't want/need it. So fuck off.  I'm sick of dealing with people! Let me be detached and blissful in peace!   Current Mood:  Angry   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hate stuff. I wish sometimes that people would get a clue. I hate being pestered. It's so annoying. Everyone has to know what I'm doing, what's wrong with me, how they can help, who I like, who I don't like, what I'm doing next Tuesday, and so on and so forth. Dammit, can't people just leave me alone and let me solve my own problems? Has it ever occurred to anyone that if I wanted help I'd just  ask ? What a novel idea! Too bad a lot of people I know are complete MORONS.  I don't trust anyone anymore. I have no reason to. Except Monica. I've known her for a very long time (what most would consider too long), so I have to trust her. But I don't have the capacity to trust anyone else anymore. I'm sick and tired of having to deal with people, especially ones I wouldn't have to deal with if it weren't my affiliation with some common person. I'm tired of being toyed with. I'm tired of all of these "friendship rings" and all the drama created by them. That's one of the many reasons I left Lindsay. I was sick of the shit. And I'll tell you something, I won't get used to it. Why won't anyone just leave me alone?!   Current Mood:  ANGRY! GRRR!!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, time to continue my explanation on why I have been so completely gone.  I visited my mother for four days (noonish last Friday to yesterday evening). She's living with her sister, who lives in the middle of Southern Missouri (a little town called Dora, if you want to know, and the whole town is basically Roy's Store (which is like a hick version of CFM) and some gas station). My grandmother lives there too. The drive down there is four hours (three and a half if Pa is driving). My aunt has become a grandmother herself. Her grandson is still in ICU though. He was a premie (sp?). He's six and a half weeks old now. He's almost three pounds, and the hospital plans to keep him for about another five and a half weeks. But back to the point I have yet to really get to. I learned a few things on my visit.  First of all, I learned what gives guys their distinct guy smell. It's the shampoo. If you use it, the scent will not go away, even if your life depends on it. I walked around for three days smelling like dude. It wasn't that bad, I like the smell of guys with good hygene. I wish girls' shampoo was that potent. Suave makes some damn good smelling stuff, but it doesn't last. The smell goes away as soon as I rinse the shampoo out of my hair. But for some reason, Suave for Men sticks to you.  Second, I have a really hot cousin. I would pay good money to do him. He is the sex god of the fluffy bunnies. The best of both of my guy worlds. But dammit, he's my cousin. The world hates me! I guess it's kindof a good thing though, he smokes, and me and cigarettes don't mix very well.  Third, I can take a lot more pain than I thought I could. I got some bad sunburn when I went floating with my aunt Mary, Mum, Zack, uncle Dean, aunt Nancy, Trent (the hot cousin), and Kelly (Trent's friend, I think she's his girlfriend, lucky duck, I envy her). When I got home, I took a hot shower. I knew it would sting. And it did. Like a bitch. But I didn't cringe and whine like I normally do. I'm getting tougher. Maybe. I dunno. It was just one of those weird things.  Fourth, my mother STILL has no consideration for others. Or at least me. I nearly choked to death on the float trip and the car ride from Dora to Rolla (roughly a two hour ride). On the float trip, she  had  to sit in the front of the boat and I  had  to sit behind her and tempt myself to tip the canoe so the ones she had left (along with the ones she was smoking) would be ruined. Again, the world hates me.  Fifth, I did a lot of thinking while I was away. It was one of the few things to do. I thought a lot about God. I prayed a lot too. And I questioned my beliefs. I realize that I was more secure as a Pagan. I didn't fear as many things as I do now. I wasn't so paranoid and insecure as I am now. I'm a nervous wreck now. The afterlife scares me. Sometimes I almost wish I was Pagan again, just so I would be so afraid. And I hate Christians. I can't get much more hypocritical. Well, sortof. I hate them because they try to force their beliefs onto other people (mostly the Protestants more often than Catholics). I hate people like that. They're the reason homosexual people can't marry. They're the ones who thought AIDS was a gay disease (morons). They're the reason we're at "war" in Iraq when we should actually be in Afghanistan. And I hate Europeans and Americans. I hate the latter more. I read a book,  Searching for Booger County  (which is a book on the history of Douglas County), and I found out that after the U.S. gained its independence from Britain, it had 45 treaties with one band of Native Americans, and it didn't keep one of them. FOURTY-FIVE! We're such selfish greedy pigs.  Sixth, I came to a conclusion. AIDS was God's way of controlling the human population. We have overcome every one of our problems as the human species with science. We don't adapt to anything anymore. We make the world adapt to us. And, we can't fix AIDS with science. First He targeted the gays. I don't have anything against them, but apparently He does. And now He is going after the whores, pimps, bastards, rapists, teenagers, and druggies. He used human's ignorance to the disease to his advantage and spread it around the world to the point to where we couldn't control the spread once we found out what it was and what it did. And he was successful. I give thanks to God for giving humans this incurable atrocity. He has done well, and will rid the earth of a lot of stupid people. Unfortunately this disease has a long incubation period, so it takes a while to kill everyone off. But at least this lets it spread without anyone knowing. God is a mastermind, and for this calamity I give Him eternal praise. I think this is his best miracle to date. Well, except maybe with the Virgin Mary and all. So this is his second best miracle. It's still good.  That was quite a mouthful. I feel cleansed now. Maybe I'll go have a cookie.   Current Mood:  Not really sure   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For a good while now I've been in league with Black. Who is Black? He's from Rhode Island and he wants to take over the world. I can't remember how it happened, but I did something that pleased him and got promised much land to my name, and thusly joined his plot to dominate the world. So dear readers, I humbly ask you to join our cause and actively participate in our forums, the  urlLink World Domination Forums . Join, or Ilpalazzo will smite you. And Black will then smite your remains. And then I will smite the remains of your remains. And you don't want to know what will happen after that. Just join already. And don't forget to   actively   participate!   Current Mood:  EVIL   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'll start with the initial reason I was gone. I was grounded. Why? Let me explain.  The twelfth of this month was the Sheared Wit 2000 - 3000 / End of the School Year party. And being the fun-loving person I am, I was the one who threw it.  Big mistake . I'm not throwing another party until graduation. Anyway, I found out that day that I have three less friends than I thought I did. So here's what happened:  My brother is a moron. But we all knew that already. Anyway, Pa was out shopping for snacks and such (that he was supposed to have had done already) and Zack comes downstairs looking for him, which he  knew  he wasn't supposed to do. Being the annoying spastic child he is, we (my "friends" and I) are quickly annoyed by him, and thusly Brett gets the bright idea to ducktape his hands behind his back and his mouth shut. So he's kicking and jumping and struggling while Lane, Drew, and I are trying to hold him down. Naturally, we decide to tape his feet too. Drew isn't exactly gentle with Zack, and his head gets banged on the floor. And so he cries. And cries. And cries some more. And it wasn't because it hurt (he told me so himself after all was said and done). And he's still crying when Pa gets home so I get grounded (but not before I get into a huge argument with him).  So now my brother hates me more (if that's possible), I get into an argument with Pa (oh fun), and I'm embarrassed out of my eyeballs in front of my friends as I'm grounded into what seems like an eternity. But that's not why I'm mad. Na, the worst part was that I didn't get   ONE FUCKING APOLOGY  . From any of them. Some friends they turned out to be. So now I'm down to five friends (more like four friends and one boyfriend, we have yet to see how this turns out...). It goes from nine to five in one event. Sortof. Noodle never showed up, nor did she give me any notice whatsoever that she wasn't going to show up. I have an idea of why, but I still need to talk with her about it. But it's not like me and her are really close friends anyway.  I'm trusting fewer and fewer people nowadays. I'm keeping more and more secrets. Not other people's secrets (well, I do, but that's not what I'm talking about). I'm going back to how I used to be. A sour, mean, and friendless hermet. But at least that way I wouldn't havve to expect anyone to  attempt  to befriend me. What excellent friends I have.  P.S. To my still-existing friends (currently Monica Ginny Genell Ryan and Dave), I lurve you all and none of the above insults and/or complaints are meant to be directed at you. You all still rock.   Current Mood : Blank   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been gone a while. So I have quite a bit to blog about. So here I go! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Had quite the interesting encounter with Dave last night. The whole time we were talking I kept dropping "I love you"'s all over the place and even hid a few in some screenshots of my desktop that I sent him. And he had no reaction to them. Sorry if I'm being selfish, but I feel neglected since he doesn't show his love for me as often as I show my love for him. He apologize for last night, but that doesn't change the fact that I feel unwanted. Who can blame me? Here I am trying to show him how much I care (he keeps saying I don't show it often enough around him) and he does nothing for me. And when he talked to me again this afternoon, he said he wanted to stop hugging me and stuff around Pa because "he will get to know pa better that way." I understand that Pa might not like us doing that in front of him (it's just a hug anyway, and he has yet to say anything to me about it), but Pa already likes Dave and I don't think it will make much more of a difference. Way to make me feel more neglected. I need to go out Wednesday before I explode. It was just "lovely" that Dave had to make sure he left with me feeling very very alone. Maybe I'm meant to be alone. Ever since I started to pray for his safety down in Vegas, his situation has been getting smidgens better and mine getting worse. I guess God wants to protect him from me since I'm an awful sinning Christian who doesn't read the Bible or pray often enough. He doesn't deserve someone as terrible as me. I guess that's why I get treated the way I do. I have a feeling that our relationship is going to spiral downwards when he gets back. I hope not, but I have this gut intuition that it will. Maybe his lack of attention-giving to me is what draws me towards the who, since the who is a very cuddly touchy lovey person. I wish I knew what the hell is going on with me.  I feel so very alone...   Current Mood:  Turned Away   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ker-layout change (again)! I can't make up my mind. I like variety. Which may be a problem. Let me elaborate:  I think I what the who again. I think he's cuter than Dave. In a kindof happy fuzzy cuddly bunny way. I'm ashamed to say that, since I'm supposed to be Dave's loyal girlfriend. Especially since he's going to Nevada for two weeks and I promised him nothing would happen while he was gone. I just emailed him saying I wouldn't meet anyone. I guess it's true since I already know the who. I wonder if the who whats me, but the who usually avoids those types of questions. The who won't even answer questions about our friendship. I really have no idea what the who's opinion of me is. Maybe I could get Monchan to weasel it out of him. But then again, I had her do that a while back and he apparently didn't. But I still have to take into account that the who is good at hiding how he feels (most of the time) and may have kept it a secret this whole time or maybe developed feelings recently. *sigh* I'm really hopeless.  Monchan was really upset about the prank last week. I hope she'll realize that it's my fault for agreeing to go ahead with it and that me and Dave are fine. The only thing left is me needing to forgive myself for doing it, which isn't going to happen any time soon. Me being mad at her for it hadn't even crossed my mind until I read her DeadJournal. I'm still not mad at her though. Maybe I'm too forgiving, or maybe she's too paranoid. I don't know. In any case, we're both at fault for the prank, but nothing is going to get accomplished by being mad at others for it.  Dave has noticed me changing. We talked about it a lot the other day. I weaseled a lot of things he disliked about me out of him. He apologized for saying what he did the next day. I really don't mind him saying things like that, as long as he still loves me for the whole instead of only little bits here and there. He had made some valid points about most of the things he said, and apparently I'm either not changing fast enough or I'm not changing the right things. I feel bad talking about us though, seeing as the who lurkes in the back of my thoughts every now and then. He'll dissapear from my thoughts, but it's only temporary. I'm so selfish and unloyal. I don't know what I should do with myself. I'm such a disgrace. I think this predicament will lead to a much bigger problem in the future...   Current Mood:  Worried   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't think I'm humble enough. I'm mean, I lie, I lack morals, I'm arrogant, I'm insensitive, I've broken the law, heck, I'm just a terrible person. I make jokes about people, I gossip, I'm stubborn. Ugh, I hate me. I don't study enough, I'm a terrible driver, I can't get a job, I swear a lot. I don't trust people, I don't let people get very close to me, I reject people I like, I'm a social introvert. I've even beaten up my brother. My brother!!! My younger 11-year-old brother!!! (He was 9 or 10 when I beat him up though). I'm closed-minded and hypocritical. I'm very critical of other people (most of the time negatively). I'm such a terrible person.    I'm watching Fruits Basket hoping some of Tohru's mannerisms will rub off on me. Again I remind myself that I need to make cookies... But then, I have to write an essay for school first... beh, I find myself in a bind...    My brother is coming home Wednesday. All he's going to do is pick a fight, which doesn't help me out any.    Ryan hit me yesterday. Twice. Once for drinking a shot as a toast to the birthday of two aunts and an uncle, and again for fighting with Dave earlier that day. *sigh* I'm so terrible...    I can't poke him anymore either. Well, I  can , but I won't. He told me to stop, and I have to respect that. One more step towards becoming humble. Kyuu, he had to put up with my drunk aunt yesterday when he picked me up, and I still feel bad for that...    Why can't I just be a decent person? I think I'll listen to some Collective Soul and start on that essay now...   Current Mood:  Discontent   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dave says that now that we're no longer together, he doesn't have to work out our problems. If he's going to go ahead and ignore that, he might as well ignore me altogether. Some nerve he has.    Thus another friendship is down the drain.    People are difficult. I hate them all. Sometimes I wish I didn't have friends. Of course, since I'm in a semi-sane state of mind right now, I know that's a very BAD thing. That reminds me, I need to make Ryan some cookies...    Curse long distances! Justin would totally be another best buddy if he didn't live in RHODE ISLAND. Goddamn. I'd have so many more friends if all the cool people didn't live in Michigan and RI and Norway... Fucking hell.    I've  become such a pottymouth. It doesn't really bother me, there's no meaning in the words to me. After all, they're just words. But when I'm in public, I tend to come across people who don't think they're "just words." Stupid pricks. Them and their pop culture... eww... *shudders*    And since you people never seem to be satisfied with what I say, I'll put it here for future reference: I'm attracted to Ryan. He's cute, innocent, charming, and incredibly cool. He's got a job and he can drive. He's responsible, and his parents are practically non-existant so he gets to do a lot of things he wants. But, I don't want to date him. That's right. You heard me you bastards. I don't think he has the aspirations I'm looking for in a future partner. I need someone with a plan. And flunking out of half of your classes in high school is not what I'd call a plan. On top of that, he's kinda like Genell. Heck, he even compares himself to her. That means I can't swear and pull as many perverted sex jokes around him. I don't think I'm sensitive enough for him anyway. I'm a very conceited person.    If you don't mind, I have to go take my amoxicillin and then curse myself for my pitiful existance.   Current Mood:  ...   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Monica and Ryan apparently stayed the night at Dave's last night. I swear if I hear of one more friggin social event that I would like to be at but can't for whatever reason, I'm gonna cut off someone's fuggin head. And the worst part? THE APOLOGIES. Oh. My. Gods. If I hear one more flipping apology over something small and insignificant, my rusty spork will be very bloody at the end of the day. I mean seriously, I don't mind not getting my fortune cookie. I don't need a big long explanation filled with excuses galore (and TERRIBLE spelling accompanied with annoying shorthand). All I needed was "We're sorry, we forgot about the fortune cookie, we'll find a way to make it up to you." That's all! Don't blame the "crappy" restaurant, don't blame the fact that you were in a hurry, don't blame the fact that you spilled some of your food. Honestly,  I don't really care .    I remember reading advice about breakups. "Keep it short, simple, and to the point. Don't dwell, or you'll only invoke unnecessary emotional pains." I'd give the same advice about apologies, especially over little things. It was just a fortune cookie for crying out loud! I could have walked to the China Wok up the street and got one for a dime if I wanted it so bad! Jeezus!    I wonder when people will begin to learn from past experiences. I also wonder when Dave will start listening to me. Because he STILL has yet to show me that he does. I know it may seem mean of me, but it's times like these that I'm glad I'm not with Dave anymore.    Current Mood:  Annoyed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sick. I have strep again. AGAIN! In less than a month's time! Pa thinks I have mono. I wouldn't be suprised. And I spilled water on my monitor and it fucked up the brightness. Black looks dark gray now.  The sleepover I have been looking forward to SO BADLY has been called off. I've been looking forward to it all week. Well, since I found out anyway. And I wasted TWO HOURS shaving in preparation. Son of a bitch.  I was called arrogant today. Go figure. I've been calling myself that all along, but no one would listen to me. So when I finally manage to convince myself otherwise, it comes back and bites me in the ass.  My back is starting to hurt. Someone just kill me now. This knife looks awfully friendly...   Current Mood:  Sick   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yep, me and Dave are over, after seven and a half months. Actually it happened yesterday, but I'm lazy so my blogging isn't always done instantly.  I think I enjoy being single too much. I'm such a flirt. Don't get me wrong, that had nothing to do whith why I broke up with him. Well, it was taken into consideration, but it wasn't the deciding factor.  I love being a teenager sometimes. Minus school and work and whatnot. I wish my whole life was summer vacation. I enjoy defying my dad and doing stuff I know he wouldn't want me to do and would certainly kill me for if he ever found out. It's a wonderful feeling. The rush of adrenaline is enticing.  So back to being a huge flirt. That's right, I'm a flirt. Before Dave, I was afraid to hug a guy. But now, I wouldn't be suprised if I found myself trying to get down someone's throat. It kindof sickens me. But flirting is still fun. I have yet to kiss anyone who isn't family or boyfriend (minus Lane, but she doesn't count). And I'm sure I can control myself. But now every one I know are potential victims to my hugging and cuddling and whatnot. Especially Ryan. Gawd, I hate hormones, but I love them at the same time. The rest of this summer is going to be quite interesting...   Current Mood:  Flirty   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok I know I'll get yelled at if I don't blog today, so here goes.  I've had this recent IRC fetish. It's awesome. The people in IRC are really cool and generally friendly. I get ops in two or three channels that let me kick people I don't like (I like to excercise my power a lot :D), and I've managed to drag Ginchan and Boots into it so I'm not completely alone all the time. It's great.  I'm getting dragged on a road trip next summer (or maybe the summer after, depends on how fast we can amass enough money). We'll be going to Florida, Rhode Island, Michigan, and Canada (Alberta). Ginny, Monica, Justin, Travis, Sam, Takeda, and I are all going to get crammed in a van for two weeks. We haven't completely figured out what we're going to do after everyone gets picked up, but I'm thinking we'll pitch a couple tents and camp out in the Canadian wilderness a couple days. The exitement I have for this trip makes me want to pee myself. It would make a nice graduation present.  Ok I'm tired and in the middle of an arguement with Dave (go figure), so I'll blog after I go see Anchorman with Monica and Ryan or something. Maybe.   Current Mood:  None   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG INDEPENDENCE DAY!  I love a holiday whose soul purpose is to light stuff on fire and make it legal. I shot a roman candle into my neighbor's tree, it was great. I burned myself countless times setting off "Cannons," which was fun since my bro thought I couldn't set off two at once and I DID and it was SWEET!  Anyone ever notice that the 4th of July is a week long?  Other than that, I didn't really enjoy these past four days. Dealing with Lane and Dave and  especially  Brett really takes it out of ya (he's still pestering me for shit!).  Talking with a few friends of mine I've noticed how much other countries are better than this one. I really want to move to Norway a lot now.  Not much else to blog. My life is getting boringer.  Grammar is for wussies!   Current Mood:  Not really sure   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Within the span of this last week I have been called mean, arrogant, immature, bitchy, whiny, stupid, too flirty, whorish, sour, overdramatic, and lazy. All of which I've TOLD ALL OF YOU ABOUT BEFORE. Goddamn, you people are complete morons not to have known this before. The too flirty thing is a new one though. I never really thought it was bad until I got chewed out for it the other day (not gonna say by who). I'm just a terrible person. Period. A while ago I told some people that I wanted to change myself to be nicer, but they all replied something along the lines of "No, accept yourself for who you are, learn to love yourself, etc. etc." But, this week, Ginny said "Grow up and stop bitching." Not only does that contradict what she had already said, but I'd have to say she does the same. I really don't enjoy talking to her anymore, because all she says to me is that I have some type of personality fault or that she's incredibly in love with this guy from Canada. Neither of those are very entertaining. They're not even occupying. I've also noticed that I've become incredibly antisocial as of late. I don't really talk to anyone that much. Not even Monica, and we ALWAYS have something to talk about. If I'm on the phone for longer than 20 minutes, I can guarantee that it's because the other person is talking alot *coughryancough*. When I talk to people over IM, there's often long (long being over ten minutes) pauses. When I'm around people in person, again, there's a lot of silence. I have to be around at least two people to be able to converse at a moderate level. But whatever. I think I'm done for now.   Current Mood:  Turned Away   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, I'm pathetic. Time to give up on Justin completely. He obviously likes Steph better anyway. I don't like her too much, I think she's a bit too childish. But that's just me. And, on a side note, Sev is better. He's nicer. Well, in general he's a better person. And modest. Modesty is good. And he's more open to his feelings. No angsty "I don't love anyone" crap.  I really want to rant about that, but I don't have any words for it right now. Stupid lack of ability to blog...   Current Mood:  Flirty   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I need somewhere to keep this, before I lose the little torn diary page it's written on. This entry was from March 9, 2000.  "I can't wait until my birthday. I want to have a party on the 29th because Erica's is on the 30th and mine is the 28th. We could share it. My mum whipped me over 10 times (somewhere around 14 I think) today."  Looking back on that, I have no clue how I could talk about such a happy thing and follow it up with one of the few things that makes me cry. I remember when Dave saw that slip of paper. That was the first time I cried in front of him. How I hate my mother...  Just reading it makes me want to cry again...  Changed the template back to accomodate the new mood icons courtesy of Livejournal. No, the images are not direct-linked, I have them hosted on my photobucket account. All I'm saying is that I didn't make them.   Current Mood:  Depressed   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink CLICKIE!  Now you all know who I am. I managed to filter out the rigged ones.  I read Justin's LJ today. It's depressing. I want to pity him, but I don't pity people. It's just not who I am. Yeah, I'm a cold and heartless bitch. So fuck off already. He really confuses me sometimes. I don't get it. I've given up on him. And, like Ryan, I'm still attracted to him. I've just realized that no way in hell will I ever get to be close to him. It makes me sad. I wish I could get into his head and just find out already. Goddamn me and my morals and personal codes!  Apparently my blog is PG. I gotta work on that. Post some nude or violent pictures or something. Yeah, you'd like that you sick pervert.  Supposed to get a new wardrobe today. Yeah, we'll see how THAT goes. Pa doesn't want me to wear jeans ripped in the knees. Because, y'know, those are my two most comfortable pairs of pants. Damn it all!  Layout change. The other layout was too yuppy.  Doctor's appointment Friday. For checking out my back problems. My back makes me feel old. I'm not supposed to have back problems when I'm sixteen. It's just not right.  People make me sick. Don't ask me why. I don't feel like explaining right now.   Current Mood:  Blank    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>