<Blog>


<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's easy, specially when the fast lane is the treadmill under your sore feet. An update for all those worried by my health problems. Clued out? I was discovered with a massive BP problem in December and have since then given up my old life in the fast lane and adopted the treadmill.   Earlier the daily rush used to start from the moment I got up at 7:30 to make it to work. I now go to the gym regularly, so I get up at 6:15 instead and start rushing to the gym, then back home, quick SSS and brekker and hit the Georgetown-Oklahoma route (okhla also recently got re-christened !!)  Is it helping? I guess it certainly helps me fall asleep at 11, even in the middle of a party. It also helps me to further lose touch with my family! Surely it is helping my cholestrol too. Thanks to Subu - who admonishes me if I miss as much as a day at the Reebok gym. And to Payal - who struggles along bravely in my absence. Also thanks to the gym instructor for lightening my wallet. He ensured I purchased new Reeboks!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK. Here is a poll for you about my future career options. Shall I (a) continue being a slave (b) continue being an underpaid slave (c) start hunting heads (d) start selling palm pilots   Recently noticed that many friends & acquaintances start dialling my number as soon as they want a job switch. LK, Sandeep Deshpande, Aashim, Ashish Redij, Indranil Ghosh - are the more recent ones. Also - many consultants call me to ask not whether I want a new job, but whether I know someone who wants to earn 40 lakhs being marketing head of a telecom major! :( As things stand, I am able to satisfy both ends primarily because I use a palm pilot!   Ergo, one assumes that there is money to be made here. As one Naresh Aggarwal told me last night, the cleanest money is in brokerage. You earn simply by getting people to meet each other!! What say? Shall I ask Nasreen for an internship?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HNY to everyone!!  Thanks Sasha for brewing up this blog – good to know what's happening in respective lives and share random thoughts.  It was a very nice surprise to talk to some of ya'll during the party. When the call came, we were at this newly opened desi restaurant called  urlLink  Chaat Café   – had heard some good things about it – Indian fast food (Tikkas, rolls, chola-bhatura’s, etc). Turned out it had the most ludicrous version of a spicy seekh kabab and a chiken tikka roll – surely concocted by someone who has never relished either. So the call was a nice diversion from the negative rants going around our table.   Yet another sorry pass at Indian food here. Though, surprisingly and not so surprisingly in some ways, Dallas now has over 60 desi eating joints – up from the 20 odd since we moved here 4 ½ years ago.  But the 2 am Pindi dinner sure beats 'em all.  Nonethless, more power to the desis!  Georgetown (now with an  urlLink online newspaper   too) rocks man – that place is so inconceivably different from 10 years ago when I had my factory there. And some of us used to go hunting for beer across the border after sunset. My parents moved there last year and are quite loving it.   As for Sasha's poll, why do you have to make them options mutually exclusive? Hunt the heads, while selling some palm pilot’s (or PDA’s as they are called here) on the side. All the while, continue spicing up Delhi with the airwaves. And yeah, wait for my call on job (& country) switching :-)  Lastly, but not the least(ly!!) congrats to all the  “burra sahibs”  on their new jobs and global movements – keep ‘em shaking folks!!  Cheers, Sandeep   P.S. Now read the “original” TOI online as is – with ads, pictures, et al.    urlLink TOI Online 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night at a neighborhood cocktail in Georgetown, Payal and I met an extremely interesting & engaging gentleman. He's in his 50s and was the head of treasury at Grindlays at the age of 32, after he had completed being a chartered accountant in London. He started his own enterprise around 1990 and hired some of the brightest people in the financial markets. Now he runs a reinsurance brokerage - relative oblivion, though he still employs 50 people. Any guesses yet? Preetie?  The man was Naresh Aggarwal. The company - Brisk Financial. Which hired the likes of our Kohli and one Gulbir Baweja!  The world as usual continues to be a small place. We dont know why we were at a 50+ party. We dont know why the host introduced us to his good friend Naresh. We dont know how we started discussing banking. For some reason Gulbir and his non-resident status came up. And Brisk got mentioned. An hour after we had been guzzling drinks with him!!  He said to say Hi to you Preetie.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LK, Preetie and I think Sunny are regularly using this site now. That is effort rewarded in itself!  Georgetown Fact. Did you know that Georgetown now boasts of the highest density of high price gymnasiums anywhere in the country? It's a little know fact. There are 27 over-expensive gyms which charge in excess of 30K per year for a population of some half a million people, which beats Mumbai & Delhi hollow. Delhi has 35 odd and Mumbai 45 or so!   Georgetown has yet to discover the benefits of volume over value! You therefore also have a big clutch of fancy resto-bars (or  restro-bars , if the entrepreneue knew nothing about what he was doing in the first place), none of which offer any happy hours, and are proud of the fact. They eventually will learn the competitive lessons of the GK2 M Block market - every bar/pub/club has happy hours all the time. And business is booming. Which brings me to the Budhdha Lounge (MGF Mall), where I went a couple of nights ago on the insistence of someone who said it was 'roaking'. Nice place... provided there is a crowd. I was 1 of 3 people sitting in very quiet corners! The 2nd person was with me. The 3rd was perhaps the owner drowning his sorrows!? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bhaiyon and girls, Kya kahoon, news of these parties @ Sasha's makes me gnash my teeth! (in envious despair Sasha, envious despair!) Lucky you Preets... Have a ball in Feb in the ol' hometown! News for you all - I've finally cut my Gordian's Knot of Research & Media, and will be charting new territories (for me) of Business Management... BM for Oral-B in Gillette Mideast & Africa region. Seems to be a time for changes - Sasha/Payal, congrats on your finally moving in... gotta see Sholay on your home theatre soon with a glass of fav. brew; Rahul, congrats on your hurriedly arranged shaadi.... some people just don't learn from others' mistakes! Kartik, BIG congrats for the big one... shows that patience in sticking to the same company pays for some. To all the rest, Cheers! and Enjwaai!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys.... heard all about your reunion party at the newly baptised GG.... and i wish u had pushed it by a month!! NV NV NV.... However, plan to be in Delhi on the weekend of 6th-7th Feb.... catch you guys then...! unless the village of Delhi loses more of the gang to the likes of LBS and the bid bad corpo world!! Cheers for now.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just saw a news flash on the internet that Kartik Iyer will be heading Initiative Media nationally. Been trying to call him for the last 30 minutes, but his phone is busy I think with all the congratulatory messages.  This will mean of course that Kartik will attend even fewer get togethers, and arrive at 11:30pm if at all he does. Maybe I can get him over for a special housewarming in the summer of 2009! Cheers Kartik. More power to you!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the Saturday past, Payal and I finally got around to hosting what looks like the first of many housewarming parties. With the weather being what it is, any additional warming is welcome.   It was a surprise party - for those who attended that is - since everyone got to meet someone they did not expect. Suffice to say - Debashish Shyam was there!! After procratinating for 2 years, I finally met Debashish a week ago, since we wanted to do biz with Hindustan Times, which is where he works now. Subu, Ritu & Sudhin, Rajesh & Simi, Ishita, Bunty, Ila, Nasreen, Naresh (of the palm reading fame), Vikas Jain (1 or 2?? The one who went to IIMA!), Kochie (brimming with news that Radio Mirchi is the #1 station in Delhi) - everyone came complete with spouse and without kid!! Who was missing? Kartik Iyer - who had a 8pm meeting on a Saturday night. Does the guy ever go home???  Subu loudly proclaimed Kochie to be a 'rascal'. Everyone liked the food. And the drinks. Drinks were better! Everyone left at 1. No one sang any songs. Was that good or bad? You decide.  Oh. The big news of course is that Sudhin is off to the LBS soon to attend a global leadership program. I think Ericsson wants him to replace Saddam soon!! The other big noose is the one our architect friends are tightening on the Mathurs... after taking 5 months to do our apartment, they are taking another 4 to finish theirs!!   More soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The blog is inspired by the one my ex-boss and friend Arun Katiyar started recently. The idea was simple. Staying in touch with people who you have lost touch with; but whose e-mail id you still somehow have. Also, having recently moved into a concrete heaven of sorts, it is natural that I have a lot to share about Georgetown - nee Gurgaon. I am told that the name changed to Georgetown some time back; I was made aware only recently though by one Anup Jain.  In the Georgetown/Gurgaon dilemma lies great intrigue. From the stray cows near the glitzy malls; to underwears drying in million buck condo balconies... the range of expressions and oddities are quite funny. Quite like India Shining. Shining in parts, Stinking in others. Like India, I love Gurgaon. For now.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Georgetown's fancy malls are all disabled & infant friendly. Mostly all. They have special lifts, special loos, ramps et al.   The condo blocks are another matter altogether. The one I live in for instance. Given the astronomical price of these apartments, there are obviously many senior citizens here who have managed to save half a crore to stay in the relative comfort & luxury. But guess what? Anyone who has shaky knees (or no knees at all) needs to first drive into the basement parking lot and take a lift from there. Same for toddlers in perambulators!! From the ground level, one needs to go down 15 steep steps to take a lift like the rest of us do.  The best part of this is that there is no one to sue. Not obviously at least. The builder - DLF - says they have already handed over the condo complex to the owners association. They have also signatures from each of saying that we have no claims on them at all (fine print on page 873 I think). Hafeez Contracter who is the purported 'designer' has designed as per a brief.  Am wondering what I can do about this. Not grow old hopefully.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spent last night watching God Alone Knows... an avant garde sort of movie made by one Bharat Dhabolkar - slightly famous copywriter and ad man, known best for his 'topical' Amul campaign (LK? topical =?).  The movie is all in desi English and quite engaging. It is a spoof aimed at politics. But quite an amazing concept. And is great fun for those who enjoy spoofs on current music. I specially enjoyed a bit about Yamraj needing an ad campaign to improve his image. And they find the LOW ADV AGENCY to do their campaign. The campaign itself has yamraj calling 3 damsels 'makhkhan ki doniyon' by a village well, and proceeding to pull out of the well, a dead body which is 'cold'. Enjoy the rest when/if you catch the movie.  By virtue of my position in the media biz, one gets many free movie invites (popcorn is free as well)... and tomorrow night we shd be seeing a preview of the Runaway Jury at the new luxurious PVR screen in Georgetown. The difference? Evidently they serve you booze and snacks in your seats!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent the entire last week in Mumbai writing my obituary. That is all I can call my business plan for 04-05; I along with my team will die delivering the numbers being asked of us. As is the wont when in Mumbai, one must party hard every night... I partied hard in the conference room with 21 other fellow sufferers at the Taj Landsend. Just for the record, I also spent an hour of each morning in Mumbai (hung over or not) in the gym busting my bulges!!  Managed to sneak one solitary evening with Radha & Poonam, when we had some exceptional prawns and fish doled out by the best cook in that part of the country accompanied by some good Glen. More power to the residents of Chaitanya Towers.  Preetie was in Mum the same day as well. But was recovering from the sudden shock of leaving Sing in her hotel room. She promises to breeze thru Delhi in this week, but suspects that she will not be able to make it to Georgetown for a drink. What a pity!!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      24th March. It happens to be Payal's birthday, and was the day India played Pak for the final of the ODI series. One was naturally torn between the 2 causes. Traditionally Payal & I go out for a fancy dinner on 24/03. And Payal is not that big on cricket. Having said that, the significance of the series had sunk into her and so we decided to go to a pub/club with a large screen, down a few and celebrate india's win, which was by 7pm looking more than likely. A few things then happened.  First, we could not find a free seat in the entire Vasant Vihar area. VV is brimming over with nice new pubs with large screens. And each of the 4 we tried were bursting at the seams with cheering maniacs!! Strangely, when I went out to see the World Cup matches - even the final - there was never this sort of cheering frenzy in pubs!  Left without an option, we decided that we would do a fine dining sort of thing and end with a late night movie. We drove into this China Club in Georgetown for a meal. This is one of the fancier places in the Delhi/GGN area (the other being Odyssey - also in Georgetown). It was also the only place ever that the steward asked me whether I wanted my beer with head or without. I wanted head, no beer.   After an extremely good meal, we ventured into the MGF mall planning on buying tickets for Matchstick Men at PVR. We missed the movie because in the main atrium of the mall, around a huge screen were 2000 people cheering every ball at 10 in the night. It was an amazing sight. People were hugging whoever was standing next to them and the atmosphere was electric despite all the shops being closed.  urlLink Check this out   Incidentally - 'Paycheck' - the movie we finally managed after India won the match, was about good enough to put us to sleep. And my wife is still asking for her birthday gift! She refuses to accept the Samsung Cup as adequate reward!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Syed, a colleague in Bangalore that I knew slightly, now as well as when I worked in Bangalore, died on Friday night. He was 27.  Evidently he went with a heart attack in his sleep. Not known to be more than a social drinker, and a medium smoker, he was a regular fun loving guy. Single still, which I guess was a blessing.   Why is he on my blog? Well - one - some of my memory of him is good, specially from the indya days. More importantly because, since Saturday, I am spending more time thinking of all the things I am doing which I should not - like smoking. And things I am not doing, which I should be - calling old friends, discovering new ones, spending more time than I manage now with my mother, planning my family's finances, getting my retina checked and so on. Get the message?   Syed - your enigmatic smile lives on.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some distance below there is an interesting one from Sunny, explaining i think the circumstances of his son's existance. Hmmm. Another on the way? Preetie started to post but gave up midway I think. She is in Delhi today, but headed quickly back to Sing I think.  Had a blast since Sat morning. Spent the entire day in a bean bag in front of the TV, watching India thrash Pak and then saving their skin in the last over. The only time I got up was to exult over Kaif's blinder. What a catch.  Then we arrived very late in the night at Mani Anisha's place in LPN. These are the guys who have done our lovely flat, and then Sudhin/Ritu's, before crunching in an office project for Ishita. Ergo - all client+friends named above were invited. many drinks and one joint later, left for home at 2:30 holding my gut from the pain of laughing too much. Good company. And am told the food was great as well.   Sunday was devoted to sleep. No better way to spend one's 37th birthday. I did notice some black hair emerging in the morning though. Sigh. Thanks all of you for the wishes. Those of you who did not call - the fact that you forgot my birthday is enough excuse to make the long distance call!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Payal has this habit of running into school mates of hers all the time. And she recognises them even if they came to school for a week. That, and  Georgetown helped me find a couple of old friends. Why Georgetown? Because much as everyone hates the distance and the parking problems, you just cant keep a Dilliwallah away from the glitzy malls.  Couple of Sundays back at the MGF Plaza - it was Micky Bedi - whose wife went to Mater Dei... the last we saw them was at their wedding 7 years ago. Mobile numbers and promises to meet have been exchanged;  hopefully we will meet again soon.  Couple of days back, Payal ran into another classmate - this time at Arcus - who happens to be married to the famous news anchor Vikram Chandra. Vikram grabbed my number from Payal and riddled me on where I spent many a colorful festival 17 years ago. The memory of course was his home in Moti Bagh and their farmhouse. Holi after Holi at the fag end of our school years, he and I would get drunk on beer, sitting in the sun. His parents were an indulgent lot, and I remember now having had some superb afternoons at their place.   That was another time and place. Vikram and I promised to meet. The lucky man is actually free for lunch... which I cant say for myself!!  To this huge crowd of people who keep telling me that I am extremely good at 'networking' and 'staying in touch', let it be known, that I am NOT in touch with a single person from my school days. No bosom buddies, no first loves, and specially no rich father's kids - of which Modern VV had plenty! Having said that, the call from Vikram reminded me that I had a good life back then as well; and so have promised myself that I will track down Raja, Vijay, Vinay, Akash and many others who I will look up in the class photo. Amen.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ........    Quick update and a few random thoughts from the US!!!   Joined in the Atlanta office - finished with my first week and am currently headed back to Atlanta after spending the weekend at home in Dallas - will continue living the consultant’s life for a few more weeks – shuttling weekly between Atlanta & Dallas. And we are somewhat sad at leaving Dallas too. It has been home for the last 5 odd years, the only city we have lived in this country, a place where I came to get an MBA and ending up getting mucho more – a bunch of friends, a son and about 20 extra kilos to name a few. Being quite settled in here - this is gonna be a difficult transition in some ways. It almost the same feeling that I had when I left Calcutta for Delhi in 1982, left Delhi for Lucknow in 1986 & then Lucknow for Delhi/Ghaziabad in 1990. The feeling when we left Delhi to move to the US was a tad different – I guess the excitement of going to Amreekaaa overshadowed the rest. Shit, I just realized after writing this that I HAVE moved around quite a bit in the last 20 odd years!!! I am actually averaging a city every 4 years since 1982!!!  And I do know for sure of another move waiting down the road – that of coming back HOME – when is an open question!!   I want ya’ll planning a visit to the US to put Atlanta on your agenda – for some reason Dallas did not fructify in the past 5 years for any of you except Sasha, who had a fleeting and namesake visit a while ago!!!   Let me also share a very interesting incident in our lives. In 2000, I was in the final year of my second MBA and almost 4 years married. Shefali was mentally getting ready to get pregnant; I was mentally getting ready to get a job. We knew it wasn’t a good time to reproduce as we needed time to settle down first. Anyways, Shefali’s chachi came visiting in August (her younger son was joining college in the US) and was with us for 3 weeks. When I say “with us” I mean like “24/7”. And in all the respectful traditions, she slept on the bed (in our 1 bedroom apartment) with Shefali - and I had to make do sleeping on the couch/“gadda on the floor”. Needles to say it was a tumultuous time in some respects. Midway through her trip, she found a distant cousin in Dallas and they decided to take her out for a few hours. And those few hours, my friends, brought about the conception and existence of Shivyaan!!! So that really taught me the importance and significance of “just” a couple of hours.   I tell this story because as we move to Atlanta in April end (after Shefali finishes with her education), Shefali’s chachi is planning to visit us again (the same son is now graduating) in May for about 2-3 weeks. Will history repeat itself??  Dunno yet, as she has no “known relations” in Atlanta.  If you know of anyone we can have her visit for a few hours that would be extremely helpful – and very appreciable (as the Amrici’s say).   On that note, I’ll sign off. My flight is about to land and I am on my 4th Scotch. It’s been a bumpy ride so far (literally and figuratively). My best wishes to all & I feverously pray that “MAY ALL YOUR UPS & DOWNS BE IN BED”.   Adios. Amigos.   Sunny 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reproducing below a mail from Sunny... another way to look at overstressed lives. And the theory of relativity. Ppl have been asking how the dudes in the US are... cant remember the last person to ask... Sudhin I think... easy reminder of the blokes in the US is served from the bar in our appt in Georgetown... a photo of 3 men lounging in 1 chair (together) after a few drinks... as always!   "A lecturer was giving a lecture to his students on stress management. He raised a glass of water and asked the audience, "How heavy do you think this glass of water is? The students ' answers ranged from 20 g to 500 gm.   "It does not matter on the absolute weight. It depends on how long you hold it. If I hold it for a minute, it is ok. If I hold it for an hour, I will have an ache in my right arm. If I hold it for a day, you will have to call an ambulance. It is the exact same weight, but the longer I hold it, the heavier it becomes."  "If we carry our burdens all the time, sooner or later, we will not be able to carry on, the burden becoming increasingly heavier. What you have to do is to put the glass down, rest for a while before holding it up again."   We have to put down the burden periodically, so that we can be refreshed and are able to carry on. Whatever burdens you are having now on your shoulders, let it down for a moment if you can. Pick it up again later when you have rested.... Rest & relax." 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes it seems to be standing still... like say on this blog. I was amazed to come back today and notice that my last posting was 2 months ago!! So this post. In the middle of corporate hurry blurry, one tends to lose sight of all the finer things in life... like blogging.  In the middle of it all, also realised that I have not taken a vacation in over 2 years now. Sold my soul to the company basically. So I decided that I would take the entire team on a river rafting trip. Do some bonding, team building and so on...  So off we went last weekend to Shivpuri - near Rishikesh - to raft in the rapids of the Ganga. The heat was killing, but it was still one helluva trip. White water rafting - if you have'nt done it before - can be pretty daunting. Suffice to say, I was surprised by the number of people who conquered their fear of water and actually got into the rubber boats. And even more surprised that barring a couple of people  everyone  was game to jump off a 40 foot cliff into the water! Even with bungee jumping behind me, I still had to fight off the fear of the unknown and almost push myself off the brink.  The rafting was fun. The volleyball games improved enough by the 3rd day that you wanted to turn professional. The trip ended, but yeh dil maange more! Srinagar anyone?   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>