<Blog>

<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I thought maybe that if I didn’t look at you,  I’d forget that you’re there.  That maybe, I can fool myself  into thinking the world is not cruel.  I thought maybe, if I avoided your eyes,  I wouldn’t see the void in it when you look at me.  That maybe, I can have the choice of what to imagine  your eyes would reflect if I do get to look at them.  I thought maybe, if I ignored my quickened heartbeat, I’d have a chance to forget and move on.  Maybe, if I hardened my heart to your charm,  I’d recover the controls of my senses.  I thought maybe that if I acted as if I didn’t see you,  I wouldn’t realize that I’m in pain;  That maybe, if I pretended hard enough,  I’d be able to convince myself I’m fine.  I thought maybe if I lied to myself often enough,  the lies would take on cosmic power  and be truths in themselves.  Maybe I can believe that you don’t matter to me.  I thought maybe, if life would be kind,  it would spare me from the wrath of reality.  That I could just go on and make-believe  that you and my pain do not exist.  I thought maybe, the heavens will hear and take pity on me and then I would no longer be immersed  in a sea of maybes but of certainties. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
        It catches up with you.   Late at night, when you’re alone with your thoughts, and trying to fall asleep, it catches up with you. Just when you thought you got away with it. Just when you thought the day is over and you can finally rest. It catches up with you.  The worst part of your day has just begun. In the silence, your personal demons are awakening. The night won’t save you. Sleep won’t come. Peace of mind evades you no matter how much you long for it. This is their hour and you - their reluctant guest of honor. It won’t help to fight it. You’ll lose. Without question. Rationalizing won’t help. The night is deep and logic and reason have become irrelevant. You are alone. Utterly. Helplessly. Find your voice and scream from the depths of your lungs, but it won’t drown the chaos in your head. Meet your demons. It would do you well to get acquainted with what will be familiar.  Meet your sadness.  Sadness creeps up from behind and chokes you. Slowly. Silently. Deliberately.  From the deepest and darkest recesses of your soul where you tried to suffocate it, it rises above and vents its anger. Sadness avenges itself against you. Accusing you. It derives its strength from your deceit. For every faked smile and hollow laughter you gave, it doubles its strength inside your own dark underworld. Biding its time. Waiting for the perfect moment to pounce when you are alone and there is nothing to shield you. No gay laughter of friends. No drone of lecture in the classroom. No artificial entertainment on the television.  When everything else is taken out, all you have left is Sadness. It is preceded by the empty feeling of void in your heart. It is accompanied by the nagging worries in your mind. Flanked by the hopelessness in your spirit. When you’re at your most vulnerable, it strikes.  Tears eventually follow. But when Sadness is at its strongest and most vindictive, you won’t have the mercy of tears. Being able to cry is merciful. If you’re not able to, all you’re left with is this choking worthlessness vibrating in your core, echoing through your whole being. An open wound stinging with pain but you can’t scream. You can’t do anything. You endure it. You endure it until you can’t take anymore. Even if you’re pushed through your limits, you have no choice but to suck it in.  Sadness is the well-guarded monster you keep inside of yourself and tell nobody about. You feed it by ignoring it. Denying its existence. Convincing yourself that you have it under control. The more you suppress it, the scarier it becomes.   A frown. A knot in the eyebrows. A twinge of loneliness. A feeling of rejection. A lack of escape. A taste of imprisonment. An overwhelming sense of frustration. An infinite ocean of negativity.  The next thing you know, you are fighting for breath. Drowning in your own sea of sorrows. Flailing your arms for rescue. But something pulls you down. You struggle. Gasping for life. But still, something drags you forcefully below. When you look to find out what it is, you find your own self pulling you down. Your smiling, laughing, suppressed double with its fake mirthful face, grabbing you down.  Welcome to your hell. And here is your steward, yourself.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My knees were unsteady when I was making my way to the stairs up the second floor. I don’t know exactly what was making me nervous, and I didn’t realize it would be this hard.  This would be the last time I’d walk through these halls. Eight months of walking past these steps without even paying attention, and here I was on my last day, wondering how I’ve never noticed how imposing the façade is. I felt intimidated again, as I felt on my first day. I’ve come full circle.  My short talk with my boss was just that – short. I kept my explanation concise and straight-to-the-point and didn’t offer any further explanation of why I was leaving. True to his nature, he didn’t ask for any, either. He asked me to email my resignation letter, though.  I approached my old workstation like a guard-dog would approach a newcomer. I didn’t know if the workstation was still vacant and I felt like an intruder. I went right down to writing the letter, which I realize I didn’t have any previous experience of and thus, I had to make something up from scratch.  “I am putting forward my intention to conclude my on-the-job-training term from your company…”  “…[It has] almost [been] eight months since I started and I am grateful for the valuable exposure to the actual work environment…”  “…I am thankful for the opportunity to have been able to go through this experience…”  It sounds like a load of crap, but I really did mean what I wrote, however cheesy they are. Eight months is still around 3% of my whole life and that’s not something you can just turn your back on.  The office was my first stop during the weekdays. As early as 7 am, I was on my workstation, tapping on my computer. Sometimes, I was the first person on the floor. I spent a lot of graciosa breakfasts on my table.  I completed the clearance form in less than an hour. I had to have a number of people sign it – people who haven’t spent a full minute with me on my whole eight-month stay. It’s amazing how they think up of these stupid bureaucracies. Everything has to be about labels. Have the Sys Ad sign, the School Supplies officer, the Accountant. Heck, those are the first time I’ve seen those people. And I don’t owe them sh*t. And they know that. They haven’t seem me before either – go figure.  If they made any sense at all, they would have asked my direct superior for a real evaluation, not that stuck-up guy from HR who was flaunting his passable command of the English language on my face. Oh, come on. Spare me the serious stance and your pseudo-intellectual pretense at being well read by quoting Gestalt psychology on your email signature.  My direct superiors would have been more capable of assessing of how I have performed. The form I completed couldn’t have reflected that. How could it? Three horizontal lines are all the space they gave me to sum up everything I did. I couldn’t write down how I dragged myself out of bed each morning at 5.30 just to be at the office by 7. I couldn’t write down I drive myself insane with worry if I completed a task efficiently. I couldn’t write down how I was so set on making a good impression with the added pressure that I was from the best university in the country. Three lines? I don’t think so. I ended up not even filling up half of a line.  They don’t know who I am. They are absolutely clueless. Most of them probably have me filed away in their minds as “just the OJT”. Well, maybe that’s unfair. I bet some of the team members would also know me as the one who was entrusted with the documentation because nobody in the development department, being the computer geeks that they are, wants to bother with grammar and descriptions.  I take it all in stride, though. I am no whiner. Maybe on the inside, but never vocally. Basically, I’m a suck-it-in-inside kind of person. So, I don’t really care what they think of me. All I could say is: Good riddance! I’m glad I’m done with that.  After the clearance, I went to the mall and bought a box of assorted cakes and went back to the office and left it to the guard and addressed it to my now-former supervisor.  I went back home and felt a little guilty that I didn’t personally say goodbye to my first team leader in the company and so I texted him. “Hi, Sir. I didn’t get the chance to tell you, but I wanted to thank you for everything and for being the coolest first boss anyone could ever hope for.”  His reply: “Thanks for the good work, Lia. Hope we could get to see back here as a regular employee some other time. Thanks. Wishing you all the best under the guidance of God.”  Now that I’m cleanly done with that phase in my life, I can finally get back to my nervous breakdown without any more unwanted interruptions.  My resignation should have also included the line: “I am on the verge of a nervous breakdown and you can understand why I should want to discontinue…”  At twenty-two, I’m having my first-ever official nervous breakdown. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I should go out more. That’s what I’ve concluded after I had my fortune read for the very first time.   The fortuneteller was nothing like I expected. Maybe that’s because I watch too much movies and television. The stereotype I have is that of Whoopi Goldberg in Ghost conning her way by using eerie voices and weird eye movements.  There was nothing supernatural about the way she looked. She was a fairly thin lady of about mid-thirties with an open and welcoming demeanor about her. She looked just like one of those mothers who tag along their kids to church.  I wasn’t expecting a life-altering experience. But I did hope I would be told of something even remotely mystical. Something like when Santiago went to that Gypsy woman in The Alchemist. But nothing like that happened. Sigh. No treasure in the Egyptian Pyramids, then.  Three minutes into the reading, I was stuck between the feeling of repressed laughter and the feeling of irritation.  “Where’s your boyfriend now?” She asked.  I shrugged and shook my head. I realize I should’ve said something to enlighten her that my nonexistent boyfriend was nowhere right now. But I guess there was something in my reaction that made her ask the next question.  “But you  do  have a boyfriend, right?”  “No, I don’t”  “But you had a boyfriend before?”  “I’ve never tried it.”  “You haven’t tried having a boyfriend before?”  I nodded. The last thing I needed right then is a fortuneteller trampling on my ego, rubbing it in my face that until now, I’m a member of the no boyfriend since birth club. But that exchange was still pretty funny, if you look at it differently.  She said that she was asking me these questions because it was clear to her that I have been hurt before and I was very hesitant to “play the field”, so to speak. She then proceeded to tell me about not one, not two, but three guys who apparently like me a lot. Now, the situation from funny became outright hilarious. The catch is: I don’t pay any attention to them. There’s this other guy, though, whom I really dislike and am irritated at. Now, there’s a lot that fit that category.  My cards also say that I will meet someone whom I will fall head-over-heels in love with. But she warned me to leave something for myself and not give my all out to this person because I’d get up getting hurt badly and it would lead to the deterioration of my health. I should also be careful of a married or very experienced man who will show an interest in me.  What is she talking about? This is me, who’d rather spend my Saturday night watching TV or re-reading a good book than go out and party. There are probably five or so guys whom I consider friends, and apart from them, I don’t have any more male acquaintances. And three?! Yeah, right.  And it didn’t stop there. The pattern of cards placed around the queen of hearts that apparently represented me (Yeah, I know, so cliché) showed that my future looks practically peachy. My parents love and think of me, there’s prosperity on the way, and even chances for abroad. Plus, all my four wishes’ answers are yes. Now, does it get any better than that?   Hear a great perspective of your life for just twenty pesos . If there’s an ad, that’s what it should say. These readings were not unique to me. Most of us had similar analyses, which is kind of a bummer, because a part of me wanted to believe that even half of it would be true.  The reading for twenty pesos was not that bad. True, I could’ve gotten all that encouragement and rosy future shtick from my friends for free, but I thought the cards and the palm reading was a nice touch.  I don’t really see myself looking for another session anytime soon. That one is enough to last me for a long while. I thought maybe I should give the forecasts a chance to even have a chance. And that’s when I concluded I should go out more. How else would I meet the two mestizos and the other moreno guy, huh? ( *wink, wink* ). My life’s a sitcom. No matter how hard I try to look at it as a dramatic saga, it’s a sitcom.  There was one thing that really amused me about the whole experience. It was the first thing that she told me when I sat down and extended my palm. She told me I am intelligent.  Intelligent. That killed me. If I were  really  smart, I should’ve gone straight home and watched the re-run of X-Files on TV. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever thought so hard that everything you see blurs and you can feel the earth rotate?  Have you ever hit your fist against a wall over and over and over again just to measure how much pain you can take?  Have you ever wished so hard upon a star that everything else dims and it becomes the only light you see?  Have you ever fallen asleep to the ticking sound of the clock and took comfort that it matched your heartbeat?  Have you ever woken up from a dream with your hand clutched to your heart and your eyes damp from too much tears?  Have you ever wondered how it will all end and asked yourself whether you have lived too much, enough, or at all? 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "What were you thinking?"  "That's it. I wasn't. Ironically, my head was never as clear than when I've decided that I was going ahead with it."  "If there's anyone who has to go, it should damn well be Jericho Rosales."  He laughed.  "Hey, I'm not kidding, ok? Don't ever scare me like that again.  Ever . I know it seems like you're like given a preview to hell right now, but believe me, it will get better. Think about it: How could it get any worse?"  "You know what? Of all the people I wish to talk to, it's you, because your hell is closest to mine. Well, no offense meant."  "None taken."  He smiled but did not say anything.  "Just... I don't know. Just breathe. Breathe, ok? You have to start somewhere. Start with your breath."  He nodded at her noncommittally. She stood up to leave.  " ’My future is a cadaver crunching in a very fast decay...’ "  She looked back at him and raised an eyebrow. "Plath again?"  "No. Mine. Narcissistic, huh?"  She shook her head and closed the door behind her.  He sat alone in the empty room, silently contemplating. Everything seemed to be trivial. Funny. Because he was so convinced he would be dead by now. He had written his farewell journal entry to his fictitious friend Holden. His stories and poetry were neatly set aside to be left posthumously. He even returned the rented VCDs. It was funny that those were all he managed to put into order.  The poet stood up. This called for a walk. Walking was his substitute to weed. He would've preferred the real thing, but walking would have to do right then. Stepping out into the open air of the street, he was oblivious to the usual cacophony of the city. Instead, his mind wandered elsewhere.  He remembered his flunked subjects. His suspension from the University. The painful talk with his parents. The equally painful email he had to write to his aunt who was supporting his college education. The pleading. The refusing. The white lies. He found it amusing that he had to lie to spare them all from the pain of knowing the full extent of the reality.  "Nobody fails if everyone studies."  His mother's words echoed within the hollow corners of his head, taunting him. Aggravating him that he had to be burdened by the truth.   "I don't have the heart for it," he had said. And barely getting the words out, he choked, "You would never understand me because you don't even read the books I read."  He remembered his asphyxiation attempt. Somewhere along the long and painful effort to restrain his breathing, a tiny part of him wanted to let go. He remembered his struggle for breath. In his life full of difficulties, he tried to deprive himself of something that was easy. The air was his and it never failed him, was never disappointed at him, and never had to question him.  A vehicle's blare snapped him back into his senses. He quickened his steps. He had to get home soon. He had to find his copy of J.D. Salinger's Catcher in the Rye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Pwedeng magpaturo? Feeling ko kasi nang nagsabog ang Maykapal ng kagalingan sa pagpapahumaling ng mga kalalakihan, parang nagtago ako sa kailaliman ng isang liblib na kweba at wala akong nakuha ni katiting man lang.  ‘Ika nga, being too charming was never one of my faults. Ang opinyon ng ibang tao sa akin sa unang tingin, kung hindi repulsively abrasive, eh, coldly indifferent naman. Alam ko yun, kasi tinanong ko ang mga kaibigan ko kung ano ang first impression nila sa akin. Meron rin namang iba na medyo tactful at sinasabi na I  “look comfortable being alone” , self-sufficient daw kumbaga kaya walang nagtatangkang lumapit kahit sino.  Eh, sa mga crushes ko, ‘kanyo? Paano ako umasta? Parang male-male na may speech defect at dyslexia o di naman kaya parang di-makabasag pinggan na noveciada sa kumbento – pormal na pormal at hindi nagsasalita o kung hindi naman parang isang sobrang dedma na weirdo. Sitcom ang crush life ko. Slapstick na may pagka-spoof na may pagka-horror.  Abnormal ba ako? Ba’t di ako marunong magpa-cute?  Ilang beses nang nangyari na andyan na sya sa tabi ko. O kaya sa harap ko. Nakangiti sya. Alam n’yo ba ang pakiramdam na parang disconnected ang logic mo sa motor senses mo? Ganon. Hindi man lang ako makatango. Andali lang magsabi  “Uy, ‘musta?”  Aargh. Di lang ‘to katorpehan. Katangahan na talaga.  May mga pagkakataon naman, ewan ko lang talaga kung bakit, na hindi ko talaga kayang malapit siya. Parang hindi ako mapalagay kaya ako ang lumalayo. Group meeting namin. Syempre andon sya. Ewan ko lang kung saan nagbabakasyon ang diwa at dila ko kaya’t daig pa ako ng ibang extra sa mga telenovela. Buti pa sila, may mga one-liner, ako talaga, wala. Anyway, napansin yata ng mga kasamahan ko na masama pakiramdam ko.  “Okay ka lang?” , ‘ka nila. Nakatingin si lalaking pinagpalaan sa akin. Sa akin. Gusto niya ring malaman kung okay lang ako. Ako. At ano ang ginawa ko? Bilis, ano sa tingin nyo? Tumayo ako bigla sabay sabi nang,  “Bili muna ako paracetamol.”  Tapos, lumakad ng mabilis palabas. Sa totoo lang, sumakit nga ulo ko. Sa sarili kong ka-weirdo-han. Ha-haay.  Hindi naman palaging  “don’t-know-what-to-do/say-whenever-you-are-near”  ang eksena ko. Nakakausap ko naman. Minsan, talaga lang nabobobo ako. My IQ shoots down a few points pag andyan na object of my affliction, uhm, affection pala. Magkaharap kami sa lamesa at nagke-kwentuhan. Nabanggit sa usapan namin na Kapampangan ang roots ko. Sabi niya,  “So, it’s true pala na girls from Pampanga are pretty.”  Reaction ko? Wala. Tameme ako for what seemed to be an eternity of uncomfortable, tense silence. Sabay tingin sa sahig. Ano ba naman inaasahan kong makita doon sa sahig? Cue cards? Teleprompter? Bilis, ano sa tingin nyo? Dahil hanggang ngayon di ko talaga alam kung bakit. Iniba ko na lang ang usapan. Siguro nga wala sa personalidad ko ang mag-react sa mga klaseng remark na ganon with a  “thank you” . Pero, it would have been characteristic of me to have said,  “Uy, ah. Wag ka naman gaanong magpa-obvious na nagkakagusto ka na sa akin.”  Di lang common sense ang nawawala sa akin. Pati sense of humour.  Normally, I am a fast thinker; even quick-witted, sometimes.  Kumbaga, parang DSL, mabilis ang response time. Pag crushie ko na ang kaharap ko, nagiging 28.8 kbps na dial-up ako. Oras ang lumilipas bago ko nalalaman kung ano ang pinaka-akmang sabihin. ‘Saklap.  May kaibigan ako. Kung ako ay hindi pa nakakapasa ng pre-school sa pagpapa-cute, yung kaibigan ko, may ph.d. na. Nakalimutan ko kung nakailang nobyo na sya, sa sobrang dami. Ako, ni isa, hindi pa nagkakaroon. Sabi niya, you have to give a motive daw. Yung mga tipong, pasulyap-sulyap daw o kaya pangiti-ngiti sa taong gusto mo. She tried to tell me that flirting is something every girl should master.  Hindi ba pwedeng ibang paraan na lang? Wala akong talent sa  “beautiful eyes”  kahit noong bata pa ako, eh. Hindi yan isa sa mga naging  “tricks”  ko noong toddler pa ako. And I don’t think reciting  “Ten Little Indians”  count as a flirtation skill. Pero ang pagpapa-cute is just a way to get to know the other person better, di ba? Sabi ko sa sarili ko, baka pwedeng mag-tong-its na lang kami. Ako pa bibili ng isang malaking supot ng mani. Mas magkakakilala kami sa ganoong paraan. As they say, you learn more about a person in five minutes of play than in an hour of talk. O, sige, baka mas gusto niya ng Uno, ok rin lang sa akin.   Eh, pano nyan? Kailangan ko pa rin syang yayain mag-hang out para maglaro. Based on my track record, malamang, makakaubos ako ng isang supot ng mani mag-isa nang di oras.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hindi daw niya talaga gusto. Deeper level of friendship lang daw talaga ang nararamdaman niya para kay lalaki. Friendship ka dyan! Eh, halos mangiyak-ngiyak siya na nagkekwento sa akin na uuwi daw yung lalaki sa Bacolod para manligaw sa kababayan niya.  Pwede ba?!  Kung may gusto, aminin! Wag lituhin ang mga kaibigan. Lalo nang wag lituhin ang sarili.  Si kaibigan number two. Ah, eto. Astig ito. Officemate niya. Matipunong lalaki daw, eh. Hindi makukumpara ang ilong at mga labi niya maski kanino pang nilalang. Hindi lang inamin, pinagnanasaan pa! Acquaintances sila, sabay kumain ng dinner sa office. Kung ano-ano na lang. May mga kwentuhan pa sila tungkol kay Ayn Rand na plus pogi points syempre sa friendship ko. Ang pangalan ng lalaki, hindi lang nakuntento na isulat ng paulit-ulit o kaya banggit-banggitin ng tahimik sa mga dasal. Gi-noogle pa! Aba'y akala ko, pang research lang sa school ang Google, mantakin nyo ba naman at ginawa pang instrumento na pang-stalk ng tao?!  Ang problema, gusto niyang makahanap ng kamalian sa taong gusto nya para madali na lang daw kalimutan ito. Ewan ko ba kung ano ang gusto nyang malaman. Baka ikatutuwa niya kung may lahing kapre ang crush niya o di naman kaya tig-aanim ang daliri sa paa. Sabi niya sa akin, mabuti pa na habang maaga pa ay mawalan na siya ng gana at tiyak na masasaktan lang sya pag tinuloy-tuloy niya ang pagkagusto dito. Parang  "where's the logic?"  kaagad ang dating nito sa akin, pero gets ko naman, kahit papaano.  Yung isa naman,  "you made me stronger by breaking my heart"  ang soundtrack ng buhay. Ang love story nyan nung nag-umpisa ay, naku, napaka-kumplikado. Love thy neighbor ang favorite commandment ng isang ito. Nagkagustuhan sila kaya lang disapproving ang parents niya kaya ala-Romeo and Juliet na itinago sa pamilya. Long distance love affair pa dahil nasa Maynila si lalaki samantalang nasa Cebu naman friend ko. At, hindi lang yun! May girlfriend si lalaki sa ibang bansa na di nya pa pormal na hiniwalayan. Ano, daig pa ang ibang telenovela, di ba? Sa madaling salita, pagkatapos ng sangkatutak na away-bati at makailang beses rin nang burahan ng phonebook entry sa cellphone, nauwi rin sa hiwalayan. Buti na lang kanyo at ang Romeo and Juliet/ Salawahan/ LDLA love story nila ay hindi nauwi sa crime of passion news item.   Yung pinaka-huli ko naman na kaibigan, isinumpa na lahat ng kalahi ni Adan. Ayaw nya na daw talaga magkagusto sa kahit sino man lalaki. Pramis daw. Ito naman kasi siya, bihira lang talaga mahulog sa lalaki. Sa mga iilang pagkakataon naman na ma-inlab sya, eh, dun pa talaga sa mga walang kwenta tao. Yung mga tipong nakikipaglokohan lang pala o di naman kaya mga walang respeto. Eh, sino nga ba naman ang hindi maiinis sa ganon, di ba? Kaya sya, sabi niya di bale na lang daw na walang love life, basta wala naman daw syang sakit ng ulo at sakit ng damdamin. Peminista na nga ito ngayon, eh.  Ako, simple lang kwento ko. Hindi pa ako naiin-love. May mga false alarms, pero wala talaga. At naisip ko rin, keysa problemahin ko pa yang love story ko (or its lack thereof), masmabuti pang concentrate muna ako sa peedeekyu story ko. Hindi niyo alam ang peedeekyu story ko? Wag na, mahabang salaysayin. Madugo at madrama. Sa susunod na lang. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You see that animated GIF of Jason Mraz? Ah, the ordeal to have that three-second-clip on this page.   To start things off, I downloaded his "The Remedy (I Won't Worry)" music video. And then I wanted to crop a portion of it so I got Ulead Video Studio 6. But the video was in MPEG format so I had to get Blaze Media Pro to convert it into AVI. So now, I have an AVI file, but I wanted to post it so I had to get AVI-GIF converter. After this, I already have an animated GIF of the clip, but its dimension was 320 x 240 - which is huge! File size was around a 1000 KB. So, I had to download Animation Shop because it can resize animated GIF. After resizing it, I was able to upload it.   Whew.   Now, I'm stuck with all these trial version softwares for the next thirty freaking days. All that trouble just to see Mraz in his bright red cap peer up at me from a tiny window.  Those couple of hours weren't that much waste of a time, was it? 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I recently downloaded the banned music video of  Pearl Jam's Jeremy . The one where a screwed up kid  (Jeremy, of course)  took a gun to school, stood in front of his class and ... well, you all know how it went. I thought it was way cool. It's a great song and the video was very edgy. I like edgy. Watching the video is like watching a short film noir where you can't take your eyes off the screen and you're seated at the edge of your seat. There's something fascinating about the dark side of human nature that compels me to shut up, watch, and listen.  I let my mother see the video -- bad idea. Of course, she found it too morbid and disturbing. She asked me to immediately delete it. What was I thinking when I asked her to see it? That she'd find  Eddie Vedder  and the suicide anthem cool, too? Uhmm, I guess my IQ was on the blink at that moment. Mothers. They think their kids are just that. Kids. Even if they're twenty-two years old and have their own thanatopses.  (I didn't delete it, by the way.)   Hey, I just saw a tiny mouse run across our floor. And I swear, it jumped a distance of about a foot. No kidding. It's like the mouse was a long jump athlete in the rodent world. Boy, I better start raising my energy level. Even lower mammals are evolving to be more physically active.  Carry on, little mouse. I'll catch up with you after I post this one.  (riiight...)  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        If you don't know who he is: you're missing out on   a lot  . This good-looking guy is a very talented songwriter, singer, guitarist, performer. If his music is not enough for you, check out his online journal  here  and find out how an amusing writer he can be.   What I like best about Jason Mraz is that he's all about the love for his craft. It's not about the fame or the money. In fact, despite his international success, he still shares a "dingy" apartment with two of his friends. Now, is that keeping it real or what?  I'm gonna marry this guy someday. Jason, honey, we still have to finalize our wedding details. Call me soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This peer-to-peer software program has me clutched against its claws. And me? I'm the willing victim. And I've got 7.34 GB of hard drive to prove it. Yep. Piracy has found a way to snake its way devious ways into my netsurfing. Alert the open seas. Captain Hook has found his competition.   In my personal (and somewhat flimsy) defense, I don't make a profit out of these downloaded items. I could take those mp3 files and make compilation CDs, sell them for a hundred bucks apiece. But I don't. Hmm. Though thinking about it now makes me wonder if I should. Sounds like a lucrative thing... but, no. I'm sticking to my principles. (What principles am I talking about?!)  Also, I could say that those downloaded video and audio clips of Jason Mraz and John Mayer have convinced me that I should buy their original albums. And that's what I'll do. I've heard their songs and I'm convinced that I want their originals. See? Something good has come out of all those hours I've spent in my downloading.  The world is a better place once again. (Well, for Jason, John, and me, at least.)      
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Describe what you feel like waking up on Monday morning.    I feel like kicking myself for the nth time because I never learned how to sleep early. Thus, I also feel sleep-deprived.    If you could relive your life, what would you do differently?    Yeah, some parts of it, I guess. It'd be hypocritical of me to say that I've lived my life the best possible way I could. And if I were given the chance to relive it, why spoil it all over again when I know better this time? It's evolution. You're now equipped with wisdom and experience. Not using these advantages to be a better person than you were before is plain illogical.   What is your favorite TV show?    I like CSI and Crime Night (The New Detectives, FBI Files, Medical Detectives). I also like Gilmore Girls, Will & Grace, and Whose Line Is It Anyway. Gore and Laughter. What a match.   What is your favorite book?    It's gotta be J.D. Salinger's The Catcher in the Rye. Holden is absolutely unforgettable.   What is your favorite type of music?    Rock - which is so vague because it's like the umbrella term for everything else. Acoustic guitars. Some alternative, a little pop. But please, no Britney Spears. I'd rather swallow needles.    Have you ever wished for true love?    Have you ever read a cheesier question?! LOL.   Describe your most embarrassing experience in school.    I forgot my schedule and walked into my class, unaware that it was about to end in five minutes (which would explain the snickers and puzzled looks of my prof and classmates). Of course, I'm trying to repress the REALLY embarrassing one that involves stepping down from a jeepney, ripping of my jeans, and a close acquaintanceship between my knees and the road asphalt.   Suggest a book for me to read.    Refer to my favorite book. Ayn Rand's The Fountainhead is way cool, too. You might find her ideas a little crazy, but I assure you, her fictions are worth all the hassle. And if you're into conspiracy theories, check out Dan Brown's The Da Vinci Code. It'll blow you away.   If you could be ten years older, would you be happier?    Hmm, I really don't know.   What is your favorite film?    Well, I don't know about favorites, but I like "Phone Booth" a lot. I love the way it's written so cleverly that the majority of the scenes happen in one area. Very gripping. No special effects, just a solid story. I also like Fight Club. Edward Norton, lots of violence, and a twist of psychosis. What else do you want? =)   Describe what it feels like to be in love.    This may sound like I'm the grinch of true love and romance, but I really wouldn't know.   Have you ever done something, but regretted it later?    Oh, sure. If you ever went malling with my friends and you forgot to wear comfortable shoes, you'll regret it, too.    What are your hobbies?    Reading, writing, netsurfing, and TV. Okay, okay! I'm boring, I know. No need to rub it in. =)   What is your deepest fear?    (Aside from snakes and other reptiles) Losing any of my loved ones.   If you could meet one person, dead or alive, who would it be?    I'd like to meet J.D. Salinger and ask if I could read some of his unpublished stories about the Glass family and maybe Holden. Or Gabriel Garcia Marquez and ask short story writing pointers.   What is your favorite thing to wear?    t-shirts. denims. sneakers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up at three in the afternoon.   I was nursing a slight headache. I wouldn't categorize it as exactly a hangover, but it's the closest thing I could get to one. After all, I only had one bottle of beer. Which is all I can take because I'm allergic to alcohol.  It was my first day back in Cebu, my favorite city. I love this place. Our family has lived a somewhat nomadic lifestyle because we moved around quite a bit. In fact, right now, we're "geographically distributed". I'm here in Western Visayas, my dad's in Central Luzon, My mom's in Northern Mindanao, my sister's in the National Capital Region and my brother's in Misamis Oriental (I forgot the regional name of this one ;).   Of all the places I've stayed in, Cebu is special to me. Because it's well-developed, but it's not as crazy as Manila. It's not as crowded and it's not as polluted. Everything is so accessible - the pier, the airport, the mall, the schools, and even the resorts. There are tiny little details about the place that makes it unique. But I guess its people also contribute to this because generally Cebuanos are cool.  My friends, for example, are great people. They may be a little crazy sometimes, but I think that adds to their charms. Yesterday, for example, the reason we went out is because Abad (we all call her by her family name) had a sudden urge to sing "Eye of the Tiger" in karaoke.  After they sang to their hearts' content, we went to Dunkin' Donuts and talked about a lot of things over coffee and hot chocolate until sunrise. And these people can talk about anything. And I mean, anything. Books, movies, television, celebrities, careers - anything. I remember that the conversation even veered towards sexually transmitted diseases. How it got to that I couldn't quite exactly recall.  It was half past five in the morning when we all decided to go home. They all walked me to my building which was just a few blocks away. It was nice - strolling along Osmeña Boulevard, laughing together about shallow things, while the sun makes it slow appearance.  I didn't get to sleep right away when I got home. My allergy was starting to act up and my itchy skin was somewhat uncomfortable. But I've had worse attacks than that one. I watched some TV before dozing off. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Bwisit.   Kung bakit naman kasi kailangan kong magbarko papuntang Cebu. Barko lang talaga ang tanging paraan. May eroplano nga pero mahal. Quadruple ang pamasahe.  Kung bakit naman kasi di kami mayaman. Yun pala ang tamang tanong. Edi sana mas mabilis, mas kumportable. Pero mas mabilis at mas kumportable kung marunong akong mag-apparate. Isang incantation lang, poof! nandoon na ako sa paroroonan ko.  Kung bakit naman kasi di totoo yang lintik na mundo ni Harry Potter. Haaay, ewan ko ba.  Naiinis talaga ako tuwing sasakay ako ng barko. Naiinis ako na kahit sa tourist class, magkakadikit ang mga cots. Mga di mo kilala na tao ang katabi mong matulog. Creepy, di ba?  Pero wala nga ako choice. Hindi kami mayaman at walang wizarding world.   Bwisit.   Nang ihatid ako ng nanay ko sa pier, medyo nasesenti ako ng konti kasi nga matagal-tagal na naman bago ako makauwi. Kaya lang naudlot lahat ng pag-e-emote ko nung natandaan ko ang kalbaryo ko bago ako makarating sa safety ng sarili kong kwarto sa Cebu. Ang pinakamalaking hadlang: ang pagsakay sa barko.  Ako lang kasi mag-isa. Big deal yun. Andami po kayang tarantado, manggagancho, at manloloko sa mga pier. Mukha pa naman akong anghel na vulnerable sa mga masasamang loob (ehem!).  Number 73 ang cot number ko. Pagdating ko dun, may babae na nakiusap sa akin na makipagpalit ng cot para magkatabi sila ng asawa/boyfriend nyang Hapon. Nasa adjacent bed lang naman so pumayag na ako.  Kalalapag ko lang ng bag ko sa cot #105 nang may isang mayabang na lalaki na lumapit sa akin habang patext-text sa kanyang 3310 na cellphone. Tinanong niya ako, "Excuse me, miss, are you alone?"  Medyo nag-alangan muna ako bago ko sinabing oo. Gusto ko sanang magsinungaling pero malalaman rin, eh. Aba, di mo basta basta vino-volunteer yan na information. Mukha pa naman siyang sanggano.  "Is it okay if we exchange cot numbers?"  Grrr. Medyo matagal bago ako sumagot. Tumaas kilay ko. Deactivate nice person mode tuloy ako. Pinakita ko talaga sa kanya na he was an unwelcome annoyance.  "Which one's your cot?" tanong ko sa kanya.  Ako, di ko gustong nag-eenglish pero pag ako, in-address mo in such, di ako nasisindak. Kaya naiinis ako sa mga tao na ginagamit ang english speaking skills nila to intimidate others. Buti kung tama lahat. Akala kasi ng iba, budburan lang ng mga "you know" , "actually", at "like this/that" ang pananalita nila, magaling na sila. Hindi ako intellectual snob. Ang sa akin lang, panindigan mo ng buong-buo.  Tulad ni mamang mayabang, napasubo tuloy sa kanyang pag-e-english. Sabi nya in broken grammar, "I am a police officer and I am protecting these people so they can safely arrive."  Inayos ko na lang talaga yang sinabi nya. Katakot-takot kasi na [sic] kung verbatim ko pa ilalahad. Yung mga people na tinukoy nya nga pala ay isang grupo ng Filipino-Chinese passengers. Mapuputi't mga singkit. May mga matronly women, may mga matatandang lalaki rin. So, anyway, pulis pala si mamang mayabang. That explains the authoritative air (read: kayabangan).  "Why don't you just give me your cot number so I can check it out and let you know whether or not it's fine with me."  Vaguely, tumuro sya sa may kaliwang banda.  "Which one exactly? The one against the window or somewhere else?"  Irita na ako at this point at bawat butil ng aking pagkainis ay halata na. Andami pa kasing pasakalye, eh. Buti na lang at soon after, natauhan si mamang pulis at direkta nang itinuro yung cot nya. Tinanong nya ako kung ok lang sa akin. Pumayag na rin ako para matapos na ang usapan namin at nang lubayan nya na ako. Nagpasalamat sya at inabot ang kanyang kamay para magpakilala. Grrr. Frowning, I gave him a terse nod and didn't say anything back. Pwede ba?! Go away!  Nang nilipat ko na ang mga gamit ko sa cot #11, umupo muna ako at sandaling nanood ng TV. Sabi ni Julius Babao, may pinaslang na naman na bakla, ngayon naman sa Valenzuela City. Habang nakikinig ako sa nagbabagang balita ng TV Patrol, dumating na ang may-ari ng cot na katabi ko. Lalaki.   Bwisit.   Hindi na ba matatapos ang kalbaryo ko?! Inayos nung lalaki yung beddings nya. Ako naman, kunwari nanood pa rin ng TV pero naghahanap na ako ng malilipatang cot. Nang nag-undock na ang barko, lumipat ako sa isang bakanteng cot na walang katabi. Brod, walang personalan, matter of privacy lang.  Cot #52 ang final na tinulugan ko, finally. 73-105-11-52. I-scramble ko kaya ang mga numbers na yan at itaya sa Lotto? Hehe.  Nang na-settled na ako, nagkaroon ako ng pagkakataon na obserbahan ang mga tao sa paligid ko. Discreetly, of course.  May babae't lalaki na nag-uusap sa unahan. Mga coño. Tisoy si lalaki at cute rin yung girl and alam nyang cute sya. Alam nyo kung bakit ko nasabi? Kasi sa likod ng baby tee nya ay ang big, bold letters na nagsasabing "Major Cutie". O, di ba?  Nasulyapan ko yung mga Fil-Chinese na binabantayan ni mayabang pulis. Baka may kidnap for ransom threats sila. O kaya mga kilalang pulitiko. Ewan ko ba.  Hindi ako gaanong nakatulog. Masyado akong paranoid na baka mawala yung mga gamit ko o kaya baka dumating yung may-ari ng cot na nilipatan ko. At saka sino ba namang makakatulog in a room full of people you don't know. Buti kung may kasama ako, eh ako lang talaga kaya parang overly wary ako sa environment ko.  Nang malapit nang mag-dock ang barko kaninang madaling araw, tiniklop at sinoli ko na beddings ko. Actually, di na talaga kailangan tiklopin kasi itatambak rin naman lahat yun sa laundry. Pero nung mga bata pa kami, sinabihan kami ng nanay namin na di dapat ganon ang reasoning namin. Maayos iniabot ang beddings sa amin, dapat maayos rin syang ibalik.  Namis ko tuloy nanay ko nung inaayos ko yung beddings ko. Haay, ganyan talaga ang buhay. Parang life.  Sa buong 12 hours ako sa barko, isang beses lang ako napangiti. Nung malapit na sa Cebu pier ang barko, may mga batang babae na nakadungaw sa bintana at nagsigawan ng, "Ay! Si Ate Marina! Si Ate Marina!"  Hehe. "Ate Marina" daw. Feeling close! ;) 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Bakit puro black ang gamit mo?! Yung bag mo, yung sapatos mo, yung jacket mo, yung isa mo pang bag, pantalon mo, pati t-shirt mo! Bakit itim lahat yan?!   Nanay ko. Bahagyang nanggagalaiti. Pinupuna color perception/fashion sense ko.  Linawin ko lang sandali. Dark blue ang t-shirt ko, hindi itim. Ang pantalon ko, kahit itim nang una kong binili, ay kupas na ngayon. Kaya grayish na sya.  Balikan natin ang nanay ko. Ganito talaga tuwing nagiimpake ako.    Ano ba yang t-shirt na yan? Dadalhin mo pa ba yan? Eh yung binili ko sayo na skirt and blouse, di mo dadalhin? Hindi mo siguro ginagamit ang mga yun doon, ano? Magsuot ka naman ng mga may kulay paminsan-minsan.    Dark blue ang favorite color ko. Pero marami akong gamit na kulay itim. Maliban sa in-enumerate ng nanay ko, itim rin lahat ng pens ko, mga diskettes ko, mga pantali ko sa buhok, sinturon ko, at kung ano-ano pa.  Gusto ko ang black kasi hindi agaw-pansin. Tsaka di sya nagiging corny o baduy. Natatandaan nyo pa ba nung na-uso ang neon colors? Nakakapangilabot. Buti na lang kanyo at hindi neon ang naging paborito ko. Kung nagkataon, edi mukha akong walking highligter ngayon.  Aalis na nga pala ako mamaya. Goodbye to the comfort of one's own home. Hello again to overrated independent living. Yung mga di pa mulat sa hubad na katotohanan, iniisip siguro nila na napaka-cool to live on your own without parents to breathe down your back. To a certain extent, totoo yun. Ikaw ang boss. Master of your fate, captain of your soul. Masaya kasi diskarte mo lahat. Nasa sayo kung saan ka pupunta, kung kailan ka uuwi, at kung sino kasama mo. Depende na lang sayo yun at sa upbringing and convictions mo (naks!).  Pero, ikaw rin bahala sa lahat. Budget ng pera, hanap ka kung saan ka kakain, mag-aayos ng damit mo, maglilinis ng kwarto, tapos syempre mag-aaral ka pa. Pero ang pinakamahirap kapag nagkakasakit ka. Walang mag-aalaga sayo. Kawawa kang bata ka.  Try mong trangkasuhin ng linggo. Kahit groggy, bili ka gamot sa botika. Absent ka sa lunes. Pero pasok ka sa martes na parang zombie. Try mo. Ang saya. Promise.  Anyway, sign off na ako. Kelangan ko pang i-double check things ko. Sigurado namang may kakalimutan ako, susubukan ko lang to put those at a minimum. Sana di toothbrush maiwan ko.    (Ang title ng entry na ito ay hango sa unang line ng kantang "Rocket Man" na isang Elton John original na ni-cover ni Jason Mraz. Yun lang. =)   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If Guns n' Roses had an album named The Spaghetti Incident -- this, my friends, is an entry about the Chicken Curry Incident.  It all started with a good intention.  I'm leaving tomorrow and I thought I'd give my mom a break and be the one to cook lunch. I usually just help with the dishes and steer clear from anything that involves open flame and sharp objects. I followed her instructions, but insisted that I needed no supervision.  (Yaahh-bang!)   Okay, kids, don't try this at home. Or anywhere else, for that matter.  What you need for this recipe:  (Sorry I don't do measurements. Measuring are for wimps and not for lazy people like me. Hehe.)   1) chicken  (duh.)  2) curry powder  (double duh.)  3) garlic 4) onions  5) bell pepper 6) potatoes 7) carrots 8) salt  9) pepper 10) milk  (coconut milk, preferably)  11) cooking oil  ... and!  12) reliable attention span.  (You'll NEED this. Trust me on this one.)   Here's what you need to do:  Fry the chicken in oil. Not extra-crispy frying. Just let it brown a little. Set that aside. And then, fry the potatoes and the carrots. Set those aside with the chicken, too. Now, saute the garlic and onions. Dump in the chicken and vegetables. Sprinkle it with the curry powder, salt, and pepper. Put in the bell peppers. Mix it all well. Put in a little water and then the milk. Cover the pan and let the whole thing simmer in low heat.  Easy, huh?  I did all those with  veeery  little trouble. Sure, there was the occasional altercations with the splash of hot oil while frying or the sporadic dropping of utensils. But other than that, I did fine. In fact, I thought I did a helluva job.   I was so damn cool about the whole cooking thing that I turned on my computer and started surfing a bit. I dropped by my favorite sites, most of which are fellow bloggers'. One of the blogs featured the Goo Goo Dolls' song, "Here is Gone". And I remembered how I really liked the song. I had a hard disk drive crash a few months ago and lost all my old MP3's, including the Goo Goo Dolls' songs. So I downloaded "Here is Gone", and the other old ones like "Name", "Slide", "Iris", and the Rzeznik solo, "I'm Still Here".  After that, I logged on to my instant messaging services. I lurked to find out on who's online and checked my emails. Grrr. I hate spam. I hate chain mails. I hate emails with subjects that contain the words: "enlarge", "live video", and "XXX".  Delete All. Confirm?  Hell, yes!   So there I was, idling in front of my computer for almost an hour when all of a sudden, something hit me. No, an anvil didn't fall on my head. I mean, a surge of alarm shot through me and I immediately sat straight up. I know it's so prosaic, but it's like there were warning bells inside my head but I had no idea what they were for.  Looking back, I must've looked stupid while I stared blankly ahead and tried to remember what I missed.  Processing... processing... processing... processing...    Oh. My. God.    The pan was still on the stove!   I could've given The Flash a run for his money the way I ran. When I got to the stove, there was no flame, but the knob was still turned on. When I opened the pan's cover, the sauce was entirely evaporated, but thank goodness, nothing was charred. I guess the low flame was put out by some lucky wind, just in time.   Whew.   An hour. I actually left the whole thing for  an hour .  (Why am I sensing that motherhood is not something meant for me?)   I told you. You need to have a reliable attention span. Well, better than mine, needless to say. Anyway, the end product was drier than the desired texture. But, hey, I'd rather choose that over charcoal. What started with a good intention almost ended up being burnt beyond recognition.  I'm Lia, Queen of the Klutz, and I survived cooking lunch. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Nung toddler pa ako, gusto kong magkaroon ng policeman na laruan.  Hindi ko naman matandaan kung bakit. Baka siguro na-uso na ang RoboCop ng panahon na iyon. Hindi lang ako sigurado. Basta, ang alam ko, nung tinanong ako kung anong gusto kong laruan, ang sinagot ko, gusto ko ng policeman.  May voice tape kasi kami na ni-record ng nanay ko nung mga maliliit pa kaming magkakapatid. Two years old ako nuon, three ang kapatid kong babae na kakaumpisa pa lang mag-aral ng pre-school at seven years old naman ang Kuya namin.  Sa Middle East kasi nagtrabaho ang tatay namin noon. Pre- gulf war  at pre- US war of aggression against terrorism  pa nun. Matagal nagtrabaho bilang inhinyero sa ibang bansa ang tatay ko kaya maraming sulat at pictures na naipon ang mga magulang ko nung nagco-communicate sila. Kabilang dito yung voice tape na binanggit ko. Wala pa kasing email nuon.   Dun sa voice tape, pina-perform kami ng nanay ko ng mga nursery rhymes. Yung mga tulad ng  Hickory Dickory Dock ,  Baa Baa Black Sheep , at ang walang kamatayang  Jack and Jill . Pinagdasal din kami out loud ng prayers. (Grabe, ang bait kong bata noon) Gaya ng  Our Father  at  Hail Mary . Teka, The Lord's Prayer nga pala ang tamang pangalan ng  Our Father . Kasali rin nga pala dun yung  Now I Lay Me Down to Sleep .   Now I lay me down to sleep;  I pray to God my soul to keep.   If I should die before I wake,   I pray to God my soul to take.   Ngayon, pag naaalala ko yang dasal na yan, medyo naiilang ako. Di ba parang medyo morbid sya na prayer para sa isang bata?  Kung mamamatay ako bago ako magising, ipinapanalangin ko na kunin na ng Panginoon ang kaluluwa ko.  Parang hindi wholesoeme, di ba?  Anyway, marami pa kaming toddler tricks na ni-record sa tape. Mga singing, counting, alphabet, at question and answer. Parang nagpapa-showcase kami sa tatay ko para naman kahit na hirap sya na magtrabaho sa malayo, matuwa naman sya sa amin na ang gagaling ng mga anak nya.  Nang pinabilang ako from one to twenty, ang sabi ko,  "...fourteen, fifteen, seventeen, eighteen..."  Pangitain kaya yun na Math ang magiging weakness ng academic life ko? ;p  May precursor rin pala ang pagkabulol ko. Ayon sa akin, twenty-one years ago, ang seven continents of the world ay:  "Ey-cha, Africa, Europe, North America, Chout America, Antarctica, Ochrelya."   Ang saya-saya.  Ang  kuliiiiiit  ko pala nung bata pa ako. Hindi lang ako terrible two. Terrifically, terrifyingly, terrorizing, terrible two. Feeling ko, kung makita ko ang two year old self ko, makukurot ko talaga sya sa singit. Sa tape, ayaw kong ibigay yung mic sa kapatid ko. Gusto ko, akin lang palagi. Tapos, ginugulo ko sila kapag sila na ang nagre-recite. Umiyak talaga ako ng pagkalakas-lakas nang pinapaawat na ako ng nanay ko. Umabot siguro yung mga hiyaw ko sa mga kapitbahay namin.  Naaaliw akong paulit-ulit na pakinggan yung voice tape na yun. Andaldal ko kasi for a two-year-old. I find it amusing to hear myself so loud. Parang nag-peak ang talkativeness ko at two pagkatapos nun, it all went downhill from there.  Natatawa rin ako sa mga tantrums ko. Kasi madalas kung may nagco-comment na maswerte daw ako kasi ako ang youngest sa pamilya, lagi kong sinasabi na hindi ko nararamdaman na may special treatment sa akin. Pero kung pakikinggan ko yung tape, talagang hindi ko maipagkakaila na bunso nga ako. Ako yung pinagbibigyan. Pinagpapasensyahan. Yung hindi pinapatulan.   Pero sa tingin ko, never naman kaming naging spoiled. Hindi lahat ng gusto namin nasusunod. Tulad na lang nung policeman. Sa pagkakaalala ko, hindi talaga ako nabilhan ng policeman. Manyika at stuffed toy lagi ang binibigay.  By the way, I just checked. The movie RoboCop was released 1987. Eh, kakaumpisa ko na ng grade school nang time na yan.    Bakit ko talaga kaya gusto ng laruan na policeman noon?  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
            May ticket na ako. Sa Friday ang alis ko. Buti na lang at pwede na silang mag-issue at most seven days in advance. Hindi tulad ng dati, the day before aalis, tsaka pa lang sila nag-i-issue. Kalbaryo tuloy tuwing babalik sa school pagkatapos ng bakasyon. Parang sardinas ang mga tao. Siksikan. Mainit. Sobrang tagal ang hintayan bago ka makakuha ng ticket. Yung tipong kung maaga-agang tatawagin ang priority number mo ay pwede mo syang i-auction sa mga naghihintay at di malayo na may magbi-bid sayo ng halaga katumbas ng isang one-way ticket.  Sa mabuting kapalaran, pwede na ngang one week in advance.  Konti lang ang tao kanina sa ticketing office. Mga labing-lima lang siguro. Apat ang counter kaya akala ko mabilis lang ako matatapos. Kaya lang, isang computer lang ang gumagana kaya inabot rin ako ng isang oras sa paghihintay. Halatang aburido na ang mga kumukuha ng ticket. Eh, kahit nga yung mga tiketera sa counter, nagkakainisan na sa isa't isa. Lalo na si tiketera sa counter 2 at si tiketera sa counter 3. Nagdadabugan sila pag nagpapasahan ng pera at passenger slips. Nakasalubong yung mga kilay nilang dalawa at parang nakasemento na ang mga simangot sa mukha nila. Hindi na yata nakapagtiis yung isa at pasigaw na sinabi,  "Ano bang problema mo, ha?!"  Hindi sumagot si tiketera sa counter 3. Linabas nya na lang ang galit nya sa kawawang printer na paulit-ulit nyang sinapok nung nagkapaper-jam.  Akala ko magsasabunutan na sila doon. Buti na lang, may konting comic relief sa pagitan nung ale na nauna sa akin at saka nung isa pang tiketera na medyo malamig-lamig ang ulo.   tiketera : Ilang pasahero lahat ang kukunan ng ticket?  ale : Apat.  tiketera : Apat lang ba? Anong mga pangalan?  ale : Ian, Michael, at Sheryl Angeles. Naida Toral at Julio Serda. Apat lahat. Tatlong bata at dalawang matanda.   tiketera : eh, lima lahat yun, ah.  ale : Lima nga.  Di ko napigilan na matawa dito. Sana nga di ako narinig nung ale. Naaliw lang naman talaga ako sa exchange nila.  Pagkatapos kong nakuha ang ticket ko, pumunta kami sa sementeryo. Death annivesary kasi ng lola ko ngayon. Naging family tradition na kasi na bisitahin ang puntod ni lola tuwing death anniversary at birthday niya, maliban pa sa todos los santos. Actually, bumisita rin kami kahapon kasi pinananaginipan daw ng nanay ko ang lola ko.  Hanggang dito na lang ang kwentuhan tungkol dyan at baka mauwi sa isang episode ng  "Nginiiig"  ang entry kong ito. Bigla ko pa naman na-realize na malapit nang mag-hatinggabi at ako na lang mag-isa ang gising.   Yikes . 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Kung naligaw kayo dito at nagbabakasakaling may mahanap na makabuluhang bagay para basahin, ikinalulungkot ko na ibahagi sa inyo na blog ko ang nadatnan nyo. Wala akong analysis ng relevant issues dito (at least sa ngayon). Hindi ko alam kung ilang percent na ang nabibilang ng Comelec at kung ilang beses nang inakusahan na may kinikilingan ang NAMFREL.  Dito, sa blog entry kong ito, ang bida ay ang S-hook. Ulitin ko sa inyo:  S-hook . Hindi L-hook, hindi cup-hook. Kundi S-hook. Sabay-sabayin nating bigkasin:  "S-HOOK" .  Nag-umpisa kasi yang kwento na yan nung nawala ang metal trash bin namin sa harap ng bahay. Ang sagwa, noh? Lalagyan lang ng basura, mawawala pa. Hindi namin alam kung may kumuha nito o tinapon na rin ng mga humahakot ng basura. Ipinapasalangit na lang namin.   Anyway, nung nawala yun, sinasabit na lang namin sa gate yung supot ng basura namin, gaya ng ginagawa ng iba naming kapitbahay. Tuwing alas singko ng hapon at dadaan na ang garbage truck, kukunin na lang ng mga basurero yung sa mga supot sa pinagsabitan at iitsa na lang nila ang mga ito sa trak. Maliban na lang dun sa mag-asawa sa kanto kasi nagtitinda sila ng banana-q at marami silang tinatapon na balat ng saging araw-araw. Kaya isang drum na metal ang basurahan nila. Hindi pwedeng isabit.  Ang problema, ganito. Ang gate namin ay walang  decorative curls  tulad nung sa mga nakakarami. Yung mga tipong paalon-alon na disenyo na makikita sa mga grills. Ang pagkakayari nung sa amin, puro horizontal and vertical bars. So maliban na lang sa isang maliit na corner kung saan ito nila-lock, walang ibang pwedeng pagsabitan ang supot. Eto naman ang problema sa ganito. Masyadong mababa ang pinagsasabitan nito. At kayang-kaya siyang abutin ni Stray Dog.  "Stray Dog"  ay ang pansamantala kong ipinangalan sa maliit na asong gumagala sa kalye namin.   Light gray ang kulay ni Stray Dog. Teka. Baka puti sya na madumi lang. Pandak syang aso. Kung sa sasakyan pa,  "lowered" . Kapag nakikita ko sya - eto, pwera biro - binabati ko sya ng, "Hello, Stray Dog." Minsan, hindi ko napansin na may matandang aleng nakatayo nung isang beses na kinausap ko si Stray Dog. Ang sama ng tingin sa akin nung ale, para akong baliw. Eh, alangan namin bawiin ko pa? Dedma na lang ako at umasta na hindi pambihira para sa akin na kausapin ang mga ligaw na aso. Wala, parang natural lang.  Asan na ba ako? Yun na nga. Kayang abutin ni Stray Dog yung pinagsasabitan namin ng supot kaya pag walang nakakakita sa kanya, kinukutkot nya ang plastic at nahuhulog ang mga laman nito. Pag umaga, nagugulat na lang kami na puno ng kalat ang harapan namin. Mga cellophane, mga pira-pirasong papel at kung anu-ano pang kalat na nanggaling sa binutas na supot ni Stray Dog. Katakot-takot na wawalisin ang iniiwan ni Stray Dog. Dagdag trabaho. Magdidilig pa ng halaman, magsasampay ng damit, magpupunas ng alikabok, magma-mop, etcetera etcetera... tapos wawalisin ko pa ang kalat ni Stray Dog? Dapat masolusyonan.  So, ang naisip kong lunas sa lahat ng ito: S-HOOK.  Sa taglay niyang hugis, maari kong isabit ang isang dulo ng S-hook sa isa sa mga horizontal bar ng gate namin (dun sa medyo mataas-taas), tapos, yung kabila naman, pwede isabit ang lalagyan ng basura. Hindi na siya maaabot ni Stray Dog. Ang galing, di ba? Elegant solution. Parang  Quicksort , na laging ine-example ng prof ko noon.  So kaninang umaga, may misyon ako. Bumili ng S-hook. Ang di ko inakala, mas malaking misyon pala ang hanapin ito.  Sa unang hardware na pinuntahan ko, wala daw silang ganon. Sa pangalawa, medyo nahilo ako sa tinanungan ko. Excerpt ng conversation namin:   saleslady : Ha?  ako : S-hook.  saleslady : Ha?  ako : S-hook.  saleslady : Ha?  ako : S-hook, Miss. ES. HOOK.  Saka niya lang ako naintindihan. Wala daw silang ganon. Haaay.   Dun sa mga sumunod naman, laging ibinibigay o ipinapakita sa akin ay cup-hook or L-hook kahit na emote na emote na ako sa pagkukumpas ng daliri ko para magdrowing ng letter "S" sa hangin. Sabi pa nung isang Tsinoy na pinagtanungan ko, baka pwede na daw ba yung cup-hook sa paggagamitan ko. Pwede ba? Mas alam pa ba sa akin kung ano ang pwede at kung ano yung hindi? Kung pwede ang cup-hook, edi kanina pa ako bumili ng isa sa mga dose-dosenang cup-hooks na pinaggigiitan sa mukha ko.  Yung isa naman, pagkatapos ko syang tanungan kung nasaan ang mga S-hooks nila, tinuro ako sa ibang counter. Pagdating ko naman doon, puro sinulid, karayom, at gamit sa pananahi lahat ang nakadisplay. Naisip ko tuloy na baka ako ang may problema. Natanong ko sa sarili ko, "Bulol ba ako?"  Ibang klase pala ang enlightenment na naidudulot ng paghahanap ng S-hook. Nagiging reflective ako sa sarili kong mga pagkukulang. Pinakapaborito ko nga pala sa lahat ng tinanungan ko ay yung nakasimangot na babae na parang walang kaligayahan na nalasap sa buhay. Isang beses lang ako nagtanong, tapos, without looking up from the notebook na sinusulatan niya, sumagot siya ng: "Wala. Cup-hook, L-hook lang." Edi walang paliguy-ligoy. Tapos ang kwento.  Sa madaling salita, sa dinami-dami ng pinuntahan kong hardware, bigo ang hangarin kong makabili ng S-hook. Pero, may naisip akong pansamantalang solusyon: curtain hook. Mas maliit ito pero the same concept applies.  Walang kwentang usapan. Punta na lang kayo  urlLink dito  para may katuturan naman ang masagap nyo.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Wanted: S-hook 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nagising ako kaninang umaga sa pagkalakas-lakas na pagkanta ng  "You Light Up My Life" . Pwera biro. Version ng nag-eensayong Christian choir member sa katabing building ng inuupahan naming apartment. Sobrang lakas ng mikropono niya. Alas diyes na ng umaga kaya hindi mo namang masasabi na nambubulabog sya ng tulog. Alangan namang isigaw ko pa na, "Hoy! Alas kuwatro y media na ako natulog! Inaantok pa ako!" Mahaba-habang paliwanag naman iyon na mahirap nang isigaw pa lahat.   Isa pa, nang nagkalaon, napansin ko namang magaling ang pagkakanta niya. Maganda ang boses at kuhang-kuha ang tono.  Nanay ko naman, himbing na himbing ang tulog habang todo bigay sa pagbirit yung babae. Kasi kung ako, 4.30 na nang natulog, siya naman, alas sais na. (Wala po kaming lahing aswang, FYI lang.) So ang naging alarm clock ko kanina ay ang makabagbag-damdaming lyrics ng 70's na kantang ito.   You light up my life  You give me hope  To carry on  You light up my days  and fill my nights with song    Ewan ko lang kung tungkol pa rin kay Kristo ang awitin nya. Pwede naman kasing i-interpret ang  "You Light Up My Life"  as either romantic love or love for God. Tulad ng kanta ni Gary V na  "Gaya ng Dati"  (Maliban na lang dun sa linya ng  "Panginoon, ako’y nabulag ng mandarayang mundo, ako ay patawarin Mo..."  na malinaw naman ang ibig sabihin). May kanta rin ang Jars of Clay na ang chorus ay  "I want to fall in love with you..."  Kung yun lang ang pakikinggan mo, di mo talaga aakalain na para kay Jesus pala ang kantang yun. Pero kung alam mo yung title, halata na. ( "Love Song for a Savior" .)  Astig ang performance ni kapitbahay. Pang  Star in a Million . Kahit si Fritz Ynfante walang masasabi. Kaya nga lang, malakas. Nagising ako. At dahil dun, hindi ko siya hihikayatin mag-audition. Bumangon na lang ako at inumpisahan na ang hundred little chores na kailangan sa household maintenance. (kung sa Starcraft pa, ako yung lowly SCV,  "reporting for duty, Sir!" )  Maiba ako ng kwento (kaya nga digressions, eh). Habang nanananghalian kami kanina, sabi ng nanay ko, may sasabihin daw sya sa akin. Akala ko kung ano na. Yun pala, nung madaling araw at mag-isa na lang daw syang gising at nagpapaantok, may humila-hila daw sa dalawa nyang daliri sa paa - yung katabi ng thumb at index digits.  Natawa ako. Sabi ko baka nananaginip lang sya. Pero hindi daw talaga at gising na gising pa ang kanyang diwa. Baka 'ka ko, imagination nya lang yun dahil sa pagkakulang ng tulog. Pero sigurado daw talaga sya. Ang paniwala nya, baka daw nagparamdam ang lola ko dahil sa lunes na ang death anniversary nito.   Tumahimik na lang ako. Magtakutan ba kami sa hapag kainan?! Parang di yata angkop yun. Besides, maghuhugas pa ako ng plato. At hulaan nyo kung ano ang last song syndrome ko na naging soundtrack ng dishwasher scene ko ngayong araw? Galing.  "You Light Up My Life"  nga. Very bright students. Class dismissed.    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        A couple of weeks ago, while sitting alone in the backseat of my uncle's pick-up, I broke the frame of my glasses. I was seated with my face too near the window and when the vehicle lurched, I bumped my forehead into the glass and the frame broke near the stems.  "Ikaw na nga lang mag-isa dyan sa likod, nagkakaaksidente ka pa?"  - my uncle laughingly told me. My propensity for little accidents (...spills, mishaps, crashes, collisions, injuries...) is a long-standing family joke.  ( "Hello, everyone. My name is Lia and I'm an absolutely moronic klutz." )  I tried to  Mighty Bond  the thing, but it didn't last long. And being true to my character, I put off going to the optometrist until today, when I realized I have to leave for school in less than two weeks.  My mom accompanied me to the optometrist who is also a family friend. While we waited, my mom, the opto, and the opto's elderly dad talked about local politics and heart ailments for the good part of an hour. Me? I stared at the floor and got closely acquainted with it. It was tiled. With alternating bright red and white diagonal pattern. I'm weird, I know. So, sue me.  This is my take on the whole thing. If I wanted to chat, I would've called you up and said, "Hey, what about coming over. Let's catch up on things." But if I wanted to have my glasses checked, well, I would want to have my glasses checked. Small talk - I never really got proficient in it. If I had one peso for every single time I was smack in the middle of an awkward gap of silence while talking with an unfamiliar acquaintance, I'd be freaking rich. I'm never disrespectful, let me just get that straight. My parents made sure we were brought up to be polite to everybody. Now, politeness I've got down pat. Warmth and ease with casual conversations - that's another thing. Why would I ask somebody a question I have no interest in hearing? I can get the weather and current events updates on the news, thank you very much. And for all I know, those pointless questions are equally irritating to the other party as they are to me. So I go do what I do best: keep quiet.  My mom has always found this attitude of mine frustrating. Once, we were on one of our usual  you-really-should-give-people-a-chance-before-you-say-you-don't-want-anything-to-do-with-them  conversations when she told me, "The problem with you is: you're not diplomatic." When she saw that I was about to loudly protest on this statement, she backed up and corrected herself, "Okay, okay.  Para kang tatay mo, di marunong makipag-plastikan. "  Now, that sounds more accurate. And I don't know if that's a bad thing. Wouldn't it be worse if I knew how to be plastic/pretentious? But I understand my mom's concern. She just wants me to be well-equipped in the world of social interactions. Maybe eventually, I'll get the hang of it. With the right attitude towards people, a stack of pleasantries in my head, a smile on my lips, a song in my heart, a dose of multivitamins, a supply of Band-aids in my wallet, a healthy breakfast... wait. Where was I?  Oh, right.  Anyway, when I went back alone to get my new glasses, the elderly doctor (the opto's dad) who was talking with my mom earlier in the day, made --  *wild gasp!*  -- small talk with me.  He asked me where my mom was and I told him that she would just come back next time to try on her reading lenses. I answered him in a combination of Visayan and Tagalog.  "Are you Manila-born, hija?" He addressed me in English, this time and from hereon, sensing that I was not so comfortable with the dialect.  "No, Sir. I was born in Pampanga. My dad's from there."  "Pampanga? Then you're pro-GMA. Did you vote this election? For GMA?"  "Yes, Sir, I did vote. For Arroyo." (What  actually  happened to me inside the precinct is a loooong story, but let me just say that I am honestly glad that President Arroyo is leading the polls, and not the actor FPJ.)  "Why did you vote for GMA? They know how to cheat. You should've voted for Bro. Eddie."  Hmm. Okay. I forgot they were born-again Christians. I just smiled stupidly back at him and wished that the adjustments with my frames would be over. I tried to hide my relief when it was done and I finally tried my glasses on. I really didn't care how perfectly it fit, I just wanted to get out of there as fast as I can because I heard the old doctor talking to the woman beside him about me. "This girl is smart. She's studying computers in U.P. Everyone knows U.P. is U.P. ..."  Oh, God. Talk about embarrassing situations.  When I was handed the case of my glasses, I quickly thanked my opto and turned to her dad and told him that I was going to go ahead.  "All right, hija. Be a good girl, ok? Don't let everything get into your head.  Be good. "  I smiled, nodded, and said my thanks.   I couldn't have gotten out of the shop quicker.  I don't know what "letting everything get into my head" means. And what's he talking about? I  am  good. Not exactly good in exchanging pleasantries, but  good  nevertheless. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The few times I venture out into the world where I am required to actually interact with people, it takes me a second or two before I convince myself that I  don't  have a sign on my forehead that says, "Keep Away."  I was queuing at the ATM machine the other day. A middle-aged woman fell in line after me. She kinda reminded me of my  Aralin Panlipunan  teacher back in my sophomore year of high school. There was nothing noteworthy about her except for the way she looked at me. The moment she arrived, from my peripheral vision, I could see her closely observing me (in my opinion, somewhat disapprovingly, too) from head to toe with knotted eyebrows. I glanced down at my clothes and discreetly checked whether I had anything on my hair or face. I'm not a punk, ok? Granted, I'm not angelic either (not by a long mile) but I thought I looked decent enough to suppress any form of suspicion.  While the queue progressed, the lady after me, Mrs. Oracion (I decided to name her after my high school teacher for the time being), slowly inched her way to stand closer to me. I was tempted to say, "You're encroaching into my interpersonal space, Ma'am. The average ideal distance is around 18 inches, but in my case, it's  waaay  farther than that." But of course, I didn't say that. I contented myself with leaning forward against the railing. When I was already the next one to use the machine, Mrs. Oracion hesistantly tapped me on the shoulder and asked me if I could help her out with her ATM transaction because she left her eyeglasses and couldn't see quite well without them. I nodded and weakly smiled at her (These obligatory smiles of mine is a whole different story altogether.)   Anyway, I then figured out that the weird looks and invasive proximity were just all about asking me for help. Why couldn't she have said that right away? She could've spare me from the paranoid thoughts in my crazy head. So while  queue_item_1  to  queue_item_n-1  sequentially dequeued, she was sizing me up whether or not I was amiable enough to ask assistance from. When  queue_item_n-1  exited from the booth, I politely told Mrs. Oracion, "Ma'am, mauna na po kayo sa akin. Pagkatapos ko kayo tulungan saka na lang ako susunod." (I forgot to translate myself in Visayan at the time, but instead addressed her in my default Tagalog tongue). She gave me her PIN, and at her instructions, I transacted a balance inquiry and a P3000 withdrawal for her. She profusely thanked me afterwards.  This incident is the reason why I was thinking about whether I have some unknown repelling pheromone. This is not an isolated incident, mind you. It happens to me all the time. My friendster testimonials say a lot about how I come off as a stuck-up, snobbish jerk to most people who meet me for the first time. And for good reason, too, I must admit.   True, I don't like to be around a lot of people. I'm not shy, though. I'm just easily annoyed. By the noise. By the inanities. I don't have the patience. I'm not one of those sunshiny people who greets everyone with a beaming smile. I'm not that way. I don't mind being alone. In fact, sometimes I  prefer  to be alone. But if one gets to know me long enough to let the ice melt and the wall to break down, I'm actually pretty nice. Ask Mrs. Oracion. The ATM lady, not my high school teacher.  Aralin Panlipunan  was never one of the strongest subject.    (Pardon the occasional geek jargon. But I think it's pretty understandable by context.)          
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Minsan, iniisip ko kung bakit may mga habits ako na masasabing weird ng ibang tao. Pero kapag natatandaan ko ang mga quirks ng nanay ko tulad nang inutusan niya ako na magscrub ng sahig ng alas onse y media kagabi, hindi na ako nagtataka. Gising pa nga naman kami dalawa at medyo maputik ang sahig kasi maulan buong araw. Natural nga naman na linisin ito. Maghahatinggabi nga lang. Tutal, wala naman daw akong ginagawang produktibo. (In my own defense, may ginagawa naman ako ng oras na yun. Nagda-download ako ng mga kanta at lyrics ng  Three Doors Down  at  Jars of Clay  - na ngayon ko lang nadiskubre na marami palang magagandang kanta maliban sa alam ko na.)  Anyway, sa madaling salita, sa kalaliman ng gabi, I was down on all fours, scrubbing the floor. Scouring pad ang sandata ko.  Zonrox , sabon, at tubig ang bala ko. Natuyong putik na nanuot sa pagitan ng tiles ang kalaban ko. (Hindi talaga binitiwan ang analogy, eh, noh?! Hehe.)  Di naman kasindak-sindak na naglilinis ako ng sahig. Sa katunayan, kaming magkakapatid ay hindi estranghero sa gawaing-bahay. May mga panahon naman na may kasama kami sa bahay para tumulong sa trabaho, pero kadalasan kami-kami lang talaga ang gumagalaw. Kaya nung nag-college na ako at may nakakasama ng roommates sa boarding house, napupuna ko talaga kung sino ang mga marunong magtrabaho at sino yung mga señorita sa bahay nila.  Ngayong bakasyon na ako lang ang bum sa bahay at nagtratrabaho na ang mga kapatid ko, wala akong kahati sa mga utos. Alam ng mga kaibigan ko yan. (Online ko lang sila nakakasalimuha ngayong summer dahil wala ngang pasok). Tuwing bumabalik ako galing sa isang BRB na message, natatanungan agad ako ng:  "Are you done watering the plants already?"  O di naman kaya pag sinasabi ko na kailangan ko munang mag-log-out, sinasabihan ako ng:  "Tama, maghahapunan na nga pala, maghain ka na tapos maghuhugas ka pa ng pinggan."   Natatawa na lang ako minsan. Kaya nga habang ikinukuskos ko ang sahig ng sabon, iniisip ko kung ilan kaya sa mga kakilala ko ang di kinakailangang mag-manual labor. Just out of curiosity lang naman. Pero hindi mga elitista ang mga pinakamalapit kong kaibigan, eh. Palibhasa'y pare-parehas lang kami lahat na anak ng mga middle-class na pamilya na tamang-tama lang ang pamumuhay. Nakakakain, nakakapagpaaral hanggang kolehiyo. Nagigipit kung minsan, pero nakakaraos din, sa awa ng Diyos. Walang mga assets na ipapamana kundi yung edukasyon lang na pinagtustos sa amin. Yun na yun. (walang magiging drama tungkol sa last will and testament, di gaya ng old-school teleserye plot lines sa telebisyon) Minsan, sa sobrang kasanay ko na ang kasama ay mga tao sa pareho kong socio-economic level, nakakalimutan kong di lahat ng tao, kagaya ko. May naging kaklase ako na babaeng sosyal. Kung manamit sya araw-araw, parang laging may pictorial sa isang telenovela (description po nung isa kong kakilala, hindi akin).  Napansin ko na mahahaba fingernails niya na french-manicured. Without thinking, natanong ko sa kaibigan ko kung pano kaya maghugas ng plato at maglaba ng damit yung kaklase namin, kung nagga-gloves kaya sya. Hello?! Ang tanong: naghuhugas at naglalaba ba yun?! Oo nga, noh. Tanga-tanga ko naman. Di ko kaagad naisip yun. Malamang hindi nga.  Maraming nagsasabi na mahirap kung nasa gitna ka ng spectrum. Kunwari, hindi maganda, pero hindi pangit. Hindi matalino, pero hindi bobo. Hindi lalaki, pero hindi babae. Yung mga ganon. Mga alanganing sitwasyon. Ang mahirap kasi dun, hindi mo alam kung saan lulugar. Parang di lubos ang acceptance at belonging. Sabagay, superficial lang naman na observation yun.  Kung pag-uusapan naman yung pagiging hindi mahirap pero hindi mayaman, sa tingin ko, okay lang yun. Kaya mong mag-adjust sa iba't ibang klase ng tao. Saan ka man masabak, hindi gaano kalaki ang agwat na sinusubukan mong abutin. Mas bukas ang isip mo. You can be sensitive to the plights of poverty without being bitter towards wealthy people. Or you can be appreciative of material things without losing the perspective of the hard work spent in earning every single one of them.  Something like that. Ewan ko ba. Basta alam ko, paggising ko kaninang umaga, malinis sahig namin.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ako ay isang dakilang  sounding board . Ayon sa Merriam-Webster Online Dictionary, ito ang kahulugan ng salita:    sounding board   Function:  noun   1 a  : a structure behind or over a pulpit, rostrum, or platform to give distinctness and sonority to sound  b  : a device or agency that helps propagate opinions or utterances  c  : a person or group on whom one tries out an idea or opinion as a means of evaluating it  Syempre, di ako yung  a  o  b  dahil hindi naman ako isang  structure  o isang  device or agency . Ako yung taong madalas napagtatanungan kung ano ang masasabi ko sa bagay-bagay.  Liwanagin ko lang. Hindi ako walking encylopedia with expert opinions. Hindi umaabot sa technical knowlede ang extent ng pagiging sounding board ko. Although may pagkakataon rin na kahit nasa bakasyon ako, nakipag-text marathon sa akin ang former soft eng teammate ko para magtanong kung tama ang pagkakaimplement nila ng help system.   (Oo, Computer Science major po ako. Medyo nakakahiya ngang aminin dahil ang fact na ito ay hindi reflective sa anyo ng weblog na ito. Pasensya na po at hindi ko kinakarir ang HTML.)   Ang mga tinutukoy kong bagay ay yung mga medyo personal. Tipong  "Ok ba ang crush/manliligaw/liniligawan ko?"  or  "Bakit wala pa akong boyfriend/girlfriend hanggang ngayon? May mali ba sa akin?"  or  "Hindi niya ako pinansin the whole week. May ginawa ba akong masama?"  or  "I like him/her so much pero taken na sya. What should I do?"  or  "Ako, pag-umabot ng trenta at wala pa rin akong nakikilalang matinong lalaki na di lang ako paaasahin sa wala, mag-rerebelde na lang ako at sasali sa mga komunistang NPA sa bundok. Ano sa tingin mo?"  Teka. Ibang kwento na nga pala yun.  Etong mga tao na 'to - di naman talaga nila kailangan ng kausap na sumasagot, eh. More often than not, rhetorical questions lang yan. Ang kailangan talaga nila ay isang tao na makikinig sa mga hinaing nila. At -  (enter: stage left)  - ako yun.  Dahil likas na hindi ako madaldal (in writing lang po ako maraming salita), good listener ako. Sounding board nga, eh, di ba? Makinig ka lang at be empathetic, ok na yun. Mas nakakasama pa nga minsan kung magsalita pa ako. Alangan naman sabihin ko na "Ok naman yung crush mo kaya lang parang laging natutupi ang dila. Ang 'phone booth' daw ay  Fon-boath  tsaka ang 'candy' daw ay  cain-day . At nagpakamatay daw si Kurt Cobain nung  Ef-rel  5, 1994." Syempre di ko pwedeng sabihin yon. Nakita mo na ngang high na high na ang tao sa pagka-inlab tapos babarahin mo. Walang ganyanan. Pero kung pinipilit talaga akong ibahagi ang saloobin ko, sinisigurado ko na sincere ang sinasabi ko. But still diplomatic.   Pero napansin nyo ba? Madalas puro tungkol sa isyu ng pag-ibig natatanong sa akin. Ewan ko nga ba. Kahit ako nagtataka kung bakit ako ang mapalad na tao na ginawang "Dear Ate Charo itago nyo na lang ako sa pangalang Nena" ng mga kaibigan ko. Ako nga itong wala talagang karanasan sa aspetong yan, ako pa itong kinukulit. Na-explain na nga pala ito ng isa sa mga "kliyente" ko. Iba daw kasi ang perspective ng isang di pa napapana ni Kupido. Di madrama. Malinaw. Hindi smudgy ang thinking. Ewan ko lang. Amateur (and unsolicited) psychological interpretation nya lang naman yun.  Ayos lang naman sa akin maging sounding board. Advantage nga minsan kasi marami akong naiisip na storylines at characterizations. Marami-rami na rin akong nasulat base sa mga napakinggan ko. Aba, raw human drama yata yan kaya may authenticity ang attempt mo if you put it into words. Hindi naman sa ginagamit ko sila. Pero ganon na nga rin siguro.  Minsan, nagugulat nga ako sa mga walang pag-aalangang shine-share sa akin ng mga kakilala ko. Sabihan pa ba ako na iniiwasan nyang maging binatang ama at nagpapractice ng safe sex. Hay, naku, that's very prudent of you; tularan ka sana ng mas maraming tao. Pero pwede ba?! Wag nang isalaysay sa akin ang mga detalye ng bagay na yan. Mahirap mabura ang mental imagery. Eeww.  Sana lang, wag umabot sa point na ibabalik sa akin lahat ng sinabi ko kapag di kanais-nais ang kinalabasan. Tulad ko, pag ako nanghihingi ng payo, kahit anong mangyari sa huli, di ako nangsisisisi. Wala namang nag-utos sa akin na sundin yun, eh. Desisyon ko pa rin na ipa-photocopy ang isang 500-page textbook at hindi na hintayin ang pagdating ng next batch of stock sa susunod na buwan. Bah! Malay ko bang perwisyo pala ang bitbitin yun tuwing may lecture! Teka. Ibang kwento na nga pala yun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is somewhat amusing because I was just talking with  urlLink someone  about this. And he was right on the money when he diagnosed me as a schizoid (Psych major know-it-all! Hehehe). Although I still maintain that  "antisocial"  - in the non-technical, layman's term - may also mean  [adj]  shunning contact with others; "standoffish and antisocial"; "he's not antisocial; just shy"  (WordNet Dictionary). :p    schizoid    urlLink   Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I wrote these very, very short prose fictions mid-September of last year (2003). I was failing my Calculus class at the time and couldn't quite absorb the art of solving for trigonometric integrals ("∫sinⁿ xdx where n is a positive odd integer" --- Aaargh!). So I decided to write things that were lightyears away from math.      Going Down    They were waiting for the elevator to reach their floor. Just two strangers in an almost empty office trying to ignore the uncomfortable silence between them and just praying that the elevator doors would open any minute now.  The awkward silence lengthened and she broke it first.  “So, how’s the ankle?” She casually asked not looking up at him, but continued staring at the floor.  “Excuse me?” He asked in confusion.  “Your ankle. How is it? The sprain from last weekend.” She looked at him as if he should know what she’s talking about.  “Oh, it’s better, thanks. I’m sorry, but do I know you?”  “No. I saw you at the courts last Saturday. I saw your accident. It wasn’t a foul, though. You just slipped.” She was staring at the floor again.  He was looking at her as if she was half-insane, but he nodded in agreement.  Elevator door opens. He walks inside but she doesn’t follow. He raises a questioning eyebrow. She smiles at him and before the door closes, he heard her say clearly, “I am going down.”     Her Loss    “She doesn’t know what she’s missing. She’s missing a lot by choosing that…  that character  over me.”  “Yeah, she’s missing a lot. She’s missing on jeepney rides with you and siopao snacks, and three-for-ten-pesos roses on the church sidewalk.”  He was now eyeing her with narrowed eyes and she was trying hard not to laugh.  “But because she chose that…  ‘that character’  over you,” She continued. “She’ll have to content herself with riding on  ‘that character’s’  shiny new black Honda Civic, Starbucks, and imported Holland Tulips. Tsk, tsk. Silly girl. She’ll regret it.”  “You’re not funny. Some friend you are.”  He sighed heavily and she couldn’t stop herself from chuckling.  “Why does it always have to do with superficial things? I don’t have the cool car, the cold cash, the flashy cellphone, and good looks.”  “Hey, come on. It’s not really all about that.” She placed an arm over his shoulder. “You’re funny, you’re smart, you’re charming, and you’re not bad looking.”  “You think I’m all that?”  “I think you know you are all that.”  “No, I don’t. You tell me.” He asked with feigned innocence.  “Cut it out.” She said, getting uncomfortable and taking her hand off his shoulder.  “You think I’m cute.”  ”I said you’re not bad looking. Don’t push it.” She shoved him away.  “You think I’m cute.”  “Shut up.”  “You think I’m cute.”  “No, I take it all back. I think you’re retarded.”     Both Apologies    “I didn’t ask you to help me out! I didn’t need any help. I was fine. Perfectly fine!”  She forcefully punched him in the upper arm and looked straight into his face waiting for a reaction. She was raging mad.  He attempted to say something but all he could manage to stutter was, “But I…but I…” Eventually, he gave up and closed his mouth and instead started to rub his sore arm where she had hit him.  She glared at him for a few moments more before angrily walking out of the room.  He considered walking out after her but decided that it is best to let her anger cool down first. He sat down at the couch alone in silence. After a few minutes, she walked back into the room carrying a small towel stuffed with ice cubes. She shoved the cold compress into him and pointed to his arm.  He confusedly looked down at the towel on his hands as if it was some foreign object.  She sighed in exasperation, snatched the cold compress from him, sat down beside him, and applied the ice to his arm. “Keeps it from swelling,” she muttered. He nodded quietly, still a little confused but grateful that she was not in hysterics anymore.  After a few moments, the both of them quietly said at the same time, “I’m sorry.”  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was a little past two o’clock in the afternoon when Mrs. Esperanza informed her daughter that they were going to go to San Nicolas and that she “should get her face off the monitor screen right this minute and put on a different shirt”.  If it would’ve been any other day, Ellen would have probably begged off and rattled off a few excuses to get off the trip. But she wasn’t in a mood for any arguments. Besides, her Internet downloads were doing pretty well and she couldn’t really surf that much because it would eat up on the bandwidth of her downloads.  “How far exactly is San Nicolas?” Ellen asked her mother as they were on their way to the terminal where jeeps bound to the nearby towns were situated.  “Around 35 kilometers,” her mother answered.   San Nicolas is her mother’s hometown. Ellen has been to the town quite a number of times before, but only during special occasions like fiesta and Todos los Santos and mostly it was straight to the beach or to the cemetery. This time, Ellen’s mother wanted to talk to someone who could accompany her to talk to someone else.  Networking , that’s what Ellen remembers it to be the politically correct term. And there’s no better place to network than in San Nicolas – where everybody knows everyone else and there’s absolutely less than six degrees of separation from the notable people.  Ellen could not quite wrap her head around the thought of how it was to grow up in the quaint, small town of San Nicolas. It must be tough, she thought. Not being able to have the luxury of being a nameless face in the crowd. This is one of those places where one false move you make will be an invitation to have someone squeal your actions on your parents, may it be their business or not.  As their almost-empty jeepney sped down the highway, there was little to talk about and much to think of. Ellen wondered what goes on inside the little huts that dot the roadside. Do they have televisions? What do they do for a living? Do they have access to newspapers, computers, and telephones?  The concerned activist in her who asked those relevant questions was replaced by the morbid reader in her. It was that part of her who remembered to have read somewhere that it is in the most rural places that crime is so hard to prevent and solve because of the isolation of the people.  Banana trees curtained the golden fields of palay on either side of the road. Once in a while, they would pass by a school where the shrubs that surround the fence were encircled by whitewashed stones, a typical “decoration” practice of the far-flung area.  The road was uninterrupted, the traffic nonexistent, and there were very little passenger pick-ups on the way. Soon, Ellen and her mother got off right in front of the Municipal Hall of San Nicolas. The  munisipyo  was a small building in the center of town with a park in front where a fountain stood at the middle.  Their first stop was the police station. A couple of the police officers were having a mid-afternoon drinking session right at the police outpost. Some of them politely greeted Mrs. Esperanza. It was one of their policemen’s birthday, they said, and they were just having a little celebration. A uniformed lady, coming out from the inside office, welcomed the newcomers and asked them to step inside.  Sitting on one of the benches provided for waiting visitors, Ellen caught snippets of the conversation between her mother and the policewoman in the nearby desk. They were classmates in high school, Ellen figured out. And then,  Tiang , as her mother addressed the other woman, went about her narration on how there had been a problem in her father’s will and how her siblings have cheated her out of a sum of their inheritance. Very soap opera circumstances. At the mention of a third reading of the will, Ellen tuned herself out of the conversation and brought out a book that she always carried inside her bag. She almost couldn’t stop herself from kissing the book at her gratitude that she had something to do.  Twenty minutes and a good couple of pages later, Mrs. Esperanza was leading Ellen out of the station and into the house of another of her mother’s friends. Inside the well-kept and clean house, an elderly couple received them, Aling Melda and Mang Rudy. More talk. More pleasantries and catching up before the real intent of the visit were brought up. Going straight to the point will be nothing short of impoliteness and Ellen was realizing the delicate politics of small town interaction.  It was later decided that Aling Melda would accompany Ellen and Mrs. Esperanza back to the city. The three of them had to walk two blocks to reach the stop where jeepneys headed back to the city loaded passengers. The children and some of the people idling on their front porches gave Ellen looks that seem to say that they know that the passersby aren’t from around town, except of course for Aling Melda who taught for decades in the local school before retiring.  Ellen looked down at herself. She did not look like a balikbayan or a mestiza or even a city slicker. She did not look alien. In fact, she could pass up for someone who has lived in this mining town all her life. “If it’s not the way I look that gave me away, it must be in the way I look at them,” Ellen thought to herself.  Aling Melda must have noticed Ellen’s discomfort and asked Mrs. Esperanza in the dialect, “Is your daughter still tagalog-speaking, Connie? Still can’t understand the vernacular?”  “She can adequately understand the dialect, but they still speak tagalog at home,” Mrs. Esperanza replied.   Twenty-two years old and I still get addressed as a third person in my presence , Ellen thought irritably.  It’s not the way I look; it must be in the way that I cannot communicate with them as well as I would have liked .  Halfway on their way back to the city, a man and a bound up goat got inside the jeepney. Ellen gave out a small shriek of horror as the head of the goat brushed her knees and she immediately put her feet up on the seats. A few casual comments from the passengers were directed at the goat – if it was old enough to be slaughtered and how it would be best served.   It’s not the way I look; it must be the way that I react to live goats and cannot bring myself to think about caldereta but pity for the animal’s cries.   “Billy the goat.” Ellen told her mother nonchalantly. “I’m naming this goat Billy.”  Mrs. Esperanza chuckled. “Billy the goat. Okay.”   Throughout the rest of the ride, Billy would let out primal cries that would make Ellen jump. When they reached the intersection, Mrs. Esperanza told the driver that they were getting off.  “Bye, Billy.” Ellen silently said to the tied up goat before she got off.    11/9/03 2:00:42 AM - 11/9/03 4:00:07 AM   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wanted to first gather my thoughts before writing anything else but I'm finding it hard to put a lasso around them. Maybe it's better off this way. To think less and just get right to it. The more I think, the more I edit out myself, the more superficial the things I write. I end up trying to be cute and funny when in fact I'm really not feeling either one.   It's my personality. I want to have everything in some logical order. Alphabetical. Chronological. By height. By width. By importance. Everything should have a head, a body, and a tail.  But no, not this time. I just want to say something and I don't care if all my sentences start with "I". I've always tried to avoid that in writing. I. I. I. I just realized it doesn't hurt me when I do that. It doesn't hurt one bit.   All I wanted to say is that this is what I want to do. I just want to write. Some people think may think that I suck at it, but I don't care. They're not going to stop me from doing it. I'm not going to stop trying to express myself. Because there's nothing else in this world that makes me complete than my stupid, pathetic writing.  Other people have weed. Or alcohol. Or relationships to turn to when they're down or when they're happy. I have my pen and journal. I have my computer. I have my  words .  Rainer Maria Rilke said that one should find out the reason that commands one to write. I am now confessing to myself that I would have to die if I were forbidden to write. I'd probably have been long dead, anyway, if not for the escape offered by my writing. There have been times when I was sure I was losing my grip on life and reality. But words were there to comfort me. I could string them together to express my frustrations. I find it consoling that in my alternate world of prose and verse, I am the architect of the events. I have control over how something goes, unlike in my own life.   You . Whoever you are that personify the negativity in the world. You need to know this. I know you're going to make it hard for me. You're going to tell me I'm not good enough. That I don't have the skill for it. That I'm not worthy to be read by others. I'm going to pay you no mind. You can't tell me what I can or cannot do.  I have the heart for it. No amount of rejection, criticism, and condescension can ever break it. This is who I am. Get used to my blabber because I'm not going to stop until I'm heard.  You can't take it away from me. I'm not giving up my writing because I'm not ready to give up my sanity. I'm not competing with you but with myself. Because ultimately, I'm not writing for you. But for my own sake.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
             Si Mary Shaira yang nasa kanan. Ira kung tawagin namin ang two-year old niece kong ito. Dumaan sila sa bahay kanina, kasama ang ten-year old kuya niyang si Joshua at auntie ko na lola nila (na "mommy" ang pinapatawag sa kanyang mga apo, at wag "lola", please lang.)  Cute si Ira, di ba? Mala-anghel ang itsura. Sa totoo lang, mabait naman talagang bata ito, medyo hyper nga lang kung minsan. At maliban na rin lang kung umaandar ang pagka-astigin nito at sinusuntok ang lahat ng makita nito habang nandidilat ang mata sabay sigaw ng "Hawa!" (Visayan term po ito na ang loose translation sa tagalog ay "Alis!")  Sinabi ko nang mabait na bata si Ira, di ba?  Mabait naman talaga. Sobrang playful nga lang kasi nga nasa stage ng "terrible two's". Kuya Joshua nya ang usual object of Ira's "cariño brutal". Kung "maglaro" ang mga ito, daig pa minsan ang first round ng Pacquiao-Marquez match. At, wag kayo! Si Ira ang gumaganap na PacMan. Si Josh, pinapaiintindi na lang namin lahat na di dapat patulan ang kid sis nya. Kaya minsan, pag masakit na talaga ang mga tama ni Ira sa kanya, nagpipigil na lang siya ng iyak. Naiintindihan ko rin naman si Josh kasi nung minsan sinuotan ko ng sandals si Ira, bigla nya akong nasipa (ayaw kong isipin na sinadya nya) at sapol sa tuhod ko ang tama. Masakit sya, in fairness. Nagka-bruise pa ng konti. Natutuwa si Ira sa mga painful slapstick comedies brought about by her playfulness. Niloloko ko nga magulang nya na baka may sadistic tendencies yung bata. (Pabiro ko lang po sinasabi yun. At sa mga concerned sa home upbringing ng pamangkin ko, wag po kayong mapraning. Born-again Christians po ang mga magulang at lola nya at sa katunayan ay malapit nang maging pastor ang tatay niya. Weird lang po yata ang sense of humor ng bata.)  Ako ang napagod sa kakapanood kay Ira habang walang tigil ang ikot nya sa sahig. Paikot-ikot na parang trumpo. Giggling all the while. Titigil lang sya kung makakakita sya ng sapatos na susuotin. She gets a kick out of that - wearing shoes too big for her. Oo nga pala, tumitigil rin sya kung susubuan mo sya ng chocolate. Yung mga tigsi-singkwenta centavos na nakabalot ng foil. (Tanong lang: bakit kaya kahit anong ingat ang pagsubo mo ng pagkain sa bata, it's inevitable that they'll spoil their clothes? Or worse, yours?)   Anyway, nang naubos na ang tsokolate, binuhat ko si Ms. Madungis at pinatong sya sa lababo. Binanlawan ko kamay at mukha nya. At syempre nang natapos, ayaw nyang magpababa. Dahil nadiskubre nya ang faucet at pinihit-pihit ito. Sobrang hina, sobrang lakas. Sobrang hina, sobrang lakas. Ang kasiyahan nya, di mo mawari at aliw na aliw syang nakikita ang agos ng tubig. So pinagbigyan ko sya sandali bago sya nilapag sa sahig. (Self snapshot at this point: chocolate stains on my PE t-shirt, and water splashes from the faucet adventure - well, you do the math).  I went to my computer to check on my downloads for a second but the next thing I knew, Ira was extending her arms to me, asking to be seated on my lap. (She knows how to open doorknobs already, I made a mental note). She found the keyboard amusing and started to press the ones she could reach (i.e, the spacebar, the Ctrl key, and the Windows shortcut key). I had to distract her from this and so I launched the screensavers previews. Boy, did she like those! She'd clap her hands whenever there's a change in the image. She yelled "Fish! Fish!" when she saw the aquarium screensaver. But I think she liked 3D Flower Box best. It elicited the most shrieks and giggles.  I'm the youngest in the family which is probably the reason why I'm kinda fond of kids - no matter how messy or playful they get. Ira and Josh are just two of my numerous nieces and nephews (children of my cousins).  They left late in the afternoon. Ira waved to me goodbye (one of her perfected "tricks"). I was left wondering about faucets and screensavers. And trying to figure out at which point in growing up do they cease to be wondrous things. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ironically, I haven't seen this one yet. I wanted to belong in "Fight Club" or "The Matrix". But I'm guessing "Say Anything" is still way better than "Power Rangers". LOL.    Say Anything...    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
              "Love actually  is  all around."   This film is probably the nicest romantic comedy I've ever seen. ( My thanks to Joy and Ryan for suggesting it to me ). It's one of those movies where you don't realize that you have been grinning for a whole hour while watching it. Usually, this genre does not appeal to me but this one I really liked. No overly cheesy lines; it's all about subtlety.   It's made up of multiple story lines so I was impressed by the smooth transition from one to the next. And an underlying relationship among all the stories has been established by interconnecting characters with one another. Something like the local movie "Jologs" idea. But this one's so tastefully done you won't get distracted by the overlaps.   And it really doesn't hurt to have a powerhouse cast. Emma Thompson, Hugh Grant, Alan Rickman, Colin Firth - even Billy Bob Thornton makes an appearance as the American President. I am so amazed how secure these great actors are in their own abilities that it doesn't bother them to share the limelight. The characters they portrayed are endearing. They're so real and anybody can relate to at least one of them.  I particularly like the character played by Colin Firth, the heartbroken writer who fell for his Portuguese housekeeper. I like the whole "love is a language" concept. Oh, but I also found Laura Linney's character really funny (" Do you think  everyone  knows? Do you think  Karl  knows? ") LOL. That killed me. It brought back a lot of personal memories of paranoia about the object of one's affections/attractions/obsessions. ;)  Watch this movie. If you're in love, it'd make you feel thankful that you are. If you aren't in love, it'd make you feel that there's nothing to be afraid of. Love is within your power. All you need to do is do something about it. I think that's the dominant theme in the film, which is eloquently stated by Liam Neeson's character when he was encouraging his stepson to confess his love to the girl of his dreams.   "Tell her that you love her. You've got nothing to lose and you'll always regret it if you don't."   It's all about the hanging your balls out there, in the end (figuratively speaking, of course). It doesn't matter if you have a high fieldgoal percentage if you only risked a few safe and insignificant shots. What about if you need to go for the winning shot attempt? Would you have the guts to take it? It may be the only chance you get but it's also the only thing that counts.  Damn, I really should work on my analogies. I absolutely suck at this. But despite the lame basketball explanation, you get my drift, right? Good. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I always hum along to John Mayer's "Why Georgia" and I just realized I have no earthly idea who Georgia is. Or if it refers to the U.S. state.  But you gotta hand it to John Mayer. The guy knows how to put his words together. Nothing too profound but just honest, give-it-to-me-straight-without-a-chaser kinda thing.   Because I wonder sometimes about the outcome of a still verdictless life  Am i living it right? am i living it right? am i living it right?   I like that. My thoughts exactly! So I guess not getting the part about Georgia is not that big a deal. But if anyone of you out there knows who/what Mayer was referring to, drop me a line, will you? It's all in the pursuit of knowledge. Amen. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Kenshin Himura 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today, I exercised my right to vote for the first time.  Don't worry, I don't want to talk about politics. Heaven knows I've had my fair share of political conversations/arguments the past few weeks to last me until the next election circus. Besides, I don't really like to talk about whom I voted for and why. Because: (1) it's none of anybody's business; and (2) that's what ballot secrecy is for. Think about it. There's a reason why we're not electing officials based on the count of a show of hands. To put it succinctly, I'm just not confrontational. Do and vote as you please and I'll appreciate it if you show that same courtesy to me.  I just wanted to say how cool it felt to be part of the electorate. I had a say in the country's future. I mean, yeah, it's one vote and it probably won't be counted if someone screws up in the polls, but it still was something.  Let's just pray that the final results will be credible, unmarred by cheating. And let's pray even harder that FPJ will NOT win. (sorry, I couldn't help myself with that one >8^)    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I woke up at 6 am. I had gone to sleep only three hours before. Being up at three am is not something unusual for me. (" Hello, everyone. My name is Lia, and I'm an insomniac. ")  Anyway, I tiptoed out of of the house at that ridiculously early hour. I walked two blocks towards the bakeshop. Chocolate or ube or mocha. Chocolate, definitely. No contest. Carrying with me the cake in a box, i crossed the street and bought a bunch of white flowers.  Now here's the tricky part. When I got home, making the least noise as possible, I tried to place the flowers inside the usual container but the stems were too long so the whole thing kept tipping over. I considered just laying the flowers on the table in an artistic sort of manner (read: the lazy method) and just let my mom arrange them in the vase herself when she wakes up. But, no. I decided that I shouldn't let my mother worry about her own flowers. So I took a pair of scissors and cut about a third of the flowers' length, stuck it in the vase and poured some water inside.  When my mother woke up, my brother (who conveniently took a passive role in all this thing) and I greeted her a happy mothers' day and told her that we got her flowers and cake. She was obviously touched by the gesture but was more shocked to know that I got up early to get them. She even asked me three times if I  really  was the one who bought them. She couldn't get over the thought that I was up before noon.  My mom's great. She's loving, warm, funny, upbeat, and she screams a lot when watching boxing games ( Sorry, people, I'm still nursing some residue of the Pacquiao-Marquez draw ). God knows that she deserves a whole lot more than cake and flowers with trimmed stems stuck inside an old vase. I just hope she knows that we love her a lot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        There's something wrong with her , I thought to myself.   She has been talking nonstop to me for the past twenty minutes. I have been staring blankly back at her and I was beginning to wonder whether there was anything in my expression that was egging her to go on with her twaddle.  I hoped that our instructor would arrive shortly so I would be spared from the verbal relay of my seatmate's lifestory to me. She paused for a while and caught her breath. She told me that she was really talkative by nature (no kidding?!) and asked me whether her chitchat was starting to get on my nerves. Of course not, I said.  Aaargh. Damn my courtesy and political correctness.  And so she went right back to it. She started to tell me about how she met a cute guy in a disco club last summer and how the guy asked her to be his girlfriend that same night and without letting a moment pass, she acceded. That's the reason why even if she lives two rides away, she opted to go to enrol at the school because the guy was an engineering major there. Now, here's the clincher. They haven't seen each other again since the night they met. She all said this matter-of-factly.    There's something  terribly  wrong with her , I thought to myself.  I tuned her out for a while. This was my first week at my new school and I am amazed on how much there is to adjust to. This is probably a good thing so I can practice my flexibility. It pays to be a well-adjusted person. I just hope it pays well in cash. Hehe. =)  Anyway, back to my seatmate. She was saying something about how she was so embarrassed during her class earlier that day because when asked about her own definition of psychology, she couldn't think of anything to say. I nodded and smiled at her sympathetically. She was really friendly and I wanted to be nice to her in return.  When it was clear that our instructor was a no-show, I started to put away my things. Miss Talkative abruptly asked me out of nowhere, "Kinsa'y uyab nimo?"  I literally choked and coughed out loud. How weird of her to ask such a personal question when I barely know her. Besides, the question was unexpected. I told her that I wasn't in a relationship because I am preoccupied with a lot of things and have no time to look for headaches.  Something about the way she gawked at me told me that she didn't get my answer and the intended humor went over her head.   Sigh.   Man, I hope my M-W-F's will not always start out like this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You wouldn't believe what happened to me last Thursday night. A fire broke out two buildings away from where I live. Some of you might have heard about it. It was also in the national evening news. The church of the Seventh Day Adventists in front of the Capitol building was burned down to the ground.  It was around 10.30 in the evening and I was reading when I noticed that the occupants of the other rooms in my floor were running down the stairs. When I opened my door, the suffocating smell of smoke assailed my nostrils. There was a fire nearby, they said, and that we should all get out. I came back inside my room and put on a second shirt over the one I was already wearing. I desperately looked around to find out what I should bring along. I thought about unplugging my system unit, but thought it was too heavy.  Here comes a natural calamity and all I could think of is my computer and my files in the hard drive. Give me a break. That's years worth of file accumulation.  Anyway, all I ended up bringing was my mobile phone. When we all got to the ground floor, we crowded ourselves together. I noticed that most of the other tenants were in their sleepwear and all carrying their own phones. We were right outside our building's parkway where we saw the blazing fire eating up the old wooden house across the street. A giant bonfire. It was chaotic. Firetrucks, firefighters, police, ambulance, media coverage. A woman even fainted from shock.  A freshman kid named Marga clung to me. She tightly held my forearm and kept telling me how scared she was. I just found out that we have been floormates for a couple of weeks now. That night was the first time I saw her. She heard me praying under my breath and prayed along with me. My prayer was repetitive and uncohesive. Somewhere along the Our Father's, Hail Mary's, and Glory Be's, I think I might have also recited Grace before Meals. No freaking kidding.  I really didn't know what to do. I felt all alone and I couldn't think of anyone to ask help from. I finally texted my brother and sister about my situation. Which is really stupid because my brother's in Cagayan and my sister's in Manila. I am in Cebu, for crying out loud. Panic has taken over my logic.  My sister called me up and told me to stay where I was because she contacted Jansen and asked him to come over my building and help me out. He arrived a few minutes later and told Marga and I to distance ourselves from the area because it was dangerous to stand so close to the fire where electric posts might fall over. He led us a few meters away and stayed with us until the chaos subsided. Jansen asked me why I didn't call him up directly and my sister from Manila had to be the one to tell him about the fire. Well, I forgot about him. I couldn't think straight at the time. Of all the things I could've brought, all I managed to bring was my phone. No wallet, no valuables, no documents, nothing. How stupid is that?!  Anyway, we were finally allowed to get back into our own rooms at around midnight. Before he left, Jansen told me to text him if anything else happens. We're already like family, he said. Very true.  I didn't get to sleep right away that night. Not only because the electricity was turned off due to the fire, but because I couldn't stop thinking about what happened. What could have happened. How life sometimes gives you these little jolts of reality checks. How blessed I am to be safe. Before I went to bed, with a warily-guarded candlelight, I wrote to God.  Someone asked me whether my entries in this blog actually happen or just made up. They're all true. I guess you could call these entries as candid snapshots of my everyday life. My own personal scrapbook of mundane experiences. I don't know how to explain it, but it validates my existence somehow.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It happened so fast that I'm not really sure how it happened exactly. Maybe it has something to do with my sleep deprivation and fatigue. Maybe. But that theory wouldn't really explain how I managed to knock down my bathroom sink and faucet.  Yes, my dear ladies and gentlemen, I am (dis)pleased to announce that my carelessness has reached monumental levels. I have already graduated from petty crashes and minor damages. I am now experienced in the destruction of plumbing fixtures, as per my demonstration early this morning.  All I know is: I was reaching for the soap.  (That's my defense, your honor.)  The next thing I knew, the whole sink fell off from its hook on the wall. On its way down, it hit the water valve of the other faucet and knocked the whole thing off from the wall.   So there I was, bleary-eyed from just waking up from not-enough sleep, soap in one hand, trying to process the whole scenario before me. The sink was awkwardly dangling on the wall, supported only by the silver tube thingy (the only thing that didn't come off the wall). The whole faucet handle was on the floor and there was water gushing out from the hole in the wall where it should have been. There was water everywhere! A mini-hydrant geyser right inside my freaking bathroom!  I wish I had a video of myself at that exact moment. (I bet a lot of people who dislike me would want one, too). All I could think of was:  HUH?! What the heck happened?!   Now, the slow thought processing may be attributed to tiredness. It has been one looooong weekend from me. Last friday, I had some of my subjects encoded. Saturday noon, I left for Manila with my mom via Superferry. We arrived Sunday morning. We got home in Antipolo early afternoon. I left for the airport early Monday morning. Waited awhile at the PAL Centennial terminal before acquiring a ticket. Left at 3 o'clock. Arrived in Cebu an hour later but there was a downpour at Mactan so I finally got back here at the dorm at 6.30 already. All this time, I didn't have enough rest. When I woke up at 6 am this morning, I was nothing short of a zombie. So, there. I rest my case.  Eventually, I realized that I had to do something other than just stare at the mess. I carefully lifted the sink and hooked it back into the metal fittings on the wall. I picked up the valve and tried the suppress the water flow with it. No use. I went out of my room to ask for help and the good thing was, Alvin, the utility guy was sweeping the dorm corridor. I gave him the jist of the situation. He took a second to look at the indoor waterfalls and said that he'd be right back. I sat down and waited for him to get back, silently hoping that my floor won't get flooded. When Alvin came back, I thought he brought a wrench or a screwdriver or whatever the heck is used for that kind of situation. Instead, he brought a piece of cylindrical wood. It is from a tree branch that he had cut down. Hesitantly, I asked him what it was for. He said he would just plug the gushing hole temporarily until he could call someone to fix it later in the day.  Hnh.  To make a long, stupid story short, I unplugged the hole when I took a bath and when I was done, I plugged it back in. Could any other morning be weirder?  Anyway, I finished my enrollment (finally!) before noon. I went back to the dorm at around 4 pm. When I saw Alvin outside the building, I asked him if my faucet was fixed.  "Ate, hindi pa naayos kasi walang ano... yung ano..." He gestured with his hands.  Steering wheel? headband? Needless to say, I'm not good at the charade of plumbing tools.  "Sige, 'Vin. Bukas na lang." I didn't have the time to wait for the actual name of the missing tool.  "Oo, 'te, paaayos ko na lang bukas."  I can't get over it. Until tomorrow, I have a twig for a faucet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The past few days, I find myself walking a lot. It's crazy, really. It's like I'm some kind of participant in a walkathon with no finish line. I've been following up my transfer credentials in my old school and I've also been processing my enrollment in my new school. (At this point, let's disregard the whole story on why I'm switching schools. It's a different story altogether. One that involves anger, denial, acceptance, and sudden surging attacks of terroristic tendencies against heartless, inconsiderate, power-tripping college administrators.)  I'm okay.  *breathe in, breathe out, breathe in, breathe out...*  I'm fine.  Anyways.  Lahug and Labangon are not in close proximity. I should know. I've been going back and forth these places as if I'm hopscotching. The jeepney route 12L (Ayala - Labangon) has become my closest friend. I'm considering naming my firstborn Twelve El. I just don't think any of my friends would want to be godparents of a kid named after a transportation route.  The technical institute I'll be attending has a sprawling campus. Lots of walking involved. The departments are located in separate buildings. More walking involved. Its buildings have multiple floors. Even more walking involved.  When I was trying to have my subjects evaluated, I had to go around all the other departments and colleges to have my units signed. My majors subjects are in the College of Computer Studies, naturally. But the minor ones are scattered all around. So there I was, being my usual absentminded self, staring with mouth agape at the room numbers on top of the doors. Thrice, I walked past the department I was looking for. Three freaking times. Gosh, I can be imbecilic at times.  The Math department was in the third floor. The Physics department was in the fourth. Good thing I asked beforehand where both departments were. Can you imagine if I went up all the way to Physics and then went all the way down again, not knowing that I passed Math? The horror! I would've clubbed myself to unconsciousness. I felt like if I had to climb any more steps, I'd reach the stairway to heaven in no time.  It also doesn't help me that I'm such a klutz. There were a couple of times I tried to enter the wrong doors. Particularly in the EDP, I forcefully tried to open and shove the glass door a couple of times before I noticed the people inside who have been trying to get my attention and motioning to me to use the other entrance. Aargh. So embarrassing. I almost considered not going inside.  I also left ALL my papers with the guy who encoded my classes. The stupid thing was, I remembered to come back and get my ballpoint from him, but I left all the important papers I have been processing all week. Blame it on my pen fetish. The guy was nice enough to come down and look for me to hand me my papers. But I don't attribute that incident totally to my klutziness. The people at the room were watching NBA and the encoder and I had to literally yell to each other to hear ourselves amidst the boisterous cheers and loud conversations.  Now, the guy to girl ratio of the school, as I roughly estimated, is 5:1. It's a man's world. Which is understandable, as most students there are either engineering or architecture majors. My friend Sweet Honesty (yep, that's her real name) is an ECE major and she was once enrolled in a class where out of 40 students, she was the only girl. If I was one of those "so-many-boys-so-little-time" kinda person, I'd be delighted. But, I'm not.   More likely, "So many chances to make a fool of myself, so little time." 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Meet Jansen. He and my elder sister Mae have been friends since their college sophomore year. Back then, they bugged me about their research assignments. And when the time came that they were already looking for jobs, they bugged me about their resume contents. Jansen is a staple entity in our lives. He's there when Mae's got problems. And he's also there when he's got problems. And me - I don't hear the end of either of their problems.  Anyway, Jansen's girlfriend got pregnant early this year and so they decided to have a civil wedding. Well, the pregnancy itself is ill-timed, but as a whole, Jansen's ready for marriage. He's turning 25 and he has a stable job.  Now, here's the catch. My sister's in Manila right now. I am the one who's here in Cebu. Therefore, ergo, entonsis: I am supposed to go to Jansen's wedding. I thought about begging off and offering an excuse for not being able to attend but the couple actually dropped by my place to personally invite me and through long distance calls and text messages, my sister adamantly insisted that I go. It isn't that big a deal - if you're not me, that is. The thing is, accepting the invitation means that I have to be in the company of people I don't personally know. It isn't that big a deal - if you're not me, that is.  I don't have much experience with weddings. I've only been to a few. I remember turning down an invitation to be a bride's maid when I was in high school. It was kind of not-nice of me, but there was a frilly gown involved in the whole setup. Enough said.  So anyway, saturday morning, I found myself walking towards the Capitol.  My building is just across it. I could look out of one of my building's front windows, and I'd see the imposing facade of the Provincial Capitol. I walked towards the front entrance, forgetting that it was closed on saturdays. Stupid me. So, I walked all the way to the other entrance and entered the rear building. There was a security guard at the entrance.  "Sir, asa diri ang RTC branch four?" I asked him.  "RTC? MTC ni sya na building."  "RTC man ang gi-ingon sa ako."  "Unsa di-ay imo tuyo, 'day?"  "Civil wedding sa ako amigo, Sir."  "Aw, MTC gyud di-ay. Tu-a sa fourth floor and branch four. Isuwat sa imo ngan sa logbook."  I mentally made a note to smack Jansen in the head for mistakenly telling me that it was RTC and not MTC. After writing my name in the log book, I headed up the stairs to the second floor. Up the stairs towards the third floor. When I got there, no more stairs. They don't really think that I should fly towards the fourth floor, do they?  An elderly man walked by and I politely asked him how I could go up the fourth floor. He led me towards a dark passage where a narrow stairway was situated. I thanked the old guy and then hesitantly walked up the steps. I half-expected the boogeyman to come jump out from nowhere and push me off. Eeerie place, that was.  I was waiting alone outside the sala of Judge Tormis ten minutes before the appointed time of 9.30 am. I paced around the corridor and browsed through the schedules of case hearings posted outside the doors. Grave defamation of character. Slight defamation of character. Sum of Money. Unlawful detention. Attempted homicide. And I said to myself, what a wonderful world.  The other guests started to arrive twenty minutes later. The couple and their parents arrived around ten o'clock. We were all ushered in the courtroom. I sat in the backmost bench. The groom's mother came and sat on my right. And the bride's mother sat on my left. Jansen came by and introduced the two women to each other because as I just found out, it was their very, very first meeting. Do you know those slapstick comedies where the funny person gets stuck between two people and finds it hard to excuse himself/herself? Well, I was the funny person in this scene. I tried my best to extricate myself from the beso-beso and the handshakes and the pleasantries and the whole shebang. I transferred seats.   Jansen, sensing that I'd rather be in a dentist chair for a tooth extraction than be in this room full of strangers, sat beside me and chatted awhile. We were both sleepless. He, from his graveyard duty from work, and me from another bout of insomnia. But his eyes were more bloodshot than mine. He introduced me to the guy beside me. It was Jay, his housemate. I nodded at him. Introductions are never my favorite things in life.   The judge finally came at around a quarter before eleven. She called the couple and the rest of us stood nearby. The whole thing was over in ten minutes - just a fraction of the whole time I waited. What irony.  When we came out of the Capitol building, the objective was to hail a couple of taxi cabs for the guests to head towards the reception area at the Cebu Grand Convention Center. Jansen wanted me to be in the same car as himself, but his relatives insisted that he went ahead first so the others can just follow him. Before he left, he told me that I could call up another friend of ours to come to the reception so I wouldn't feel out of place. One by one, the taxis were occupied. I remembered the J.D. Salinger story, "Raise High the Roof Beam, Carpenters" where Buddy Glass was Seymour's only guest in his wedding and he also had to share a cab with the guests he didn't know. Well, in my case, the couple's relatives crowded themselves in the first cars. Jay and I were the last ones left and we had to wait a few minutes for the next cab to come by.  Finally, we got on one. We rode in silence all the way to grandcon. When the cab pulled over, I took out my wallet and extended my fare. Jay offered to pay it all. No way. I insisted that we should split it. He took my money and said no more of it. Good boy.  Jansen welcomed us and led us to our seats in a round table for twelve. The other people in the table were their aunts and uncles and a few cousins. They just stared at us. As an effect, I took out my cellphone and held it discreetly under the table. I texted my friend Abad to hurry up and get there fast. Jay, who also probably got awkward from the staring we got, stood up and excused himself. The coward never came back. He stayed at a different table. Before the food was served, Abad thankfully came and I got a bit more relaxed. At least I had someone to talk to.  After dessert, we stayed awhile. Abad and I chatted with a five-year-old girl, the daughter of Jansen's landlord. The kid's company was ten times better than all of the other guests' combined. Grown-ups. Ugh.  When the timing was polite enough, we said our goodbyes and congratulations to the newlyweds. Jansen thanked me for coming over. He knew that the whole large-scale socializing is not my thing.  And friends really know you well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was fifteen - or sixteen - when a doctor told me that I "think too much". He was an opthalmologist and I came by his clinic to have my eyes checked because I had an episode of red-static vision not long before.  I was on my way home from school when my sight went blurry and everything appeared to be speckled like a bad TV reception laced with frequent static images. Only, instead of black and white, they were red and white. Pretty freaky actually. That's why I went to the doctor for some answers.  Clearly, the problem was with my eyes - or so I assumed. The examination showed that my vision was all right. The specialist then told me that the problem was in my thinking too much. He told me that there are times when the brain gets overloaded, it manifests its stress through the vision.  Hnh.  My prescription was to let go of my worries and just relax my thoughts every once in a while. I was then referred to a neurologist. And that really freaked me out more that the static vision did. Because - well, it's my brain we're talking about here. It's the seat of my existence. And just the thought that there MIGHT be something wrong about it disconcerted the hell out of me.   it felt a little bit like there was an implication that I'm crazy. Although, apparently, if the opthalmologist thought that way, he would've referred me to a shrink. For all I know, he wanted to, but was just being diplomatic. I'm not sure. I'm really not.  What I know is this. You don't tell a fifteen year old that she thinks too much. Just be glad at that age, she's really thinking at all. Although, the doctor had a point. Worrying is a bad habit to break.  God, I wish I could turn off the flow of my thoughts like a faucet.  All right, time for bed, I have to stop thinking now. Off. Zzzz.  It doesn't work that way. This is the reason why I lay awake most nights, seriously considering suing the Sandman of negligence and malpractice. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love dusks. And rain.   It rained hard at dusk today. And there were sporadic thunderclaps. Just like in The Sound of Music when they were singing My Favorite Things. I'm not scared of thunders. I have a friend who is, though. She jumps in fright every time there's thunder. We tease her about it sometimes. But I realize that we shouldn't. There are just things that one is entitled to be fearful of. Fear is a funny thing. It betrays you. It makes you vulnerable and exposes to the world all the things that you value and hold dear. Maybe it's your life. Maybe it's your pride. Maybe it's your wealth. Maybe it's your loved ones. Each one of our fears reflects our inner selves. It's probably better if we keep our fears to ourselves. So that the whole world wouldn't take advantage of us and of the things that paralyzes us or makes us weak.  The world is a funny place. It's chock full of clueless people. Six billion pathetic lives. Six billion dreams. Six billion fears. Six billion prayers. I hope God has voice mail. And a damn good database system. I don't blame Him if He overlooks my prayers. I bet my priority number is 5,999,999,999. And that's cool with me. Because I fear nothing. Nothing I'd admit to, anyway. Besides, everyone knows that the Lord is our shepherd; we shall not fear.  I'm sure God will get right to me soon. How do I know? Because He made it rain at dusk today.  And I love dusks and rain. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I take a twenty-minute jeepney drive every day on my way to school. There's an old abandoned house that I pass by which I always notice. Its walls is spray-painted with graffiti and its windows are boarded up with planks of wood. Apart from the dilapidated appearance of the house, what catches my notice about is the old man whom I usually see sitting on the floor of the front porch.  The old man is a scavenger. He has long, unruly hair and his skin is covered with dirt and grease. His clothes are tattered and his feet are bare. He could've been any other homeless person on the street except for one thing. I always see him -- sitting on that porch with sheets of paper on his knees and a pile of pens on his side -- writing.  He chooses to write. I bet a lot of people would disapprove of a tramp who spends his whole day writing and not doing anything constructive. But what if writing is all he wants to do? Shouldn't he be given credit for just going after what makes him happy and complete?  Maybe in his realm of reality, nothing is as important as being able to put his thoughts into paper. Nothing else. Not food, not shelter, not clothes. Absolutely nothing else. How many of us  sane  people display that intense passion? Maybe sanity is just a scapegoat for cowardice. That convention is not normarlcy but just the politically correct label for taking the easy way out.  Because if you love something, there should be no question in your heart nor your mind. You just take the leap. You just sit right down with your pen and paper, unmindful of your personal state and the rush of people passing by and judging you.  I envy him as hell.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>