<Blog>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was very sick today. I woke up with terrible cotton mouth and my whole body was sore. Sucks that I had to get sick on a weekend. I actually ahd planned to start drinking at noon today. So much for that. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.punkrockaerobics.com/   Check this out. They actually have a book now. I should get it just cause it's cool (not that I'm gonna do aerobics). Behind it is Hilken Mancini (Fuzzy) and Maura Jasper (she drew the old dinosaur jr album covers) awesome.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today Jeff and Marcie came over again shortly after I got home from work. We drank and played guitars and sang. it was a lot of fun. damn I've been drinking way too much. let's see Friday Saturday Sunday Monday and now Wednesday. At least it's fun. I've been feeling good lately. The band sounds good. I'm happy for Jeff that he's feeling better. I should be actually applying my skills at work soon and I got some work done for my dad and brother.  Songs in my head today: Dinosaur Act - Low, The New Year - Death Cab For Cutie, Better Off Without a Wife - Tom Waits
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We jammed today and then got drunk on tequila sunrises from the bottle Mike brought me from Mexico. Loren promises that I'll be up and at work on time tommorow.  goodnight.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Practice last night went really well. We have four songs down good and there is two or three more on the way. I'm really getting the feel of playing bass. Me and Jeff were playing really tight together. Danny brought over some beer so we had a bit of a buzz going while we played.  I went to bed before 10:30 but I was still really tired this morning and I ended up being late for work (again).    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
         image from Teen Girl Squad at  urlLink homestarrunner.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I bought 28 records for $1 (Canadian) each at the CFCR record sale. Since I've gotten into vinyl I've been buying stuff that I never imagined that I would (new wave stuff, prog, folk, classic rock). I feel differently about records than I do about CDs. I really do listen to everything. For that price why not?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Am I ever tired. I'm going to bed right away, I swear. This evening we ordered Pizza and played hearts and watched Corky Romano and played Gamecube and drank beer. Sounds like a very typical Friday. We were considering catching a midnight show of Kill Bill at the Rainbow but it didn't work out. Hopefully the band will practice tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Girls Are Short   Early North American  Upper Class Recordings (2003)  This Ontario duo makes gleeful electronic pop that won't insult sensitive ears. I'm not a follower of the genre so the only thing I can compare it to is The Postal Service, but it's not quite like that. One of the vocalists sings in a yelping "do you want fries with that" voice the other sounds like a teenage girl. Track 4, "Perfect Sound Forever" (isn't that a Pavement single???), is particularly beautiful with a melody that brings to mind Guided by Voices' "Tractor Rape Chain" and back and forth positive/negative boy/girl stanzas. However, some of the poppiest numbers approach Vengaboys territory. Other songs sound like (very good) Playstation game soundtracks.  I have only heard one of their songs prior to buying this album ("tigertail" from an earlier EP) and it was a crunchy fun guitar song. I find it interesting that Girls Are Short have roots in non-electronic pop. There is a great hidden track on  Early North American  where they bring out the guitars once again.  So yeah... go to the website, listen to the samples and, if you like, pick it up.   urlLink http://www.upperclass.to/girlsareshort.htm 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;1. The Postal Service - Give Up &nbsp;2. Portastatic - Summer Of The Shark &nbsp;3. Broken Social Scene - You Forgot It In People &nbsp;4. Outkast - Speakerboxxx/The Love Below &nbsp;5. The Dears - No Cities Left &nbsp;6. The Shins - Chutes Too Narrow &nbsp;7. The Weakerthans - Reconstruction Site &nbsp;8. Death Cab For Cutie - Transatlanticism &nbsp;9. My Morning Jacket - It Still Moves 10. Jim Bryson - The North Side Benches
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Turns out that I can't publish this from work. That's okay. I can write a bunch and then publish it once a day. Anyway I just added Titles and URLS to my posts. Here is my message board.   urlLink http://b5.boards2go.com/boards/board.cgi?user=norevolution 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've got a lot to say but I don't feel like saying it. I guess I'm just testing this out for now. I love how it will publish it to your webpage with ftp (and it's free to boot!). I have wanted to do an online journal on my web page before just with html but it was too tiresome. This quick and easy way will equal lots of posts. The only thing that would be nice is if people could add comments to my entries. I have a free message board that I will link to for those purposes.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this is my first post
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Pixies tickets go on sale on the 21st. and they're freaking expensive! $27 plus whatver else ticketmaster gets you up the hoop with. No way will I go to two shows if I'm going to Coachella. I think they're overestimating the draw of this event. People will not be flying into Saskatoon and Regina and Winnipeg from all over the world to see The Pixies. Stupid ticketmaster. Limit 4 tickets per person??? why?  I still haven't bought my Coachella ticket but I think I'm going to book my days off from work tomorrow.  Merge records will be re-releasing the first three Dinosaur Jr albums later this year as well as a new LP by J Mascis. Sweet! Finally a label that will do the man justice.  A new Wilco album has been annouced. Can't tell you when the release date is right now. I'm also looking forward to the new Descendents, Frank Black, and Modest Mouse albums.  I bought some records at this huge flea market at Prarieland Park. Can't remember everything I bought right now but there were some good finds. I'm entering all my records on the computer so soon enough you will be able to see what I have.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I slept through my alarm. At 8:18 I phoned work and told them I'd be in in half an hour. At about 9:10 I'm taking the exit from the Preston overpass to Circle. It's icy and my car starts to skid. Next thing I know the car is backwards on the road and the rear corner behind the gas tank hits one of those huge lamp posts, knocking it over. Some guy gives me a ride back home. I call the cops - they're already there getting it towed. Then I call my dad. Then I call the insurance company. The towing company says it's not drivable. I really hope that they don't write it off because the Camry is a freakin' legend. Whatever they give us for it won't be worth it, the car is invaluable to me and the family.  I got my roomate to drive me into work. I got here at 10:45 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just got back from watching a friend of a friend's band play at Bud's. Had a few drinks. Yes I do have to work at 8. I met a great girl - she seemed intelligent as well as attractive. Even though she seemed to like me alot I never said too much to her and I never got her number, damn. You know how hard it is to talk to someone during live music. Especially for me, I have terrible "bar hearing". I wish I knew how to do these things. Hopefully I'll run into her some other time.  My friend said that he is going back to the hometown this weekend. I might go. It all depends. I don't really feel like the drive. But my parents are gone, which is bad and good. I can stay out all night or at least get some reading done. Hmmm, tough choice.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Modest Mouse rocked on Last Call with Carson Daly last night. Work is sort of fun now. Coachella is most likely on. I might go to 2 Pixies shows. I no longer have a TV and DVD player in my room. It's a beautiful world. It's a wonderful life.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      okay what the hell. This is the funniest and awesomest thing ever. The Pixies, after not playing for over ten years, are making Regina and Saskatoon their 2nd and 3rd stops on their reunion tour. I'm almost disappointed in a way because now I have hardly any reasons to go to Coachella (The Flaming Lips, Wilco). If I stayed here I would go to the Regina show as well. That would be wonderful to follow them all the way from Winnipeg down to Coachella.  Wed 04/14/04 Winnipeg, MB Burton Cummings Th. For Perf. Arts  Thu 04/15/04 Regina, SK Doris Knight Hall  Sat 04/17/04 Saskatoon, SK Prairieland Exhibition Park  Sun 04/18/04 Edmonton, AB Red's  Mon 04/19/04 Calgary, AB MacEwan Hall  Wed 04/21/04 Victoria, BC Curling Club  Thu 04/22/04 Vancouver, BC Commodore Ballroom  Fri 04/23/04 Vancouver, BC Commodore Ballroom  Sat 04/24/04 Spokane, WA Big Easy  Sun 04/25/04 Boise, ID Big Easy  Tue 04/27/04 Eugene, OR McDonald Theatre  Thu 04/29/04 Davis, CA Freeborn Hall   So yeah, should I spend over a thousand dollars to go to Coachella? I dunno. I already had my heart set so I want to. If The Flaming Lips and Wilco play Bumbershoot this year then I would really feel bad because I was planning to meet an internet friend in Seattle in September. Woe is me. haha yeah right. This should be great news, how come I feel weird.   Seeing Frank Black last year was great. I'm skeptical to think that the rest of The Pixies will make it that much more special.  I wonder is Coachella will just end up being me and Curtis. I think we should take Greyhounds if it is but I would love to go to Vegas and travel back up the coast and through Seattle.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Saturday, May 1st  Radiohead   The Pixies   Kraftwerk   Wilco  The (International) Noise Conspiracy  The Rapture   Desert Sessions  Hieroglyphics Kinky  Stereolab  Future Sound of London  And you will know us by The Trail of Dead  Peretz  Death Cab for Cutie  Laurent Garnier LCD Soundsystem Living Legends Sander Kleinenberg Black Keys The Sounds Howie Day Junior Senior Mark Farina Moving Units Sahara Hotnights Electric Six The Stills Seb Fontaine 22-20's Juana Molina  Phantom Planet  Dios Jem Q and not U Erase Errata The Section Quartet DJ Icon     Sunday May 2nd:  The Cure   The Flaming Lips   Air   Belle & Sebastian   Basement Jaxx  Paul Van Dyk  Bright Eyes   Atmosphere   Thursday   BRMC   Cursive   Le Tigre   The Crystal Method  Dizzee Rascal Adam Freeland  Mogwai   Ash  2many Dj's Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra Muse Sidestepper The Thrills  Broken Social Scene  The Sleepy Jackson Ferry Corsten Prefuse 73 !!! The Cooper Temple Clause Sage Francis T. Raumschmiere Stellastarr* The Killers Home Town Hero The Section Quartet   It somehow seems disappointing now. Although it's god to see that The Flaming Lips are in and in a good spot. I bolded the bands I'm excited about and Italicized the ones I'm sort of interested in seeing. I am sad to see Sparta and My Morning Jacket gone.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Modest Mouse will be on Carson Daly on Tuesday. Death Cab will be on Friday.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The Preparation 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. New Frank Black disc in April. NEAT! Each one of his releases gets better in my opinion  2. Sounds like Coachella may be a reality. My roommate is in on it. We're investigating driving, bussing, and flying options  3. I forget what number 3 is  3. Oh yeah. I'm a total dork but this week was a good one for comics. I'll write some reviews as soon as I'm not so tired  4. I just got two new DVDs Curb Your Enthusiasm: Season One and Bob Dylan: Don't Look Back. Curb is awesome. Haven't watched Dylan yet.  5. The  urlLink threeohsix.org  benefit show is tomorrow. Should be good (or at least nice to meet a few people in person).  p.s. tomorrow is Friday. Time to get shitfaced ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Broken Social Scene @ Louis - March 7th. Write that down.  Yay! Missed them last time because I wasn't hip enough to know who they were.  opening will be The Stills, I heard their song on CFCR the other day. They are to Interpol what Pilate is to Radiohead.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's the tracklist for  Good News For People Who Love Bad News   01 Horn Intro 02 World at Large  03 Float On  04 The Ocean Breathes Salty 05 Dig Your Grave  06 Bury Me With It  07 Dance Hall 08 Bukowski 09 The Devil's Work Day 10 The View 11 Satin In A Coffin 12 Eric's Interlude 13 Blame It On The Tetons  14 Black Cadillacs   15 One Chance   16 The Good Times Are Killing Me    I bolded the songs that I know from their live set    Also, the lineup for this years Coachella festival is amazing! I am seriously entertaining the notion of going (May 1st and 2nd)  Wilco ,  The Flaming Lips ,   ...And You Will Know Us By The Trail Of Dead ,  My Morning Jacket ,  Broken Social Scene , !!!, Dizzee Rascal, LCD Soundsystem, the Sleepy Jackson, Prefuse 73, (International) Noise Conspiracy, Air,  The Pixies ,  Radiohead , Kraftwerk, and  The Cure .  Stereolab ,  PJ Harvey ,  Bright Eyes ,  Death Cab for Cutie , The Black Keys, Sage Francis, Basement Jaxx,  Sparta , Electric 6,  Thursday , the Yeah Yeah Yeahs, The Streets, and  Weezer 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Yesterday I went to the Broadway musical bash. It was a lot of fun really. It was people from the Broadway players doing songs from a variety of musicals. (I swear it seems like I do gayer and gayer things every day)  I bought this book last night. I enjoyed it even more than Ghost World or 20th Century Eightball. I liked it so much that I just ordered the other 4 Clowes graphic novels from  urlLink amazon.ca . I can really relate to Clowes and the elements of truth in his characters. The misunderstood frustrated misanthropes whose only glimmers of hope get shattered - that's me.  Damn. I guess you're probably getting the impression that I've been having a string of bad days but actually I'm feeling inspired and I want to do some writing and recording today. I have to take Blue Crush back today and I haven't watched it yet (I want to watch it for the ocean cinematography, dammit, I swear - I don't care if it's cheesy). Also we rented the last four episodes of 24 season one. My room, and my whole house, needs serious cleaning. I'm sure these things will get in the way of me doing anything creative today.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I bought this journal yesterday. I think it's really fun because it is obviously intended for girls. But not only am I a comic fan but I think that it might get my left-brained creative feminine side inspired and I'll be able to write some good stuff. I'm using it for lyrics of course - my journal will be here. I had this really messed up dream involving a jacuzzi last night that I will keep to myself but maybe write a song about.  So anyway this journal is a good addition to my plan to act like an arty fag to attract cute punk chicks.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As you may know Billy Talent didn't show up Friday night at The Pat. Apparently they got stuck in small town Saskatchewan. Whatever. I'm sure I've driven worse roads. I wonder where they were stuck? Could it be my buttfuck home town?  Once hearing that and dancing to The Rumour for a few songs we left and I ended up having one of the weirdest and most hilarious nights of my life (I won't get into it... yet).  So the make up concert is tonight. I phoned The Pat and they said that the opening band will start at 10:30 and BT will be on about 45 minutes after. Anyway, that's fucking stupid - I have to work at 8:00. I would have to be masochistic to go. I'm usually up until about 12 anyway but I don't want to be tired tomorrow, especially since I haven't completely finished my bout with strep throat. Billy Talent= worth it? Probably not. Tonight is a mystery to me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey I'm going to Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind tonight and then Tricky Woo.  ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Anyway, I'm going to try out for a band this Wednesday. They are very indie influenced and have a keyboard. I'm excited and nervous. I haven't told Jeff that I'm doing this. I feel bad about betraying him since what we are doing is sounding so great but until we have a drummer it's just going nowhere. I'm not saying that I'm quiting the Bob/Jeff band. I still will put just as much time into that. In fact, this will be good, I will be dedicating all my free time to music instead of just wasting it.  I can't wait until Thursday. Jenn's coming. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      March 30th - Tricky Woo @ Amigos - This will rock my Tuesday!  April 1st - Joel Plaskett @ Amigos - I already got a ticket but Jenn is coming in that night so I don't know if i'll make it  April 6th - The Pinch @ Lydias - Finally more Pinch. Best local band ever, perhaps?  April 8th - The Fembots @ Amigos - I saw them opened for The Weakerthans last year but I didn't pay much attention. Will give them a listen and consider going.  April 24th - The Constantines w/ Jim Guthrie @ Louis - I will probably miss this because I have a dentist appointment in Yorkton the day before  April 28th - Destroyer w/ Frog Eyes @ Amigos - I'll be on the road to Coachella so I'll miss this  May 1st - Young & Sexy @ Amigos - Damn I'll miss this too, I love this band.  May (2nd to 8th-ish) - Urge Overkill @ Louis - Shit I will miss this too. The unbelivable reunited UO!!!  May 12th - The Evaporators @ Amigos - NARDWUAR!!!!!!!!!!!  June 26th - DOS @ Amigos - Mike Watt and his ex-wife Kira's bass duo!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On Friday night me and Curtis decided to go see Blue Rodeo at The Briar Patch. This is where all the people from the big curling event go to get tanked up. I phone ticketmaster at about 6 o'clock and they said that there was still tickets and it was cabaret style and that it was too late for phone orders but tickets would be available at the door.   We get there and the place was huge, like an airplane hangar, and it's completely sold out! So we're standing around the entrance like idiots looking for scalpers. It would have been a lot easier if we had a sign that said "Need Tickets" since neither of us are the type to ask everyone if they had extras as they entered.  how did I get in? stay tuned...  Sunday - BSS
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I don't know if 150 is a good score or not but I won the first frame Friday night. I took tons of pictures and videos.    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This morning was terrible! Not only was there the typical Monday morning tiredness but I accidentally took a slice at my nose while shaving. As soon as I got on the bus all the seats filled up. I was the only one standing up and the whole time I was dabbing my nose with a tissue that was already saturated with blood. It kept bleeding for the entire half hour bus ride and for another half an hour at work.  To make this worse I twisted funny somehow last night and stained my back again. I was in pain and some of the work I had to do included lifting. I just ended up looking like a lazy ass.  Then three PCs in a row that I was rebuilding had bad CD-ROMS. Frustrated, tired, and in pain. :[   Now that I cleaned my room I'm pretty bored. I can't go anywhere because I still have no car until the snow melts. I could read some books or work on my website but that kind of just seems like a waste of time too. I could work on my dad's website and my php/mySQL skills but I'm not motivated to do that either.  A couple things that do rule though include:  Action Packed  - The Best of Jonathan Richman and the new Teen Girl Squad cartoon at  urlLink homestarrunner.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yay! I just got my holidays confirmed and I have a plane ticket to Vancouver for the evening of June 30th. My return is for July 6th. Jenn will pick me up in Vancouver. In total I save nearly 300 bucks by doing it this way. Oh, and Jonathan Richman is playing in Seattle on July 2nd. Yay!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jenn left this morning as I went to work. It was a relaxing and romantic four days. I just bought a plane ticket to Vancouver for June 30th returning July 6th. I hope that I can get these days off. I'm going to fly to Vancouver because it is much cheaper than going directly to Seattle and the flight times are more flexible and much shorter. I really hope that works out and it's great that the plan is alraedy in progress. Jenn is going to be so pleased. I hope she phones from the road tnight so I can tell her.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday I had an optometrist appointment at 5:00 and I completly forgot about it. I phoned at 7:30 to apologize and reschedule. I feel pretty dumb about it.  Now that that mundane news is out of the way I'm very excited that my girlfriend, Jenn, is driving all the way here from Seattle to visit me today. I went to work half an hour early so I could be out sooner. There was no one here when I got to work so I had to wait around for the door to be unlocked. I have no idea what time Jenn is gonna be here anyway. An unfortunate thing is that the band does have to practice this weekend. I wasn't sure when to schedule it best so right now it's 6:30 today. I hope that works out good for when Jenn gets here somehow.  I have no idea what me and Jenn will do. It's pretty wet and gray and cold out. But we're gonna drink martinis and watch movies. We kept the weekend pretty much open.  Okay I'm sick of writing. Later.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      June 3 -  Sparta  - Louis - Should be worth going to. I was too exhausted to watch them at Coachella  June 24 -  Calexico  - Amigos  June 26 -  DOS  - Amigos - It will be amazing to see Mike Watt, even if it is as DOS.  June 27 -  Manitoba  - The Odeon - What is this music like in a live setting? I'm going to listen to the album again and see the price and consider going.  July 17 -  Joel Plaskett  - Amigos - I missed him last time even though I bought a ticket. He doesn't stay away very long.  August 1st -  A.C. Newman with All Night Radio  - Amigos - This guy is from The New Pornographers. All Night Radio has members of The Beachwood Sparks     urlLink Amigos Schedule  this is the link to Amigos. There are some other bands that I may want to checkout.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi there!  I haevn't updated this in so long. It's ironic (perhaps?) that I only update this when life is uneventful. I have so much to tell you about. My trip to Coachella and Seattle, my wonderful girlfriend Jenn, the band I'm playing bass in (Asterid), my new nickname ("The Dutch"), and a wack of other junk.  Also, I'm in love with The Moldy Peaches right now. Listen to them.  I'll give details soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, my band Asterid will be performing at Lydia's open stage night on Tuesday June 1st. Be there or be there.  - The Dutch
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Last night I saw DOS at  urlLink Amigos . It was part of the Sasktel Jazzfest. DOS is Kira (Black Flag) and Mike Watt (Minutemen, fIREHOSE). They both play bass unaccompanied. I was surprised at how well it worked. Watt just sat in the chair plucking away and Kira was up bouncing around the stage. About half the songs are instrumental and Kira sings on the others. They played two 45 minute sets and there was no opening band. The crowd was an unfortunately small group of local hipsters and jazzfest patrons.  Watt was selling his book  urlLink Spiels of a Minuteman . I got a signed copy for $10. He didn't bring enough to go around for the fans. I also got my  Double Nickels on The Dime  CD liner signed and got a picture with Watt and Kira.  After the show I had another beer at Curtis' place and played the excellent Wario Wares on Gamecube. I passed out there.  Today me and Curtis went looking at yard sales. Didn't find much but I did go to one that was held by some kids that post on  urlLink threeohsix.org  and I got a The Rentals CD, a Beavis & Butthead video, a NOFX LP, and Tank Girl on DVD all for $9.50.  So now I have nothing to do for about 3 hours and then  urlLink Asterid  is practicing at 6:30. After that Todd is having a BBQ at his house and I'll be going to Manitoba (the band, not the province) at The Odeon.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Calexico last night. Really damn good. I want to write more but I'm pretty tired. Yeah they were good. They fucked shit up quite nicely. I'm pretty much into seeing anything that isn't just guitar/drums/bass these days. I got home at 2:30 last night. They played "Man in Me" by Bob Dylan (made infamous by The Big Lebowski) and, of course, The Minutemen's "Corona". The singer, Joey (I think), noted that Mike Watt will be coming here in a couple days so doing another cover would be alright. He said he used to work for SST in the 80s and Watt would phone and just say "WATT FOR GINN". Pretty funny.  Opening was the "Five Star Acoustic Duo" they were really good but played twice as long as an opening act should.  So yeah I'm pretty excited about the DOS show. Manitoba on Sunday should be swell as well.  I ran into James from The Pinch after the show. He says that they'll be playing at Lydia's the day before Georgestock and opening for White Cowbell Oklahoma as THE LITTLE WEINERS, a Ween cover band.  I also told him about the soundman problem for The Odeon show and he says that he would be able to do it. Sweet. I hope that works out. The show must go on.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Our proper debut will be 7:30ish at The Odeon on Tuesday July 6th. Be there! Other bands playing are Tombstone Diaries, Playing In Traffic, Phd, and an another TBA
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After work today I went to the comic store and Pat sold me 3 hardcover ultimate spider-man comics for $65. The cover price is $48 each!!! So I got a great deal. They are still shrink wrapper and are huge volumes so I'm going to read them and then sell them over ebay and make my money back and then some.  When I got home I was really craving my last bowl of chili so I look in the fridge and MOTHERFUCKER -- it's missing. I check the sink and the empty bowl is there. I told you that Jeff and Marcie stayed over last night which I was okay with but as if they had to eat my chili. Jeff already owes me 5 bucks and I let him come over and eat my steaks and I buy beer and he drinks them and I let him and his girlfriend stay the night which was all good. But grrrr. Anyway, I'm just over reacting. He just owes me some steaks, that's all  So I had about 4 perogies left and I ate them and checked the messages. Oh shit! We're practicing at 5:30 today. I eat and go out the door. I'm 15 minutes late but I went as fast as I could given the circumstances. Mike's not there yet anyway. He shows up and we run through our 4 new songs and they go pretty damn great. We quit at 7:45 and I decide that I still want to go watch Greendale even though I'll be going alone since Curtis' friend is visiting him from Mexico.  I thought I was gonna be late but it was The Broadway Theatre's member appreciation night (free movie for members!) and there was still a bunch of speeches and prizes going on. It was pretty boring for me, I just want to watch my free Neil Young movie.   The movie was really good. It was uneven at times but all-together beautiful. It was shot entirely on super 8 and there is no dialogue. All of the store comes from the songs which are sometimes (badly) lip synched. Right now my favoirte song from it is "Grandpa's Interview" it's so long and gorgeous with those slow-motion guitar solos that make me love Neil & Crazy Horse.  Well tomorrow night Calexico is here so I'll be checking that out.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just got back from  urlLink The Broadway Theatre . I watched a collection of shorts called The Animation Show, it was really good! I found out that Greendale, the Neil Young movie, will be playing there soon. I put it in my calendar to go see it on the 24th since I'll be in Seattle during the other showings. I'll have to get the guys to reschedule practice that day. Anyway, going to the movies at Broadway is fun and I need to do it more often since there are some interesting shows coming up.   I finished cleaning the main floor today and stuff. Ummm, I'm forgetting what else I was gonna say.   NOW PLAYING: Greendale - Neil Young & Crazy Horse
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just woke. I did a lot last night. I'll write about it in the next post. Modest Mouse was supposed to be on Jimmy Kimmel Live last night so I set my VCR for nothing when I cam home to find a different episode. It will be played Monday. Damn, I still can't cancel my cable. That and I want to wait for the final episode of The WB's Superstar USA.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I want these. Damn, as soon as I think I'm saving money I find some more crap that I like. My clutter is out of control.  I make good chili.  Later, b
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        On Friday night when I went home my dad bought a bucket of Chester Fried Chicken for me and my brother to eat.   The mascott on the box of Chester Friend Chicken is a smiling and waving cartoon chicken with a red cowboy hat.   so i'm sitting there eating my chicken and I look up at the bucket and all of a sudden lose my appetite and feel sad. Look at Chester so happy and cute and he's going to die so I can eat him.  It's pretty weird when places advertise their food with a cute picture of the animal you're about to eat...occasionally eating itself, really disturbing.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Damn I was supposed to get a raise at May 5th. That's one year of working here. It's in my hire letter. I better get it next payday. I better get that sweet sweet back pay or I'll have to take matters into my own hands. Bastards!  (not that I deserve a raise)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A few things since my last update so I'll write in reverse order, (memento style):   tomorrow  is my day off. I have to get the CD player out of the wreck of the Camry and then I'm going home for the weekend. I haven't been since before my trip. There was ice on the lake last time I was there. I'm going to show the family all my pictures from the trip.   Tonight  I'm going to see Sparta. I'll go about 9ish. I hope it's not sold out. They were at Coachella but I was too exhausted to get up close to see them so I just wandered back and forth between them and Desert Sessions and bought a hat. I am excited to go tonight though I do love their album and I want to hear what the songs from their new one (out in July) will sound like. I bet the opening bands will be crappy screamo crapo.   Last night  Dean phoned and said that the band was going to meet at The Yard & Flagon for some beer and snacks. I felt bad because I was going to chat with Jenn at 10 but I felt like I had to go to this since it was the first night after the show and I skipped the last two (or was it one?) night outs.   Right after Dean phoned and I was on my way out the door Evan phones on his cell from Lydia's.   he was all like "you're not playing tonight at 10?" "No that was last night" "Didn't your email say Wednesday" "No, but thanks for coming out!"  Anyway, so I went and it was fun. Todd told the funniest story I've ever heard:   this comes from a male nurse (like fokker, y'know) who works with my Todd's wife.  this great big woman came into the hospital. She had a ginormous fat apron. y'know a big roll that hang over. She was complaining about pains. They lifted up her gut and guess what???... They saw a chip bag under there!!!! After that this guys job was to lift up the gut and scrub the infected area everyday.   It does sound like an urban legend to me but if someone is so obese that they don't notice a chip bag under their flesh they deserve to be ridiculed.  They played good tunes at The Yard including Pixies, Frank Black, and Crooked Fingers.  I got my mini-disc back from Dean. He said it sounded like crap. I knew it would. I told them that it should be recorded open air through my headphones but Dean just was like "you.. are gonna... record through headphones????? ..(disapproving look)... are you serious????)" FUCK YOU! I recorded 2 nights of Modest Mouse that way and they sounds fantastic and also some other stuff. All great. I knew that the soundboard would be unbalanced.  well the soundman did get a good recording of the girl playing gone for good on my mini-disc. I'll rip it to mp3 and share with you people, but maybe I should get her permission first? It's really good. Her name is Miranda Roberts.  so here's what it sounds like VOCALS: loud and clear - this is actually my first time really hearing the lyrics. GUITAR and KEYS: goes from between medium loud and barely there. BASS: barely audible DRUMS: very quiet.  Hopefully the mp3s that Dean made are salvageable. By listening to the recording I think it didn't sounds as awful as we thought but we all blame the sound coming through our monitors for screwing us up.  well I talked to Jenn when I got home at 12:15ish. She wasn't really mad at me but I hate to disappoint her like that and she's afraid that I'm pushing her away. I'm not, she's more important to me than anything else. I felt like a shit.   Tuesday Night: The Show   The first guy was just some dude on an acoustic. He was good if forgettable. Next were two guys on acoustics who were all GQ looking. I'll withhold their names but I called them Terrance and Phillip. Totally lame. They played a Jack Johnston song and covered Disarm. One guy looked just like Josh Homme/Craig Kilborne. One guy had a harmonica with headgear and we were wondering if he was even going to play it. Whatever.  Next was Miranda Roberts. She did a wonderful version of "Gone For Good" by The Shins. After she asked if anyone knew them and me and Mike and Dean shouted out. I have it on my mini-disc and I should share it with you all.  We were next. Dean's whole family was there to watch and cheer us on. We got the soundman to plug my mini-disc into the soundboard to record so he went to excessive lengths micing the drums and my bass amp but then gave us shit for not starting. The sound through the monitors was horrible and I messed up the beginning to almost every song and we stumbled through a lot of spots. There were times when we couldn't hear the guitar or keyboard. Last time was fun but this time I was sweating bullets and nervous. I still managed to smile now and then and look like I was enjoying myself and instead of like I was scared to death. Luckily we knew the songs well or we'd be screwed.  None of my friends that I emailed showed up. I saw Duch's friend whatsherface there after but just talked to her for a second. I wonder if Jeff is mad at me for being in this band. That kind of pisses me off that he doesn't come out and support me and see what I'm doing musically. Dick!  Next was a guy named Joey who Mike and Dean saw puke his guts out before going on.  He definetly had a look but his songs were just power chords with only one strumming pattern.  Next they had prizes for the bands. There was a pink thong from Schmata to be won. Everyone at our table was chanting THE DUTCH THE DUTCH THE DUTCH (that's my nickname that the band gave me). The hostess drew ASTERID from the cup and I went up to receive it. hehehe. They said I had to put it on so I put it on my head! Later at the table I signed it. Good times.  Oh yeah and next was the Nickelback Jr. band: Eye of the Round. The singer looked just like Chad Kroeger but with dark hair and stood the same and sang the same. The other guitar player also sang the same. They even had a song where they said "this one is about a small town called Kelvington". It was about how small towns destroy you. There last song was called Ponds or something and they said "we got really drunk and wrote this in 15 minutes" I was like "oh not 5 like the rest of your songs". Fun to mock. I have pictures.  The last dude I saw played acoustic and had a really good voice. He did Sweet Child O' Mine very nicely. But then he started to talk and had this crazy ego so I decided it was time to leave. Loren stayed a little while longer.  (pictures coming soon!)   urlLink asterid.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey!  Asterid is playing at The Unitarian Centre on August 9th. We're playing with National Monument, Oh Jeh Lye La, and Parade Against Parades. It's gonna be super-awesome. Be there!  I installed Red Hat Linux 9 on my PC last night. Rock on! I installed the works. 3.5 gigs, most of the stuff I probably will never use but you never know what you're gonna use. It's a learning experience. I want to set up a webserver and a ftp server. I still have XP on it too. I have a 6 gig partition for windows and another 6 gig partition for Linux. I also have a 800 meg hardrive that I don't know what I'm gonna do with.  So yeah, my personal and professional life are going place baby!  This weekend I'm going to go visit the family at Duck Mountain. I hope the weather is great. It's a long weekend but I want to come back Sunday night to see A.C. Newman @ Amigos. Also the Fringe Festival started yesterday so I want to check that out next week. And next weekend is the annual Duck Mountain camping party blowout. Me and Curtis are gonna get retarded whether you come or not, but please do come. The more the merrier.  Damn, you'd think I was in a good mood.  Love you to death dear reader...  &nbsp; dutch out.   Recent Listening: Crust Brothers - Marquee Mark Spoon - A Series Of Sneaks various - Gimme Indie Rock v.1
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey,  I'm almost definetly going. I found out my last day of work will be Sept. 3rd. I got a plane ticket to Seattle for Sept. 2nd. School starts on the 8th.  The lineup is now annouced on the  urlLink official  site. I must say the Saturday and Sunday lineups are underwhelming. But I am looking forward to Built to Spill, Death Cab for Cutie, Pixies, Crooked Fingers, The Walkmen, President of the United States of America, and Cobra High.  see ya there ;) 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last night I went to an all-ages show at The Unitarian Centre. FYI, I did some research after and found out Unitarianism is a religion where you can pretty much believe whatever you want and it's very liberal. cool.  The first band that played was No Birds. They are a 10 piece band with a brass and string section. They play lengthy moody experimental rock pieces. Usually instrumental. There are some major talents within that group and I think that most of them are high school kids! You'd think that at best high school kids would just show a hint of promise but this music is fully realized. I bought their CD  Don't Rely on Dying Young .  Next was Parades Against Parades. A four piece that had the other drummer and the other guitarist from No Birds. They played post-Dinosaur rock in the vein of 764-HERO or the rockier side of Broken Social Scene. I dug the sound and they can only get better.  Both No Birds and Parades are a part of  urlLink The Teargas Recording Tree . A collective a like minded local musician (think Saskatoon's answer to Elephant 6). Anyway, I'm really impressed and I must say there's something special going on in this town/scene.  Next was Edmonton's Fractal Pattern. They were really good musicians and played their guitars with bows and had a french horn player but somehow I didn't fine their 9 minute epics to be as engaging as they should be.  The last band to play was Clann Zu. All the way from Australia. They are on  urlLink G7 . They sounded like Radiohead but the singer was a bulky Henry Rollins kind of guy. It was weird to hear that high little voice come out of his mouth. They were good but it wasn't really my thing and it was late so I went home.  So in short. Yay, for the local kids and The Unitarian Centre is a good evnue with good sound. Look out for shows there.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The  urlLink bumbershoot webpage  still hasn't announced the artists lists but I looked up which bands will be playing in Seattle between September 3rd and 6th on  urlLink pollstar  and I see some good news.  Pixies, Death Cab For Cutie, Lou Barlow, Presidents Of The United States Of America, Nancy Sinatra, The Walkmen, Cobra High, Crooked Fingers, and Built to Spill among others are gonna be there. sweet! Things are looking good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I'm playing bass in a band these days. This is a shot from our July 8th show at The Pit Studios.  Check out our  urlLink website  to see our schedule of upcoming shows and to hear some of our songs.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         The historic Bixby Bridge opened up the beautiful Big Sur area of coastal California to the public. Allowing the construction of scenic Highway 1. It's one of the prettiest views I've ever seen. Look at it! You got the ocean, cliffs, beach...  I took this pic with Curtis' camera on May 4 on our massive Western United States road trip. you can see the rest of the pics from that trip  urlLink here .  On the trip we went to Las Vegas, The Coachella Music Festival, LA, The Hearst Castle, Seattle, and Vancouver among other places.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         On my last trip to Seattle me and Jenn took a trip East of Seattle to the beautiful Snoquamie Falls. The televison series Twin Peaks was shot there.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I took this pic on my last day is Seattle right before we hit the road back to Vancouver. Me and Jenn look dark and brooding and sexy. It was about to rain. We're happy people really.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Clann Zu/Fractal Pattern/Parades Against Parades/No Birds  - July 13th -  Unitarian Centre  - We're going to this to talk to some people about setting up some shows soon. Also No Birds is awesome.  White Cowbell Oklahoma/The Little Weeners  - July 16th -  Amigos  - The Little Weeners is The Pinch playing ween covers. I might have to go home Friday but I seriously need to go to this for a few reasons.  Joel Plaskett/Peter Elkas  - July 17th -  Amigos  - Saturday. Will I miss him twice in a row. I love my brother but it's kind of inconvenient having him stay with me. Peter Elkas is formerly of The Local Rabbits.  The Fine Options/Champion, Alberta  - July 23rd -  Amigos  - The same night as The Pinch. Why god, why? We might be playing with Champion, Alberta so we better go here to schmooze.  The Pinch  - July 23rd -  Lydia's  - They're playing three sets so I should be able to catch some of it.  A.C. Newman/All Night Radio/The Neins  - August 1st -  Amigos  - I think All Night Radio broke up. The Slow Wonder LP is really good.  Despistado  - August 10th 7:30 -  The Ex (free stage)  - Regina band makes good. I really enjoy their song I downloaded, "A Stirsticks Prediction". I owe it to everyone to check it out. Pilate plays after them  By Divine Right  - August 11th -  Amigos  - Did you know the bass player for Broken Social Scene used to be in this band? "Come for a ride!"  Sarah Harmer  - October 5th -  Broadway Theatre  - yay, I heart her.  Fly Pan Am/Mono  - October 9th -  Amigos  - Ummm Fly Pan Am has members of God Speed or something.  also rumour is that  Metric  will be coming back soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi, I'm sad to say I'm back from Seattle.  We're playing a show tonight at THE PIT on Broadway. Doors at 7:30. We're opening for Radical Attack, Forgiveness Denied, & The Soccermoms. $5. See ya there!  as always  urlLink www.asterid.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Future Soundtrack for America  (August 17th - Barsuk Records)  01 OK Go: "This Will Be Our Year"  02 David Byrne: "Ain't Got So Far to Go"  03 Jimmy Eat World: "Game of Pricks"  04 Death Cab for Cutie: "This Temporary Life"  05 Blink-182: "I Miss You (James Guthrie mix)"  06 Mike Doughty: "Move On"  07 Ben Kweller: "Jerry Falwell Destroyed Earth"  08 Sleater-Kinney: "Off With Your Head"  09 R.E.M.: "Final Straw (MoveOn Mix)"  10 Bright Eyes: "Going for the Gold (live)"  11 The Long Winters: "The Commander Thinks Aloud (Future Mix)"  12 will.i.am: "Money"  13 They Might Be Giants: "Tippecanoe and Tyler Too"  14 Clem Snide: "The Ballad of David Icke"  15 Yeah Yeah Yeahs: "Date with the Night (live)"  16 Fountains of Wayne: "Everything's Ruined (acoustic)"  17 Nada Surf: "Your Legs Grow"  18 The Flaming Lips: "Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots (live on the BBC)"  19 Old 97s: "Northern Line"  20 Laura Cantrell: "Sam Stone"  21 Tom Waits: "Day After Tomorrow"  22 Elliot Smith: "A Distorted Reality is Now a Necessity to be Free"   -Also available with a book by McSweenys -A fundraiser for  urlLink MoveOn.org  -Jimmy Eat World covering Guided By Voices??? -That Blink-182 song is a guilty pleasure of mine -Bush is still a moron    The Late, Great Daniel Johnston: Discovered Covered  (September 21st - Gammon Records)  01 Teenage Fanclub w/ Jad Fair: "My Life Is Starting Over Again" 02 Clem Snide: "Grievance" 03 Gordan Gano: "Impossible Love" 04 Eels: "Living Life" 05 TV on the Radio: "Walking the Cow" 06 The Rabbit: "Good Morning You" 07 Calvin Johnson: "Sorry Entertainer" 08 Bright Eyes: "DevilTown" 09 Death Cab for Cutie: "Dream Scream" 10 Beck: "True Love Will Find You in the End" 11 Sparklehorse w/ The Flaming Lips: "Go" 12 Mercury Rev: "Blue Cloud" 13 Thistle: "Love Not Dead" 14 Vic Chestnutt: "Like a Monkey in the Zoo" 15 Starlight Mints: "Dead Lovers Twisted Heart" 16 M. Ward: "Story of an Artist" 17 Guster: "The Sun Shines Down on Me" 18 Tom Waits: "King Kong"  -this is a 2 disc thing. The second disc will be the original Daniel Johnston versions of the songs -Wow! TV On The Radio doing "walking the cow". -I'm gonna get Vinyl to order it for me. -The title is misleading Daniel JOhnston is alive and (maybe not financially or medically) well
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Aug 9 National Monument, In Media Res, Parades Against Parades, & Asterid @ Unitarian Center ($7 admission - Doors at 7:30/ Show at 8 pm) Bring your dancing shoes!    National Monument are from Winnipeg. In Media Res are from Vancouver. Parades and us are local. This is our first real gig besides our two open stages and our misplacement at The Pit! Come and squirm!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I signed up for  urlLink myspace.com . It's like Friendster but has a blogging feature and is way more customizable. It has some pretty big flaws but it's okay and I'm surprised by how many people are on it. Loren's even on it.  It would make more sense for me to have my blog there because more people can see it and are more likely to comment but I like this thing damn it and I'm sticking to it.  view my myspace profile  urlLink http://profiles.myspace.com/users/5841707    recent listening: Neko Case - Blacklisted Pinback - Blue Screen Life The Decemberists - Her Majesty... A.C. Newman - The Slow Wonder
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On Sunday night I drove back into the city. I was driving into the sun about half the way which was painful but in a beautiful way. I gave Dean a call and we both wanted to go see the A.C. Newman show at  urlLink Amigos .  We got there around 11 and the show hadn't started yet and there were a lot less people than I expected. Cover was only $8. We sat right up front.  Opening was The Neins from Vancouver. None of them looked older than 20 years old but, damn, they did impress me with their songs. I'd say they pretty much did everythimg right. The singer was a lot like Jonathan Richman in his lyrics and mannerisms and they way he stared into the audience. Musically they had the vancouver sound and a bit of the Beatles via Elephant 6.  After the Neins played I bought A.C. Newman's LP and The Neins CD (both excellent, btw). Deans and I talked to the drummer and bassist/keyboardist of The Neins for quite a bit. It's really good to have Dean in our band because he's a born schmoozer. Anyway, they're really nice people.  Next A.C. Newman played and the place started to fill up a little more. Still nobody got up to watch which was a little disappointing. The girl playing bass was from The Gay and the drummer was from Copyright. I don't know where the guitarist/keyboardist, Shane, was from but he was really good. Various Neins came up and joined on some songs. Overall I found that the vocals and guitars were too quiet and it would have felt more livelier if people had gotten up. The set seemed really short but was altogether really good. I still have "The Battle for Straight Time" in my head.  I grabbed a poster from the wall after and saw that the drummer was about so I had him sign it. Some other kid was getting things signed too so the drummer led us into the back room to hang out with the bands. They had tons of beer to spare so they offered us some. I had a Sol. Everyone signed my poster and I got Carl to sign my LP jacket. I hung around for awhile and talked about The Pixies and transportation and then I left to find Dean. He was talking to The Neins again and I let him know there was free beer back there. LOL. I swear me and Dean probably talked to Mr. Newman for an hour. It felt like we were interviewing him after awhile but he was really nice and didn't seem annoyed at all. We talked about doing the solo thing, Neko Case, The United States, touring, festivals, Vancouver, The Fiery Furnaces, Clinic, Spoon, Modest Mouse, Franz Ferdinand, the last Pixies show, San Francisco, Austin, The New Pornographers...  We chatted with The Neins a little more and they demanded we take some beer home with us so I did. Those two Sol were sure refreshing on Monday afternoon
     
    
</post>



</Blog>