<Blog>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Damn damn damn fuck fuck fuck! o my arrghh im am mad! this is the offical first vent on this site. they have me working on friday night when that was the one day i requested off! but nooooo i have to work and only 2 people could have taken my shift and one cant and i doubt the other can either!!! so mad i hate working! work sucks. if u dont already have a job dont get one they suck except for every few days a month when u get paid those are the only good days! ok i think i might be ok now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yea so i cleaned my room again...went to work again...came home and had a quickie at the jacuzzi :) and that was the extent of my funfilled day! o my gosh! but yea anyhow PSA- For everyone that doesnt already know Erin is PORN! Jessica is a BITCH! and i am well we havnt decided yet but im sure we will find something but for now im just mads. yea i am one exciting person i know and sometimes you can't handle it but one day i will have u all trained to be my lil uhm poodles or something...whats this i here about multiply thumbs up on PCH that i missed chloe! damn i feel so unloved lemme just say.  REMINDER~The Club has a singles meeting on sat night u better be there or be square...or something-much love and happiness  P.S-I have the cd jess! TOXIC 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       YAY! Finals are finally over and guess what!? i survived! thats right i might not have passed but at least im still here.  to releive the stress that finals gave to us jess, erin and I went shopping! *Chloe i kno we said we were gonna go to hollister and not south coast but our plan changed! im sorry sweetie i should have called you!* but shopping was fun Abercrombie having big sale right now! erin bought a 4 doller abercrombie shirt even the boys have to give her some props for that one. i cant say the same for myself because well i didnt save so much but i have really comfy pants and a new shirt to show for my none saving-ness-ness or something... but yes this weekend should rock not only because it is a 4 day weekend baby but because the the sub club of The Club is meeting. Thats right its a singles club meeting... WoOt wOoT! but anyhow it still makes me laugh to think that some people whom i wont name think that Mr. Happy is a dildo! thats right folks but in all seriousness Mr. Happy is not a Dildo. but yea i think imana go do something semi productive...or just watch me some good ol' quality tele-vision.-muahs! 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey again yea subway food for uhm me school sucks work sucks people suck...haha fooled you im kidding nothin sucks cept for wait...i wont say but yea anyhow yea people around me are really depressedishy (not a real word but its kinda skitzy) and its making me kind of down and that kinda isnt cool cuz i dont like being down all the time or having my friends down so when i kno that my friends are down i like to introduce them to my lil friend buddy... yea thats right buddy is a very cute lil teddy and is everybodys friend no one can hate teddy... ;) but yea anyhow imana stop writin in this lil box thing cuz its good to think OUTSIDE the box... yea but seriously imana go talkto by girls and boys- muahs  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so finals suck major ass especially when you forget to bring your books home to study with... yea guess who did that. your right it was me i kno im real bright... some might even say stupid though i disagree and think they should  go screw a monkey or something. but no hard feelings here :) not at all but yea finals do suck and if anyone wants to take a break from studying ya'll can come over here cuz most likely i wont be studying! woot fuckin woot. yea  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Ya'll this is my "site" no not venting or anything ;) although if i must i will bitch. but yea anyhow there really is no point to this at all except for the fact that sometimes i like to talk to myself...or wait no i just like to talk. this prolly wont be very personal i will prolly just put interesting things or things that made me laugh on here but it might evolve and turn into something else i dun really kno cuz i cant see the future...late 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey so today i recieved some interesting news some of which i had known before and some of which was completly new to me. firstly i knew my dad was in the army and shipping out again pretty soon but what i didnt know was that he wanted me sister and i to be there as his ship left. In a way this doesnt sound all that bad but when you consider that i havnt seen my or talked to my father since 4th grade and he has just started showing any intrest in me at all these past few months it seems slightly strange especially considering that he does call my sister every week and has been for almost a year now and i never knew until november. But now he has bought me a plane ticket to North Carolina valentines weekend so that my sister and I can see my little brothers and a little sister whom i have never seen and the rest of my family from his side. ou would have thought that someone would have called me sometime  in the past 6 or so years before now sent a card on christmas or my birthday but no. I am going to go considering that there is the strong chance that i will never be able to see my Father again (seeing as thats how war works and to quote my father "When the bad guy shoots, we shoot back...) yes i know incredably hick but hey i cant help it thats how we are. so yea thats my interesting news that i learned I am sort of happy knowing that they still realize i exist  and would like to see me but i am also kind of mad and hurt that no one had ever bothered before to see or talk to me. only in a time of potential death do people start remembering children they abandoned or friends they forgot, but i guess thats also when people see how much they can stand to have placed on them in terms of forgivness. so peace and love ya'lls i hope your not as confused and messed up as i am. i will always love you and i will never Ever forget anyone you no matter what. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yea jacooooozi school sucks i wish it would just go away but hey i dont have a 6th again so im am a very happy lil girl! woot or should i say woat... :) uh go see big fish its a pretty good movie ahh i have nothin to say except...nope i have nothin so u people go get a life and stop readin this i wont have anything interesting or particually juicy in here so yea if u want juicy shit go eat a pear 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yea been a few days but thats allright...by now im sure half the world knows about my weekend...not my fault. and yea there is drama in my lil world but hey how long could we have possibly gone without a lil flava once in a while right? the meeting was mostly fun parts were shitty or should i say shitfaced...ha yea but we will have another one soon enough im sure...so yea other than that life has been a little bit boring with school and work and church and all but thats ok things can only get better! everyone must keep lookin up! on the up said i passed the one class i thought i might fail...but my ok class dropped with my stupid final! have i ever told ya'll that i hate languages? well i do like for reals dawg..or something and yea imana miss the OC i just realized this and that suck like big hairy guys' monkeys balls...but i dont so ha take that  all u monkey owners out there. im gonna shut up now and go...catch ya lata 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Folks here are a few rules of what not to do one your way to tumbling class... i just thought i would share 1.) dont drive over concrete grass. there is no excuse for it although it is good for your abs. 2.) never trust directions when it says .1 miles it isnt. 3.) Always stop at dance studios and say "Hi im a dancer gone retarded can you please help me find my way to cheer/tumbling class?" 4.) don't show up a half hour late for your free class, it looks bad and makes you truly feel retarded. 5.) always have fun being lost for 40 minetes especially when you are getting pissed off and want to cry. 6.) be good to your car the poor thing never did anything to you and im sure concrete grass doesnt taste so good. 7.) even if your intention was to do something good for your health stop at Arbys and have some class A+ junk food. I promise you will feel better after you do like 9,000,000,000 crunches :)                                                So those are just some of many many rules of what not to do on you way to cheer class. So as i predicted  in my first entry today hangin out with clo certainly helped my mood i hope it will last. peace and love and crabs for everyone! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yea i had a really sucky day and i dont really know why. i was just kinda down cept for a few moments when i was with my girls and hopefully later at tumbling class i will have a good time with chloe. that should be good. i did alot of walking today i was quite surprised at how i wasnt tired at all seeing as that was the most i had walked since freshmen year...lol damn walking to school. so anyhow nothing important to say today except that im sorry to everyone i was kinda mean to this week it hasnt been a good week for me and i took it out on other people. sorry much love 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yea i read my friends entry and i know that she is sincere in what she is saying and i hope that she will be forgiven and that all will be well in the world...or at least my world. fat chance of that actually happening but i can always dream. :) yea i am one crazy mofo. my lil iron broke so i had to have my curly hair the past couple of days and well i have been getting mixed reactions some love it some think straight is just better(including myself) and some say it looks like 80's porn hair...Thank you Ryan. but yes ya'll will be seeing alot of the messy lil curls that i have to call my hair until i get a new straightening iron so woat. o and everyone needs to stop telling me that i copy Erin in saying ya'll or ya'lls ok cuz where i come from (NOrth Carolina which is in the SOUTH) we say that and i have grown up saying that and it freakin pisses me off that people would say i am copying someone else. thats my biggest freakin pet peeve i hate when people try to be someone else but i hate it more when i am being myself and people try and tell me that im trying to be someone else so please everyone just stop telling me that ok? but yea anyhow i will stop ranting and random ass stuff and i will wait till i have something of importance to say before i write in this damn thing again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok first of all WHY CANT WE ARE JUST GET ALONG? it seems like this year has just been full of all kinds of shit and it fuckin sux freakin blue asss monkey butt if u know what i mean but seriously no one is perfect so dont expect them to be. No one is always nice in fact sometimes they are a bitch. and no one is a perfect angel sometimes they are slutty or drunk or whatever. so forgive and forget i know how it is to go and change your life because your friends are spilt. i know how it feels when someone hates you or you hate someone and it sucks sinething maybe not butt maybe ass. so anyhow i will use the X, Y, and Z thing cept this time Y is diff cuz i can talk about myself as much as i want. Y just say your sorry to X and Z chances are(100% positive) they will forgive you and apologize as well. X i know your hurt but forgive Y and apologize, Z i know your not made you just have you opionions about how things should be done and so does Y but you should all be able to think in their own ways. X and Z  just ask Y if she would just not use your names in her profile im sure if she saw that you cared so much she might just keep using X's and Z's sometimes all you have to do is ask people and they will do what you would like. Y  try using the letter thingy if it will cure the friendship suffering i think its worth it and i think that you might see it that way as well. I know julie and i want everyone to get along she barly sees any of us and when she does it seems like someone is mad at someone else at any given time. and I of all people should know how it feels to have her freakin friends hate eachother and talk shit on each other and it sort of sucks because no one will fuckin listen. so if everyone could all just get along i would appreciate it ok? muahs and hopefully peace and love will come your way. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey so its been awhile a long long while but hey what can i say? i went away last weekend to North Carolina yay that was great i got to see my best friends from North Carolina and have pix so if anyone wants to see me and my friends or me and my brothers and sisters im me and ask they are too cute and im way excited. hopefully i will be goin back this summer and get to spend more time with my brothers and sister(the ones i dont live with) and all that Work sux major ass they fired my favorite person and i am looking for a new job at a real restaurant so i can get training so i can get accepted to the C.I.A! woot (culinary institute of america for all ya'll out there who dont know i want to be a chef) yea so that means no more shitty panera even tho i have worked there 8 months (sigh seems like such a short time when i say it that way but it has seemed like forever...) but yea places i am thinking of applying to Jimmy Z Grill, Brittas Cafe, Islands, Steelhead. yay o and i am applying at Cornell you guys doesnt that make me sound smart? until people ask what i want to major in... but yea my mom always assumed i would be goin to OCC so now that she realizes i want to go away for college to a REAL college she keeps saying well why dont you go to the school in Pasadena? or maybe Las Vegas, or what about San Fran? that isnt as far as New York. lol yea New York as far away from here as i can get...I will miss all my friends here but hey im only close to maybe 10 at the most and there are always holidays and besides most will go away to college as well (but i cant say i wont miss you guys.) yea anyhow Friday night was interesting though i feel bad about making plans with some of my friends and then ditching them but i was supposed to go shooting with Byron and Chloe for so long and i havnt since i was like 10 (I know its just an excuse but thats the truth) and yea i have a problem lately with having an idea asking people to hang out and then suddenly switching my plans i guess im just indesicive lately which i should stop being and yea be normal for once. and i need a date to Winter Formal (oh wait sorry   Spring Ball   ) anyhow that doesnt look promising and it kinda sux i dun really wanna go without a date cuz why spend all that money on a dress and hair and makeup and ticket and food and pictures just to dance with yourself? eh not fun kinda boring actually...even though i will have my friends...ugh who would have thought people got dates like a month before hand i was thinking about then but i just dont know who i would ask really it would have to be someone i know and someone i have fun with otherwise it would just suck ass. but yea anyhow enough about that im getting depressed. Uhm i have been getting to hang out with my old work buddies alot lately and its been super fun i missed them all have quit except for 2 how sad is that? well i hope i can "chill" with them more often but yea imana go now cuz im sure your bored by now. muahs 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thank you for reminding me Chloe, Madame de fuckin Berry go fuck urself up the fucking nose in a pit of cow shit......and enjoy it. hehe so i couldnt resist but seriously i fucking hate her. i will tell you why just come with me to the land of Hate de fuckin berry stories. First off she has berrys for brains, she tries to teach french but everything she says is completly different from the book. i trust the book over her anyday. Second i missed alot of school the past 2 weeks and  so on tuesday i went in and asked her what i had missed on Friday and Monday hers what she said, "we did the vocaulary and the grammer from chapter 6 so just do the workbook for that and study" so i did. Today i come into class and she starts talking about a skit. Now i like skits so i was like hell yea a skit i studied this week so i actually knew what the fuck she was talking about. but then she said "ok who wants to go first?" so i was floored, and in my mind i had thoughts running as if giant strawberrys were chasing them. "whatr!?! there is a skit due today?!" "Oh my fucking God, i dont have one!" "I don't have a partner." "She will blame me for not knowing." so slowly i inch out of my seat in between skits and make my way to her desk. When i get there i say "Excuse me Madame de Berry but i dont have a skit and i didnt know we even had one assigned seeing as i wasnt here on friday or monday." so guess what she says "Well I gave the class time to work on it friday and its your respondsibility to find out your assignments" hearing this i turn beet red fuming very very pissed off because the first thing i did upon my arrival in my fourth period french class on tuesday was to ask her what we had done, and this skit was NOT one of the things she told me. so i say "But Madame i came in on tuesday and u did not tell me about this skit." this is the part where she basically calls me a liar to my face. But luckily by this time the whole class is listening to our heated discussion in the corner of the room. Two of my french one buddies chime in "But Madame de Berry we didnt work on our skits at all on Monday or Thursday and you havent said a thing about it this week." Madame knowing she is caught in a lie  just sits there looking at me. Then two more of my friends Andy and Ali say "Madame if you gives us one more day we can rewrite our skit to include her." But this did not satisfy Madame de Berry. So now we are staring at each other with a look of pure hatred in our eyes. I'm sure she hates me almost as much as i hate her. What happens next was sort of a surprise but mostly it wasn't seeing as how i was right. "Allright" she said "This one time i will excuse you, But no more if you miss one day you can'y make up the work you missed and you won't be excused."  Ugh i know these past two weeks i've missed a lot of school but that is the most i have ever missed in my entire life. So i was very indignant at this point and sort of tearing up. But i did not let her see and just walked back to my seat where i could vent in peace. Needless to say i Hate her. so here is what i would like to say, Madame de Berry i hope you go to hell and i wish you would be fired because you are a terrible teacher and you are not a very good person. There i have gotten my angry out of me, and i want people to know that i am not a violent person and i dont normally hate but this is a very very special case. So leave me the fuck alone ok? Thanks its much appreciated. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo dawg sup...ok ok fine i admit it i look like freakin whiteout leave me the fuck alone! lol yea so my Dad shipped out to Iraq today, it sucks ass everyone says to me that it will be ok and that he will come back but you know what? there is a big freakin chance that he won't he is looking for land mines over there. Land mines blow up. people near land mines blow up. If someone had told me about 6 months ago that i would care so much i wouldnt beleive it, but considering that as of late I have actually been talking to him and that side of my Family finding out things that i had never known. Learning things that make me want to move to Oklahoma to live with my STEPmother as oppossed to my REAL mother, thats pretty sad i think. so yea anyhow I have been collecting applications to actual resturants near my house because i need a new/second job. partially because i am getting tired of the one i have and partially because i need at least 6 months in a tablecloth restuarant before goin to CIA. yea yea so im kinda bored right now and really i have nothing of any use to say right now so imana leave peace yo   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey guys so someone told me the other day that my blog was boring. at first i was shocked and sort of sad about it but then she said you havnt added anything forever! my excuse? well i was away for a while, i have a boring life, i was sick...well those are all true and thats all well and good but the truth is that this blog really is kinda boring compared to some others...(JULIE!) damn they always show me up! but guess what i have some news for you! and its quite interesting...ok question how would you feel if you (by chance) meet the girlfriend of a guy you'd been hooking up with? and that they'd been going out for like a year? but you had only known this guy like 4 months? UGH! thats how i felt. a little shitty, used, pissed off, and kinda sad because i really wouldnt have expected that one. i guess it kind of showed when he had to leave the room to talk to his "best friend" at 4 in the morning and had his "best friends" picture on his computer screen. but hey i have pictures of my best friend right? haha well anyhow even though i've had numerous offers i think i will pass up someone hiring a hitman or someone breaking his knees or in my friends words "offing" him. lol you guys are so sweet and always cheer me up. I know that one day i will find a guy who isn'y shitty and actually likes me crazy porn hair and all...last remark Ryan, of course. Anyways thats just a little vent there i'm sure there will be some interesting ones coming up in the near future or at least i will find something to write about for you guys however many there are probably like five. but yes thats my current boy situation and no i am not a "pimpette" Love always you own maddy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yea so who aced their french exam today? thats right i did! take that madam de Berry! oh yea i had an awesome weekend! im me about it if u care. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, ok. I just got this email today because I never go on this screen name anymore. And I saw this and I joined Maddy's bloggy-majig... and noe I get to write in it?! That's SO COOL. If I'm wrong and I'm just invading someone else's blog when I'm not supposed to, then tell me. But first you have to stop laughing at me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       O My GOd its been so long i dont know where to start so i wont but eventulay(mr. Pei talk) i will maybe. but for now imana just go back and read my old ones. SPring break in 4 days! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The Dante's Inferno Test has banished you to  the Eigth Level of Hell - the Malebolge!   Here is how you matched up against all the levels:     Level    Score       urlLink Purgatory   (Repenting Believers)   Moderate       urlLink Level 1 - Limbo   (Virtuous Non-Believers)   Moderate       urlLink Level 2   (Lustful)   Moderate       urlLink Level 3   (Gluttonous)   Low       urlLink Level 4   (Prodigal and Avaricious)   Very Low       urlLink Level 5   (Wrathful and Gloomy)   Low       urlLink Level 6 - The City of Dis   (Heretics)   Very Low       urlLink Level 7   (Violent)   Low       urlLink Level 8- the Malebolge   (Fraudulent, Malicious, Panderers)   High       urlLink Level 9 - Cocytus   (Treacherous)   Very Low      Take the  urlLink Dante Inferno Hell Test   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the title say it al about my day. First off i write on myself with pencil during my math test which i aced(yay) and then i almost trip on my own 2 feet(booo) but then during 4th period my french class (im sure you all remember me ranting about Madame de Berry earlier this year) well this class started out like always kinda sucky but then She "remembered" that there was a survey for juniors and senoirs about prom that we had to do right quick so she starts talking  #1 WHo is going to prom? all 5 junoirs raise their hands including me because i was considering going because my friends wanted me too, but wasnt really planning on it. #2 Who is going with a date? and again everyone raises their hands except for poor lil ol me...yes thats right folks i was dateless dont be too shocked. Then out of the blue my teacher stops the survey looks at me and says " O i think i might know someone you can go with.) first thing that pops to mind "O lord what is this crazy lady talking about?" SUddenly Avinash pops up and runs to the door and in walks Aria with a dozen gorgous roses, and what i would call an admirable attempt to speak french he says "Chere Maddy, Voudrais-tu aller a la "prom" avec moi?"  and me pink in the face and speechless just sit there grinning and nodding my head. sigh im and such a dork. so he walks over and asks, "so was that a yes?" and I finally can speak and say yes so he hands me the roses and away he went to class. hehe after class im walkin to my locker and i have like a million people tell me congrats or ask me what i said lol how did everyone  else know before me? truly amazing so that was my lovely day and julie has a date! yaya  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Damn Damn Damn augh im mad it keeps not working... 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    there we go 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
         So yea havnt been on in a hella long time but i have good news...I get to go to Germany and Italy in October (if i save enough money) and go to the Culinary Olympics! (YAY!) and a cooking school in Italy (OMG) the only thing is this depends on my getting a second job because i really need to buy a car for work and school next year and i have no clue how i will get this much money. bleh Grades are up so thats cool i just have to work on English.    If you don't have Your liscense get off your lazy ass like i did and go here--->  urlLink    and get your permit! its super easy and takes very little time.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, I think my heart stopped. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       still eh no one sees anything they are blind to what they don't understand. (wow thats deep) 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whats it been like the past few days? 1) living hell 2) very depressing 3) astonishing 4) best time of my life 5) worst time of my life 6) happiness for other people 7) sadness for me... :\ what can i say its been a weird few days 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh My Gosh. Abra Your right! how could i have possibly forgot all that? who could forget me you and aria trying to see who could stand on the lane dividers longest in the bee infested waters of my pool and how could i for get the soggy grass at the park where we sterted digging holes with the "dig a ma jig thingys" oh and yoiu and me running away and table dancing in the dark. and returning so we could steal the swings which you promptly fell out of.(hehe thats was great im sorry) and finally we we leave the park the boys hitting a car while we hid from them (whoops!)and then us stalking the huge castles in my neighborhood. o and i forgot to tell people to bow down to princess abra when i talked about the movie....hmm well thanks for the reminder hun and to bad those didnt make it into the original paragraph story... 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       haha so tonight was crazy cool. it started out with aria and travis showing  up at my work again and us deciding to go to my house. then we decide to make it a full on movie night and we order ginas get lord of the rings and get travis playstation cuz my vcr is broken. But it wouldnt work so we try and watch it on my comp....i dont have a dvd player and i so thought i did. so abra comes takes travis to his house to get his tv and speakers. meanwhile aria and i start to put the drinks in the fridge only to discover when we try and open the box that there was one leaking. so into a trashbag it went and i go change into real clothes so we can go return it as i am walking down the stairs aria says "do we have the reciet and do we really need to return it for one can" hmm good point so on with refridgerating the Slice. travis and abra come back and we hook up the tv and start to watch...5 mins later we decide that we wanna go to the jacuzzi instead because we all saw the movie and we wernt rally in the mood. aria and i both have swimsuits abra borrows  one and travis is stuck cuz he doesnt have any and he looks like he is in an asian gang with his jeans and white tshirt. Hehe so leaving the pool i take my key and abra and we go outside the gate(which opens from te inside without a key but we tell them you need a key. so aria hops the fence and me and abra sit there laughing and tell travis to just open the door and walk through. haha what fun.so back from pool. we still have 45 mins to spare so we go to the playground. weeeee! the slide was fun the grass was mushy and the boys were trying to scare us.lol abra and i run off and hide up the hill so the boys cant see us. then they lock us out of the car... :( boo hoo so they drive off and we run the oppisite way. 10 mins later we are at my house and aria has to go home. ho hum i go inside and abra and trav are about to leave. but trav comes to my door and we decide to hit up some cha for tea yummy. we arrive get tea and start to play scrabble. hunger strikes i get me some super spicy chicken yum me and abra eat that all up mmm it was good. i woop some ass at scabble hell yea i got 211 :) then its time to go home and me and travis make the skript for a really bad porno...to be continued the next time anything interesting happens...o and abra we do all have to go to a kareoke bar sometime soon and shrek 2 on tuesday! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wow. My respect dropped so much in one sentence. I cannot beleive it. I am stunned. allright well wow. i have you in my prayers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yea i havnt written in here in a long time. im sorry! lots of stuff has happened but im to lazy to writ eabout any of it except that i am now officially a senior! yay class of 2005! this year should be good if not fast. nothing else really to say. Oh summer will be awesome! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i forgot to tell everyone to go read invisable monsters kevin has it and im reading it in poli sci and its awesome so far if you like sex and drugs lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       haha recap of the past few days... -friday work yuck then julies house to sleepover -saturday more work then i forget if i did anything -sunday the fourth of JULY!! yay that was super fun whole day was good morn afternoon evening and late late night good -monday Disneyland a lil sunburnt but excellent other than that. get home 1 am fight with  mom till like 2 30 get grounded till sunday but i have work this weekend anyhow so whatever... there u go aria i updated it for you now everyone can know partically nothing about my weekend cept for like a lil tidbit here and there which doesnt explain very much!! ha muahs to everyone 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Catchy 90's song by  Stroke 9   I  L-O-V-E  it&nbsp; :)  &nbsp;   Little Black Backpack   &nbsp;  I&nbsp;know it, it's a shame a  shame I can't show it I see it, I can see  it now but I'm so far below it  &nbsp;  don't wanna talk about it I say why  not don't wanna think about it I say  there's got to be some good reason  for your little black backpack up,  smack, turnaround he's on his back  &nbsp;  &nbsp;don't want to tango with you I'd rather  tangle with him I think I'm gonna bash  his head in and this shouldn't concern  except just don't expect to get  your bloody black backpack back  &nbsp;  I feel you, yes I can what about that  don't you understand and I sense you,  its something sensual but its less than I  planned  &nbsp;  (CHORUS)   you're trying to find a reason for the way you feel  tonight you're mind is lined with layers of lead have  you heard one thing that I've said    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       dude its been like a week O M G!&nbsp; just kidding so i have what 2 days of summer school left yay! so happy then its of to FLorida and north carolina for miss mads over here.&nbsp; yep yep&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;hmmm so go to my myspace&nbsp;  urlLink http://profile.myspace.com/users/5490063    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>