<Blog>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wednesday, January 28, 2004 Â  And the storm continues... Last week my sister called me (she lives in Arlington) and had me to talk to a guy on the phone. He was Chinese and didn't believe that a white girl like myself could speak Chinese, too. Well, I was busy so I cold Chinese Boy to IM me. It turns out that he didn't have IM, so he downloaded it just for me. (All together now: aaaaawwwww). He sent me a picture of himself in a swimsuit and the boy is CUT. 8 pack, amazing abs. The works. And he likes me(of course).  Last night, I get a text from my sister's phone that reads, "Hey it's Chinese Boy. Just wanted to let you know that I will be seeing you at Spring Break." Turns out my sister invited him skiing with us. Oh, dear. That could be a disaster. I already have a harem of men up there...  - posted by Fuoco @ 9:45 AM Â  I am the proud owner of a cream-colored suede Moschino belt. I've been eyeing it since October. I was ready to buy it then, and drop a hundred bucks on it, but then I saw the black pirate belt. I went back to Neiman's yesterday and they had the belt on sale for 15$. Oh happy day, oh happy day. Also, yesterday I bought some new K2 rollerblades. Spent way too much money on them but I've been coveting them for a while. Now I can go put on cute outfits and woo the boys (like I need ANY more following me around). - posted by Fuoco @ 8:43 AM Â  More Physics Grad Boy IM:  Fuoco: So, what are you up to? Grad Boy: Reading CNN, current events. F: Oh, so that's why you're ignoring me. But it's aight, those things are more important. GB: No, you're current events, so I'll quit with CNN. Too cheezy, but too cute. - posted by Fuoco @ 8:41 AM   Tuesday, January 27, 2004 Â  Physics Grad Boy IMed me: Pysics Grad Boy: you're special Fuoco: in a good way, or in the, "oh, she's speical" kinda way? PGB: in a...i can tease her about being special because she's really something special kind of way Fouco: thanks PGB: you're welcome - posted by Fuoco @ 3:45 PM Â  The phone rings at 2:51 am... who could it be?  None other than Single Cell. What the fuck is he doing calling on Monday night at 2:51 in the morning?  Booty call, I guess. And there is no way I'll comply.  I answer the phone.  Single Cell: Do you know who this is? The conversation is followed with a bunch of "huh?" and "what?" on his part. He wants me to come party with him. There is no noise in the background. He is probably partying alone with his one eyed snake. Just my guess. I respectfully decline.  Single Cell: When are you partying? Fuoco: Wednesday. Give me a holler on Wednesday. SC: YOU give ME a holler. F: No way. If you wanna hang, you call me. SC: Fine, we'll both holler at each other. F: Yeah, but you holler first. When it rains, it pours.  I wanted to wake Mexico up and tell her, but I figured she didn't want me to get her out of bed to talk about SC. So I giggled myself to sleep. - posted by Fuoco @ 2:51 AM  Monday, January 26, 2004 Â  Band Boy is back Last night Band Boy IMed me-- I haven't spoken to him in 6 weeks: Band Boy: Hey what's up? Fuoco: Nothing much. You? BB: Same old, same old. F: Same old as in you won't accept my offers for a reconcilation? BB: I was always up for that. :) F: Then how come I was unconditionally shot down every time I asked you to hang out? BB: Circumstances. I really was busy. But I've been up since 9 recording our new album so I'm going to go to bed. We'll talk soon, allright? F: Well, Mr. Rockstar, why don't YOU IM me when you have some time. BB: Yes ma'am. Gnight. Life is good.  Yesterday I was also asked out by Law Boy and by Physics Grad boy. Life is really good. - posted by Fuoco @ 9:47 AM
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink create your own visited country map   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The guys at the liquor store (all five of them) near my work know me by name. I walked in today, and I heard of chorus, "F is here!"  They then decided I HAD to try an expensive brand of vodka. I couldn't say no to free vodka!! So, I had some... then I asked for a second tasting.   So smooooooth. If only the bottle weren't 50$... Oh, XO vodka...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't think that Homer (who does not like that nickname, so he shall henceforth be known as Mr. X), appreciated the effort that it took three drunk chicks to go to Taco Cabana at 3 am and sneak his favorite food into his house. And I don't think he liked tripping over that cone, either. Oops.  Lemme explain.   Last night, France, Red & I went out for Teacher's birthday. After buttery nipples at the house and loads of shots downtown, we were pretty tipsy by the time we left (I can always guage my drunkenness by how much I lust after Single Cell-- and last night I told him to call me, dammit!!).   We were a bit hungry, so we decided to head to Taco Cabana to get some grub, at which point I thought of Mr. X, all asleep in his bed-- prior that night I had called him and after he told me he was going to work at 6 am, my tipsy self told him I wouldn't call him anymore that night so he could get some sleep. While at TC, however, I realized that I had not promised not to go BY his house. So I bought his favorite TC food, and proceeded to find his house, with a few difficulties.  The three of us stealthily (or so we THOUGHT) crept into his house (it was unlocked), and after "aaawwwing" over cute Mr. X was in his sleep, we left the TC bag riiiight in front of his bedroom door. We stealthily crept out. As we were getting into our car, one of Mr. X's neighbors came & invited us to a kegger in his back yard. He had Dos XX, so we were enticed to go, but after taking one look into his scary, dark, empty backyard, we fled the scene (after spending 15 minutes looking for Red's lost credit card, which France found).  We took Red home- she had a quiz in the morning, and in the middle of the road on the way we spied a orange cone. We decided Mr. X NEEDED that cone for his house. He HAD to have it. After dropping off Red, LV & I made some illegal U-turns and eventually had the cone in our possession. We once again crept quietly and very James Bond-like back in Mr. X's house and placed the cone in the middle of his bathroom, right in front of the broken bathroom sink. We crept back out, quiet as mice, and went home.  Today, talking to Mr. X-- who was NOT amused or appreciative of his two gifts-- told us that both times we woke him up with our giggling our clicking heels against the wooden floor. Damn heels. I guess we weren't as quiet as we thought. I guess I shouldn't turn in that application for the CIA.  Makes me so sad that he wasn't happy with presents. :( Those were given out of drunken love. I could have kept the cone for my own home. But noooo: I decided to be altruistic and all I got was a big fat unhappy Mr. X.  Saddness...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, even though I saw my dad yesterday for all of five minutes, I still didn't get my birthday gift. I am concluding that he was seriously mad at me, so now I really don't get it. I think that I deserve one. I am a good daughter and I make him proud (or I like to think so). So, I've decided that he's gonna give me a birthday gift whehter he wants to or not. I'm gonna use his Amex (in my name) and go on a little shopping spree at the Co-op, cause he knows I buy my books there, charged to the Amex, which he pays for. I'll tell him a book came in late... instead, I'll get that TX sweatshirt I've been coveting for a while, that costs 50 bucks!!!  Go me!!  I am a horrible daughter?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone, now you can comment on the stupid shit i do on my blog, so excited, so everyone add this comment thing on your blog!!! hopefully it works, if not, pop me an email and i'll try to sort it out!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After my  horrid test this morning, I checked my voicemail. One missed call, "hi honey," --it's my dad-- "I'm in Austin, so give a call on my 4th cell phone number." ---WHat the FUCK?!? (that cussing was about his being in Austin, not the 4 cell phones).  I call him back, and it turns out both my dad and my brother are in town for a work convention. I tell my dad I was heading up to the convention to see them. My dad said that he was leaving town in 30 min, but would be back tomorrow, and could we have lunch. Fine. What about my older brother? Well, he'll be in meetings all day.Fine. Get me a pass to the convention.   A pass to the convention means free stuff, and here's a list: 25 cokes and dr peppers, 2 tshirts, dozens of pens, 6 pack of water, 6 pack of orange juice, 2 bags, 2 huge coffee mugs, coozies, key chains, 3 packs of tortillas, an industrial-size bag of chips, salad dressings, plates, napinks, cups, forks (which I have started using now that I dont have a dishwasher)... then on to the GOOD stuff- all the free food I got to sample: hamburgers, fried shrimp and chicken, quesadillas, ice cream, ice cream toppings, chips, french fries, onion rings, frappuchinos of all types, more ice cream... so so stuffed!!  AND, I got a ticket out of someone for free drinks, dinner, and dancing tonight!  Yessssss-- finally get to wear that new dress!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Now accepting applications for the Zappa Tampon Krappa sorority.   Requirements:   Must be able to party till the sun comes up  Must be willing to dance & sing any time, any where Must partake in crank calls at random hours of the night  Must want to wear big sunglasses while hiding condoms on people's front porches in the middle of the night  Must be handy with a calligraphy marker Must be able to define "cuchina"  Must be able to wear cute but painful shoes in the sake of fashion (and that includes cute but unconfortable clothes, too)  Must be spontaneous  Must want to wear amazing jewellery even if it chokes you to death   More to come...   Please contact myself, or the Queen of Spain for more details.   Zappa, Zappa, Zappa,  We're gonna Krappa, Krappa, Krappa...   ...more of the song to come when inspiration hits me... 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Darling LV/Queen of France-- your choice, forgot to mention one veeeeery small detail about Sat night.... she and Red signed my ASS! One cheek a person! And they are still there!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For all y'all that knew my dad was mad at me... he called me yesterday!!! this might not sound like a big deal, but trust me, it is. We used to talk DAILY, for the past month-ish, we've spoken only because of necessity, and that was rarely. Yesterday he called  me for the first time in weeks! (and yes, i am BIG daddy's girl!)  yipeeeee!!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From LV's blog-- whom I shall now call France...  ... got ready for DT and F and Red came over...we chilled, got ready and took a cab to Fado once again...trying to stay out of the Mardi Gras crowd. We get there meet up with Mexico and friend and the bar sucks! The guys were all old and moldy looking...it just wasn't entertaining. We go to Lucky Lounge afterwards...once again kind of a older guy crowd. I did see a guy with a shirt that looks oddly similar to a tablecloth of my mom. Left and went to Red Fez which I used to absolutely love!...it was ehh last night. I commandeered a cool paper flower that was attached to the building while waiting in line. I loved it and got comments all night about it. We danced with these fabulous black guys celebrating their friends graduation. They rocked and we finally started having some fun. We got into the dancing spirit and decided it was time to brave 6th street...well at least make a trip to CT. No surly coppers this time but Lisa and I did learn a new word from our great and worldly friend Red....cugina....how great is that. Lisa and I annoyed the group by using the word as much as possible in every sentence and in every situation all night long.... a little later the cugina expanded into a gesticulating cugina. It was great fun. We went couldnt' get into CT for free and we all refuse to pay cover. So we went and totally slummed it on 6th. Went into the Ritz and some club called Exodus. Man..I don't think there was one attractive guy on 6th last night!   (F's parenthesis-- ran into Mustang & spill boy-- i got drinks and shots and they got us in Friends- danced there a bit- okay. got to see single cell, lookin' hot as usual...)  We left before 2am to get a cab and chilled at my place trying to find an after party....thats when the prank calls started. We started calling Homer and leaving crazy messages and then it escalated to calling various people in F's phonebook and leaving them crazy messages. Once again we owe it to Red and her innovative thinking for the newly founded Zappa Tampon Krappa which is headed by Regina phalange. Well I guess we have the writers of "Friends" to thank but Kate remembered it and so we are forever grateful. We provided much entertainment for ourselves. We then went over to Homer's house making a detour to F's house. There we sifted through her fabulous jewelry and picking up a zillion condoms. The condoms were then left all over Homer's house and front porch in signature Zappa Tampon Krappa style. Alas, the night was then over for me. We all went our respective ways and except for some 5am calls I slept till noon. Homer supposedly left a message...I checked it my sleep and erased it. I have no clue what it said. Bottom line: This weekend was amazing!   more post note from F: I couldnt sleep, so when my phone rang I 5 am, i jumped at the oppurtunity to leave the house to head over to Homer's. We chilled, watched the Simposon's (like Homer ALWAYS does-- but it's funny!!) and chatted. 'round 6 everyone was passing out, and i was heading home when I was coerced into sleeping over at homer's again. he was right though, why drive home at 6, might as well sleep a few hours there...  now, am trying to write a 8 pp spanish paper- but i am easily distracted...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, went out with LV and a bunch of her friends. Met up, drank wine, went to Fado. Been SO LONG since I'd been there so I'd forgotten how many non-skanky guys there are. Examples, a whole Fire Squad. Yum! We drank a bit (not much) danced in front of the dj who took all our requests, and chatted it up. Started chatting to the dj's friend- and Irish boy who decided to show us his nipples three times by midnight. They were both pierced. Great. Irish Boy was very cute, albiet a bit skinny, but I decided to give him a kiss as we left. I went in for the kiss, and came at me with his tongue. When you first kiss someone, don't stick your tongue in her MOUTH. I was a bit repulsed. So I left without making a big effort to have him get my number. (LV meanwhile managed to chat up Floppy Hair Boy for a drink, and she spent some time with a tall hot firefighter. Go her!)  Headed over to 6th to check out the Mardi Gras debauchary, but I was unimpressed. Crossing the street towards Coper Tank, I put my hands in the air in a 80s punk rock style, and sticking my tongue out. A cop came and grabbed my arm and I asked me if I was intoxicated.  Me: I am NOT intoxicated, give me a breathalizer test, cause I've only had ONE beer" (spoken with attitude). Cop: "Intoxication means when you're in public and you're trying to endanger yourself. You were walking across the street with your hands in the air, acting like god, not looking at oncoming traffic..." Me: "But I did look at oncoming traffic, I saw the cars were way beyond that stoplight..." --cop cut me off Cop: "No you weren't! Quit arguing unless you want me to arrest you..." Me: I said okay, and walked off... ...looking for LV-- she was drunk, and was hiding while I was yelled at. haha! I'd done the same thing in her place!   One of the best parts about the evening--  I was wearing my 12 foot long (REAL) pearls so whenever guess offered to give me their beads, I could shake my head and tell thim I'd take them "only if they're real."  We decided to be good and catch a cab home pretty early, 1:30. But at 2:30 I got a phone call from Homer. He had a bunch of his out-of-town friends staying with him for the weekend while they partied it up for a bachelor party. He asked me to bring over toilet paper & beer. I happily complied. House full of tipsy guys and ME. Sure thing!   I headed over and stopped at a red light-- it's around 3 am and no one is on the road so I decided to run a red light, as I often do cause I get impatient. As soon as I made the illegal left turn, a cop car comes into view... slowing down, maybe... yes, definately slowing down... SHIT! make first right turn possible, then left turn, then right turn, hoping cop can't find me. Finally get to Homer's house and run inside and hide.  Got to Homer's house and one of the boys kept on staring at me and telling me I was cute (which was nice, considering I looked pretty skank with unwashed hair, sweaty from dancing, and smelly bar clothes, but hey, I'll take it!). We hung out and drank beer, me sitting all cuddled up to Homer until the Boys started quizzing me about Homer. I spent an long period of time being grilled about my "relationship" with Homer (since when have we had a relationship!). "Sooooo... y'all dating?" "No." "Y'all sleeping together?" "No." "No sex?" "Nope". "Friends with Benefits?" "No again." "So what are y'all?"  I looked at Homer. "We're friends, I guess." They didn't buy it and kept quizzing me all night long.  Homer had to work at 9 am, so he went off to bed. I followed soon thereafter, with snickers coming from the Boys.... for no reason, I might add!  I crawled in bed with him, and he was fast asleep and even though asleep, his arms were open and ready to cuddle. It amazes me how much I hate being touched when I sleep, and yet I like being pressed up again H.  I --finally-- passed out and I left in the morning right before his alarm clock went off...
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The day you are at your most tired, with no sleep, with dark bags, with no makeup, with ratty clothes you found on the floor, are the days you see EVERYONE that you want to look glam for.  Yesterday ran into an old high school crush and I looked like shit. I had forgotten his name (hey, it was a while back) but at least he remembered mine. I just wish that I hadn't been looking like hell.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I get a voice mail:  "Flaminiiiia (pronounced very Italian-y)... this is the Vegetable. Calling to see if you're still mad at me. Call me back, home phone XXX-XXXX, and cell XXX-XXXX."  For those of you that don't know who The Vegetable is... he's the DJ at a local hotspot. Been super-nice to me: on my bday let about 15 of us in for free, guys & girls. He told me that he'd call me to take me out to dinner, but he didn't. So last weekend, when we were out, I went by the club and told him off-- kinda kidding, but he took it seriously.  Haha. But I don't wanna go out with him now that he's called. Is that bad?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, when my friend ... I'll call her Paris was in town we went shopping and spent waaay too much money. After a few mojitos at happy hour, we decided to go roller blading. The sun was setting as we drove to the park so we pulled over to a parking lot and skated there. Didn't fall, but after about 45 min we were ready to go home.  Watched Le Divorce at Homer's House- it was okay. Paris went home and I was bored so Homer came over to my place. I showed him pictures of places I'd been to and we chatted till the wee hours of the morning. He fell asleep, attached to me, all cuddled up. I just lay awake. I can't sleep if someone touches me... so I don't why I let him do it. I guess it IS nice to be held once & a while. Either way, he cracks me up & I enjoy talking to him. This morning, I was supposed to be at work at 10 am... I called in with some excuse and didn't get there till after noon. Oops. Really tired today, but till head over to kickboxing. Hope I can gather some energy to keep my eyes open and not get kicked in the face again!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay folks, a friend decided to give the link to my old blog to people who dont like me, so I deleted it all and changed the url.  Maybe a bit harsh, but I felt the need to not let this person read my blog anymore.  I don't care how many of your friends read my blog, just make sure that they are NOT one of the guys I gripe about in my daily musings!  Thanks!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So annoyed...  It's amazing how much Physics Boy is annoying me lately. Another dude from Friendster annoyed me so I blocked him from my AIM, looks like Physics boy is treading thin waters. Here's an example...  Me:    nutella rocks my world Me:    in a minute i'll have finished a WHOLE jar Him:    maybe i can steal some from your lips (side note from me.. EWWW) Him:    :) Me:    no way Me:    it's all for me Me:    totally hoard it Him:    what if i bought a jar Him:    and put some on my lips Me:    i'd prob eat the jar before you got a chance to touch it Me:    dont mess with me and my chocolate   Am grossed out about that comment... should I be, though?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good times with the pliers...  The best part about this weekend (other than the AMAZING snow fight that all of 6th street partook in) was finding a pair pliers in some club. I LOVE my pliers, & I LOVE the fact that I now OWN pliers. I will have to find things to ply. Such fun. But anyways, I kept them in my front jeans pocket, so everyone could see them (got some funny looks), and when I grooved to the music, they grooved with me. Then the bouncer of some club saw them and told me I couldn't have them cuase they were a weapon. I went to the owner of the bar, and told him, "I am a black belt in Tung So Doo. My  body  is a weapon, so those pliers will do jack shit of trouble in your club comared to ME." And I got my pliers back. I walked around all night pinching people in the ass with the pliers, and they would turn around and get mad at me, but I would exclaim, "Hey! Don't blame me, it was the  pliers~ "
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, Farouche called me and asked me if I wanted to go see an Ice Bats(hockey) game. The Ice Bats sucked and lost, but we had a blast watching the hot men skate around and get into fight, watching the coach break the plexiglass, and yell, "Knucklepuck," and, "Show us the Flying V!!" Good times.  We left the game, headed home and immediately started taking shots of pure liquor: crown, amaretto, and finished off my bottle of Tuaca. We thought that if we were hammered enough, we wouldn't feel the FREEZING-ASS weather, snow, rain, sleet. Oh, yeah, great plan.   Homer came and picked us up, we were pretty hammered. Ran all over 6th street, club to club, as usual. Went to see Lil Cap'n Travis-- Homer's favorite band. Then we realized it was snowing. So we ran out on the street and Farouche and I had a snowball fight. We ran back up and got Homer and as soon as he stepped outside, we pummeled him with snow balls. The bars closed so EVERYONE was outside partaking in a city-wide snowball fight. Farouche and I were SOAKED to the bone, but we weren't cold. Interesting. Very interesting, indeed. Homer was cold, but we still kept throwing snow on him.  Ran into Mustang Boy and ex-Spill Manager. Threw snowballs with them. I think I kissed ex-Spill Boy, but a bit fuzzy. Ran into more rugby guys that fell in love with Farouche, so they got her number and called her all night long. On the way back to the car, Farouche & decided we had to pee so bad, that we did it in an alley way, next to Homer's car. While we were peeing, Homer was throwing snow on us. Hard to pee that way!  Homer took us back home, at which point, sober as I was, I hopped in my car with Farouche, went to Homer's house, picked him up, then went back downtown to pick up Mustang and Spill. Drove them to their houses. Mustang picked up Farouche and bodyslammed her into the snow and made out with her. We hung out at their house for 10 min before our wet clothes finally started feeling wet and cold. As we left, I gave ex-Spill boy a few kisses. Don't really know why, but it seemed appropriate at the time.   Dropped Faraouche and Homer off at home, and 40 miles later, plastered, the city covered in white, and no accidents, I got home, too. Tore my wet jeans off, and slept in my coat, scarf and shirt. That's the way to do it, baby.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, a couple of days ago, Physics Grad Boy & I were IMing:  Me: I am tired, just got back from kickboxing. Boy: Where do you work out? Me: Up north. Boy: At __________? Me: Yeah, how did you know that??? Boy: I used to work out there.  Good to know. So yesterday I asked my boxing instructor about Physics Boy, and instructor said he was a nice guy. Turns out he's a black belt in Tang Soo Do. I was impressed. So, last night, after movie night with Mexico, I went to a bar with LV. After seeing some old friends from freshman year, I decided to call up Physics Boy and invite him for a beer.  He shows up-- cute. Doesn't make give me butterflies in the stomach like Jersey/Blue Shirt Boy, but he's nice and cute. Tall. He kept on looking at me and telling me how cute I was. I just told him that flattery didn't work on me, and he insisted it wasn't flattery. Meh. It just made me uncomfortable  He's cute, but this weekend I'm still gonna give Jersey one LAST phone call, cause he makes my knees knock together...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I LOVED Spain's recap of my birthday weekend, so I am posting here. Too cute!   This weekend was also F's bday! quick summary of bday activities: "wrapped" apartment with scandalous items, Changs!! with rockstar parking and without great fortunes (we had the waiter bring us heaps of fortune cookies until we found acceptable destinies. this ended in piles of cookies we couldn't eat because of all of the amazing chocolate cake, lots of cellophane, and stacks of little papers), downtown revelry, LAST CALL! (as in, neiman marcus), more shopping (as in every major store in area in austin), kat takes a break, F. gives away witty presents "for the record....the only problem i have with alcohol is that i'm running low on vodka!" DJ VEG, manager matt, single cell, tiny, drink bouncer (dunno name), other bartender friends...ending in five girls locked out of apartment at three in the morning (so we crash at F's friend's house....all i have to say is elimidate!!! oh, and a tshirt that is currently being held for ransom) Angies Restaurant, a visit to the capitol....
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I LOVED this, from  urlLink Noella's blog   check it out, she's too funny...  ThreeÊSituations in Life where it's OK to Lie:   1. You're busy making your seven bucks an hour at a job that you are completely over-qualified for, and an applicant eager to get a good word in withåÊyour boss asks, "So, how do you like working here?" You say, "I totally love it, it's awesome," and go back to arranging bra foundations. What you really want to say is, "Look, bitch, my feet hurt, the damn ligting in this place makes me look awful, and I have to listen to a softcore porn soundtrack all day, and later, some old woman will ask me how her bra fits and I will have to stare at her saggy boobs and saggy stomach while trying to keep a straight face and hoping to GOD that I don't look like that in twenty years."  2. You have unprotected sex with your boyfriend and he's SUCH a gentleman that he decides to be an man and give you forty bucks for the morning after pill.Ê However, you are broke.Ê And you are HUNGRY. And yourÊSUV has no gas.Ê And a tank of gas and McDonald's sounds sooo good.Ê And maybe a happy hour or two.Ê So, you leave it up to fate and when he calls to make sure you bought and took the pill, you say, "Sure, baby, I took care of that this morning."  3.This one's easy:ÊMother:Ê"So, how'd your job interview go?" Child: "Oh, it went really well.Ê I don't know if they'll hire me, cause there are ALOT of qualified cantidates...but maybe the other three I have lined up this week will pan out...oh, and can you send me a hundred dollars, cause I really need a job and I have NO gas in my car, so I can't get to all those wonderful job interviews unless you give me money!" Haha...job....interview....riiiigt. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a blast for Part II of my birthday weekend. After a fabulous lunch at PF Chang's (with party hat, noise makers, flowers, a tiara, chocolate cake and a free bday lunch for me :) - it was delicious) we shopped all day at the mall.   Went out (there were 6 of us in the core group) and everyone met up with us. Good times. After hours of dancing, we headed back to Mexico's place, only to find out we were locked out!! So, I called Homer and told him we were locked out (hint, hint) and told us to come to his house. So, five of us crashed at his house, and the poor boy had to work this morning at 8 so he let us stay at his house all morning and sleep in. Love you Homer, you're the best!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, as soon as Ireland made it to town, we went out (accompanied by Farouche). I called my Cute Boy in Blue Shirt (whom I'll now call  Jersey ) and told him to meet up with us. Everywhere we went, I got my free shots, and everywhere we went Farouch knew people. She was one popular gal. When we made it to Copper Tank, the DJ there had to rap my name, of course, and he gave us free coozies with his name on him (he's sponsored by Miller Light). He told me he'd call me and take me out this week for dinner. Not attracted to DJ, but he's funny. We headed over to Friend's (where of course, my luck, Single Cell was working the door) and drank a lot there (the DJ called my name out) and the owner bought us all lots of shots. Ireland was dancing it up with Dude that she met at CT, that found her at Friends.  Finally, Jersey shows up, and he was cuter than I remembered. We talked for under a minute and he had to go next door to find someone. I told him I'd call him with postparty plans. So... I needed postparty plans-  fast ?! Farouche TELLS one of her guy friends that we're having a postparty at his house. We leave the bars, go to Farouche's, get booze and head over to the postparty (which turned out to be us three girls, and three guys). Jersey calls and he comes over with another dude. He's toooooo cute. They leave soon (or what seems like it, but it was probably 3:45 am), but Jersey says he'll call the next day....  I get home to find that my house has been wrapped!! There are streamers, silly string, balloons, condoms, and a furry leopard all over my door and windows. Too cute!  The birthday weekend has taken off well indeed. And tonight, Spain is coming to town and we are gonna rock the house.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Night Out with the Guys   Last night I cooked dinner for two of my brother's friends. Good food, good company. I dashed out of their apt at 11:30 ran home and changed and met up with Mustang Boy and two of his friends. He told me they are were at Random Bar. I was walking in the bar, when I noticed the door man was none other than Single Cell. Dammit! He told me he had called me and left me a voice mail last week and seemed pissy that I didn't return his phone call. All I could say is, "Have you seen Mustang Boy?". So, I ditched Single Cell to hang out with Mustang.   While we were drinking and shootin' the shit, a cute boy in Blue Shirt walks by. I wanted him baaaad. So, I walk around the bar, casually walk by him and tell him that he needed to smile. When I told him that, a smile spread across his face.  Fast Foward to four bars and numerous drinks later, Blue Shirt Boy is the same bar with me again. Mmmm.... I say fate. I walk by him again and tell him that he's still not smiling. He told me that whenever he sees me, he smiles, and that I catch him at all the wrong time.   Homer and his friend call me to see if they cam meet up. When they get there, I magically procure four Dos XX for them. They were thrilled.   Blue Shirt Boy walks by again, and talks to me-- I forgot what he said, but the next thing I know is that we're making out. Oops. In front of Mustung Boy and his two friends, and Homer and his friend. But aparantly NO ONE saw. WTF?? So, cute boy gets my number, asks about postparty plans and he says he'd call.   I get home, 2:30ish, Homer calls. I was bored and not tired, so I went to Taco Cabana to get us food. While talking to Homer, Mustang Boy calls. I switchover to find out that Mustang Boy wants me to give him head. When I laugh and say no, he starts getting mad at me. This pisses me OFF. Whatever happened to us being FRIENDS?!?! So, while I'm yelling at Mustang Boy, I get another call waiting. This time, an unknown number. Blue Shirt Boy called!!!!! I told him that I already had plans tonight for postparty shit so I couldn't hang out, but that I call him the next day.   Food in tow, I head over to Homer's house. We drink beer, eat Taco Cabana and watch the Simpson's. Around 4 am, I get another phone call.... it's SINGLE CELL with the booty call. When I tell him that I'm not going over to his house, and that he can't come to mine (I wasn't there) and that he can't come to Homer's house, he gets pissy. I told him I'd call him the following day (yeah, right).   I called Thailand at 3 am, then again at 4 am. Oops. A bit hammered. Hope I didn't wake her up!!!  Homer and I hang out-- laughed my ass off. We passed out on the couch around 5 in the morning, and I came home and went to bed around 5:40. Ugh.   Just a little tired. Must rest up before tonight, because my party posse is coming to town!!!!   Four booty calls in one night-- must be a record! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friendster is Assaulting Me...  What IS it with all these guys messaging me from Friendster. Here is the newest one:   Since partying like an eighties rockstar is one of my favorite hobbies, and since you are connected to two of my more off the hook crazy friends who don't even know each other, I had to see if you wanted to go out and tear shit up or just chill and chat. email: XXX@yahoo.com, mobile# 512-917-XXXX   I mean... I checked his profile out and he is 35. On my profile it, I am 22. Uh, I don't think so...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Am SO tired of Physics Grad Boy being so nice, no matter WHAT I say (I am so spoiled; listen to me, "Wah, wah, wah"). Example:  Physics Grad Boy: that's sweet of you Me: what can i say? I'm being magnanimous-- i'm not usually sweet Physics Grad Boy: i know Physics Grad Boy: you're spicy Physics Grad Boy: like thai food Me: more like a bitch Physics Grad Boy: and a hot one at that  Will  he  ever  give up!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just put 100% pure silk sheets on my bed. Aaaaahhhhhh, luxury. I had them made in China and never bothered to use them. But, oh lord are they silky...  Now I wanna booty call someone just to hook up on them.  No booty call... must study for first test tomorrow. First test of the last semester of my undergrad career. Study. But sexy silky sheets..... must.... study....
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, since I am sitting in bed, crippled, and bored to tears, I have been terrorizing everyone's blog with random comments. And for that I must apologize. But I really am bored. And the vicodin is telling me to do strange things-- like comment on Blogs.  Anyways, whilst having ice cream with Farouche (who graciously came and picked me up) and Red, I remembered something my buddy RP (if you IM me, he's the dude on skis that I have as my buddy icon) told me in New Mexico the morning he woke my ass up at 8:30 AM to go hottubbing.  RP, "It's gonna be a beautiful day, F. Wanna know how I know? I look outside and hear the birds chirping. And somewhere in the woods there's a squirrel humping a turtle. How can it  not  be a good day?"
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was starving earlier and couldn't get ahold of any of my friends/nannies to take me to dinner to I hobbled in the kitchen to see what I could eat. In my fridge: Dr Peppers, tub of margarine, margarita mix, sweet & sour, champagne. None adequate to take with my meds. I found some rice in the cabinet and started boiling it. I somehow lost my balance, lost a crutch, fell over and in the process knocked over a glass. Dammit. I had to go put shoes on (a painful process) then sit on the ground, both legs sticking out (cause I can't bend my hurt one). Had to pick up shreds of glass, then had no where to put them since I couldn't reach the trashcan. I dragged my ass on the floor (hoping I didn't miss a piece) picking it all up. Hopefully I got 'em all.  Then I hopped back to my bed, bowl of rice & Dr Pepper in hand, no crutches. I've found you can't carry things with crutches. Hopping to my bed, however, I spilled half the rice and shook up the coke so that when I opened the can, it sprayed everywhere. Grrrrrreeeaat.  What can go wrong now?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been sitting in bed all day, miserable and bored. Went to the doctor this morning, but since I was in so much pain she couldn't examine me very well. Meh. I got more drugs, stronger ones, I hope. I want to leave my apt, but there is no way I can get more than 20 feet. Can't drive my car yet, too much pain (at least I got a handicapped sticker for when I can drive my car) and I can't go very fast with my crutches.  Life is miserable.  I wonder how I can pull off going to Cain & Abel's tonight. Must think of plan. Must also wash hair as to not scare off the whole bar with my offensive smell. I mananged to crawl into the bathtub last night (and to shave my legs so the doc today wouldn't have to touch my gross hairy legs like the poor doc last night) but I couldn't figure out how to wash my hair, which is gross. It needs to be washed. I pounded through 45 min of kickboxing last night before I hurt myself, so I got pretty sweaty...   Mmmm... back to C&A... how to get there?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you that don't know, I blew out my knee tonight whilst kickboxing. I wasn't even in any kind of a fight or anything, I was demonstrating a kick to a newcomer. I fell to the ground, screaming in pain and just had to sit there for 10 minutes, while everyone worked out around me. My boxing instructor kept on trying to pick me up, "F, I can  do  it." "Yeah, I know you can do it, I just don't  want  you to." So, I then got help off the ground, and help to sit down. I didn't move from there for 40 min. I sat on my butt and slid down the stairs, then got help from a stranger to hobble to my car, but as soon as I tried to put pressure on the brake pedal, I cried out in pain. I couldn't even fucking drive my car. The pain by now was intense and getting to my car had cost me most of my energy, so I was crying. I called Farouche to come and get me, but she didn't answer I left a sniveling voicemail. I got ahold of some people I work with, who came and got me and took me to the UT ER (haha, calling it that cracks me up). I couldn't even walk in the SSB so they had to get a wheelchair for me. Thank goodness no one was there to see. I was so embarrassed.  The doctor in the UT ER didn't do much other than tell me I hurt my knee, and after some xrays he decided I didn't break or fracture a bone. Well, whoopdeedo! He gave me a vicadin prescription, a note for a handicapped sticker, and crutches. I have to go see the sports medicine people tomorrow.  Farouche, the dear, came and got me from the UT ER and took me to get my meds. She went into HEB while I sat my pretty little ass in the car. She even got my Freebirds for me, while I waited in a corner cause I was feelings sick and couldn't walk through the line myslef. She's been a  blessing . And there was a big group of cute high school boys at Freebirds that were being cute, and cleared the crowds for me to get by. They put a smile on my (pain-filled) face.  Got back to my apartment, and have had great difficulties navigating around my apartment on my crutches: not only is my apartment tiny, but it's messy with shit  all  over the ground, so there's no space for crutches-- hangers, piles of clothes from the ski trip, books, notebooks, computer cords. It's a nightmare!  But I took my vicadin... and it's  NOT WORKING ! The pain is still there. I have to pee but I don't want to get up and go to the bathroom. The debate: to wet myself or go to the bathroom. Mmmmm...  So now I can't sleep. I can get reasonably comfortable, but the sharp throbbing doesn't cease. Damn vicadin. Please work.  Am going to try to sleep some now... wish me luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A couple of weeks ago, I gave a presentation for my thesis. The crew kept me out till dawn, and I had to get up and present at 9 am. Blood-shot eyes, hair that smelled of smoke, and a raspy voice. But I got my grade, "F's presentation was easily the best of the four that I witnessed. It was articulate, interesting, and beautifully focused. Her poise was exceptional. I would enjoy reading her thesis- and told her so. Superb job. Classy in every way." I got A's all the way down. Sweeeeeet! Goes to show that two hours of sleep and boozing it up before a big day actually can do GOOD. Who would have thought?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Buddha Boy & his friend followed us back to Farouche's apartment. We all hung out for a bit, I left early, around 3. I got a phone call around 5:30 AM from Red. True story: Buddha Boy got his car towed from Farouche's apartment. That makes three people...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The highlight of tonight was watching Farouche mug down with hot Buddha Boy. They kissed, and kissed, and kissed... and ... kissed. We all wished we had popcorn.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This site  made me laugh out loud. Hehe. compliments of Mr. Humane.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Ben's blog  cracks me up. I got  urlLink this  from his blog. So funny, I especially love the misspellings!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, since I was up, I headed out to watch the  urlLink Black's Rugby Team  play in a tournament. Mexian Boy was out there. I ignored him. He ignored me. Things are going well. Hung out with other rugby boys, especially the one who invited me out last night, the one who I have the hots for. There were so many guys out there, I had a blast just looking around.  Curls met up with me. We hung out. Funny conversation. We were talking about sports:  Curls: "Firting should be a sport. ESPN should follow  ME  around. I mean, look at poker?  And what's  with  extreme ping pong? Why is that shit extreme? It'd be extreme if the ping pong ball were covered in spikes!" Me: "Yeah, and if it hit you in the face, it'd cut off a piece of your cheek or something. I'd watch that."  ----- Later, about guys, I was talking about all our boys having nicknames, not real names, and Curls chimes in, "Yeah, if you give 'em names, it means they have souls. And they  don't  have souls." Me: "Yeah, I'm so proud, even our guy friends are picking up the nicknames. Look at Mr. Humane, he's calling his girl 'Seattle' instead of by her real name."
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday afternoon, I awoke around 5 from a groggy nap. I was late to Farouche's happy hour. She was having drinks & fondue at her place. I rolled out of bed, not really sure where I was or what was going on. I was so sleepy-- I guess two hours a sleep per night for the past two weeks will do that to you!  Got to Farouche's & started munching on the goodies. I was still confused about what was going on around me-- Farouche & Red just laughed. The fondue was excellent-- she had cheese & chocolate fondue. I ate them both in massive quantaties. But by the end of the night I was eating the chocolate fondue with a spoon. Yum!  Me, Farouche, & Mr. Humane hung out for a while. Munching on the goodies, drinking, & watching movies. After a while, my buddy Apostle called and asked us to meet up w/him at Club de Ville. We didn't  really  want to go downtown, but once we heard the Scottish burr of the guy partying with him, we happily got up, got dressed, and went downtown (the mention of free beers didn't hurt either!).   We walked out of Farouche's apartment, only to hear Red exclaim, "Where's my car?!". It had been towed. Red was a trooper and decided to go out drinking before getting her car out of jail.  Met up with Apostle & Scottish boy, who bought our drinks. Hung out, chewed the fat. Usual bullshit. Good times. Found out Apostle was fired from the bar where he worked because he was caught by TBAC drinking on the job. Oops.  A little while later,  urlLink Rugby Boy  (not to be confused with Mexican boy, aka, my latest Playboy) called & asked me to meet up. So I dragged Red & Farouche to the dive where the rugby boys hung out. At least we got more free drinks.  Went to get Red's car out of jail-- by not I am so tired that I am feeling delirious. I am falling asleep in my car, so I Thailand to stay awake. Thanks to her amusing conversation I didn't fall asleep at the wheel and turn into a statistic.  This morning, I woke up to my phone ringing at 9:45am. Dammit, what  do  I have to do to get some sleep around here? It was my mom, just calling to chat. Dammit, again.  Got up, checked my computer and saw that BW had IMed last night. Haha. It's his little brother's 21st birthday and they were partying it up! In the IM he told me to come over and party. Oops. Missed that one. So I called him and woke him up this morning. haha. Oops again.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night,  urlLink Farouche  (or France or LV, so many nicknames) and I went out. met up with lots of rugby boys and Mustang's crowd. partied like rockstars. Cheap drinks flowed like water.   urlLink mexican boy  (aka, Rugby Boy C) was downtown last night, and as soon as i saw him, i was in lust all over again. who needs love when ya got lust? Yum!  Later on that night, ran into  urlLink Jersey Boy (scroll down to Feb 7th) . 'Member him? Talk about lust? We talked for five minutes, me drooling the whole time. so cute. Even though I haven't seen him in two months, he still remembered my (difficult) name. We were going to meet up and party but when it came time to choose between Mexican Boy or Jersey Boy, I called the mexican.  met up with Mexican boy at his house after dropping Farouche off at her place.... he waited for me in his parking lot and started to undress me there. we made out the whole way upstairs to his place. I left his house at 7 am this morning. oops.  i need a nap. i went to sleep at 7 and my office called me at 7:30. so sleepy. but i guess the week in new mexico has made me used to sleeping only a couple of hours a night.  tonight, happy hour at Farouche's. i need to rest up!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out my friend Sasha's blog, aka,  urlLink Texan Smile . She's the one who was with me in New Mexico last week. She does a pretty good job of telling the whole long saga.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A couple of nights ago, RP (see picture on link to Red River below) told me that Sasha (girlfriend who accompanied me to New Mex) & I are "brutal." As in, we "wouldn't hesitate to tell the whole town that a guy has a small penis [oops] or kick him in the ass." Yeah, i guess if you look at it that way, I  am  brutal. Hot damn!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i forgot to tell y'all the progression of my days while in   urlLink Red River  (and btw, check out that link, cause the crazy dude on skis on that mainpage is my buddy  urlLink RP  I have been talking about in my blogs). We get up. Head to the Lift House (the bar at the bottom of the ski area) and have a vodka 7. Ski a few runs. Couple more vodka 7's. Maybe a shot or two. More runs. Then sunning on the deck, drinks in hand. By now, it's 4:30 pm and we haven't eaten all day. Head home, grab a bite, hop in the shower and get ready to go out (drink in the bathroom while we get ready). Go out, round up the crew for a night of heavy drinking and partying (and fortunately for me, most of the time my bar tabs are all of 2$).  We usually don't vary much from this routine. But one day, when we didn't ski, we headed out to  urlLink Angel Fire , a ski resort 45 min away to check out the snow boarding nationals. After piling all of us into a car, we stop for liquor, of course. Tall boys of Bud Light, and pints of Jose & Apple Puckers. Swig of Tequila followed by Apple Puckers, "It's like a margarita in your mouth!", as my friend Blondie says. Blondie is wiiiiild. Even by my standards. I can't party with her. She'll drink a pint of tequila, roll a joint & drive at the same time. Whenever she sees anyone get  slightly  bored, she'll say, "let's go get drunk," and we all usually follow...  What else? Oh yeah, we got to ride Harley's when we spent the night in Amarillo. That was fun...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let's see....  Reading  urlLink Farouche's  blog made me remember my St Patty's day story... it was a local's bday, so we were all wearing stickers that read, "got wood? happy birthday S!". for some reason i had one sticker on each breast (on top of a tshirt) and on on my ass. who knows why? but S' girlfriend (who ran the bar we were partying at) had green jello shots in her trunk parked out back. So all night long I kept on sneaking out and taking shots. then i decided i should share with others. so i started sneaking out cute boys and telling them they could have a shot in exchange for a kiss. i was making out every five minutes with a different boy. well, there was a couple sitting next to the back entrance of the bar, watching me come & go with different boys... she must of thought i was turning TRICKS!! haha, every five minutes with a different guy...   mmm... another random story... one morning, Friday I believe, I was sleeping soundly at 8:25 am, having gone to bed well past 3. in a haze, i heard my phone ring. i get up and answer: "F, it's RP. We're hottubbing." "I'm THERE!" And 2.5 seconds later, I was in RP's hottub, drinking my first beer of the morning...  aaah, to be on vacation!   I think I am running out of stories I guess...or maybe I am deliriously tired, having only slept 2 hours last night and driven 900 miles today... off to bed. more random stories tomorrow.  and, Thailand, the bit about the made up bfriend, didn't work so well... mmm...more on this later!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Folks, sorry it has taken so long to post an update... too busy skiing, boozing, and well... uh...other misadventures that I always seem to get myself into while in the mountains.  Let's see... where to start...   urlLink Boy  with a broken neck told he is madly in love with me. And he told me the cutest thing ever: "F, it's more than love... lemme explain... you know when you're out sledding all day as a kid, and you come home and you're tired, wet, and cold, and your mom gives you a cup of hot chocolate? THAT's what you make me feel like." What could I say to that? We talked all night long.. and I went home with someone else that night. Oops. All I have to say to my horrid behavior is... well, why do I keep on hooking up with Bartender when it's SO BAD? I have lots of theories, but the easiest thing right now to write is that I love taming the bad boy in him. Fun.  What else? Some of my buddies are building a fire truck (long story here). but anyways, they got it stuck going up Greene Peak. The snow was 8 feet deep and they couldn't get it out. They had to go up and get it while the snow was frozen, if not it wouldn't pull out through the slush. So, 8 people and 3 dogs piled into two jeeps armed with 28 thousand pounds of pulling capability between the two wenches on the jeeps at 2 in the morning, after we had been drinking since 10. We head up the mountain and some dumbass texans were stuck in the snow. theyw ere in 2-wheel drive. we pop them out of the snow. go further and further up the mountain and there was another two-wheel drive pickupstuck. We get them out of the snow. Then the tough job came. We had to wench our fire truck out. Anyways, won't bore you with the details, but we finally got it out. i helped wench, push, pull & dig snow. I was pretty proud and all the guys thanked me for my help. i had a blast! got home @ 6 am.  what else? mmm... lots of free booze. lots of skiing in short sleeves-- it's so hot, i have an awful farmer's tan! oh yeah, then last night i hooked up with Red Headed Boy. Mmmm... I haven't slept more than 3 hours a night since i've gotten here. We pulled two all-nighters two nights in row. Lots of booze, cigarettes, and hottubs helped.  Dont know what else to say now... oh, funny quote: Bar owner, talking to 2 chicks, "You two are cut off. Out of the bar." My buddy Juanito, chugging his beer, "That's my cue!"  Also, the night bartender & I hooked up, I had a talk with him. Before we ever hooked up this summer, we used to hang out. all was good. Post-hook up, he started acting like an asshole. so when i went back to his house, i told him that if he was going to be an asshole to me that to me it wasn't worth hooking up with him at all. he said he hadn't realized it, and from them on, he's been super-nice. haven't paid for a drink since i got here. oh, the joy of walking around buzzing all day.  been skiing pretty hard-core, too. with the local boys. they really push me. i fell face-first the other day, my first fall in a long time, and the snow now is so sharp, i cut my whole hand and arm. oops. i drank to make the pain go away. also, there was a race in town the other day. locals "bought" a racer, and if their racer won, they got money. the auction was to raise money for the kids' racing team in town. a couple of us pooled our money and had 60$ put together to buy my buddy RP, but we were outbid. the funny part is that he raced in a red, flowery SKIRT and my tight, white tank top. When it came time to announce the winners that night, it was funny. "Best female time, RP, come and get your award!" haha.  i'll quit boring everyone with my mountain stories. time to go drink anyways!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Talking to Ireland on IM. Background: a boy from  urlLink Friendster  messaged her today, and another cute boy is emailing her. So many boys all at once!  Me: Ireland, when it rains it pours! Ireland: How is it pourin' everywhere and i am still looking around trying to toss out my virginity like old bathwater  God, Ireland cracks me up. Kinda like the time some guy didn't return her phone call (or some simular scenario) and she busts out with, "Who cares?! He ain't the STAR of my SHOW!"   More IM conversation, 11:35 pm.  Me:	what is UP with these guys lately?? Ireland:	you just need a fresh crop Ireland:	these fields are plundered Ireland:	hehehe youre scarlett ohara in the field Me:	HAHAHA Ireland:	"i shall never be hungry again!" Ireland:	i knew that girl wasnt talkin about no radish  Come back to Austin, Ireland!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Both these voice mails are from Mustang Boy. First on from Friday, second one from Saturday. They cracked me up, so I had to transcribe them here:  "F you sexy, SEXY bitch. Ooooohhhhhh. I wanna do dirty things to you & your friends. My friends and your friends.... hey, formula! That's what I'm talking about. Call me back. Seriously. We're fucked up. We're gonna go eat. we're partying. the party's in my mouth. everybody's coming. i'd love for you to make it, to come... in my mouth. call me"  "F, your dirty answering machine sucks dirty red-headed balls. god i wanna be in your mouth right now. this is M, & R, & R. fuck it, we're all here! 4's a party. contrary to popular belief 3 is NOT a crowd, 4 is a party, biii-atch! can you take 4 alone? can you take 4 alone?!?!? [radio gets loud] okay, okay, i'm kidding, i'm so drunk. honestly, i wanna fill your girl up like a dirty little...like a crazy little turtle. i wanna fill your girl J up like a turtle. i wanna deposit MASSIVE semen! i'm just kidding. i thought we were gonna fuck tonight--  me, you & M. what's the deal? you pussed out. and you talked your girl into leaving. you ALWAYS do this. so next time you call me and say 'i've got some hoes and you wanna party and shit', it's CRAP. i don't believe you.  next time i want $100 deposit. cause now me & M are gonna jerk each other off... to a pool game, that we're both gonna loose cause  R's da shit. jesus, where am i going with this? come over, it's an orgy and bring your friend J. her black friend was kinda cool, but my dick is SO much bigger. i'll fill all your fucking trash cans up. call me"
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night J was still in town, so we headed DT with Red. Good drinks (free drinks). Albanian smoker boys in black, and cute Bartender Boy @ Acquarium givin' me free drinks. Rugby Boy C shows up. We hang out, we go somewhere else. Dance, chat, drink.  Head home. Drop Red off. On the way back to my place we see a cone. I couldn't resist. BW is being so cold now, I'd thought I might as well annoy him more, just cause I can. So we get the cone and drop it off on his porch. J & I laughed, at least. Doubt he will.  My phone rings @ 2:30ish. Booty call from Rugby Boy C. J goes to sleep & I head over to C's house, beers in tow. He lives 5 blocks away. I find his apt, park my car, hand him the beers, lock my car & start walking to his apt. Then I realized I didn't have my car keys. Shit! I had locked them inside the car. Just my luck.   I call the lock people, "Uh... hi, I locked my keys in my car. Can y'all send someone out. [then, under my breath,] I am so retarded." Lock guy, "Ma'am. You are NOT retarded. Don't say that." Me, "Okay, I'm stupid." Lock Dude, "Ma'am, you're not stupid. You made a mistake, everyone makes mistakes." I just roll my eyes (they stop rolling when I find out that it's gonna cost me 25$ to have my car unlocked).  Thank god I didn't lock the beers in the car. I start drinking. A bum walks up, "Hey, can I have a beer." Me, "Sure thing. Hey can you unlock my car?" Bum, "I'm not a car theif!" Me, "I didn't say you were a car theif. But do you have any friends that ARE car theives?" Bum, "Uhhh, I can make some calls." I bust out laughing.  Finally get the car unlocked, we head to C's apt to "watch a movie." The Big Lebowski was on for exactly 3 minutes before the make out session started, 2 minutes later we were naked in bed. Can't even tell you how gorgeous C is. 205 pounds of pure muscle. Mmmmmmmmmm. We played for hours, till dawn, till he fell asleep and I snuck out to go back to my own place.  I think I'll keep this one around for a while cause he gets five stars and two thumbs up. Definately worth the 25 bucks it cost to unlock my car.  Yum!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, my girlfriend J came in town last night. We started drinking at home and hopped in a cab already tipsy. Bar hopping, as usual, we met up with Mustang Boy and his crew, and J knew some people in town. J was flirty with one of her boys, and I started get flirty with one of Mustang's friends. Don't know how it happened but he & I started making out. After the makeout session (where I managed to spill my Vodka 7 all over us-- yeah, the kiss was that good) I found out that he was... drumroll...NINETEEN!!!! HAHAHAHA!!!! More makeout sessions followed (and J had a couple of her own to), and I vaguely recall kissing Mustang Boy & Ex-Spill boy. Mmm... And I remember Mustang announcing to the world, that I had "the best rack ever." Thanks. We hung out at Spill after it closed, till 3 or so, and stumbled into a cab to come home. Not too much damage done.  Today, made some rounds, said hi to people I havne't seen in a while. Managed to catch BW at home, so I went by to say hi, and I finally got to meet his roommate (it was the roommate's bed we all crashed in when we were locked out of my apt) and drumroll here too.... the roommate was totally CUTE!!! yum!  Nap time! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, after a quiet beer with the ladies at Crown & Anchor (conversations about bidets flowed with the beer) I headed to bed. I was thrilled to be going to bed before 2 am. But lo and behold the one night I wasn't out partying I got three booty calls.  Call #1- Random rugby boy. When he found out I wasn't downtown, he was disappointed. 2:20 am  Call #2- Friend in Colorado. Am I am going up there on Sunday. Nope. 2:40 am  Call #3- I was mid-dream so I didn't hear my phone ring. Mustang Boy. I checked my voice mail, "F, you sexy, SEXY bitch!! I wanna do dirty things to you. Call me. We're fucked up. We're partying... The party is in my mouth. I'd love for you to come... in my mouth. Call me." 3:30 am   Haha!!! That last voice mail cracked me UP! Haven't hung out with Mustang in a while...  Then, this morning, at 9:01 am. Friend from College Station. "F, did I wake you up?" 3 seconds later, it took me a while to focus, "Nah, naaaah, I was ... uh.. I was awake." "So, watcha doin' tonight?" [In my mind: I FU***** 9 AM on Friday, like I know what's going on!!]. "Dunno, why?" "Well, what if I came to Austin to play?" "Sure, call me later," and I hung up on her (oops) and slept two more hours.  Joy oh joy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, Red & I had planned for happy hour at The Ditch @ 5, dolla' margaritas. yum!I picked her at at 5 till 5, and it took us HALF and hour to get from 24th street to 6th street. damn austin traffic. we finally reach The Ditch only to find the parking lot FULL and no where to park. the place is so full people are spilling out of, already drunk on MY 'rita. damn them. damn them ALL.  so we went to Saba's. mmmmm... Mango mojitos saved my day.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I put a small post up about our wild Sunday Night with the Hockey Boys. Farouche/France did a better job on her blog, so I am stealing some of her material.    Sunday night: Our plan was to chill downtown at the Blind Pig..listen to some karaoke and drink a couple of beers...totally chill. Well there was no karaoke but a cover band who played some good songs (I love Roxanne...maybe its the harlot in me.). The only cute guys in the place were sitting right behind us in the booth. I was telling F how I thought one of them was kinda cute and kept on glacing over to them. Funny thing is that as time went by...more and more of them kept showing up and hanging out at the table. F got up to get us another drink and I caught the eye of one of the boys and started a very superficial conversation.. (ex: Me: Hey Guy: Hey Me: Nice music to chill to Guy: Yeah its pretty cool Me: I've never been here before on a Sunday Guy: Oh yeah? Well this is my second time to come here Me: Cool Guy: Yeah.  And it goes on for another minute or two in that same way. Meanwhile F meets other cute guys in the group and strikes up a convo with them. She lures them over to our table with her feminine arts and now our table is no longer a guyless group. We chat and drink with the guys a bit and find out that majority of them are from Canada. I talked for a bit with a frenchie from Montreal (gorgeous accent!). We also found out that we've just met a huge bulk of the players for the IceBats. (Yea! US!) This includes the very limber and jaw dropping goalie. It was fun. One cutie kept on telling me how cute I was...very flattering. We gave our numbers out (just in case). At 2am they invited us over to their place but we decided it was good time to end the great evening. F decides it would be funny to go and bother BW and so we head over there. He and his roommie sleep through our raid...we grab condoms and candy and jet. As I'm heading over to drop F off...hockey boys call me and we decide that ehh what the hell? We head way down south drink a couple of beers with them and then jet. The guys were total gentlemen and didn't make any grossly forward moves.... Well actually the guy I initially started talking to started getting a little touchy feely at the end but that was cool with me. We head home and get into bed at 5am with plans to meet up with the guys Monday night.   Thanks for the recap Farouche/France!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'Member how I said I was going to go shopping at the Co-op with my dad's card? Well, I had a better idea. Amazon.com. Who--hoooooo!! I told my dad that I got some books off Amazon for school and instead bought a bunch of books that I had been waiting for a while to get. So excited. Happy birthday to me!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I had an arm full of wine at the grocery store. I swiped my card to pay, the dude ID-ed me. I'm cool with that. But then, this snot-nosed, pimply-faced TEENAGER told me he couldn't sell me alcohol because my ID is bent!! "TBAC rules." Well, FU** TBAC and give my damn wine!! I called the manager, who, of course, let me spend my 40$ in peace.  Stupid teenagers trying to act all grown-up.  Kiss my ass.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Kathleen  started a "cool hotel" war. So, check out these awesome hotels in Africa I stayed in this summer:  urlLink Amboseli, Kenya ,  urlLink The Masai Mara  (where Out of Africa was filmed),  urlLink Serengeti, Tanzania , and  urlLink Ngorongoro, Tanzania .
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      France & went out last night to have a quiet beer at a pub and we ended up getting to bed at 5 am after hanging out with Austin Ice Batts team all night long. Good times. I've got a bit of a headache (when France came by to get me at 10:30, I was already just a wee bit tipsy) and we drank beer after beer after beer.  Mmmmm... Hockey Boys....
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past year or so, I've been drinking  urlLink Lunchboxes  (real name is Wiscon Lunchbox, I've found).Here is the how-to. Also a very good breakfast drink because it contains orange juice. This website tells you to shoot it, but I don't.  Try one!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My most heart-felt congratulations (aka, snaps & sparkles) to Joe Fradella, long time friend of mine, who has managed to put up with me for five years now, for making the  urlLink USA Rugby 7's team.  In two weeks, he'll be flying off to Hong Kong & Singapore. [Notice the envy in my voice]. We'll be following every step, Joe. Good luck!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My thesis presentation went GREAT! The prof-- a man that I heard about & almost revered for so long-- told me wonderful things about my presentation and work. He even asked me to drop him  a copy of the final product in May.  Slept three hours last night. I should have stayed home, but France *twisted* my arm into going out last night. Nap time...  I'll leave you a quote from my thesis, by the late  urlLink Bruce Chatwin : "Travel doesn't merely broaden the mind. It makes the mind."
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lemme set the scene. There is Random Bartender that i have the hots for. I was discussing with France how I should approach the subject with him:  Me: "I wanna hook up with him!" France: "You need to let him know you wanna HOOK UP!" Me: "Well... what do I say?" France: "I WANNA HOOK UP!"  Ah, the advice from friends is priceless...  Also, forgot to mention another funny fact from last night... As we were walking along to a bar, we ran into a guy that had peculiar pants on: the butt was cut out of them! It was his bachelor party, and lots of girls were signing his ass, so of course  I had too, too! (plus everyone knows me and ass fetishes, why I had my own butt signed a few weeks ago!!)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two things tonight:  1st, and not most important-- I am tired of always leaving voice mails and  never getting a call back; I am tired of ONLY & always hanging out during "drinking time," what ever happened to "sober time" with friends? What ever happened to dinner? Or a movie? Dammit, I am tired of the 3 or 4 am phone calls. I guess I have finally grown up...  2nd-- I saw rugby boy tonight. Many of you have heard about him for quite some time (right, Kansas City?)... Well I have had the hots for him since freshman year, but he had a girl friend whom I adored. We were all friends and hung out, so I never enticed him to cheat on her. I respected her too much. Even when they were on again, off again, I stayed away. Last spring, he bought a house. She moved in. This past December- January, they broke it off. She moved out. Permanently. He told me it was over. Period. Over. I've always felt close to rugby boy, maybe because when I was 18 he defended me against a couple of rugby guys who didn't like me, but for whatever the reason, I've always felt like I could trust him. I've told him about all my boys, conquests, & troubles. He laughed and we flirted. And it ended there.  After he and the girlfriend broke up and she moved out, he told me to come to his rugby game, after which, we would talk. I was chillin', watchin' the game, when I saw Her. The girlfriend. Dammit. She was still in his life. After the game was over, I went and said hi to boy and to girlfriend, and took off. Haven't seen him since. Usually, I call him to hang out or whatever. Haven't talked to him since mid-January. I've just been been busy and haven't though to call him...  I saw him tonight downtown. Big smiles, and even bigger hugs.  "F, I thought you were mad at me!!"  "Why would you think THAT??"  "Well... at that rugby game, when Girlfriend showed up-- well, I swear I wasn't lying to you. We were over. I guess she shows up to check on me, to make sure I'm not with another girl. She still does."  "I'm not mad, I've just been busy..."  "But you haven't called... I just thought... well, I thought you were mad..."  So tonight we hung out. I was thrilled. For a while, I forgot I was with France & Curls. Oops. I ran back to them. They had figured out I had run into a boy. They sure know me...  When we left the bar, I called him (okay, okay, it was booty call). He said he had to drive people home, but that we would have to hang out some time when we didn't have to drive all our friends home. He emphasized "hang out"... yeah right.  It's  hard to explain why I am attracted to Him. He's not attractive per se-- I guess it's that animal quality about him--  he'd fight anyone for any reason, and kick thier ass with his hands tied behind his back. But in private, he blushes, and he's sweet.  (Oh, and Thailand, this is the boy you kissed on NYE!!!-- he said that you are veeery naughty indeed! When I told him you weren't the "one night stand kinda girl", he said, "they never are, they just like playing at it!")  He said he'd come out tomorrow night... we'll see... I have my fingers crossed...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Writing about sushi made me think of yesterday's lunch. My law firm took me out to lunch to Shoreline Grill (yum!) for my birthday lunch-- a bit belated, but better late, than never.  I ate salad, entre, and a dessert, complete with two glasses of wine.  I love being wined & dined. I would have put out for a meal like that, too. Oh, well... no one to put out for...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to post about our sushi dinner on Thursday night.  The five babes of Austin met up at Kyoto for a wonderful meal. We ate lots and chatted even more. The beauty of the meal consited not only of the scrumptios food, but also the lively conversation. For once, we picked a quiet restaurant, inducive to talking. And the waiters kept brining water around way after the meal was over. It was nice sitting and talking with the girls without anyone rushing off to something.  Hopefully, we'll plan again...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just minutes ago, my phone rang. In mind, "WHAT THE F***?!?! Waaay too early for a phone call, it's 9:30!". It turned out to be one of my buddies in Red River, New Mexico calling to see when I was comin' back up there. This is one of the guy that got into a bad wreck and broke his neck, and he went skiing yesterday so he wanted to know when I'd go skiing with him again.  Made my day & put a smile on my face!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just called my friend N. When I called, she sounded like she was in tears.  Me: "N, what's WRONG?" N: "Well, my guy friend & I just hooked up & he had the SMALLEST penis EVER!" M: "Yeah, I hear ya."  And boy, do I ever. N, good luck with that one...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am getting so tired of chasing after friends. I guess the word "friend" means different things to different people. But I am annoyed by the fact that I have been calling people over and over and over to do stuff and they are ALWAYS busy! Arg! And their excuses aren't really excuses, cause they're probably real. It just gets tiring NEVER hearing a "yes," or even getting a rain check, "I am busy all this week, but what bout next Monday."  I am just tired of people who don't make time for their friends. Or am I a friend? Makes me wonder...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I broke my big toe. Or so I thought. I've been limping around all day, and finally sucked it up and went to kickboxing where my instructor poked it (damn him) only to exclaim, "Nah, it's not broken. But it's probably fractured." Grrr. And i worked out anyways. I'll leave pain for the wimps.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need a list like  urlLink this , too. Maybe about what not do in a bar... But this site made my laugh outloud...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I loved this introductoin to the book "As the Romans Do." Great book and I thought I'd post this intro here for all to read. If it catches me in a sappy moment, this brings a tear to my eye...   "Imagine being three thousand years old. Suppose by some mysterious process you had managed to avoid the limitations of mortality, and year after year you keep going, adding more and more experiences to your life story until you have no choice but to repeat them because you have exhausted all possibilities.  You are the very essence of what it means to be human. You have had more than your share of victories and defeats, triumphs and tragedies, moments of glory and those of abjection, times when you wish you had never been born, and times when you want to go on forever. You have loved and lost, have abandoned and been left behind, been rich and poor, skinny and fat, lived high on the hog and been forced to scramble for a few morsels of stale bread. You have seen it all, done it all, regretted it all, and then gone back and done it all again.  You are la citta' eterna, Rome, the Eternal City.  To live in Rome is to have the capacity to endure everything life has to offer -- moments of timeless beauty followed by torrents of ugliness, the bella and the brutta mixed together in a bowl of hot minestrone that has left nothing out, that encourages you to live life from a completely different perspective. There is no more mature place on earth, and that maturity has something to teach you. Other cities may be older, but Rome still lives its past. Walk anywhere in the city or the areas surrounding it, and within minutes you are confronted with the remains of something that could be up to twenty-five hundred years old, that functioned and was vital to the daily life of the romani....  This is Rome and the Romans who live in it, a city and a people of contrasts and effusion, a place that has lived so many different lives, in so many different epochs, that all it wants to do now is exist in eternity according to the wisdom of what it has learned. The lessons are obvious. Life is to be lived passionately, excessively, publicly -- in bars, restaurants, streets and piazzas -- applying charm and style mixed with a healthy respect for tradition. Romans have big appetites, for theatrical experiences as well as exquisite food."  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I sit at my lap top at 3 am & listen to my neighbors have sex with thier windows open (that is not disgust you hear in my voice, but envy-- lots of it) I have decided to write a few lines about tonight.  so, dinner at Chang's with France & Teacher-- some person's birthday. We don't even like her so we decided to skip out and go to C&A for dolla' beers. At C&A.. damn, she is LOUD... sorrrrry.... so, anyways, at C&A, ran into Rugby guys. They were all going downtown for some guy's birthday. Red, France, & Teacher had to work, so they passed. But Curls & I jumped on it. We headed DT with a dozen guys. And just us. The only two girls...   ... still there... louder than ever...   downtown: drank too much, danced too much, and had a great time. the birthday boy--his 21st-- puked and rallied all night long. We were all proud. I finally gave my number to Bartender at Acquarium, and gave him a smooch on the way out (in exchange he gave me two free coupons for drinks).  Went with rugby guys back to WCampus (Curls had a thing goin' on with the Aussie) & hung out. I am now home, pervertedly listening to my neighbors having sex... damn, i am deprived! I put my shooting headphones on and I can still hear them. What to do?    Random thought: In the recap of last weekend, I forgot to mention that at some point (I think Thurs night for Teacher's birthday) we all felt each other up. There were four of us gals out that night, me, Red, Teacher, & France, and for some reason we decided that feeling each others' breasts would be a good thing. I guess it was...  well, the sex next door is now over-- maybe I can get some sleep now!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This afternoon I went to the Hobby Lobby to buy a set of size 9 knitting needles. I left with 11 pair instead. OOps. They were having a half off sale, so I only spent $12, so it wasn't so bad.  I have started my third scarf. It's red, and it's ribbed- for my pleasure.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, prior to my test, my prof came up to me and asked me how I knew so much about the things he covered in his lectures. I explained about my mom & my background in art history, etc, and that being in school for 5 years has helped me cover basically all that there is to learn within the framework of spn civ and history. He was impressed, shook my hand and said he was glad to have me in class. I am a pleasure, he said. (NB- this is the class where I sit up front a & knit-- I take notes and answer questions, but I knit-- under his very nose).  Aaahh, joy oh joy.  Also, I know I am too smart for my own good when I ace a test without owning the book, going to class often, & when I do go to class, I knit, or fall asleep. I love my method of studying.  Speaking of skipping class... that's where I should be now... but it's raining... and I took a long test this morning...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      late at night, with nothing to do... made a booty call earlier, but dont think that the second party quite understood that it was a booty call.  sigh. oh well.  long phone calls with friends are always good. good advice and good friends. always by your side.  time to start my third scarf. finished my second one this afternoon (ps- they are all very different!)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored.   In the past couple of hours I  have:  Written a paper Studied for a test Answered dozens of emails IMed Updated various blogs Cooked dinner Ate more snacks Called people to warn about Spain's tonsillitis Called people to chat Made dinner plans for Wednesday Made drinking plans for tomorrow  Now what?...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday:  After work, went to Hill Country Weavers and dropped 40$ on yarn. Yes, on yarn! Can you believe it??  I spent the evening with France, and taught her to knit... I am causing more and more people to become addicted. So proud of myself. Since it was Teacher's birthday, we spent the evening with her watching a movie (and I knitted).   Saturday:  I finished my first scarf. Super thick, and super soft. I love it! Piddled around on Saturday till I had dinner with Spain when she got into town. Lovely romantic dinner at Romeo's. Odered a pitcher of sangria that was awful, so I told them to take it back (and they did).  Spain, Mexico, France & I went out to 4th street. Fado had some people there and we were in a chill kinda mood. Irish Boy/aka Nipples, wasn't there, but that's a good thing, I think, because I didn't want to see his pierced beauty for a fourth time.  After drinking, back to France's house, where we knitted for another 45 minutes. What a habit.  Right as I was falling asleep, my phone rang. 3:17 am. Dammit! Mr. X, formerly knows as Homer and as Manger. He was drunk and wanted to hang so I told him to come over. The bastard had seen us drive by the Fox & Hound and he didn't even think to call and have us meet up. He finally confessed he was with hanging out with friends-- aka, some cute girl he likes. Poor X. After hours of working on her, and postpartying with her, when she asked him to walk her to her car, she wouldn't even let X kiss her. Hehe.  Mr. X kept me up till dawn. meh.    Sunday:  Spain & I had brunch scheduled so we got our asses in gear & went to the Four Season to see how much champagne we could drink and food we could eat. Turns out we drank a lot bubbly, but passed on much of the food.  Yarn shopping for two, with full stomachs of champagne, not a good idea. I dropped another 50$, and Spain more than me. While picking out yarns, I chatted with a 7 year old girl. "How long have you been knitting?" "Three  years". I was impressed. She started as a four year old?! I have a lot of catching up to do!  That evening, went to a great Oscar Party. More chamagne, and lotsssss of margaritas. In our gift bags: tiaras, beads, feathered pens.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Received an email from Spanish prof on Sunday:   	F:    Some students have brought to my attention that you are being a disruptive influence by a constant chattering in the back.  I must admit that I have noticed it myself and my impression from students that do this is either do not take the class seriously or show little respect for the lecture or lecturer.  I do not want to embarass youpublicly so please refrain from it in the future.  I have checked your grades and have seen a slide from A to a lower B.  I would like to think that you can be a positive influence by contributing to the class. I will recognize you when you raise your hand. See you in class.   Te he he.  Ooops ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so much from this weekend, will try to post this afternoon...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I took  urlLink this test . Yes I was that bored. Posted results below because they are TOO FUNNY.  I am:  The Stiletto Deliberate Brutal Sex Master (DBSMf)      Edgy. Physical. Devastating. You are The Stiletto, of all types, the most likely to be a dominatrix and the least likely to apologize.       Sex is your object, and you have a LOT of it. Doubtless, you've figured out how easy it is for a dominant, assertive woman to have as many and whichever partners as she chooses. You're in control, you know what you want, and you get it, right there. It's highly likely you have a nice body, and it's even more likely we're getting all turned on right now writing this.   Your exact opposite: The Window Shopper: Random Gentle Love Dreamer      You're generally careful with your actions and words, but your test answers indicate you've hurt some people, drawn some blood. This means one of two things. Either you're calculating, and pain is just part of your game plan, or hurting the occasional guy is just the unfortunate, but natural, byproduct of your liberated sexual existence.   Our tendency is to believe the latter: you're willing to engage men on a basic sexual level, and clearly they're attracted to you. It's understandable that a few might get overly attached, and sometimes harshness is the only way for you to escape: you've got to cut your way out. After all, it's not emotional bondage you're looking for right now.    ALWAYS AVOID: The Slow Dancer, The Manchild  CONSIDER: The 5-Night Stand, The Bachelor   Hehe. It's fun. Take the test and lemme know what you're results are. I'm curious.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FINALLY!  The mexican called me last night at 2:26. Mexican, "Are you downtown?" Me, "Uhh, no" Mexican, " Everyone's  downtown" Me, "Uhhh, okay" Pause Me, "Just call me when you ge home"  I crawl back in bed to take a 10 min nap,but two minutes later, my phone rings again.  Mexican, "Can you help me?" Me, "Whaddya need?" Mexican, "Well, I'm on 6th & San Jacinto..." [pause] Me, "Yeah, I'll come pick you up, I'll call in a minute."  Find some decently clean clothes from the floor (I'm worse than a guy sometimes), phone rings again. "Uh, I'm at 7th & San Jac" Me, "I'm on my way"  As I'm looking for my car keys (always a feat to find in a rush), phone rings  AGAIN . I answer it, "WHAT?" Mexican, "Uhh, I'm at 8th & San Jac." Me, "Okaaaaay"  I get in my car and the phone rings   AGAIN  !! Me, "WHAT NOW??" Mexican, "I'm at 8th & San Jac. Just didn't want you to miss me. I'll make it worth your while, I promise."   By the time I found him, (he was in fact, hugging a light pole at 8th & San Jac), it was drizzling, and I was vastly annoyed. I was mean to him the car, and he was getting upset like a little girl. He gave me strange directions to his house (even though I know where he lives) and we unded up waaay East of I-35 in the ghetto. I was even  more  annoyed.   We get to his apartment, and I contemplate dropping him off and going home. But then I remember I'd been wanting to hook up with him for a long time. So I follow him upstairs. Usually, we are at each other like animals, but last night I made him work for it, hehe. And I must have worn him out early (that, or he was reallllly drunk) cause he fell asleep pretty early in the game. I snuck out.  Looking down at my legs, I could have used a shaved. Having surgery and not going out = not taking care of oneself. Haha, good thing he was drunk.   But yeah, he did make it worth my while.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found two  urlLink more pieces of candied corn in my purse today .  Where is it coming from??? 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This seems  PAINFUL ! Thank goodness I don't have a penis!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the first amazing weekend in a looong time. Kinda hard to go out, party, and get drunk when you're on crutches.  Last night, Farouche & I went downtown [drink at home before I headed out]. Met up with Panda, an old friend of mine. As soon as he started dancing, I told him needed to call 1-900-JOIN-A-BOY-BAND. [drink] I was drancing with Panda & Friends, I turned around to see Farouche making out with  Buddha Boy from a few weeks ago. I pulled her away and shoo-ed him off. [drink] He is annoying and I don't think she would have done it if it hadn't been drinking.  We met a dude who looked like Mozart on Acid, who had a bruised eye. When I asked him what happened, he said a mime had socked him in the face. [drink] Mime boy & Farouche were talking to each other right behind my back and I turned around  and caught them kissing. Wow, Farouche had a lucky night. [drink] The only thing I was makin' out with was my pizza later on that night.  We were talking to a witty dude from Seattle [shot: Sex with an Alligator] when I got shoved from behind really hard. I turned around, of course, & shoved back. [drink] Three guys were yelling at each other and shoving each other, so I stepped in the middle of them to try to get them to stop. I had their attention and was ready to implement my plan (which involved us doing shots naked-- that would get guys to stop fighting) but dumbass Seattle boy grabbed my arm and PULLED me away.. which  Pissed. Me. Off.  The fight broke out, tables turned over, drinks were sent flying [not mine], until the bouncers had the dudes on the ground, cowering and crying. Quite a sight to see. [drink]   Post-partied at Mr. Humane's house [drink].  Today, Farouche & I had dim sum lunch [no drink] and spent waaay too much money shopping.  Oh, and can I say that now that I have seen the final Lord of the Rings (twice), I still have the hots for most of the leading men in that movie. What is it about  me and guys who can A), wield weapons, B) kill, kill, kill, and C) well, is there a need for C? (NB- I do not like Orlando Bloom in any other movie, just in LoR).   Time to write conclusion of thesis. Here is what my prof suggested I write about, "think about yourself and what you mean when you say that you've changed.  You are very good at looking outward, observing  what you experience, and describing it.  But I think you should openly ask (and try to answer) some deeper questions: why did you travel alone? why did you go where you went?  what dangers did you seek and confront (whether physical or psychic)?  what did you learn (not only about exotic places but about yourself)?  how are you different now from what you were at the  beginning?  what to you intend to do next?  why?  That sort of thing -- more of a personal voice, less of a travelogue recorded by a camera-like observer.  Does that make sense?"  Mmmm, yeah... but where to start.   This sucks. It's 3:53pm, and I think it's time for a [drink]...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, Farouche, Red, & I decide to have a quiet night, so we head to 4th street, to Fado. There always seems to be trouble at Fado since the crowd is older and, as a general rule, the guys can afford to buy us drinks (compared to the broke-ass college kids on 6th).  We get our drinks and head to the patio for our quiet night- not quiet for long. Ran into a group of British firefighters who are in TX for special task force training (learning about structure fires because they are expecting a hit like we had 9/11). Compared to London, Ausitn is really cheap. So they started buying us anything we wanted. I was trying to be hospitable, so I wanted our Brits to sample all of our American shots-- they were laughing at the funny names: Sex With an Alligator, Irish Car Bomb, Buttery Nipples, etc. So any shot with a funny name...well, naturally we did one. This results in us getting pretty toasty, and Red getting slammed!  At some point, I was yelling "GIIIIMP" to a dude on crutches. [His friend came and talked to me and bought me a drink]. Then, I was charging toll for guys to pass my way. [Which resulted in me & Farouche getting $20 stuck down our shirts and more rounds of free drinks]. One of the Brits told me that I was the best dressed Texan he'd seen- I told him I cheated, I wasn't all Texan, and the clothes (and me) came from Italy. "That explains it," he replied.  Towards the end of the evening, Farouche & I were going strong, still double fisting, but Red wanted to go home. Just as she was trying to get us to go home, Farouche- the dear- spotted my rugby boy. I walked by him twice looking for him, and he didn't recognize me.  Said I looked really hot. I told him it was because Farouche did my make up and hair (without her-- well, let's just say that I don't own a brush). The rugby boys loved Farouche, so while I was flirting away, she was sandwhiched between two of them. Literally, like a scene from Night at the Roxy. Red had to leave, so I was cockblocked dammit.  I hadn't peed ALL NIGHT LONG, so on the way home, I make Farouch pull over and i peed on the side of the road. Oh, well.  Post-partied at Mr. Humane's house, got home 'roud 5.  Not bad for a gimp.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My ex emails me today, "Here's a heads up for you. My sister might be contacting you soon. She is going to be in Europe for this summer and wants to know if you're going to be around."  "A heads up"?!?!?!? Mmmmmmm....  (FYI, for those of you that don't know, I grew up in Italy, and my mother and co live there).  So... what? Ex's Little Sis is going to email me to see if I'm in Rome? I won't be... so, then what? There is no way I'm asking my mother if Ex's Little Sister can stay at her house. Yeah right.   So, the emails will go like this:  Ex's Little Sis, "Hey, F. Am backpacking across Europe this summer. Will you be in Rome?"  Me, "No, I'm sorry. I won't. Bummer. Have a good time, though."  She'll email something back, & I'll ignore it.   Why do people think they can hit me up this way? People I don't really know. If say (Thailand, Keg, Farouche, Linds, Phil, etc) wanted a place to crash in Rome-- hey, no problem, done deal! And if they had a little sister who wanted a place to crash, I'd think about it, but probably no problem at all. [my mother has a thing about tacky American kids who invade her house and wear shorts and flip flops and stumble around drunk].  This is reason 213 section A of "Why I Don't Believe in Boyfriends."   I am the biggest bitch ever. I should want to help everyone, unconditionally.   Meh.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (not in order of "badness" level, just random)   1- Flirt with an anonymous married man from a blog , namely  urlLink Cheating Spouse X Blog .  The flirting went as follows, from the comments section of one of his entries:  hey cheatsp, stumbled upon your blog, and read it all. i haven't ever cheated on a significant other -- yet. I am not adverse to it, mind you. But i think that if I caught my hypothetical husband cheating on me, I'd shoot him (I'm Texan, and I own guns). No where deadly, of course, but somewhere painful...  Am enjoying reading your blog, keep it up! F.  ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Thanks, F.  Well...nothing hotter than a chick with a gun...so long as it is pointed at the other guy.  Given your Texan roots, F., I am sure your the one to teach the CS proper form in "pulling the trigger." I cant wait  cheatsp ------------------------------------------------------------------------ How did you know? I hold the gun & I like to be in charge... grew up in Italy, so I have that Italian temper. Mix that with the Texan bit and the guns... well, am not really sure what you get.  Either way, enjoy reading your blog, so go out and cheat! F. ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Hmnn...F.,  Italian temper and Texan attitude. Cant get any more flavor than that...  Thanks again for your comments. cheatsp ------------------------------------------------------------------------ If you're in Texas, I'll buy you a mojito*... * He had mentioned in a previous blog how much he loved mojitos. F. ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Italian background, Texan attitude and a Cuban cocktail...and I didnt think it could get better. Sign me up... cheatsp  ------------------------------------------------------------------------ ;)  F. ----    2- Flirt with a kid . He's not exactly a kid, but he can't drink legally. Don't have the IM conversation, but I sent him that kama sutra link and made fun of him going to "dinner" when he had to run. He, he.  [In an IM convesation with Keg: keg:	omg keg:	get off the internet keg:	you are flirting with underage boy and married man] ----   3- Go to Pekiti Tirsia Kali, aka, a Filipino Stick & Knife fighting class FIVE days after knee surgery , but I LOVED it. Loved the fact that there eight guys in the class with big sticks, and I was the only girl. I loved it even better when they sparred and one got beat in the face and bled. Yes, I have bloodlust. And yes, I will keep going to Kali. My next Dr appoitment for the knee is on Wednesay, which means I can catch Mondays' class before my Dr KILLS me! Also, the intimidating thing about Kali class is that most of the guys that I worked out with are my  instructors  in my kickboxing class. Kinda strange being their "peer" of sorts. ----   4- Eat cookies for dinner after working out .No explanation needed there. ----   5- Go shopping . Did I really need all five of those shirts, a new brush, and a new swimsuit? Hmmm ---- 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink I know what all y'all are getting for Christmas next year!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today is a good day because :  1- I found a piece of candied corn in my purse. Am not really sure where it came from, but it tasted good nonetheless.  2- I manged to sleep past 6 am for the first time in weeks, since my knee injury.  3- I turned in my thesis rough draft into my advisor, who said it was perfect; he didn't even correct a comma. Today, I turned in a copy to my second reader.  4- I'm reading 'Angela's Ashes' for the third time, and lovin' it.  5- I'm gonna get some this weekend, and the anticipation alone makes today a good day.  6- My bloody bandages wrapped around my leg get to come off tomorrow. Yippee!  7- Because my kickboxing instructor (and the whole class) sent me a Get Well Card (it's where I hurt my knee), and it makes me happy to see it. Plus, today I'm learning Kali, a martial art that I can practice from sitting down (so I won't strain my knee).  8- Oh, and because I'm sure that somewhere there is a squirrel humping a turtle, and that makes me  happy.  9- Additionally,  urlLink Keg  sent me  urlLink this site, which is already giving me lustful thoughts . But am not sure how  urlLink the Curving Knot would work , and  urlLink the Stag position makes little sense to me , but hey! who am I to criticize a centuries-old art? Anyways, this site made me happy. Will bone up (hehe) on material in hopes of an interesting weekend.    Today is bad because :  1- Pap smears. 'Nuff said.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up this morning, incisions giving me a bit of trouble. mmm... oh well.  Tire is flat. Call AAA, they inflate. I go to a service station, "Ma'am you need new tires, the steel is poking through." It was indeed. Drive to NTB. Tell the dude I need to front tires, then I call my dad and let Dude talk to my Dad. I can hear my dad talking to Dude, "No French tires!!" LOL.  New Tires and Alignment set me back less than $300, lots less than  urlLink Keg spent on hers!   The Dude at the NTB was funny. He refs wrestling matches, freaky ones. Last week, he refed a match between Lizard Man and Leopard Man. Both FREAKS that are tatooed from head to toe. They should keep blogs, wow, talk about interesting. (Freaks).  While I'm waiting in the lounge, reading Angela's Ashes (great book!) and watching VH1, "The Fab Life of Pam Anderson," other NTB dude kept walking in mumbling about his hang over, "Mah gurl left me, mah dog bit me, what can go wrong now?"   Last night, for the first night in weeks, I had relatively little knee pain, so i fell asleep like a baby.... to be awakened by a drunken call. Wishing it was a booty call (which I was in no state to take thanks to my bloody bandaged knee), I was disappointed to find out it was only a  urlLink very drunken keg . Actually, glad she called. Always good to hear the other half of the world is out partyin' it up!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I logged into Blogger, I noticed a slogan, "Blogger: your brain on the web."  God, I hope  not !! More like lack thereof.   Right now, in bed, on Vicodin (not cause I'm in pain, but taking it just to piss my father off --behind his back mind you-- b/c he wanted me to throw away all my unused vicodin pills. 30 of 'em. Yeah right. I have a whooooole bottle. Keepin' that shit just in case), I do solemnly swear to get into trouble this weekend. Major trouble. I can take my bandages off on Thursday, so Thursday night I am placing a much-needed booty call. Maybe South of the Border, maybe into Yankee Land. Usual dilemma. But somethin' is gonna happen.  Oh, and check this blog out,  urlLink Cheating Spouse .
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am bored. Bum knee, dont have to go to work this week=me being bored. So I read some of my old blog entries, DAMN I've been boring lately. VEeeery boring. And I apoligize.  Now that I'm back on my feet again, hopefully I'll start getting into trouble... we can only hope...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, Ireland came over and shot the shit with me. My dad cooked dinner, and my brother brought ice cream and cokes. We were set. Had a great time knitting together and catching up.  Today, I accompanied my father to Paris... Paris, Texas, that is. He bought a ranch out there and he wanted me to see it. So I sat in the car, drugged up on Vicodin, and slept. The ranch is beautiful. Green, green, green. The Red River is the far side of the border (right up against Oklahoma).  For lunch-- The Catfish King. Yum!  Then-- the day's hardest challenge. Cleaning myself. Am not allowed to take bandages off for a week. The bandage starts at my ankle and ends around my upper thigh. I cannot get this thing wet. So I keep my leg poking out of the bathtub to bathe myself and wash my hair. What a feat. And the phone rang in the middle of all this. And, of course, I had to get up and see who it was (thankfully, I did, cause it was my brother wanting to know what takeout Chinese I wanted. Side note- living in third world countries has taught me to not be grossed out by puke, cause in China & India... maaaan, I was puking all the time! So yesterday, my dad baked some cornbread. He put cheese, and corn, and hatch chilies it it. It smelled  so so so good!  So I asked for a piece. I promptly puked up the one bite I ate. I settled onto the couch again, and tried another bite. Puked that up too, oops. Then I tried a third bite. That one didn't stay down either. The cornbread beat me. So I sent my dad to the store for Sprite and Jello, the two things I know I could keep down in those circumstances). So back to my bath... my hair wasn't rinsing off properly in the bathtub water-- just made everything soapier. So, drained the water, and ran my head directly under the spigot. Needless to bother you with more details of my exciting life. Shower is taken. I am clean (yippee). Am trying to return to Austin on Sunday. We'll see how that goes tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm aliiiiiive.  Surgery went well. I can finally straighten my knee out the whole way.  A bit loopy and drugged up...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was already in a shitty mood as I was leaving Austin today (missing boat parties, lake parties, house parties, rugby parties, etc) and when I was pulled over, it only made my day worse. I knew I was going over 81 mph.   Cop: You know what I pulled you over for? Me: Uhh, probably speeding. Cop: Yeah, I clocked you at 81 (in a 65). Drivers license and insurance, please. Me-- hand him my license (cracked and falling apart-- praying he didn't know why it's so ruined)... look for insurance, look for insurance, pray that I have it... finally find it. Cop: This is expired by three months.  Please  tell me you have insurance. Me: I do, I do (I know I do, it's the ONE thing my dad still pay for, and he's anal about these things). Cop: You still live on TG Street? Me: Yes, sir. Cop: You a student? Me: Yessir. Cop: Yeah, only a student would live on TG Street (WTF? What did he mean by  that ?!?) When did you get your last ticket? Me: Actually, officer, I can't remember (what he doesn't have to know is that I have a stack of warnings). Cop: Wow. Good for you. We went through that whole, "where are you going and why routine, bla bla." Cop's radio comes on. Cop: Weeeell, since you're a student, I know you can't afford this, so I'm going to let you go. I have to run to a wreck anyway.   SWEET!!!  I called my dad-- who gets tickets all the time. His one comment, "F, life  really  isn't this way."   For ME it  IS !!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Speaking of things I've lost... dammit, now that I can't find that earring, I'm thinking about all the things I've lost in my life (lots), but recently... my favorite leopard thong underwear. DAMMIT. When I snuck out of the Mexican's house in the middle of the night I couldn't find them, then when I asked him about them, he acted like I was making shit up, that he couldn't find them. DAMMIT! I want them BACK.  Also-- 'member that fucking HUGE pearl earring that I lost to the gods of good sex last summer? Well, I want my sacrifce back. The Gods did not reward me. I am TIRED of loosing earrings. Period. I've changed my mind: the good sex (er... great sex) was NOT worth it, neither is the funny story. I WANNT MY EARRINGS  BACK !  Thank god I can't misplace my Prada breifcase.   DAMMIT! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I lost a gold earring today. An expenisve gold earring. An expensive gold earring from Italy.   I called the Dr's office, called Central Mkt, called the florest, looked in my car, at work, in my house, and I even went back to campus and retraced my steps (a feat in the gimpy state I'm in, lemme tell ya). No where to be found.   SO SAD! :(  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  Easter bunny whipped at church service 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should have created  urlLink this  blog. Wow.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This past weekend, I took my crutches with me when I went to Connecticut  because I thought I'd have an easier time at the airport if I was considered a gimp. I was right (which I usually am :)). Got to cut through lines, be driven around the airport in a car, use the restriced elevators, board the plane first, sit up front, and often people even carried my stuff. Joy, oh joy. I think I might invest in a pair on crutches to have with me whenever I travel. The only problem is that I don't use/own/believe in backpacks so whatever I carried kept on falling off my shoulder and hitting me in the chest and was generally a pain in the ass.  The downside of the crutches is that EVERYONE HAS AN INJURY story and they want to share it with you.  Like I GIVE a shit!  Everyone has had knee surgery, ankle surgery, broken leg issues, pins in their fingers, and one dude even sold tools to doctors for knee surgery. Ahhhh! It was a never ending discussion, in which I had to participate. After a while, I started making up fanstastical situations on how I hurt my knee: I resuced a baby from a burning building and fell and hurt it on my way down the stairs; bowling tournament; hiking glaciers in Patagonia last week I slipped, oops; having wild sex, I hit it against the wall and popped the meniscus out; bird watching- fell out of a tree... and lots more, some even worse to believe. But people ate them up. I was selling crazy, and people were buyin'.  Other than that, CT was great. A bit cold for my taste, and the people are snobby, but it was nice. The women are DECKED OUT- between their Hermes bags worth $10K, their 4 Carat diamonds and their clothes, each outfit I saw must have been worth at last $40-50K. Ridiculous. And the high school kids were worse, shopping for graduation outfits (worth over $3K) at Ralph Lauren that they were going to use once and throw away. I didn't see single shitty car, not even something in the mid-range was anywere to be seen. Only Beemers, MB's, Jag's, etc (not that I am complaining, I got to drive the Beemer around all weekend-- crusing speed: 105 mph. I was praying to get pulled over so that I could use my "stupid TX girl routine" that I had all worked out).  Back in Austin for a couple of days, till Thursday afternoon- at which point, joy oh joy, I'm going BACK to exciting Fort Worth for my stupid knee surgery on Friday. Hopefully I'll be able to drive back on Saturday, but I doubt it. I wanna get the fuck out of FtW so I'll hurry back.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       NB: if you are grossed out by girls talking about gross shit (no pun intended) then do NOT NOT NOT read below .   Chick 1:	oh man...that sushi is doing a number on my digestive tract Chick 2:	ME TOO 1:	i'm glad we left the bar cause I started to feel it then 1:	was something in the sushi a diuretic? 2:	yeah, i've alreday hit the shitter, too!!! 1:	haha 1:	same here 1:	just got back 2:	aren't we gross 1:	ehh 2:	i just might post this conversataion on my blog  1:	whatever everyone craps 1:	hahaa 1:	that would be hilarious 2:	i know 2:	us and our crap talk 1:	well...gotta talk about something 1:	might as well be about something everyone knows a little something about   How nasty are we, on a scale from 1-10? And if you wanna know who the mystery chick is, just ask!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I decide to have ACL surgery this summer, the ski trip is off. The one thing I was looking foward to... oh well. Keg, you still wanna go to Central America? How long you wanna go for? What about Brazil? I have relatives there that can hook us up...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you I haven't told yet, here are my MRI results. Pretty grim.  ACL-- torn. Initially they thought it was 100% severed, but no, the bastard is hanging on by a thread (literally). My knee is so loose that the dr was amazed that I had been  walking  on it for the past 6 months (and even more so that I had been skiing and kickboxing on it, too).  Medial Meniscus-- ?? Where is it? It wasn't in the MRI. It has popped out of joint. That's why I can't straighten my knee. The Dr wants to go in and fix my ACL, but he can't operate until I can fully extend my knee, which I can't do because the meniscus is in the way, blocking my knee extension.  I  have to pop my meniscus back in to joint . WTF???? Talk about PAIN!! I have been trying to straighten my knee all day, to no avail.   Surgery scheduled for Friday, April 16th. In a WEEK. The Dr said he's gonna pop the meniscus back in for me (unless I can do it before then) and "clean up me knee."  CLEAN UP MY KNEE?!? . My knee isn't a fucking kitchen!!!! Arg! And I have to be back on my feet for school on the following Tuesday. Dammit. Dammit.  DAMMIT .   Conclusion. After this first "minor" surgery (why do they call it minor? is  any  surgery "minor???) I have to work on my knee's mobility, and when it's back to 100%, they're gonna go BACK in and fix my ACL. A much less "minor" surgery. Life is gonna be one fucking party for me in the next few months.   On a lighter note, at least I got my honors cords today, even though I skipped the boring ceremony. Being on crutches  does  have its advantages.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a lovely yesterday at Hula Hut with Broken Neck Boy, his old girlfriend, and her friend. It was strange. Me & Broken neck boy sat on one side of the table talking about all the scandals I've caused in New Mexico and about our common friends, while the 30-something people sat on the other side talking about their 50th high school reunion (hehe). The Girlfriend hated me because I told Broken Neck Boy that I could never seriously be with a guy unless he could ski or snowboard  WELL , and by that I mean better or as good as me. I couldn't respect a guy that couldn't. Period. And Broken Neck Boy agreed with me, he said he could never be with a girl who couldn't ski well. The Girlfriend then gave me an evil glare (I've seen her ski- not so hot, not so hot, at all!). I just kept sucking down my piña colada. Yum!  After lunch, tried to nap, but the whole world decided to call me. Made an appointment for an MRI in Fort Worth for Monday morning. Ugh.  Party time: Spain got to town. We headed to the Tejas house for Bob Pease Party: white clothes, gin & tonics, croquet, and crawfish boil. After eating my weight in crawfish, Red, Farouche, and I headed downtown. I got lots of free sympathy drinks (yeah, me).  Got home, and tried to sleep, but people kept on calling me --till past 3. Last night was my first night not on Vicodin, so I needed sleep. Oh well, I'll sleep when I'm dead, I guess.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off,  urlLink Boy with a broken neck  is in Austin. He called me last night. He's here seeing a girl. Whatever. Hehe. I am his "hot chocolate." (see the above url for info about that).   Also, yesterday Farouche, the best friend ever, drove my gimp ass to happy hour at The Ditch. Met up with a couple of other girls, and when I informed them I wasn't drinking, the look of disappointment on their face upset me. So I helped them down two pitchers of margaritas. Yum!   Lemme tell ya, though. Me, drunk on crutches with a veeery injured knee= not a good idea!  Then we had an impromptu party at Farouche's. Broken neck boy and his girl came over, too, as well as Farouche's little sister and her friends. Full house!    Then click here to create your very own  urlLink  Pimp Name .  My favorites for me so far:  Ice Master F Sweetness Macktastic F. Sneed White Chocolate F. Rockefeller Fadeproof F Smooth Funk Master F Wicked  And best of all is  Tricktickler F. Sneed   Post your best Pimp Names in my comments! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The worst part about my knee problems is not that I have to use crutches (although that sucks), it's not that I can't drive my own ass around, nor that I can't drink booze while I'm on vicodin. The worst part is that I have a wear a sports bra anywhere I go! As many of you know, I don't like wearing bras, so most of the time, I don't. But since now I am constantly hopping on one foot and hobbling around, my boobs have started to hurt. Ugh! Hence the sports bra. What also sucks is that I look like I'm on drugs: black bags under my eyes, blooshot eyes, and lots of groaning when I move my knee the wrong way.  The good thing from all this: it's been nice to see all my friends come through for me. From offering to shower me (which I managed to do alone yesterday, yipee!) to driving my gimp ass around for drugs, food, and ice cream. Y'all rock!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am moving out of my apt TOMORROW and I haven't done anything. I  should  be packing, buuuut...there are few things better than spending a weekend in Texas style-- bbq & beer by the pool, or idling in the lake. Yesterday, bbq @ the pool with my rugby guys. Lots of beer, burgers, and guys flashing their asses. No packing done.  After the bbq, got home, packed  one book , and my phone rang, "hey, I'm cooking a great dinner. Come over." I couldn't say no to two Louisiana boys fixing me dinner. Flounder stuffed crawfish, fresh shrimp, & an amazing salad. After dinner, we [me & 3 boys] went for ice cream. No packing done.  I was late to meet Farouche, so I dashed home (I was still in my swimsuit from the bbq), put on a dress and headed out. By 12:45am, I was tuckered out, so we start heading home, when Bouncer that works at a club found out I was leaving town, so he drug me in for shots. Then I was leaving again, and some friends showed up. Then I tried leaving again, and... needless to say, I didn't get home until well past 2. No packing done.  Today, I decided to spend the whole day packing. Got up, and emailed. No packing done. Went to grab lunch with friends. No packing done. Got a phone call from Tiny (a HUGE Jamaican dude) to go to the lake. So, of course, I head out. While I was at the dock waiting for the water taxi to take me to the cove, I spied 5 guys sitting at a table. One things led to another and we were discussing Dirty Sanchez and I was rubbing suntan lotion on their shoulders. The taxi took forever to come, so we hired some random dude to drive us out to their houseboat. At the houseboat, there were 8 more guys. I was the only girl on the boat. Hung out with them, drank waaay too much, jumped in the water & lost my swimsuit, got out of the water and flashed them my nipple (the highlight of their day), danced on Tiny's sweet yacht, got home at 9... no packing done.  I just called Farouche, and we're going downtown, which means I won't get any packing done tonight either... I thought my all-nighters would be over after I graduated from college...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was a hellish day. Got up at 6 (eastern time, so 5am for me), took the train from Connecticut to NYC. Had breakfast with my boss at the Carlyle (that was quite nice, not hellish at all). Meetings till noon. Got a cab and made him hurry to take me to the airport. Thank god my flight back to DFW was running late. In DFW had dinner with a friend, went home, got my car, drove 3 hour in shitty Memorial Day weekend traffic. Showered, went to Farouche's house for drinks.   urlLink My buddy Scotland  came over with his roommate & friend to drink with us a bit. Later, we all went downtown. Don't know  how  I get myself in these kind traps, but I ended up telling Scotland's roommate that if we went to a gay club, and he took his shirt off, that I'd flash him. So he did, and I did. Sometimes I wish I were shy. None of the other boys in the club cared about my bared breasts, but Roommate decided that since I had flashed him, I  liked  him.  Pleeeease . So I spent the rest of the night pushing him away and slapping his hands when he felt me up. Mr. Octopus, that'll be his new name. And it turns out that Farouche and Scotland had decided to hook us up. Grrrr. Poor Scotland, I've tried telling him that I liked  him , but I really don't think he gets it. In one ear, out the other...  So, back to me flashing Mr. Octopus... after the deed, I stole his shirt and put it on. He was trophied. Then Farouche & I decided that Scotland should be topless, too. So we took his shirt off and Farouche kept it. At some point, Farouche, not to be outdone by moi, flashed Scotland. It made the poor boy's night. Later on, Octopus decided that he'd had enough to drink, so he climbed on the stage, with his shirt still off, and started dancing away wtih all the gay boys. Good for him. But I think he was liking the gar bar thing  a bit too much .  Today, no flashing (I hope) and lots of packing. The bbq @ 2. Yippee!  Beer & Barbeque! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Job in NYC cooler than I thought. Fast-paced, and a million things going on at once. The crazies that come in here make it interesting, too. Back in TX on Saturday, to pack up for the weekend, moving out of apt on Monday, and ACL knee surgery on Tuesday (ugh!--dr said this one will have considerable more pain than the last one!)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To all you who have no lives and live vicariously through me, I'm sad to say that I won't have much time to blog this week as I am in New York training for my future job (aka boring life). My one fun thing is that I skipped out on work to hang out with  urlLink this boy . He said he doesn't read blogs, so I guess we'll see...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For all you guys that didn't like the post on my  urlLink Machiavelli-style flirting  don't read this entry. If you're still reading on, I wanted to let everyone know that once again I manged to use my flirting abilities to my advantage. I booked a hotel for NYC on hotels.com, which has no cancellation, no change policy. I called Saturday night and cancelled the hotel,  without  paying the HUGE fee. I lucked out and got a young guy on the phone, and I found out he was based in Texas, and well, don't you know it, I live in Texas, too. So many things in common. And no $250 fee for me. Yipee!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I could graduate all over again, I would:  1. Wear underwear. Oops.  2. Not be as hung over.  3. Bring a flask and be drunk. At least that way all the jokes would be funnier.  4. I wouldn't be such dumbass. Example: While introducing my parents to my thesis advisor/great prof of mine. "Mom, Dad, this is Dr. __. He is a Shakespeare expert and wrote a really famous article on Othello." Prof, "What article on Othello." Stupid Me, "Uhhh, you know. The article. On Othello. That we read in class." Prof-- has very confused look on his face, "What are you talking about?" Me, getting annoyed, "The article on Othello you wrote. I still have it." Prof, "You mean  HAMLET ?! We didn't read Othello in that class." OOPS  Good thing they can't ungraduate me!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Am walking the stage in an hour or so and I'm hung over as hell.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me in my pink swimsuit & my big fuchsia hat, a car full of boys, & cooler full of beers. Great day for visiting Twin Falls.  Now it's nose to the grindstone. Gotta keep on packing.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a final tomorrow, which isn't a big deal except for the fact that I quit going to class four weeks before the semester was over, and before that, went to class very sporadically. This means I have no notes. I somehow got a boy to email ALL his notes to me. All  fourty-four   typed. SINGLE spaced. All those notes for the small price of a smile and some kind (if untrue) words. Go me.  While these 44 pages were printing, I made an ice cream run. Unlike most girls I know, I don't diet. While in line to pay, I asked the boy in front of me if he would pay for my ice cream, too ::smile, smile:::, Well, of course he would want to do that. I was really expecting a no because I was looking verrrrry shabby. But I got my free ice cream and walked out. Leaving the boy open-mouthed. I guess he thought I would  talk  to him or something. Please. I have reading to do.  Yes, you can have your cake and eat it, too. And no, you don't have to lie in the bed you made. And you're really good, you have someone else make the bed for you!  ::evil grin & cackle, then rubbing hands together::  Machiavelli would be proud. I'm sure of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spent a lovely afternoon yesterday packing all the things I won't need in New York, ie, thousands of books, dishes, flower vases, etc. The other day Red stole a stack of newspapers for me to use to pack, and the newspapers happened to be The African American. So I've been wrapping my  martini & champagne glasses while reading about the African American community.  Scottish boy called and we went to have a late lunch and drinks on the Lake with Thailand. After a long nap, I get ready to go to a birthday party wearing a shirt that I've owned for TWO year but never had the guts to wear- yeah, it's  that  scandalous. It was hot.   Thailand & I headed downtown, she was wearing a new pair of jeans that were super hot! We danced the night away. Somehow, hamstrings a bit sore today.  I guess that has to do with the fact that I danced some awesome house/techno music. In Italy, in my early teens, I danced to this kind of music ALL the time. Now, I can't stand its repetitiveness for more than half an hour. But last night, at a hopping club, the dj decided to switch from top 40 to 80's jams (which I LOVED) to some awesome European techno. As soon as that techno came on, I went even  wilder . The only other person in the whole club that could keep up was a French-Tunisian friend of the mine. Everyone else basically quit dancing and stared at us. I was  groooovin' .   Then some dude started videotaping me (a BIG no-no, unless I know you). I was enjoying the dancing so much that, instead of starting a fight myself (which I would ususally do), I talked to one of the bouncers who took care of it for me. ----   Am throwing a party, graciously being hosted by Farouche, this coming Friday to get rid of my numerous bottles of booze before I leave Austin. It'll be a pre-party gig. We'll be kicking everyone out before midnight so we can go down and shake our bootays in the dance floor.. then I graduate the next morning at 9. Oh, yeah, the party is also for my graduation. Minor. Getting my friends drunk on my extra booze is more important. The goal of the night: to make sure i am STILL drunk at 9 when I walk the stage. I'd rather still be drunk than hung over!!   Btw, am not very keen on moving up to Yankee Land. But I have no choice. In too deep. And no alternatives.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'Nuff said.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I walk into a club/ bar/ restaurant/ anywhere the opposite sex might be, I feel like a lioness on the prowl. The second I step through the threshold I know, within two quick heartbeats, if I will hunt down anyone in the bar. I scan the room. 99.9% of the guys present aren't even worth my glance. And yes, this is superficial, but I'm not talking about finding my soul mate here.  Take tonight for example. I had been swimming, hanging out by the pool, & cooking all day with friends. I went to the bar for dollar beer night on a whim. Because I had been swimming, I had no makeup on and my hair was still a bit wet and plastered to my head. But I stepped in the bar and -- am not trying to sound pretentious here-- but heads turn. Even dressed in my jeans & t-shirt, without makeup, I can make guy look at me. I call it magnetism, my friend Leah calls it   je ne soi qua , Austin Powers calls it Mojo, but whatever it is, I think I have it. And that's all that matters. The attitude.  I was let down by the selection of males tonight. Drank my lone beer. Left disappointed.  Other instances, I'm rewarded much more easily. Last week on campus, for example, I was walking to class. A handsome guy was walking towards me. I could tell by the way he was looking at me that he found me attractive. And it was reciprocated. When he walked next to me, I pulled my sunglasses down the bridge of my nose and smiled at him. He walked past me and kept his head swiveled to keep his gaze on me. He kept turning to look at me until... well...  He hit a pole.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My buddy from New Orleans had a craw fish boil this afternoon. I showed a bit late, swimsuit on, and towel in hand. I was the only girl in a swimsuit; all the other girls, "didn't want to get wet" or "had just washed their hair."   I was the first person pushed in, of course. And I was still wearing my sarong.  But that's the story of my life.   I love crawfish. And I especially love sucking the heads. If you're not from Louisianna or the the South and don't understand what that means... we'll, I'm sorry for you. And that's the story of  your  life! 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to mention in my weekend recap... if a funky video store clerk, who looks a bit like Howard Stern (OH OH OH, ran into Howard Stern @ The Library last night (for those of you not from here, that's a bar!)) tries to convince you to rent the movie Marquis de Sade, don't do it. The version the clerk told us we had to rent was strange: every character was an animal and Sade had a  talking penis puppet!!!   What a disaster...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday involved an early happy hour with the gang (with the addition of Mr. Kansas City, who is back in town for a wild weekend). Happy hour= all of us getting tanked on mojitos. I lost count after four... After that, I couldn't let my buzz die, so off to Farouche's to drink my Vodka 7's. Started partying early and drank wayyy too much. Headed home, puked most the of the alcohol out to keep from getting a nasty hangover, but I got the hangover anyway. I was so passed out, that I don't remember talking to two people at 4 four AM on the phone. Oops.   At 9:30am the next morning, feeling like I wanted to DIE, my phone rings.  I got a job in New York City!!!  Am moving up there July 1st. Will be running a psychiatrist's whole 7-floor office. Yipee! My dad is pissed that I am moving off to "Yankee Land," my mother is thrilled because she can come see me. Y'all have any thoughts?   Lunch with the G-Unit and Kansas City: the greasy dim sum really helped my queasy stomach. Watched sexy movies with gals. I must say, I liked  Y Tu Mama Tambien . But that movie explains PERFECTLY why I won't hook up with a high-schooler. Where I come from, sex that lasts 4 seconds,  is considered an  accident, NOT SEX!!!!!!!!     Saturday night, Red, Farouche & I hit the town. I was hit on by waaay too many guys and was in no mood to be nice to any of them. Ended up at Fado, where some cute boy with an accent grabbed my arm and asked me to meet his friends. There were  fifteen  Irish guys all for us. The free drinks started flowing. The bar closed, we invited the cute ones back to Farouche's apartment. Only ONE of the cute ones showed up. The other two were weird and ugly. They drank and were funny. We started talking about scandalous sex stories... and well...er... I had a few... Around 4, I try to get the boys to leave. At 4:30, I stand up and TELL them GO. I call a cab. I walk them to the door, and one of the ugly ones, I believe I called him a "Fat Irish Fuck" comes back in the door, winks at me and says, "You and me. Later?" "Uhhh. No. Go" and I closed the door. Two minutes later, the cute one calls, "Hey, wanna have a drink with me at our hotel?" "NO! I already told you: in Texas, they quit serving alcohol at two. It is now 4:30." "Weeeellll, I thought  I'd ask. Shot in the dark. Had to try." God, when guys get drunk, the stupid shit they do...  The girls & I went for early morning snacks at Taco Cabana. Yum! Went to bed at 5:23 am.  We were supposed to have brunch with with Irish boys. They never called. Haha. It's better that way.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 7:16 and I'm already drunk. Wwaaaay drunk. Mojitos, baby!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, met up with a friend for a beer at 3:40, got home at 1:40am. Hmmm...  This girl, Luna, & I were inseperable last spring. The two of us together = very rowdy. One time, we ripped a stranger's shirt off. Now, her & her boyfriend bought a house in suburbia. And they got a dog. And she never goes out anymore. And I never see her. So we hung out all day reminiscing over old times...  ...and before I knew it, it was past 1 o'clock.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I understand Seinfeld now. I posted below how on Sunday my neighbors & I bonded over the hookah & booze. And now it's ruined my apartment life. I've been friends with my neighbor D since the beginning. I rarely see him, but when I do, he says hi, I say hi. We shoot the shit. I walk away. Now that I'm friends with more of my neighbors they say hi to me  ALL THE TIME  and I have to say hi  back . Grr. I can no longer turn my eyes away & ignore them. Dammit. Just now, one of my neighbos poked her head into my open window to ask me something. WTF? Thank god I'm leaving here in a month. I need to move somewhere new and be sure to stay away from my neighbors. No friends. Very un-Texan of me, and I apologize. I just don't want people bothering me all the time!   Also, I have had a cute crush one of the boys in my kali class. Cute Asian boy, built like a hoss. Have been watching him train for his kickboxing tournament coming up this weekend. By "watching" I mean "drooling over his shirtless body." Well, today I was talking to him and he was talkng about getting a scholarship to UVA and he was leaving in the fall. Blah, blah, blah [all I focus on is his shirtless chest]. I assume that he was going to grad school or law school at UVA. Was I ever wrong. He is still in  high school  and is going to UVA for  undergrad.  OOPS!  Dammit.  Dammit.    Dammit.     I call Kat and tell her my sad news. No fun play time with boy because he really  is  a BOY! And I don't play around with highschoolers. Did that once (he was legal folks!) and all I can say is, "ouch!" Kathleen then advises me to go ahead and hook up with him because it would, "make good Blog material." Since WHEN have I done anything that desperate just to  write it in my blog?????  What has the world come to?
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While I'd like to tell you that "smokin' the hookah" is some perverted way of mine of calling fellatio... alas, it is not. Sunday afternoon I had one of the best Sundays in a while... my neighbor, I recently found out, owns a hookah. So we sat outside on Sunday--all day-- and smoked it. And drank three bottles of wine. And two cases of beer. And ordered pizza. We were sitting in our apt complex patio so our other neighbors joined us for the impromptu party. We smoked, drank, shot the shit... then the bird shit started falling. I think I was shat on thrice. Oh well, in Italy they say it brings good luck, so I guess I need to buy that lottery ticket now. When the everyone started getting shit on by the birds, and the sun set, we headed indoors.   Now, to find some of that  other  definition of "smokin' the hookah"...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1- I took that stupid sex quiz again (it's too funny and amusing and it's 2 am and I can't sleep) and this time I got... drumroll, please...  GENGHIS KHUNT . The  urlLink profile is TOO FUNNY so check it out here . The profile starts off like this:  We almost called you  Brutus the Uterus  and attached this picture...    2- That jar of Nutella that I stole at a party last night... I finished it this morning.   3- I use my honors cords as a means to reach my fan high above my bed. Today, the cords got tangled the fan and I lost a tassle. Looks like, once again, I'll be the "original" one at graduation. Always have to stand out, even when it's an accident...  4- Post more tomorrow...  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weekend Update: Thursday, pretty uneventful (other than that booty call I already posted). Hung out with Joe, who played rugby with the US 7's Team in Hong Kong & Singapore. He brought me back a tshirt from the Hong Kong 7's tourney, which I thought was quite sweet. Went to a movie (with Farouche) at Alamo- I ate lots of ice cream, yum! Afterwards, the three of us hung out and shot the shit for hours. It's been a long since I've hung out with Joe, and it was nice to catch up with him. He's really one of the most wonderful guys I know-- and too bad I'm not attracted to him. OOPS, oh well.  Friday- work sucks. But I bought a new belt and earrings [this belt comes into play later]. Went out with Red & Thailand (read her blog  urlLink here ). So glad she's back in town. We went to  urlLink Carlos N' Charlie's  on the lake. Drank 'Ritas, watched Breakfeast @ Tiffany's playing on the lakeside shore on a big screen. Movie was over early enough to go downtown (for more drinking) so I convinced the girls go to out. Looking for a quite spot, we head to  urlLink Fado . Night was fun, we people watched. Drank Strongbows. Chill.  Saturday day, I stayed in bed  ALLLLLLLL  day. Read a couple of books, cook lunch. I figured since I had my thesis bound a week early, I  deserved  a lazy day.  Last night, went out with Red & her Roommate. The ladies were lookin' smokin' and strangely enough I didn't even have an inch of skin showing. T-shirt covered chest up to neck; skirt down to knees. Haha. That  must  have been an accident. OOPS!!! But it didn't stop the scary guys from hitting on me. Mmmm... must ponder that at a future date. Downtown was packed and everywhere had lines, so we headed to Acquarium where I cut in line, of course. I even get my drinks there 3 for the price of 1. Things that like happen when your friend made out with the bouncer once and you've made out with bartender once. OOPS!!! Oh well. At last I get good service now.  Lots of drinks follow us going to Spill to shake it like a salt shaker on the dance floor (drinks in hand). Found out that my buddy has started working there again. So, I exchanged kisses for drinks. I love that transaction.  I bought a belt on Friday. Still remember that? It's a thin, leather belt, that wraps around me twice or thrice, depending. Last night, while dancing feverishly to an Usher song, I thought it would be a good idea to take it off and whip it around my head like a lasso.Yeah...  that didn't work so well.  I hit some guy in the  forehead  with it. OOPS!!! I turned around and acted as if I had done NOTHING... but he probably figured it out as he saw me wrapping my long-ass belt back around my waist. OOPS!!!  Hung out in Spill way past closing time, got to see Mr.Mustang & his crew, and that 19 yr old I kissed (errr.... hard core made out with one night--OOPS!!!) whom I haven't seen in 8 weeks.  After the bars close, we headed to a house party thrown by an acquiantence of mine. Ran into some good friends of mine (who are TOO OLD to be going to that type of party) and chatted with them.  Stole a jar of Nutella and ate  half  of it when I got home at 4AM.  OOPS!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two new blogs I've added to my list:   urlLink Lujing She-Ra . That's my friend Jesse's blog (aka, Lujing- her Chinese name). Really cool chick that I met through an academic advisor when I returned from China because she was considering going. After two years, she finally is going. So check out her blog, especially this summer since she'll chronicle her time in Yunnan province. She's taking a traditional Chinese medicine course in the jungle. Wow!   Then, there's  urlLink Come Sail Away , a lost soul who wandered upon my blog my mistake (and I bet he regrets it ever since). His blog is interesting: the life of a mariner. I'd like more detials about what he does, but he's secretive, and if he told me, I'm sure he'd search me down and kill me. But Cap, if you can give any more details, I'd love to have 'em. It's an interesting read. And Cap is super-cool (he loves Dire Straights!!).  I've added their links to my list of blogs at the bottom of my page, so you don't have to find this blog entry from now on to link to them.  Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a whirlwind of a weekend in CT, lunch parties (at a house with a 13 car garage), dinner parties, wedding parties, and boat parties. I already have a date (with the son of the dude that owns the amazing cars), a bake-off (to see who is the better cook), and invites to Cape Cod, Nantucket, & Boston, as well as to more parties.  This is the way life should be.   Oh, and work is fun, too. ---
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday evening, Farouche drove up from Austin, and Red drove over from Dallas, so that we could all meet up in Cowntown. They picked me up, we used my new handicap sticker, and we went for Blue Margaritas. Yum! After staying past our welcome at the Restaurant, we headed back to my shack. All three of us piled on my bed and chilled. Talked, laughed... and when it was getting late, they left.  Saturday, I got up at 4:30 to catch a 7am flight. I got to fly first class the whole way because I'm a cripple and I can't make it to the back of the plane with the cattle.  Also, I was carted around the airport in a wheelchair. So, when I got off the plane, there I was in a wheen chair, with 4 old ladies, also in wheelchairs. I felt old.  In CT, now.  Staying with my dad's girlfriend up here who is trying to marry me off... ugh.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My uncle (I really wanted to show y'all his picture. He looks like he just stepped off a Western Set: 10 gallon cowboy hat, bandana, jeans tucked into his knee-high cowboy boots. He's really a Texan-- born & raised on a ranch, and still rides his horse every day)... anyway, my uncle and his wife (she is #3 of Who's Who of Women shooters of the 20th cent) got me a pistol for my graduation gift. I am totally stoked. It's a replica of the old Colt, used back in the wars with the Indians. Ironically, it was called "The Peacemaker."  urlLink Here is a picture, but mine has a longer barrel, 7 inch .  I've already gotten the CT & NY Alcohol, Tabacco & Firearms Bureau and they are mailing me me info to get my permit. Who-hooo!  Just call me Oakley.  And don't break into my house in the middle of the night. I might not have a semi-automatic, but it only takes one shot...  ...and I don't miss.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So for all of you that know who Single Cell is... (and for those of you that don't read  urlLink here, towards the bottom . He is called "Single Cell" because he is so stupid he only has one brain cell)...  ...anyways,  urlLink Farouche  saw Single Cell at the gym yesterday.   Hehe.   He *actually* is real person.   And yes, he is buff.  And hot...   ...and so very, very stupid.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, Friday, I went to see George Jones in concert at the amazing  urlLink Bass Hall . Many of you probably don't even know who George Jones is, but ask your parents (or probably your grandparents) and they'll know who is he is. (Read his bio  urlLink here, it's actually quite amazing .) He's a contempory of Johnny Cash, etc. I grew up listening to his kind of music, so I was stoked when my dad got me tickets. I knew ALL the songs. (I know I'm a nerd).   After the concert, I got a text message from Scotland,  Hey sexy. You're missing a good time in Santa Fe. Stop missing me for 5 minutes.    What a cutie.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, after a session with my (hot) physical therapist, Red came over to visit. She picked me up, and decided we should have Margaritas. We went to happy hour and after two extra-large 'ritas & some appetizers, I was good and drunk... joy oh joy. Needed to walk our buzz off so I drug Kate to Victoria's Secret (I bought a new bra) then to Express. I managed to not kill myself, but from now will try to refrain from drinking when on crutches.  After happy hour, Red drove me home and I passed out. My dad came home and thought I was sick. Hehe, it'll be our little secret.   On a sadder note, my (hot) physical therapist went to Alaska today to run a marathon. Will only see him once before I leave town. Saddness.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's getting close to three am and since I can't sleep, at might as well be productive since tomorrow I'll be busy being felt up by my hot physical therapist.  This morning (Wed) I went to see my knee doctor and he told me I am doing well. I finally figured out what all the cuts and holes on my knee and leg were for. And I finally figured out just exactly what he did to me (opened up knee, drilled holes in various bones and drilled hole through knee cap, passed new ligament through holes, screwed it in (screws will eventually dissolve-- how cool is that?) then closed me back up. I will never look at a power drill the same way again). He told me my knee is doing well and I'm ahead of schedule. Yippee. Then I went straight to the physical therapist because I have to get on a schedule to get my flabby leg muscles back on track, before I move to The City next Sat. And yes, I was wearing a skirt. But thankfully, I had remembered to throw on some underwear (full converage, not thongs, don't know where I found them). The (hot) physical therapist made sure I had something on under my skirt before he started me on my excersises. But since I flashed the whole world my undies, I was put into a small room all alone. Saddness. I was told to wear shorts when I go back tomorrow. Haha. I just might "forget" again.  My only concern was that my doc told me not to walk without crutches for another two weeks. I was apalled. I have little pain and am ready to GO! The (hot) physical therapist told me that my new ligament doesn't have its own blood supply yet so it doesn't have nerves, and therefore doesn't register pain. So, while simply walking, or making a wrong move, I could snap the new piece and not even FEEL it. I might hear a pop (ew!) but not feel it. The crutches look good, really good.   Oh, and my dad is taking me to get a pedicure & manicure tomorrow, and he's taking me by the mall so I can go shopping at Victoria's Secret sale. He's the best.    And Ireland, thanks for coming over tonight. Really enjoyed the company!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Only I would go to Physical Therapy in a SKIRT.  Oops  PS. I think this list could probably be extended, hehe
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Background: Scotland told me that he thinks all women are heartless bitches, and I was arguing that I am not... [I've only known him for a couple of months].   F: if you think I am heartless just because i am a girl, well, that's a fallacy Scotland: actually here's how I think of you Scotland: i think you've got a tough shell Scotland: not sure why, not sure what the history is Scotland: but I think you're actually a very geniune person Scotland: and probably quite emotional inside, but you protect your weakness well Scotland: so you're definitely not heartless Scotland: but you have to crack the shell first Scotland: that about right?   What does the jury think?  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back to my superstar self... Cap was so nice to say some lovely things about me on his blog, such as, he likes my blog (or me?) because I am, "Well traveled and with a razor wit." He also told me to, "Shine on you crazy diamond!"  Read the post  urlLink here, about me being his Blog Muse .  I've plugged Cap's blog before, but he's changed it since then, so check it out again.  urlLink Harrison's Clock by Cap   Cap, keep reading and send some of your crew my way!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know you've reached  Rock Bottom  when:  1. You're up in time for Saturday Morning Cartoons.  2. You actually watch them.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a  superstaaaahh  (will not put my hands in my arm pits and smell them because I haven't showered in two days... too difficult in my condition).  Check out  urlLink Jeff's Blog , especially  urlLink this post because it's dedicated to me!     Update: added 11:38pm, Just got another spotlight mention of my blog, this time on my devious Machiavellian flirting.  urlLink Check it out here. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I am stuck in bed, I am watching Reagan's Funeral. And it's interesting.  But I've decided that I am a  sick  person: I am watching Reagan's funeral, and all I can think is how hot all the military guys look in their sharp uniforms... All those big guns... I need help. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got a text message from a boy,                  Did I mention that I love you? But I have to find other girls since you're not here.   Growing up in Italy, I'm used to text messaging, and I love it, but few of my friends use it to its full advantage. Scotland does, thank goodness ;)  Oh, and I wrote back,          I guess you're confusing  love  with   lust !  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad, talking to a Friend, "F will be working with a pychiatrist. Good thing she got that degree in Animal Husbandry!" (chuckle, chuckle)  Friend, "That's allright, men are dogs anyway!"  Hehe, my dad has some funny friends.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting on the sofa bed, thinking about the past ten days since my knee surgery...  ...joined Netflix ...watched Season 1,2 & 3 of The Sopranos, and Season 4 & 5 of Sex & the City ...taken one sponge bath, and two "showers" with the aid of a water pitcher (because I still can't get my knee wet)  ...trying to trace down an inmate in Huntsville prison for my father so that he (my dad) can get a pair of boots made by an inmate.  urlLink More info here .  ...taken off my bloody Ace bandage once, only see inches and inches of incisions and blood ...took the the morphine pump out of my own leg (disturbing) ...gimping around on crutches because can't put any weight on my leg for a long time ...still wearing the hospital gown (that I refused to take off after the surgery)-- and I have washed it ...taken lots of drugs ...went to see my doctor at his home, while he was eating his breakfast, because I was worried about something oozing out of my leg (yeah, to family friends) ...left the house one other time to eat dinner, but it exhausted me, so I haven't left again ...lost a crutch ...my brother called me from the bookstore to ask if I wanted any magazines, and he came back with Redbook (hehe), Italian Vogue, and the UK version of Cosmo (no wonder he bitched that the mags cost him 25$) ...always being hungry. How is it possible that I've not moved my gimp ass from the bed, and yet I am  always  famished? My dad said it's because my body needs the energy to fix itself. I say, meh. ...flowers from my law firm in Austin, ...phone calls from my buddies in Italy, ...and naughty text messages from boys in Texas...   I'm spent. Time for a nap...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that I'll be working for psychiatrist who specializes, among other things, in eating disorers, I can help a certain friend get over her binge & purge problems. Maybe I can send her some sample meds, for free, to help her with her bulimia... Hearing her run the water in the bathroom while she pukes really gets old after a while...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am, alone & in bed, with a morphine pump attached to my knee, puking ever half hour, and not a single one of my friends had called to see if I am alive.  The only people who have called me are my dad's girlfriend, and a friend here in Fort Worth whom I have not spoken to in 3 months. And I  got one email, from Scotland.  Thanks folks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was my coworkers birthday so we headed out to celebrate Manhattan Style. Names on some list at some swanky club. She rented out one level and Ewan McGregor had the other. Instead of odering drinks by the glass, we got bottles. That's the way to go. The minute my drink was a quarter empty, I'd fill it up with more Vodka, no mixer needed.  I remember some dude with an eye patch-- some huge, black dude from Trinidad-- who kept telling me how beautiful I was. But I couldn't get past the eye patch. I kept telling people last night that I was a dominatrix. And they believed it because I was sporting my new black corset and I had a wicked look in my eye.   After we poured the drunk party-girl into a cab, the rest of us headed out to some European-style club (huge dance club, multilevel). The line was around the block. My friends knew people. So no waiting in line. And no paying $20 a person to get in. There we found more friends who had bottles of champagne and vodka. I danced and drank
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've always known that I am trouble, but a recent phone call,  urlLink blog &nbsp;(very last sentences), and IM conversation confirmed it. Last night around 3amEST, Keg called me asking for advice. Should she hook up with Boy. I said yes. I always say yes to questions of the sort.  Today, Keg instant messeged me:  keg: good idea: call RESPONSIBLE friend in middle of night for advice keg: BETTER idea: call F in middle of night for advice F: why? F= not responsible? keg: you're mostly responsible!! keg: responsible for the TROUBLE i get into  Oops. I should feel bad, but it feels oh so good to be evil!  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Overall, this weekend was amazing. Fun. Funny. Tiring. But incredible.   Let's analyze the goals I wanted to accomplish while in Austin for the weekend.   1--Hanging out with friends. Check.  2--lots and lots and lots of alcohol. Check.  3--lots of raunchy sex... this is where the weekend ... ahem... fell short (you'll laugh at this later). No check.   Swimming in pool with Farouche. The pre-party she and Red threw me was a blast. Everyone showed up, and what was supposed to be a small get-together with a couple of friends, ended up being a rocking party. By 11:30 I had to kick everyone out so we could go downtown... and go downtown we did. Drank. Danced. Flirted. The doorman and bartenders still recognized me after a 10-week absence. Farouche looked hot in her flirty outfit, matching her flirty attitude Saturday night. Red and Jo made some kick-ass sangria that we managed to finish off before the guests arrived. I looked hot in my new dominatrix corset. And when I was told I looked "lovely," I got pissed and demanded a better compliment. Hehe.   Kate/Red was sweet enough to drive our drunken asses around town. Thanks Kate. On the way home, I decided that it would be a good idea to hang out the window and scream at all cars...   Saturday night, after the bars, back at Farouche's apt, there was an interesting twist... six ladies (myself included) spent some time comparing nipples (color, size, etc). We could have filmed it and sold it for a bundle. Too late...   Sunday, my little sister, G, came into town. I haven't seen her in over a year, so it was cool to chill with her and her three friends. One of her friends hadn't ever smoked a bong before so she got lessons. I must admit, however, that our coachings of "put your lips over the whole hole" made her laugh more than inhale any smoke. We spent all day Sunday at a friend's lake house, barbequing, swimming, telling stupid jokes. My sister and I haven't gotten any quality time as "adults" together, so this weekend was good for our bonding. Although I was shocked to find out she bartends and is sporting new piercings and tattoos.   Now, on to the salacious bits. Friday night, I got lots of text messages from Band Boy. Here are two that I saved:   #1&nbsp;- My bed fits two.  (Don't remember quite what I answered, but probably something along the lines of, "Oh, and it fits two... for what purpose?")   #2- Spend the night naked?  (By the time I got this text message it was close to 4 am so I probably answered curtly and not like I should have).   Looking back, if ONLY I had taken Band Boy up on his offer, I might not be sitting in my office frustrated as hell today...   Anyways, so back to the story... Saturday night at the pre-party, I decided to call my Mexican. Best sex ever, so giving him a call would have been worth it, even if we had parted on shaky grounds... I called and he answered the phone almost screaming, "F?!? I can't  fucking  believe it!! Are you in town?!?" He was asleep and I told him I'd call him after the bars closed and we'd meet up. As planned, at 2am, I called. No answer. I was looking forward to my night with him so much, that I almost cried when he didn't answer. By then, I had alienated Band Boy. So, I was only left with option 3,&nbsp;a good friend, who had started flirting with me. I knew he'd be game to hook up with me and that it wouldn't hurt our friendship. My friends were worried about me hooking up with him, so they hid my car keys and made it difficult for me to meet up with. He, however, came down and picked me up.   If I am debating whether or not to sleep with a guy, I decide by the way he kisses. If he's a great kisser, it generally means that he'll be universally good. And Mr. X was a good kisser, I'll give him that.... and everything following was good as well... right up until the time came to do the deed and  he couldn't get it up ! After much effort on both our parts, I gave up and told him to go sleep.   The next morning, his roommate & I chatted while Mr. Limp slept. He asked me how the night was, and I didn't say anything. I&nbsp;didn't think I was my business, but&nbsp;as soon as Mr. L came out of the shower, he turned to his roommate, "Dude, my hyperdrive did'Õt work last night! Too much alcohol!!!" The bastard was proud!! We went to breakfast, and all he talked about was his "problem." I'll admit he was a good sport about it, making fun of himself ... and I started making fun of him... and still haventt stopped... (example, I sent him an email and told him he should eat noodles for dinner, limp noodles).   Oh, one other thing that made my weekend suck was the weather up here in nyc. Friday afternoon, I trekked up to the White Plains airport (via subways, trains, buses...). It was a long hellish ride, only to be told that all flights out of the airport were canceled due to weather. Dammit. So I had to trek my ass back to Manhattan, and fly out of LGA at 6 am. And Friday night all my friends thought I was in Texas, so they kept on calling me. So, Friday night, no sleep. I got to the airport before the sun rose, only to find out that my first flight was 2 hours late so I missed my connection. I got it all worked out. Got to TX. Drove to Austin and chilled with ladies.   &nbsp;  I guess two out of three objectives is not that bad... I really wanted some sex...   And, on a side note, leaving Austin this time was very difficult. When I moved up to nyc in June, I was eager for the move. I'd been in bed over a month, so moving to nyc seemed like a good idea. This weekend, after having have the best weekend in a long time, I really want to move back to Austin. I miss it. And I miss my friends. Y'all rock!      
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am at work, not getting ANYTHING done because all I can think about is my weekend of debauchery in Austin: lots and lots and lots and lots of boozing, hanging out with friends, and sex, of course. Lots of sex. Raunchy sex. All of Austin will be getting booty calls from me.   &nbsp;  ...Here I come...   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When a friend is in need, you  urlLink stay on the phone... even during a bikini wax...  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend who implemented the Five Step Program (below) had his feelings severely hurt by all the mean things I (we) said about him. He is madly in love with me and didn't know that I thought ill of him in any way. Oops. I guess he'll know better know. But let this&nbsp;serve as an apology of sorts (I say of sorts because I really don't like to apologize). But now that I've written this, I can keep teasing him mercilessly. So can you,  urlLink check out his web page here .     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of my guy friends recently told me about the Five Steps for dating that&nbsp;he used to lure women. I would like everyone's opinions. Personally, I used paint ceramics when I was a kid, so I would have laughed at that suggestion.. but here you go. Opinions, please. &nbsp;  Step 1: meet the girl some place, mention rowing in the conversation [note by F-- he's a&nbsp;hard&nbsp;core&nbsp;rower], she'll be interested, ask her if she'd like to try it sometime   Step 2- take her rowing at 4 or so in the afternoon&nbsp; [note, he previously had told me that girls get scared on the boats so they cling to him in fear-- hence the date on the boat]  Step 3- if she's worth pursuing after the outing (you can learn lots of fun facts when a girl is in a boat)   Step 4- ceramics with good bottles of wine&nbsp;[note- as in, paint your own plate or bowl]  Step 5- massage (the wine tends to help here)   Step 5 generally happens at my house   Then if she's cool you can go get your ceramics together and hang out more   He told me they started to know him at the ceramics place.  -----  This is the guy that recently told me he is the coolest person I know.  &nbsp;   I beg to differ...  but what do rest of my blogger friends think? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My weekend was unusually boring especially since I was left out of  urlLink Kathleen's Surprise Birthday party . Oh well. &nbsp; My weekend consisted of being alone. Finally. It seems I'm always around people. &nbsp; The most important part of the weekend was the hot Turkish dude that makes pizza recognized me when I went in on Saturday. He's is hot. Hot. HOT. And he told me I looked cute. Too bad he's just (hot) pizza boy. (Yes, I am superficial). But at least I get free pizza out of it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Everyone checkout  urlLink Kathleen's Blog &nbsp;not only because she is fabulous, but also because   it's her BIRTHDAY!!!!!!!!!!   (tomorrow)    &nbsp;   Love you    Keg and  Happy Birthday !!!!  &nbsp; (and I promise once I'll get over the colors soon) 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yesterday, not only did I  drive into NYC, have a blast jammin' the music in the swanky new car, but I also managed to avoid the  twelve  cops I saw on the way home, speeding by them close to the 100mph range. Oops. At night. Double oops.  &nbsp;  But the coolest part of the day is that I got an apartment in the nicest part of NYC, in my opinion. I guess it also depends what you consider "nice," and for me "nice" needs to be somewhere safe until I can run/kick/fight back against any type of assailant. And with the way my knee has been acting lately... Let's just say my doorman building looks good right about now.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  Had dinner last night with a very nice &amp; intelligent guy, a friend of Scotland's. Must run. Already worked more than 40 hours this week, so I am leaving the office in a giffy!   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drove car into City. Windows down. Jammin' to a cool cd.  Drove from CT to LGA airport then to work. Didn't make a single wrong turn. And with no maps.  ... Damn I am good.   Everyone check out  urlLink Kate(r)'s blog (aka Red in a lot of my postings) . She's actually really funny most of the time!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I left work late. Caught a 9:15 train back to suburbia. I decided I  needed  a beer. So I bought a 16oz Bud Light longneck from the rolling bar in front of the train. As I walked away from the "bartender" I said to the guy, "Hey, aren't you gonna card me?"  And he said, "Lady, anyone who looks as tired as you, CAN'T be underage!"
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend, like the rest of the New Yorkers and Bostoners, we packed our little BMW and headed up to Cape Cod.  Everyone  who is anyone has a house up there and goes for the weekends. I'd been hearing about this place for weeks and weeks. We were heading up to stay with friends who lived there on the beach, complete with a private stretch of the beach.  I was completely let down. The place is waaaaaay overrated. I won't go back again. The beach is sub-par, and the friends there... well, let's just not call them friends.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Although my train stories might not be as interesting as  urlLink Ben's Trolley Stories , I hope that they might keep you from yawning at your desk for a couple of minutes at least.  The other day I was waiting for the train, wearing a respectable knee-length skirt when a big gust of wind came and blew the skirt around my head, a la Marilyn Monroe. I had my crutch in one hand, my briefcase under one arm, and was holding a newspaper, as well. Let's just say everyone got an eyeful... oops.   Also this week: standing on the platform, my sleek Gucci sunglasses, high heels, another respectable knee-length skirt, and Prada briefcase. An elderly man with a can walked over to me, and said, "Excuse me, miss. But I just wanted to tell you that you look gorgeous... and if ya got it, work it."  I guess I should have been flattered, but what was that second part about?! Work it? Please, that's my middle name.   One of my friends from Austin who lives in nyc has been staying with me in Connecticut this week. It's been nice having her around. I taught her to knit so now I have someone to knit with. We get double the looks now on the trains... two chicks glammed up knitting away...   For all you who know who Band Boy is... well, he's back in the picture. We've been having naughty aim conversations (I'm  that  bored at night in CT) and he's asked me to "stay with him" when I'm in TX next week... hehe   Also, for all you who have used my crutches over the past few months (ie. Farouche, Kate(r), etc) beware: someone up here to played with my crutches in April had a freak accident yesterday and broke her LEG! So the curse is coming true... watch your step...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ride the train back & forth from CT to nyc and I get stares from everyone on the train... possibly because I am in high heels with a crutch. Oh, and because I sit on the train and knit. The knitting and the crutch I guess are odd to the average person. And so far I've commuted only four days and the train conductors already know me and save me seat. Once again, the crutch, the knitting and the big fat scar on my knee must help singe me in their minds. Oh well. Stares are nothing new for me after all. I get them one way or another.  This past weekend, drove from CT to Long Island, usually a drive that takes over an hour. I did it in 34 minutes flat. But then again I had a hard time keeping the Beemer under 90 mph. A Ferrari Modena (not my choice, if I had a choice I'd get the classic Testarossa) zipped by me. I was going about 95mph, so for him to zip by me... well, he was going  fast . I had to speed up to catch him, of course. And just as I managed to catch him, he exited from the freeway. Next tune.   And everyone's been asking me about Elimidate. I don't think I can go to the meeting with the director this Wednesday. I have a dinner party to go to. I really don't wanna be slutty, nasty and bitchy on nat'l television...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Of all the random things that could happen to me...  Today, I got a casting call from Elimidate (that horrid, trashy show, that I know all us like to watch late at night when we're bored) to be on the show.  I go in on Wednesday to meet the casting director, but now I'm having second doubts... am not really trashy enough for that show...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bad Girl's Guide to Work: call your boss from Vermont and tell him your bus is canceled due to inclement weather (while looking out the window at a *gorgeous* &amp; sunny day). Boss offers to pay for flight back to nyc the same day. You tell your boss you called the airline, but that all the seats were all sold out (while in reality you sit and drink with friends). Tell boss the only solution is for you to come back Monday. He has all the office phone calls fowarded to your cell phone, so you can bill for you time while you sit on a fucking Greyhound.  Joy, oh joy.  All this for some time with old childhood friend and her family.... oh, and Vermont really is pretty.   ----- *Title compliments of  urlLink Kathleen  (and the Bad Girl Guides). 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, my boss & I went to lunch together. I fowarded all the calls from the office to my cell phone so I was working. Leasurely lunch. Lots of white wine. And lots of expensive Italian food. Is there a better way to pass an afternoon? Good wine, good food, all paid for, and of course, I billed as well.   Off to Vermont today. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I met up with two boys that I know in town. One is actually a patient, (oops) but since we "randomly" met at gay bar, there is no harm done. Walking into a bar FULL of guys is always fun. Not to toot my own horn, but when I walk into a room full of men, some of them (or most) usually turn to check me out. Not so last night. When I walked into the room with Phoenix all eyes turned to him. I wanted to cry. It was like being a in candy store with no money!! But hanging out in a bar full of gorgeous men was blast. And I've found that the guys, no matter what sexual tendencies they may have, always buy me drinks. Yay!  So, after lots of Jager shots and pints and pints of beers with the boys, I hopped in the subway and headed home. In my drunken state, I managaed to get off at the correct stop (yay!) but then I walked 5 blocks in the wrong direction. So I had to turn around and hike it back home lots of extra blocks (not yay).  Got looks from the snooty doormen. Stumbled into bed. Missed another one of  urlLink Kathleen's  drunk dials. Last night was one in a series of many that I've gotten all week. (Yay! I love that my friends think of me when they drink!! Esp ADD Kathleen! Yay!)  Today, I have lawyers in my ofc. I was sworn in for a deposition (not yay!) 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday night, I headed downtown to meet up with Spin, it being her birthday. The club she chose as her hangout, we found out, was the locale that The Cure had chosen as their after-concert party spot. And for all of you that don't know me, I LOVE 80's music. I was in heaven!! Robert Smith was loosen' hot in his makeup-- and he looked even hotter since I'd downed a few drinks.  Our friend Kay is in the City from D-Town and part of our conversation went as follows: Kay, "Good to see you! How are you?" F, "Great. I'm not wearing any underwear." ---- Later on, F, "Hey Kay, I smoked some pot last night?" Kay, "Really? I masturbated last night." ---- Kay, you're the coolest boy I know.    Getting drunk at The Delancy Club with The Cure was allright, but lots of Spin's friends couldn't get in because they got in late. So we moved. When I start drinking, I have no clue where I am in the City, but I am always good for following the fun.  We ended up at some bar, that I couldn't find again. Ever. Lots of shots from boys. One boy with a braces started to kiss my neck. That's when Kay started being my fake boyfriend.  Around 4am, we headed over (down? up?) to an apt where a bunch of guys lived. We decided to wanted to play beer pong (called Beirut up here). So we headed out and bought beer and pizza. While in line, I spied some cute boys, all with their shirts off. I surmised they were gay, and asked where the club is. The cute gay boy told me I was, "Fabulous! And we love fabulous girls like you. We love you, but we won't fuck you. So come to my club next weekend. You're on the list. Tell 'em I sent you." Sweet deal.  I lost miserably at peer pong. I was up till 7. We all crashed one atop the other. But when I woke up at 10am, I was ALONE. I hightailed it out of the apt, only to realize I had NO MONEY. I didn't know where I was, and I had spent all my money on cabs, beer, and pizza. Oops. I saw a metro stop and hopped in and headed uptown. The nearest stop that line stopped at was 51st street. I live on 72nd. So I hiked it uptown in the  rain , yes the rain, in my clubbing gear... with all the church-goers staring at me. The rain made my outfit a bit see-through, but hey, I  like  my red bra. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>