<Blog>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at  urlLink work  and bored half to death. i have done everything on my list (my boss leaves me lists of things to do) except the printing out stuff, because the printer is being a bitch and i don't know how to fix it. a woman just called-we're shooting her daughter's wedding in may-and she found out we also do invites. she described the invites her daughter wants-she was quoted TWELVE HUNDRED FREAKING DOLLARS for 125 invitations. that's outrageous! expecially since I bet I could make those invites with a little help from Kinko's for probably less that $300. (but i bet that wouldn't buy me nice envelopes)   anyway. got my wedding dress yesterday and it's too big! which is good, since i've been trying to lose weight and i was worried that the dress would just barely fit when i ordered it.  i tried it on when i was on the phone with my mom and started crying-it finally hit me that i am REALLY getting married. i'm gonna be a mess at the ceremony, i'm sure. and my cousin beth (a bridesmaid) has threatened to stop the ceremony and yell at me if i start crying, 'cause then she's going to cry.  my eczema is full-on hectic today-i am SO itchy! i want to just peel my skin off and put on some new, healthy skin. if anyone figures out how to do that, let me know!!! (i need the new skin so i don't bleed all over my wedding dress.)  all righty... (sorry, watched season 3 of sex and the city yesterday)... i'm gonna head on out of here. find something else to do to keep me occupied for that last hour i have to be here.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the maintenance guy is here fixing our thermostat. took me 3 months to convince the guys to turn on the heat (cheap bastards) and it turns out it's broken anyway. joy. so i'm attempting not to freeze while i hang out in my room to keep the dog from going nuts barking....   in other news, i'm worried about a friend who is very ill... and i wish i could do something about it, but unfortunately i really can't other than let her know i am there for her, which i have already done. i hate situations like this.  wedding drama seems to be over for now... i swear, this wedding is turning into a soap opera. and i hate soap operas.   UPDATE:yay! the heat is fixed!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HATE WEDDINGS. seriously, why did i ever think that a big wedding was a good idea? and why did i think that my in-laws being involved was a good idea? F this, dude. seriously. Vegas sounds like the best idea in the world to me and B just isn't as into it as I am. I'm emailing the dress place right now and seeing if they can put a rush order on my dress.  I'm gonna go play some DDR and stomp out all my frustration and attempt to get warm.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, this is the first time I've done this. I have a private online journal at  urlLink IAM.bme , but that is a membership-only site. My name is Jen, I'm 23, I'm a recent transplant to the Philly area from Syracuse, NY, and I'm an assistant for a wedding photographer. I work/live at Shooting Stars Photography urlLink  , and if you want to see what I do all day, check out the site-especially the later '03 weddings. I've done all the splash pages there, as well as the '04 ones. You might be surprised to see me listed in the '04 weddings category-I'm getting married on July 17th to my wonderful fiance, Brendan, whom I live with. We have a wonderful, adorable, silly 2-year-old border collie named Jackson Pollock (or Jack, named after the  urlLink painter  and Edward Norton's character in Fight Club). He is the reason I am perpetually covered in dog hair.   I am not much of a video game player, but I am addicted to Karaeoke Revolution and Dance Dance Revolution Max 2 for Playstation 2, much to the amusement of Brendan and our other roommates, whose idea of good video games involve lots and lots of violence. Plus, they get to watch me warble at the top of my lungs and dance like an idiot, oftentimes almost falling over. At least my friends Tom and Brian (our best man) come over and join me in the idiocy. I also have a penchant for a good board game, usually scrabble or life.   That's it about me so far-further bulletins as events warrant!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so a few weeks ago i uploaded all my CDs to itunes on my computer. today i put it on random and listend to stuff while i was cleaning. a song came on by my friend keegan's former band, Roman Candle http://www.romancandlemusic.com. And then on their page there was a link to Keegan's own page-apparently he's got some EPs released now http://www.keegandewitt.com. I haven't seen Keegan since the end of freshman year at Purchase-I had SUCH a huge crush on him. But I was engaged to the asshole, and he had a gorgeous girlfriend. My friend Eric used to pick on me that we were "totally fucking" and didn't tell anyone... never happened, I'm afraid. He introduced me to a lot of amazing music and art, especially Elliott Smith. I DP'd (director of photography) his film. We were great friends. I find myself thinking about Keegan from time to time, in a "hey I wonder what's going on with him now" sort of way. So I signed his guestbook and told him to drop me a line... is that pathetic? 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just listed a TON of  urlLink stuff  on ebay.... yay for cleaning out closets! and losing weight.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      listening to the cure at work and drinking your first cup of coffee at 4 pm is fun. I got a B+ in my class, which means that i am FINALLY done with college! now I just have to get my transcript sent to SU and they'll send me my diploma. Which I should get bronzed or something after all the shit I had to go through to get it...can you even bronze paper? I don't think you can... so there'll probably be an altar to it in my new apartment or something. Or perhaps a flashing neon frame... That would be classy.  I am SO ready to move out of my current apartment... I love Noah to death, but Steve has stepped on my very. last. nerve. And it's not worth sitting down with him to talk about it, not because it's not important, but because Steve is the kind of guy who won't get the point that it's not funny or cool to make repeated death threats against me and my dog. Especially when there's absolutely no reason for it. Context: I walked into the kitchen to get a soda, the dog and I had been hanging out in my room watching a movie, and Steve opens his big mouth. I didn't even say anything to him before that, I was minding my own business. Ass. The only thing that is keeping me & B from moving NOW is that we don't want Noah to have to pay double rent, which is what it would be if we moved out. And we can't pay 2 rents at the same time-we just don't have the financial capability. Rrrrgh...  Anyway, I should get back to work. Perhaps I can convince B to go see Shrek 2 with me tonight, or at least this weekend.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>