<Blog>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1.	Give the  processes  involved in tissue processing and give the importance of each process.  2.	Give the  difference  between infiltration and embedding.  3.	Give 5 common  problems  encountered during embedding, the causes, and the solutions to resolve them.  4.	Give the difference between trimming and sectioning.  5.	Give 5 common problems encountered during sectioning, the causes, and the solutions to resolve them.  6.	What is Immunohistochemistry? 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Mr. dela Cruz is a 65-year-old male weighing 250 lbs, standing 5'5" tall. He experienced an episode of body weakness 3 days prior to consultation. Upon initial evaluation of the attending physician, he noted that his appetite has increased, as well as his water intake due to excessive thirst, and an increased urine output. What do you think is the clinical diagnosis of the patient? What tests should be performed to confirm your diagnosis? What caused the increase in water in take as well as an increased urine output?    2. Mrs. Evangelista is a 43-year-old female, married to an active seaman with two children. 2 weeks prior to admission, the patient experienced episodes of body weakness with a bloated feeling. Slight discoloration of the skin was evident 1 day prior to consultation ultrasound of the biliary tree and Blood bilirubin level was requested. Ultrasound reveals a slight unidentified mass on the gall bladder presumptive of a stone. Laboratory examination reveals a high total bilirubin, normal indirect bilirubin and an increased direct bilirubin. Urine urobilinogen is decreased. What is the reason why the total bilirubin is increased? What caused the increased direct bilirubin? What caused the normal indirect bilirubin? What do you think is the clinical diagnosis of the patient? Was the ultrasound report correlate with the clinical signs and symptoms presented as well as the laboratory results?    3. Mr. San Pedro is a 78-year-old male working as a priest. His annual physical examination reveals and increased acid phosphatase. Upon consultation, the attending physician requested for his PSA level. Noting that the PSA level is increased, what is the correlation of the acid phosphatase with the PSA level? What clinical condition is presented here?    4. A 35 year old male was suffering from difficulty in urinating with slight pain in the lower back. Upon consultation, the physician requested for his serum BUN and Creatinine. Laboratory results reveal an increased BUN and creatinine. The creatinine level is twice the upper limit. Knowing this, the doctor requested for a 24 hour urine creatinine clearance. The result of the creatinine clearance is low. What do you think is the reason for the low creatinine clearance as correlated with the high serum creatinine level. What is the purpose of performing creatinine clearance for a nephro-patient 
     
    
</post>


<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      BLONDE AND BLUE EYES   When I was little, I wanted what many Filipino children all over the country  wanted. I wanted to be blond, blue-eyed, and white.  I thought -- if I just wished hard enough and was good enough, I'd wake up  on Christmas morning with snow outside my window and freckles across my  nose!  More than four centuries under western domination does that to you. I have  sixteen cousins. In a couple of years, there will just be five of us left in  the Philippines, the rest will have gone abroad in search of "greener  pastures." It's not just an anomaly; it's a trend; the Filipino diaspora.  Today, about eight million Filipinos are scattered around the world.  There are those who disapprove of Filipinos who choose to leave. I used to.  Maybe this is a natural reaction of someone who was left behind, smiling for  family pictures that get emptier with each succeeding year. Desertion, I  called it. My country is a land that has perpetually fought for the freedom  to be itself. Our heroes offered their lives in the struggle against the  Spanish, the Japanese, the Americans. To pack up and deny that identity is  tantamount to spitting on that sacrifice.  Or is it? I don't think so, not anymore. True, there is no denying this  phenomenon, aided by the fact that what was once the other side of the world  is now a twelve-hour plane ride away. But this is a borderless world, where  no individual can claim to be purely from where he is now. My mother is of  Chinese descent, my father is a quarter Spanish, and I call myself a pure  Filipino-a hybrid of sorts resulting from a combination of cultures.  Each square mile anywhere in the world is made up of people of different  ethnic ties, with national identities and individual personalities. Because  of this, each square mile is already a microcosm of the world. In as much as  this blessed spot that is England is the world, so is my neighbourhood back  home.  Seen this way, the Filipino Diaspora, or any sort of dispersal of  populations, is not as ominous as so many claim. It must be understood. I  come from a Third World country, one that is still trying mightily to get  back on its feet after many years of dictatorship. But we shall make it,  given more time. Especially now, when we have thousands of eager young minds  who graduate from college every year. They have skills. They need jobs. We  cannot absorb them all.  A borderless world presents a bigger opportunity, yet one that is not so  much abandonment but an extension of identity. Even as we take, we give  back. We are the 40,000 skilled nurses who support the UK's National Health  Service. We are the quarter-of-a-million seafarers manning most of the  world's commercial ships.We are your software engineers in Ireland, your  construction workers in the Middle East, your doctors and caregivers in  North America, and, your musical artists in West End.  Nationalism isn't bound by time or place. People from other nations migrate  to create new nations, yet still remain essentially who they are. British  society is itself an example of a multi-cultural nation, a melting pot of  races, religions, arts and cultures. We are, indeed, in a borderless world!  Leaving sometimes isn't a matter of choice. It's coming back that is. The  Hobbits of the shire travelled all over Middle-Earth, but they chose to come  home, richer in every sense of the word. We call people like these  balikbayans or the 'returnees' -- those who followed their dream, yet choose  to return and share their mature talents and good fortune.  In a few years, I may take advantage of whatever opportunities come my way.  But I will come home. A borderless world doesn't preclude the idea of a  home. I'm a Filipino, and I'll always be one. It isn't about just geography;  it isn't about boundaries! It's about giving back to the country that shaped  me.  And that's going to be more important to me than seeing snow outside my  windows on a bright Christmas morning.  Mabuhay. and Thank you. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Life can be so simple. Waking up each morning, eating breakfast then going to work. At twelve noon you take your lunch after which is back to work perhaps. Have a little snack just before 5pm. Go home after 5, watch your favorite telenovelas, eat your dinner take a bath then go to sleep. During weekends a little chit-chat with the friends perhaps or a little Saturday night out, just to ease the tension made by the previous week and getting ready for the week ahead. But still life is simple. That is, if your life has not yet been infected by the disease called Makititis. This disease was discovered by a soon to be doctor known to many as Meme. Signs and symptoms exhibited are the following: uncontrollable emotions especially with the same specie (with or without relation to the definitive host) storming around the patient. Mind and body coordination is impaired especially when using body language. There is also a distinct affinity to the opposite sex (especially with those species whose names end with an MD, FPSP, or even USNavy -  Joke) (RMT din ata pero medjo minimal in effect) as well as slight affinity to the same sex who prefer the same sex (I think so?). Slight discomfort in conversations using extreme lasalistic english with atenean intent with matching paulinian accent. High affinity to family especially with the Father and the oldest single brother. There is also extreme outburst of feelings related to memory. There are also episodes of laughter especially with friends. The patient could also experience unpredictable madness towards you even if the reason is never you. To anyone who experienced these signs and symptoms, you are infected with the disease. Isolation must never be performed and treatment is never recommended. This disease must be spread to all human race. This disease is the causative agent of the syndrome called: wild life syndrome which then progresses into memorable life. Unluckily, this disease only affects one human being at a time, although friends would experience the signs and symptoms at a certain degree depending on your affinity to the disease. To date, there is only one patient with this case with the full-blown disease. Some are also infected but to a minimal extent. Come to think, man doesnt want to get sick (sabi nga diba: Bawal magkasakit!). In the contrary, I am infected with this disease and I love it (her). And I want to die with it. For the time being, sorry guys, you cant get the full-blown stage of the disease coz I occupy the spot.   Love is given, she gives her love in a very unique way, and I love her for that and never will I regret the day I said: I love her. (Kahit maraming umaligid man sa kanya o sa akin!)    	 		 __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Friends.  Fun.  Try the all-new Yahoo! Messenger. http://messenger.yahoo.com/  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        We are the Reason  Gary Valenciano  As little children we would dream of Christmas morn  And all the gifts and toys  We knew we'd find, but we never realized  A baby boy, one blessed night  Gave us the greatest gift of our life   Chorus:  We are the reason that He gave His life  We are the reason Jesus suffered and died  To a world that was lost  He gave all He could give  To show us the reason to live   As the years went by, we learned more of our gifts  And giving of ourselves and what they mean  On a dark and cloudy day  A man hung dying in the rain  Because of love, because of love  Because of love   Chorus:  We are the reason that He gave His life  We are the reason why the Lord suffered and died  To a world that was lost  He gave all He could give  To show us the reason to live  To live...  To live...   Coda:  Every time I see the cross  I'm reminded that He gave His  life  For you and me...   Chorus:  We are the reason that He gave His life  We are the reason Jesus suffered and died  To a world that was lost  He gave all He could give  To show us the reason to live   We are the reason but  He is the reason we live  Thank you, my Jesus  Thank you, Jesus  I thank you, Lord, my Jesus  We thank you, Jesus  For God so saved the world...  (Jesus)  (Thank you)  (You're worthy to be praised...)  (The name above all names)   		  Do you Yahoo!? Friends.  Fun.  urlLink Try the all-new Yahoo! Messenger 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         People of the world, please bear with me. I want to shout to the world: I'M IN LOVE!   &nbsp;   My problem is, I think she doesn't like me. SAD. but that's ok. It's still a first impression thing. The road to success is never smooth or what ever. Haaay.     		  Do you Yahoo!? Friends.  Fun.  urlLink Try the all-new Yahoo! Messenger 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Just nothing   It's weird, I met a long lost friend through the friendster site. We sent messages through the sites then we decided just to text each other. We became textmates. Just as we were getting to know more of each other a topic weird as can be made a good effect on me. (I don't know to her but we were closer than we were-my presumption) We had an argument with regards to meeting. We were really not that friends during our college days but we knew each other. Only that her previous boyfriend and I were dormates (thinking of a good relationship or in this case a good connection - whew). So the text war broke and its all about me being a complete stranger to her and the other legal facts about it but for me it's bearable. The sad part came when she stopped texting me so I felt bad because I offended her. Actually she said so with her last text. My words might be offending  but my intentions were not. Some of my girl-friends thinked the same way. I was wrong. And I admit I was wrong. And I asked forgiveness. After two weeks, the angels were sent and gave me all the details on how I could contact her. To date, I have talked to her at work, at home, and even saw her during her duty and brought dinner. The weird thing is that, It felt so good. As if I won in the million peso lottery (pero sana nga-kahit hindi ako tumataya). Previously I had sleepless nights,now it became worst awake even until 3 in the morning just thinking of her. Talking about weird things. But this time its a very good feeling. Weird feeling. I admit, I am weird. But I liked it.to sum it up. I think I like her.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Please visit this site: tcqcinterns.blogspot.com instead of this site. thankyou. for any suggestion please e-mail me through gbong19@yahoo.com. Good Luck to all.
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>