<Blog>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Eminem aside (can’t one be both overrated and creative?) you missed my boat on Courtney Love.  Borrowing Neitzche’s polemic on Wagner let me say my criticism for Love should in no way be mistaken as praise for anyone else in music.  Love is still head and shoulders above 95% of her industry.  I’ll be honest and admit that you’re “seething hatred” bothers me, not because I require universal praise for love, but you spew such contempt without being familiar with her work.  The “I hate Courtney Love” fan club is large, I’m probably in the minority- someone who not only appreciates her works but acknowledges the fact publicly, -but the club seems to hate the woman, not her work.  Courtney Love has released four albums, I wonder how much of that work the club has heard, yourself included.  I bet not much.  Courtney Love is an artist.  She’s angry, unpredictable, funny, sad and yes a bit mad.  But she also forces us to look ourselves, to re-examine and re-evaluate what exactly is art.  I’m with you, look at the art for what it is.  You’d have to wretch my copy of  Pirates of the Caribbean  from my cold, dead hands, but movies, music, magazines and popular culture can’t be strict entertainment.  Yes we need to be entertained and transported from our everyday lives, but popular culture also needs to move us, make us think, put into words that which we feel and recognize and illuminate what is both good and bad in ourselves.  Though I agree creativity as a whole is lacking, I don’t share your pessimism.  To borrow a worn out cliché- the glass may be half-empty (or more so), but what we have is so rich, so vibrant, I’m o.k.  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Your last post is, without a doubt, the hardest post I have ever had the pleasure of responding to. Not because of the legitimacy of you arguments, or the strength of the proclamations you made, simply because we are putting a few of the discussions to bed and I don't want to drag them out anymore than you do. So with your Josh Schwartz "one word disagreement" I will concur with you, I do think he is on the verge of something big, and you obviously think he is strolling down the right path. You must give me one thing though, you must concede the fact that Josh has started off better than any writer(TV or movie) that has crossed our paths in a long time. As for the Eisner thing, maybe I see a connection between two people that I have a serious dislike for, Eisner and Dubya, that doesn't truly exist. But I do think Eisner would be hard pressed to put a check in the Kerry box come November.  Now to the new aspects of your latest post. The White Stripes, I must admit, I do not listen to them. I have tried but they are not my particular cup of tea. So trying to argue against your superior knowledge on this topic would surely not end up in my favor. Although I do believe Eminem is quite creative, I also believe that he is possibly one of the most over-rated performers in the music industry. He has created some of the original and cutting edge songs I have ever heard,  I am  is one of the darkest and most insightful songs in the last twenty years. But the esteem most people hold him in is absolute garbage, he is not the greatest thing since sliced bread, he is a rapper who has an original sound, nothing more.  Michael Cunningham and Eric Schlosser...Absolutely no idea.   I should've expected that you would bring up Courtney Love, but it completely shocked me. You must have known that this would not be topic that would sit well with me. I have a seething hatred for Courtney Love, and maybe that blinds from this so called creativity, but what I see is a drug-addicted alcoholic with therapy bills that have to be running in the millions of dollars. When I listen to any of Love's music this is what I hear: She tries to play the guitar(which she fails miserably at), her scratchy voice reminds me of the woman you see at the end of the bar who has smoked three packs a day for the last thirty years, and her lyrics she could have stolen from a 5 year old girl who was crying and yelling at her parents in the next room. I agree with you that Britney and Christina have very little talent, but Courtney has less. Remember one thing - Madness is not creativity.  I mentioned in my last post that I would comment on the state of the magazine world so here I go. I agree with you 100%. I obviously have a different taste in magazines than you do(I wouldn't be caught dead reading  Vogue  or  Vanity Fair ), but the magazines that I used to like have gotten incredibly weak in the last few years.  Sports Illustrated  isn't exactly pop-culture(though I think sports does play a role in pop-culture), but it is now scandal driven, and articles are written about players in which the press either adores or hopes to tear down(ie. adores Tim Duncan, despises Barry Bonds).  Entertainment Weekly  is an occasional good read but it's only constant is Gliberman/Schartzbaum, the second best pair of critics out there.  It is a pretty bad state of affairs when only after four posts I have run dry on people I think are creative. Now there are probably people out there that I have not thought of, and that's my fault, but there is a serious lack of creativity in Hollywood today. This will be my final post on this topic, I look forward to the next topic and I would like to know if you think creativity in tinseltown is as rare as I do. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm feeling a bit under the weather so I will make it brief.  I'm surprised you reacted so strongly to my Josh Schwartz rebuttal.  I don't want to dig in too much deeper, rather let's chalk it up to a disagreement about one word.  You say verge (meaning edge of or threshold) I say path.  As to the Eisner debate I don't think you want to begin a philosophical disection of free will.  I wouldn't go so far to say "Eisner has done  everything  in his power to keep the film from the screen" because if Eisner did in fact everything in his power, it would never be seen.  Because it will likely be released I think Eisner did his reasonable best to stop it, but stopped short of using every drop of power and favor at his disposal.  On the final note fear of retaliation does not make you for the oppressor.  Now that I've finished with the semantics lets get back to creativity.  Regarding  Harry Potter  I've neither seen the films nor read the book but based on the voracity of your enthusiasm I have no doubts about your testimony.  My own literary suggestions include Michael Cunningham and Eric Schlosser.  Writing has been around for hundreds of years but these two have been able to read both new and original.  One of the most creative acts working in music today is The White Stripes.  I'm not going to say I don't have a few issues, at some point Jack White will have to marry and divorce a bassist, but Jack's guitar work and blues influences are taking rock music into new directions.  The other breath of fresh air in music is Eminem.  Yes his attacks on his mother, his girlfriend and homosexuals are predictable and pedantic but his stream of consciousness lyrics are the wittiest use of words in music.  My final musing will no doubt surprise you but rather than epitomizing musics lack of creativity with Christian Auguliera or Britney Spears I suggest Courtney Love.  That isn't to say Spears and co. are as talented as Love, they're not, nor am I saying Love has lost her talent and creativity, she hasn't, but she has become a caricature.  Her live, electric unpredictability has been replaced with incoherent, junkie ramblings and poor behavior. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The top five shows on television in my opinion are:  The Shield, CSI, The OC, The Soprano's , and  Nip/Tuck . Now before any of you rake me over the coals for some or all of my choices, let me remind you that this is my opinion. You mention in your last post that the debut season of  Deadwood  is not yet over so you cannot yet make that proclamation. Well I have not seen  Deadwood  so I cannot cast my opinion in either direction on that show. As for the five that I mentioned, I feel that in looking at the current season's they have gone through I must say that  The OC  nudges out  The Shield  for the top spot. Even though there are three episodes left in an already exhilarating season of  The Shield , I felt  The OC  was stronger. No show, that I have seen, meshes comedy and drama better. It's ability to make you laugh is uncanny, but it's ability to touch you on an emotional level is what sets it aside from all the rest. I believe that everyone see's part of themselves in some character on the show. I myself am a Ryan, a truly good heart but an uncanny ability to get myself into trouble.  Now let me clear up some things that you took out of context or didn't interpret correctly from my last post. 1)  I disagree with the extent of your praise for Josh Schwartz. He's a gifted writer and adaptable producer, but to position him on the verge of Quentin Tarantino, after only 27 episodes seems reckless.  I said in my post that I believe that he will soon be placed in the Quentin Tarantino category. What I meant by this was that throughout his first season he often showed signs of tremendous brilliance in his writings. I do believe that he has the potential to reach that platform, but he has not yet reached it. He does have more to prove, but no writer that I can think of(not even your beloved Charlie Kaufman) has started as strong as Josh. 2)  Disney, under Eisner, has agreed to sell the film back to the Bob and Harvey Weinstein, who are free to find another distributor for the film.  When I said that Eisner has done everything in his power to keep this movie out of theaters I was 100% accurate. Eisner has been back into a corner, by the press and the public, and had no choice but to sell the rights to Harvey and Bob Weinstein.  3) If Eisner is afraid of Jeb Bush withholding tax breaks that are being given to Walt Disney World, doesn't that mean that in some way, shape or form that George W. Bush is his candidate. Isn't Dubya essentially having his brother buy the votes of Disney's board of directors. In all honesty, I may be wrong, but this is the particular spin that I have chosen to put on  Fahrenheit 9/11  topic.  Okay! On to creativity. I had a little trouble thinking of who my next post would revolve around. As I was walking around late at night, trying to find a movie that I wanted to fall asleep to, I saw my next post sitting on my windowsill. Undeniable creativity lies within the pages of J.K. Rowling's Harry Potter series. Now my love for both the books and the movies causes me to write this post in a different format.   The Books . It was only two days after Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone was released in theaters when I went out and purchased the book. It took me all of two days to read it. It is without a doubt the most creative thing that I have ever read or heard about. Harry Potter is a book that appeals to all ages, from my 80 year old grandmother, to my 7 year old niece tiffany, to me, a 23 year old single guy. J.K. Rowling has created a whole new world that you can't help but get lost in. Places like Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry where young witches and wizards go to learn the magical arts. Diagon Alley, where wizards can find anything they need from a new wand to a brand new racing broom. As the title states, the series revolves around the exploits of young Harry Potter. Harry became one of the most famous wizards of the last millennium when as a baby he amazingly defeated the Dark Lord Voldemort. The books are also centered around Harry's two best friends Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger. Ron and Hermione are just as intriguing as Harry, but most importantly they add a great deal of depth to both Harry and the story in general. There are so many vital characters that I cannot possibly talk about them all. You have Hagrid the Keeper of Keys and Grounds at Hogwarts, Profesor Severus Snape the Potions teacher and head of Slytherin House, Aunt Petunia and Uncle Dursley, Draco Malfoy who is Harry's biggest rival(with the one exception being Voldemort), Albus Dumbledore the Headmaster at Hogwarts and the greatest wizard of the last century. The list goes on and on. I haven't even mentioned some of my favorite characters. If anyone ever said that J.K. Rowling lacked creativity I would be forced to thrash them.    The Movies.  It wasn't until I saw the first movie that I decided to read the books. The movies are so special that it made someone who didn't really read for pleasure want to read them. The casting has been incredible for this movie, and I'm not talking about all the big British stars they have put in it, but for the virtual unknowns they cast in the lead roles. Daniel Radcliffe is so charming and so amazing in the emotional role of Harry that you find yourself getting so attached to him and really feel for him because of all the tragedies in his life. Rupert Grint, who plays Ron Weasley, has his role down. The goofy and gangly sidekick is truly endearing as the youngest boy in an all wizarding family. You get a real sense of determination out of Ron, a determination to get out from the shadows of all his brothers. And then you have Emma Watson. Emma had never acted before she auditioned for the role of Hermione Granger, which is astounding because she has stolen many scenes in the first two movies and I am sure she will continue to do the same throughout the series. Watson was a huge fan of the book, I even read that she had memorized all of Hermione's quotes from the first book, and she still is. Although I believe Hermione to be probably the funnest role to play, it also is one of the most difficult. The right combination of attitude, intelligence and sass can't be easy to find. My hat is off to all three young stars. The movie is also great because it stay so true to the book that nearly all the quotes used in the book are used in the script. With a movie like  Harry Potter  it is so important to stay true to the story because the fans absolutely love the books, and with J.K. holding creative control over the movies, they no doubt will be great adaptations. The only question that I have for the Movies yet to come is whether Michael Gambon can fill the huge shoes left by Richard Harris in the role of Albus Dumbledore.  Seriously though, I think my post has ran a little long. I will touch in on your distain for the state of the magazine world next time. Sorry, I can tend to get a little involved when I talk about Harry Potter. Until next time, this is Nick signing out. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ironically our little website has followed  The O.C. ’s trajectory- stolen item (post topic/car) leads to a happy ending (sibling enthusiasm about a primetime soap/fraternal bond between friends on said nighttime soap)  To be fair I should refrain from proclaiming the best show on television until  Deadwood ’s debut season commences, but there’s no other show on television I glance at the clock and think,  only two more days, six more hours , like I do with  The O.C.   As strong as our mutual affection for the show, I disagree with the extent of your praise for Josh Schwartz.  He’s a gifted writer and adaptable producer, but to position him on the verge of Quentin Tarantino, after only 27 episodes seems reckless.  Tarantino didn’t master his craft right out of the gate, he cut his teeth on  Natural Born Killers ,  True Romance  and  Reservoir Dogs  before his brilliance came to fruition in  Pulp Fiction .  An essential element to the uber category both Tarantino and Charlie Kaufman preside is their refusal to rest on their laurels.  With each movie they are constantly pushing themselves as artists.  Schwartz’s age and rookie success bode well that he might, someday, join Tarantino’s rank, but more needs to be seen before that assessment is made.  When this topic began if you’d given me a million guesses as to who’s name you would bring up, I never would have guessed Michael Eisner.  Before I address your points, let me clear up two statements you made in your post.  1.)	 He’s done everything in his power to keep  Fahrenheit 9/11  out of American theaters.   Disney, under Eisner, has agreed to sell the film back to the Bob and Harvey Weinstein, who are free to find another distributor for the film. 2.)	 The reason Eisner doesn’t want the movie released is because it paints his candidate in a bad light.   To my knowledge Eisner has not come out for or against either presidential candidate. Michael Moore has speculated that the reason Eisner is not distributing the film is he fears Jeb Bush will withhold tax breaks for Walt Disney World in Florida as retribution.  Like you I believe  Fahrenheit 9/11  will see the light of day. Taking a page from Mel Gibson’s playbook there’s too much controversy for it to not be released.  I wholeheartedly agree with you that political movies, now more than ever, are needed.  In the late 60’s and early 70’s there seemed to be a cycle in which popular culture affected the political which in turn affected popular culture and so on.  Nowadays in a post 9/11 world led by our divided electorate, our films feel more hermetically sealed from reality than ever.  You stated wonderment at how bad Eisner has been for creativity in the entertainment industry.  I would take the argument a step further, that it’s the enormous, multifaceted media conglomerates with so many operations but only one goal-profits, that has undermined creativity in Hollywood.  Enterprises as large as Disney are so complicated and diverse they have to be run by moneymen.  Eisner and his contemporaries weren’t hired to be creative, they were hired to be CEO’s and as CEO’s they seem to be pretty good for their companies are all making money but our complaint (or at least my complaint) is money men shouldn’t be in charge of creative enterprises, like movies, music and television.  As a political science student I have to shake my head when people complain how low the political discourse has fallen.  As ugly as it gets John Kerry has never challenged President Bush to a duel, as Aaron Burr did to Alexander Hamilton.  Even though political debate hasn’t bottomed out I can’t help but grimace- we’re more advanced than any republic in history and yet our political debate is being argued and shaped by Fox News on the right and Michael Moore on the left.  An avid reader I have an unfortunate weakness for magazines, unfortunate because the state of magazine journalism is so dismal.  Rollingstone, at one time the voice of a generation, died the day they put the Olson Twins on the cover.  Vanity Fair was once a brilliant skewing and celebration of high society and celebrity, but today offers nothing more than banal celebrity puff pieces and untrustworthy agenda driven articles on the government.  Creativity, so alive on TV, is dead in magazines.  Or nearly dead, the one exception being the online magazine The Slate.  Fair, measured, insightful, and intelligent, The Slate is the only place to look for news and commentary.  Like The New Yorker, but interesting, Slate articles should be read for their writing as much as their content.  In fact, the only weakness in The Slate’s independent, original stable of journalists is occasional contributor and VF staple Christopher Hitchens.  I will now cede the floor, smiling that we have creatively expanded the scope of our discussion, for this one topic at least.  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I must say that this is a first for this website. You stole my next post. I was going to dedicate pretty much this whole post to a show that at first I made strong efforts to not watch. I felt it was just another  90210 , and to me, that show had run it's course after about the third season. You yourself(Courtney) had told me on several occasions that it was a good show. That it was extremely funny, but didn't let that diminish the drama of the show. I still wasn't convinced. It took three of my friends(you know who you are) to actually convince me to watch the show. They told me about there favorite characters, they told me about the love triangles. They did anything and everything to get me to watch the show. So one night, I was on instant messenger with one of them, she told me that  The OC  was on. With nothing else to watch I reluctantly tuned in. With her telling me who everybody was, telling me about who was into who, or who dated who I slowly started to enjoy watching the show. It was full of wit and sarcasm(sarcasm is my favorite form of humor), in watching one episode I became enthralled in it. Borrowing tapes from a friend to catch up on all the episodes. The characters are so diverse, so intriguing, that it is like nothing that is or ever has been on TV. From Ryan, the bad boy with a heart of gold. To Seth, the avid comic book fan who creates the uber holiday known as Chrismakkuh(a polymerazation of Christmas and Channikah). The creativity that lies within the pen of Josh Schwartz is immeasurable, I believe soon we will put him in the Quentin Tarantino category. Now there still is three episodes I have not seen, but I would have to say that the Thanksgiving episode is the best. It was so crazy, it brought every character in the show to the same house. You have Jimmy and Julie fighting about Marissa, Seth entertaining his two ladies, and Kirsten getting drunk. It was also hilarious to watch Sandy, Seth and Ryan do whatever they can to keep Kirsten from helping cook anything, for what she touches can no longer be considered edible. It is, without question, the best show on TV.  Now that I have expressed my anger to the fact that you stole my post, I feel like commenting on someone that lacks creativity. Michael Eisner is that somebody. He has done everything in his power to keep Michael Moore's Fahrenheit 9/11 out of American theaters. He stated that it doesn't fit in with Disney's family friendly movies. He must of forgot about that cinematic masterpiece  Kill Bill Vol. 1 . Wouldn't call that a "family friendly" movie(unless we're talking about the Manson family). Eisner has told his critics that he doesn't feel they should release a politically charged movie in an election year. To me it seems like there is no better time to release it, politics are all over the news so why not have them jump from the little screen to the big screen. It is obvious why Eisner doesn't want this movie released, it doesn't portray his candidate it a good light. Everyone knows this is the reason, he just won't admit it. Now I am not ultra-liberal like Moore, but his films always deliver a message.  Bowling for Columbine  was, at times, a funny movie, but it's true message was that firearms are to easy to obtain, and play to big of a role in society. Eisner's attempts to keep Fahrenheit 9/11 away from American audiences has seemingly failed, it just won the top prize over at the Cannes Film Festival and all signs point to it being released sometime in the coming months. Michael Moore - 1  Michael Eisner - 0.  With that, I will end my post. I look forward to seeing your take on my Eisner critique, I just feel he has been incredibly bad for Hollywood. He is a selfish, arrogant ass-face(reference from  The OC ) that is completely out of touch with the American audience. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm confused.  Tarantino is so creative it goes without saying, but Kaufman, who you admit is a creative writer, isn't in the same category?  Say what you want about Kaufman, scream that Adaptation was the worst movie ever made, but do not say it wasn't creative.  In fact if I had to rank a list I would say, as writers, Kaufman is more creative than Tarantino.  (Note: I'm not saying better, just slightly more creative)  I'm glad to see we're on the same TV page and will return the favor regarding movies.  I think David Fincher is an astoundingly talented director who has yet to make a bad film.  Some have cited his work for being too cold or dark but I think that's a cheap criticism.  Fincher, in tackling dark, murky themes, doesn't talk down to the audience, which is all too rare these days.  The other reason I particularly love his work is no one creates mood like he does.  From the sets to the lighting to the costumes to the camera work I believe anyone who's seen Fincher's previous stuff could pick out his work from a ten second clip.  It's that distinctive.  Yesterday I promised you my highpoint of creativity so here it is-  The O.C.   To illustrate how creative this show is when it first hit the air I wasn't a fan.  I found the troubled bad boy in the rich environment, attracted to the girl next door and getting into fist fights at every opportunity, predictable and trite.  But a funny thing happened, the show began to let its characters grow and found its voice.    The best thing about  The O.C.  is it takes its characters but not itself seriously.  The comic book loving Seth Cohen is a smart dork who pretends he doesn't care to belong but secretly does, expertly played by Adam Brody.  Even after making friends and landing his dream girl Seth still hasn't relinquished his geeky habit of not knowing when to shut up,like at his meeting with Summers dad.  Peter Gallagher and Kelly Rowan as Sandy and Kirsten Cohen, have created one of the most positive, realistic couples on TV.  Yes they have it all, but are constantly juggling to maintain it.  (Extra kudos to Josh Schwartz for making the mom the powerful breadwinner which dad is cool with)  Summer's character began as a one note bitch, but has grown into a refreshing mixture of frankness, self-consciousness and tenderness.  Everyone in the cast, with the exception of Mischa Barton, have brought new dimensions to usually one dimensional soap opera characters.  What makes  The O.C.  so creative in my book is tweaks the genre.  It was suppose to be a  90210  for this generation but with its pop culture references and smart, touching characters its put a new spin on television.  Schwartz and company's scripts are full of some of the funniest lines on television (divinely executed by the way).  We could spend a whole two weeks trying to decide the funniest line.  Names, characters and throw away quotes are dropped in one episode only to return later down the road, making the series work as a whole, best witnessed by the witty reoccurance of The Valley.  The Thanksgiving episode was perhaps one of the funniest examples of situation comedy ever.  Schwartz, the youngest writer/producer to ever run a television series, isn't afraid to change things up if something is not working.  How long was the Kelly/Dylan/Brenda love triangle dragged out?  Seth got together with Anna on New Year's Eve and had broken up and began dating Summer by Valentine's Day.  In no other format of popular culture do I see artists more willing to rewrite the rules than in television.  From  The O.C  to  The Sopranos  to Comedy Central creators aren't merely thinking outside the box, they're rethinking and reconfiguring the box itself. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think throwing Charlie Kaufman into the same category as Quentin Tarantino is a bit of a stretch. I will admit he is a creative writer, but unlike Tarantino, Kaufman can get so wrapped up in his creativity that he loses sight of other important aspects of the movie(ie. emotion, character development). Tarantino knows better than anyone else how to use his creativity to enhance every aspect of a film. That is all I am going to say on the never ending 'Great Kaufman Debate' we have drawn out through two topics now.  I feel you might be being a little generous with saying that 10% of television is the most creative block of all entertainment. Are you telling me that if you went through the TV Guide, one out of every ten shows you would consider interesting. No way, one out of twenty, maybe. So in my opinion it's about 5%, for we cannot forget the trash that haunts the late night and the early morning. But I will agree with you that it is possibly the most creative component that makes up pop-culture.  The few times I have seen  Arrested Development  I have enjoyed it immensely. The dry, witty comedy that is lost on most people, brings me back to the days of  Rushmore  and  The Royal Tenenbaums . Both this show and these two movies are so smart, so complete(greatly written, acted and directed) that it seems like there creators think on a higher plain than all of us commoners. My favorite episode is the one in which they use a flight of stairs as a family car, and Portia De Rossi's character gets stranded in a tree when Jason Batemen steals the flight of stairs from her. Someone who can create this kind of storyline and make it work receives my utmost respect and adoration.   South Park  is the greatest cartoon ever.  Chapelle's Show  is the funniest sketch comedy show that I have ever seen.  Reno 911  is so stupid it shows us how often stupidity and genius walk hand and hand. And  The Daily Show , oh my god, it is the most accurate depiction of what is going on in the world today. But instead of being sad and depressing(like all local and national newscasts),  The Daily Show  is one of the funniest shows on TV. Comedy Central is re-defining TV comedies, it's a breath of fresh air in polluted environment, that's why I would say that right now it is the pinnacle of comedic TV programming.  I believe David Fincher has given us some of the best films of the last ten years.  SE7EN , after a brief opening scene, it immediately cuts to a highly stylized title sequence. An intricate collage of books and photos, scissors and razors, and blood and skin eerily captures the dark, graphic tone of Fincher's intriguing mystery. The film cleverly avoids depicting most acts of violence onscreen, focusing instead on the cryptic remains of the crimes, allowing viewers to investigate along with the detectives. A movie like this is a one of a kind piece of artwork that is often imitated( Taking Lives  is a prime example of this), but this movie has a magic that cannot be copied, It is simply a marvel of modern filmaking.   You are not your job. You are not how much you have in the bank. You are not the contents of your wallet. You are not your khakis. You are not a beautiful and unique snowflake. What happens first is you can't sleep. What happens then is there's a gun in your mouth. And what happens next is you meet Tyler Durden. Let me tell you about Tyler. He had a plan. In Tyler we trusted. Tyler says the things you own, end up owning you. It's only after you've lost everything that you're free to do anything. Tyler says self-improvement is masturbation. Tyler says self-destruction might be the answer. This is how I chose do describe Fincher's 1999 psychological drama  Fight Club . David once again showed us that he is one of the most cutting edge directors in Hollywood.  Fincher also gave us a vastly underrated film noir crime thriller  The Game . This movie is one of the most brilliantly written, directed, and acted movies that has graced the big screen in some time. Micheal Douglas and Sean Penn are incredible from start to finish. This movie has so many well placed twists and suprising turns, it keeps you guessing until it's unexpected end. So it seems like to me that Fincher's creativity knows few limits, I look forward to seeing what he'll give us next.  Well due to my extremely long Fincher section I will end my post here. I can't wait to see what you have to say about my buddy David. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First off let me agree with you that Hollywood does turn out staggeringly banal pieces of garbage that are suppose to pass as entertainment, but I do believe there are pockets of creativity within the industry that run deeper than they ever have before.  Like yourself I was going to mention Tarantino but not discuss him because his creativity goes without saying.  The second name I will add to that category is Charlie Kaufman (please don't groan saying 'Here she goes again!')  Whether you love him or hate him there's no denying Kaufman is one of the most creative people working today and I will leave it at that.  I was going to save television for last because as I was canvassing popular culture for creativity I kept coming back to TV.  But since you've gone there I will dutifully follow.  About television- 90% of it is complete and total crap, but in my estimation that other 10% is the most creative block in all of entertainment.   I'm surprised you sited  Nip/Tuck  as one of the three most creative shows on television.  Like yourself I am a fan, but I find the series to be more intriguing than creative.  Let me explain that- I think there are shows on TV that are more creative than  Nip/Tuck  but I would be hard pressed to name a show that is more intriguing.  As to  The Shield  I have never seen it so I will take your word.  As to your reality TV critique I agree, not only for being unoriginal but so repetitive.  Reality shows, by their very nature are mean spirited, it's all about who's getting kicked/fired/voted off.  Yes The Sopranos and Deadwood are dark shows, but they offer an insight into why we do the mean, cold, calculated things we do. Reality TV is suppose to make us feel better about ourselves by watching people who are pettier or uglier than us but it has the opposite effect- it makes me sad it's come to this.  The reason I loved the first season of  American Idol  was because the contestants weren't out to beat each other (I became disillusioned with the show when they took Kelly Clarkson, a white girl who can sing the blues like no one's business, and mad her into a Christina Auguliera wannabe.)  Enough of who doesn't have it, lets get to who does.   Arrested Development  is a wacky, out of left field gem that is as silly as it is sweet.  The unconventional plodding and design of the show (shot like  Sports Night  with a single camera)add to its charm.  The show zigs and zags unlike traditional sitcoms so not every storyline is wrapped up in a single episode.   Arrested Development  never goes for the cheap laughs and it's outlandish storylines including my favorite when Jason Bateman uses a boat full of male strippers dressed as policeman to teach his son a lesson about drugs, are always redeemed by playing for the heart.  My second bastion of original creativity is Comedy Central. When comprising my list the first thing that popped into my mind was  The Daily Show .  Four nights a week Jon Stewart and his gang deliver the wittiest most astute commentary around.  It doesn't matter what's going on in the news, they have as much fun with the Oscars as they do with Iraq.  Stephen Colbert is a national treasure but the rest of the gang, Ed Helmes, Rob Couldrey, Lewis Black, are no slouches either.  If one's going to include  The Daily Show , you have to count  The Chappelle Show  as well.  And  Reno 911 .  And  South Park .  In my mind no network, not even the slumping HBO, can rival the amount of uninhibited, original programming Comedy Central is putting on the air.  My post has run long so I'll save my beacon of creativity and remaining thoughts on television for next time. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is a very deep question that I believe will take many posts to do it justice. Creativity is something that I actually feel is quite rare in Hollywood these days, so many studios just churn out these predictable pieces of garbage that lack imagination and originality. There are people out there who are unmistakably creative, Tarantino is a prime example of someone who's creativity that knows no limits, but that really goes without saying so I will not include him in this discussion.  I think I will start in the realm of television. A great example of creativity can be found in the F/X show  Nip/Tuck . A show that really only has four characters. F/X has done a great job in the last two years creating two great primetime dramas,  Nip/Tuck  being one and  The Shield  being the other(I will talk about  The Shield  in a later post).  Nip/Tuck 's story revolves around two completely opposite men who only have one thing in common, they're both doctors. Sean McNamara plays the seemingly perfect plastic surgeon that throughout the show finds himself battling his morals which eventually leads to him deciding to change his life, which alienates his wife, son and business partner. His business partner Christian Troy is a playboy in every sense of the word. His confident swagger attracts women by the dozen, and Christian enjoys every single one of them. The two characters are intriguing for so many reasons. Christian never has a problem with morals(they barely even exist anymore) and Sean finds himself constantly questioning if what he is doing is right. The character development on this show is incredible, creating so many different relationships between so few characters. It takes a lot of creativity to pull that off, that's why I think  Nip/Tuck  is one of the top three most creative shows on TV.  As for lacking creativity, I would have to say reality TV in general has lost all of it's originality and imagination that once captified America(I think the first  Survivor  I feel was a masterpiece of originality). You flick through the channels and you can't help but find an over abundance of reality TV. American Idol, Average Joe, The Apprentice, and the list goes on, and on, and on. It takes absolutely no imagination to throw a reality TV show into a prime time slot and watch the ratings fly. People are so bored with there own lives they want to live through these people that I would beat the crap out of if I ever saw them in person. Now I realize that I watched  Survivor: All-Stars , but that was in part because a few of those people I thought were generally kind of interesting(Boston Rob, Rupert, and Ethan). All in all though, all the major TV stations have gone way overboard with the amount of reality TV shows they decide to put on the air. Hopefully all the junkies will soon find something else to watch.  Hope I threw you a curveball or two, and I look forward to seeing what you have to say on the topic. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Creativity, defined by the Oxford English Dictionary is the ability to transcend traditional ideas, rules, patterns, relationships, or the like, and to create meaningful new ideas, forms, methods, interpretations, etc.; originality, progressiveness or imagination.  Creativity is the life blood of Hollywood so who (actors, writers, directors, tv shows, producers, musicians, magazines) has it and who's lost it? 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think you might be going a little far in saying Commodus is nothing more than Paris Hilton in a toga. If killing your father and demanding that your sister bare your child isn't evil I don't know what is. Pheonix's portrayal is one for the ages, in one of my favorite movies of the last five years. When he screams "Am I not merciful" to his sister, I got chills down my spine. That alone is enough for me to place him on my list. Come to think of it I am kind of suprised you didn't like my final pick, with your known love of Joaquin I thought you would totally agree with it. But I guess you are just full of suprises.  As for the hero/villain question I posed in Part Eight, I have a couple answers to it. It may seem a little unoriginal but I still feel that Luke Skywalker and Darth Vader gave us one of the most intriguing hero/villain relationship. The struggle was between a father and a son, bitter enemies that are related to each other is something you don't find in many movies. My other choice would have to be John McClane(Bruce Willis) and Hans Gruber(Alan Rickman). Gruber was a relentless businessman whose lethal tactics achieve his goals. Unlike most 1980s film villains who committed globally dangerous acts for liberty, genocide, or world domination,  DIE HARD 's Gruber uses guns, explosives and cunning to storm the Takagi Corporation's Christmas party and heist millions of dollars form the company. I would classify McClane as a bad luck hero, wrong place at the wrong time who chooses to intervene, and against incredible odds succeeds in foiling Gruber's plans.  Well folks, there you have it. This post ends our first discussion, I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did. Now the topic is your choice, I look foward to wrapping my head around it. Until next time, this Nick signing off. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have the feeling that Charlie Kauffman will come up again and again and again in our discussions and though I don't think we'll ever reconcile our opinions I look forward to the debate.  On the Lector front I think we've given the bad doctor more than his due, so let me wrap up by saying I believe it's Lectors extrodinary intellect combined with his unrivaled evil that makes him a great villain.  As for your argument about  Clockwork Orange  I confess I've never seen it (I'm nearly allergic to Kubrick), but in the clips I've seen on t.v. Alex strikes me more crazy than insane.  We can talk about  The Matrix  until we're blue in the face but bottom line you see three movies, I see three parts of a whole.  I have to admit I'm a little surprised you didn't have more to say about my  Gladiator  rebuff.  I guess I thought a Roman royal being compared to a poor little rich kid (Paris Hilton in a toga)was a bigger dig than it apparently is.  That said my biggest problem with  Gladiator  is how the character hides behind his power.  He's afraid of Maximus and a great villain can never fear his adversary.  I really like your closing question, it's a great way to wrap our first discussion.  I haven't had a lot of time to formulate my answer, but off the top of my head Al Pacino and Robert DeNiro in  Heat  (a moody film unfairly overlooked) and Morgan Freeman and Kevin Spacey in  Seven  come to mind.  I particularly loved Freeman glancing at Doe in the rearview mirror.  I give you the last word and after you post I will pose our second question. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First off, our taste in movies does differ. But I still believe that you turn a blind eye towards some of the holes that lie within movies such as  Adaptation  and  Eternal Sunshine . But that is an argument we should probably save for later.   Moving on, Hannibal Lector is without a doubt a splendidly detestable villain, but there are flaws in him(as a villain). You stated that you felt Lector could take on any villain in the history of cinema and come out on top. This is where I will show you beyond a reasonable doubt that he in fact could not. Now if you threw him up against a run of the mill villain like Max Cady( Cape Fear ) Lector's far superior intellect would absolutely dominate the battle. There in lies the first problem, put him up against someone of a superior intellect, ie. Agent Smith, Darth Vader, Verbal Kint aka Kaiser Soze, and he has lost his one advantage. The second glaring weakness Lector has is the fact that he is insane, but not in the way it helps most villains. He is insane because he is a cannibal, but he is refined, kind(for the most part), and well mannered. Put him up against a villain who is truly insane like Alex De Large( A Clockwork Orange  ) and I believe De Large's sociopathic behavior, his lack of conscience, his pure desire to be evil would overcome anything that Lector could throw at him. In case you are wondering the reason that De Large and Kint didn't make my top five, it is because I saw a few flaws in each character. In short, Kint runs into the same problems as Lector(his mind is his only weapon) and De Large because he would pose no threat to a hero that could go on the offensive against him, a la Jason Bourne from the Bourne Identity.  As for  The Matrix , I think on this one we will have to agree to disagree. I feel that if a movie can stand on it's own, and be separate from it's sequels, can live as a finished story without it's sequels, then it can be a vision within a vision.  The Matrix  is a phenomenal movie. As for the sequels, I wouldn't say they were horrendous, I would say they were a let down. The Wachowski Brothers in my opinion, got to wrapped up in attempting to tread on the magic of the first film and not creating a new magic with the sequels. I own the whole trilogy on DVD. I have watched the films many times, I can find enjoyment in all three movies. Although the flaws are much more apparent in the second and third installment(second film is the worst of the three). And it's not that I am overlooking the second two films in my choosing of Agent Smith, It's just that I am focusing on the first film as it's own movie, kinda like Darth Vader in  The Empire Strikes Back .  Now onto your critique/bashing of my final choice, Commodus. You stated "To me a great villain terrifies by exposing the evil that lurks in the hearts of all man." Well, I saw a lot of evil lurking in the heart of Commodus(see my last post for examples). Maximus would definitely make my top five heroes list. You need a great villain if you are to have a great hero. For instance, Sean Archer had Castor Troy, Neo had Agent Smith, Batman had The Joker, and the exception that proves the rule is Alonzo Harris. Commodus is an incredible villain because of the hero he created, Maximus was the savior of Rome. The General who became a slave, the slave who became a gladiator, the gladiator that defied an empire. The struggle between Commodus and Maximus gave us an outcome we rarely have the opportunity to see, they kill each other. Yeah Maximus wins the fight between the two of them, but by stabbing our hero in the back Commodus ultimately killed Maximus.  I hope my retort is everything you were hoping it was and I look forward to hearing what your response will be. I have a question for you though. Now this is just a spin off of the current topic we are on and I am not looking to start more arguments(I think this topic has provided enough). In your opinion what hero/villain combination is the best of all time? I will think about this question as well and I will answer it in my next post.   Until next time, this is Nick signing out. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Before I get into responding to your last post, let me get two quick things out of the way:  1)	When you say, “a little corrupted by certain movies” you’re trying to say my taste in films differs from yours, correct? 2)	What I actually said regarding  Adaptation  was it was an incredible movie and Nicolas Cage gave a great performance.  Now that that’s out of the way let me briefly retouch on our AFI/Hannibal Lector debate.  I thought this was the greatest villain, not most original villain list?  I did not choose him because AFI did too, I simply mentioned they had.  Secondly, you may be trying a little too hard to be the anti-AFI.  Who cares who they list or don’t’ list and where, I don’t.  I believe films should be examined as the creators envisioned.  Some directors confine their visions to one film, some need three and for  The Matrix  I see the Wachowski’s vision being comprised of all three films, therefore I look at all three films as a whole.  It seems to me we agree- the first film was phenomenal, the second two were horrendous- but in your critique you’re willing to dismiss or overlook the lesser films, whereas I am not.  I’m not sure about “Agent Simth, one of the greatest villains ever.”  Yes, he’s good and Weaverings performance is delicious but he’s ultimately a computer program.  Smith doesn’t strike the terror in me of other villains because he’s only pretending to be human.  To me a great villain terrifies by exposing the evil that lurks in the hearts of all man.  Final note- you say no film had done more for cinema in the last fifteen years but I have two words for you,  Pulp Fiction !  For all the endless Charlie Kaufman/critic bashing I’ve taken, you lavish  Gladiator  on me as your last pick?  Joaquin Phoenix is a staggeringly gifted actor but his character is nothing more than a Roman poor little rich kid pissed off that daddy loves big brother more and the girl rebuffed him.  To me Russell Crowe’s true antagonist in the film is the oppression of slavery and his lingering sins of war.  Throw Joaquin into the ring with Lector and I’ll but my money on Hannibal every day of the week.  Before I move on to some general villain commentary I have I’ll let you respond.  I’m looking forward to your  Gladiator  retort.  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Maybe you are not a lemming for the critics. But I still feel you are a little corrupted by certain movies. You said something to me yesterday that stuck out in my memory. You told me that you saw  Adaptation (another self-indulgent Charlie Kaufman movie), and you said that it "is an incredible movie, because of the outstanding performance by Nicolas Cage". But you wrote in your last post that  Training Day  is a decent movie, even though Washington gave a great performance. So tell me why you don't hold Charlie Kaufman's movies to the same standard as all other movies.  I wasn't trying to say that the AFI choosing Lector lacked imagination and originality(which I feel it did). I was trying to say that you choosing Lector lacked imagination and originality. One of your reasons for choosing him, as you wrote in your first post, was that the AFI chose him. And with the exception of your #4 choice Catwoman, All of your villains were in the top 15 on the AFI's list. I have tried to stay off-beat, granted The Joker and Alonzo Harris are both on the list(#45 and #50), but I felt there performances are vastly underrated.    As for your opinion on Agent Smith, you said it yourself "he is the perfect villain in the first  Matrix  film, and I mean perfect." Now that is a direct quote from your post, but you had the audacity to say that overall you are not convinced. I agree with you that the two sequels were gaudy monstrosities, but like I said, I am choosing to focus on the first film. The first  Matrix  film is the only one that can stand alone as it's own movie(taking place months before the two sequels). And I think  The Matrix  has done more for cinema than any other movie in the last fifteen years, due in no small part to Hugo Weaving's portrayal of Agent Smith, one of the greatest villains ever.  I really can't comment much on your choice for #1. I know it sounds bad but I have never seen  Schindler's List . I'm sure Ralph Fiennes gave a powerful performance, I sure that it was an intensely powerful movie with an emotional swing very few movies have ever been able to obtain. But like I said, I haven't seen the movie, so I cannot cast a decision on Amon Goeth being a great villain.  Now it is time to reveal my last villain. Another underrated performance by an actor who has given us one of those characters that you love to hate. Joaquin Phoenix delivered a performance for the ages when he brought Commodus Aurelius to life in  Gladiator . What defines a villain? Webster's dictionary states "a wicked or evil person". How wicked is Commodus? He kills his own father when he discovers that he will not be Caesar. He orders death upon the person in which his father was to name as the next Caesar. He commands the death of that man's family as well. When he finds out that his sister has betrayed him, he threatens the life of her only child(his nephew). Russell Crowe gave a tremendous performance as Maximus. We have seen that many times actors and actresses cannot hold their own opposite Crowe. But I truly felt at times in  Gladiator  Crowe had trouble holding his own against Phoenix. Commodus was the first villain that came to mind when I asked the question "who are the greatest villains in the history of cinema". All this makes Commodus a no-brainer in my opinion. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We are very lucky we live in the 21st century because if we were in the revolutionary time period I would probably have to challenge you to a duel over your last post.  Let me first defend myself against the malicious libel you hurled my way, accusing me of being nothing more than a critics lemming.  It's no secret that my taste in movies aligns with the critical consensus more often than yours, but my reactions, particularly ones as strong as my like for  Eternal Sunshine  are wholly authenticc.  I loved, loved, loved  Eternal Sunshine  not because Charlie Kaufman wrote it or Owen Gliberman, David Edelstein, etc. raved about it, but because the story, the writing and the acting touched me and made me think on an emotional level few movies ever have.  I do not always agree with the critics- I found their endless fawning over  Lost in Translation  baffling and both critics and the public were excessive in the fanatical praising of the  Lord of the Rings  Trilogy, a set of films that under the slightest examination shows enormous flaws.  A brief side note before I move on to your villain choices.  I am surprised you say AFI's Lector choice lacks imagination and originalitylity.  I won't contend it is the greatest stretch of imagination, but a reasonable argument could be made it is an off beat choice that  wasn't predictable.  I would say the institute (who's existence is both harmless and meaningless to me) in choosing an insane character, who never employs the traditional cinema mannerisms of insanity and only kills (offscreen at that) nameless extras we have no connection to, over a more traditional villain, like I don't know, say the number two choice, Darth Vader.  (As for your Darth Vader defense I like your argument but still think you're holding Catwoman to a double standard)  Here's my take on  Training Day , great performance, decent movie.  Denzel Washington's performance is spellbinding, but without a better script, a more interesting story and fleshed out supporting characters, the film is just that-one great performance.  That everything around him isn't on par doesn't take away from the performance, but ideally the performance enhances the movie and in turn the movie adds to the performance.  I don't mean to sound like I'm dismissing this villain, he was a consideration on my own list, and had the film been better it may have been just the thing to push him on my list.  I am a divided mind about Agent Smith.  Overall I'm not convinced he is a great villain, but he is the perfect villain in the first  Matrix  film, and I mean perfect.  For that story, in that movie he is unquestionably, note for note, perfect.  The second and third convolutede such convaluded messes no performance could escape the films maddening incoherence.  I think when looking at an artists vision you must look at it as a whole, so while  The Matrix ,  Star Wars  and  Lord of the Rings  have been cut up into three films they are, and should be seen, as three chapters that create one whole.  The final two-thirds of  The Matrix  is so excessive it eclipses the performance and keeps Smith off my list.  Your guess of John Doe is a strong one (Doe will be discussed later) but my number one slot belongs to Amon Goeth in  Schindler's List .  Ralph Fiennes laconic, lumbering performance is a portrait of true ugliness.  His character is brutal and powerful not from a heightened intellect or physical prowess, but from his position at the time.  The terror of the character is the realism, the strong do what they can, the weak endure what they must.  Goeth is almost beyond words and unparalleled in cinema.   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We are not snooty Hollywood types, we are pop culture aficionados. Because of that I cannot put Hannibal Lector on my greatest villains list. If it was a list of the greatest performances in the last 25 years, than yes, Anthony Hopkins would make that list, but not this one. Maybe you have been corrupted by movies like  Eternal Sunshine  into believing what all those spoiled critics out there believe.  Eternal Sunshine  was a creative movie, but because it was written by Charlie Kaufman, critics(and you) have to say that it is "an amazing piece of film making" or "one of the best films in the last twenty years". But they don't want to see that there are glaring holes in the movie, the same goes for Hannibal Lector as a great villain. It's the "Hollywood" answer to a difficult question. Choosing the AFI's choice for greatest villain lacks imagination and originality. We our here to dive into the deep end of pop culture, not hang out in the kiddy pool.   The Empire Strikes Back  is the best movie within the first  Star Wars Trilogy . The main reason behind that is the fact that the Emipre triumphs. Luke gets his hand chopped off, Han is frozen in carbonite, and what is still the greatest cliffhanger in the history of cinema, Luke finds out that Darth Vader is his father.  Return of the Jedi  is the weakest film in the first trilogy, and the main reason behind that(other than the Ewoks) is that Darth Vader saved Luke and killed the Emperor. But Darth Vader, in The Empire Strikes Back, at the peak of his vileness is the greatest villain in the history of the universe.  For now I will move on to my next villain. Alonzo Harris( Training Day ), played by Denzel Washington, is a great villain for a number of reasons. Going into this movie I remember wondering if the man that starred in  Remember the Titans ,  Crimson Tide , and  The Pelican Brief  could play a villain. But, within minutes, those hesitations are dispelled by my fascination with the complexities of his character in  Training Day . It's a testament to Washington's talent that we are convinced of his evil nature and still seduced by him. From the first moments of this film Harris taunts, inspires and even drugs the rookie he is training. The thing that makes Alonzo so intriguing(and disturbing) is that he is supposed to be a protector, someone we trust, someone we depend on. He is evil on a level that most movies don't dare go. And the most amazing thing about this character is that he does all this with a clear conscience. It is tempting to attribute the film's potency to Denzel's riveting performance as Det. Alonzo Harris. So with that, my third entry to this list has been given.  Only two left, and my last villain of this post is Agent Smith from  The Matrix . Like Darth Vader I am going to focus on one of the three movies he was in, and in this case, the first movie. Agent Smith embodied everything we love in a great villain, infinite knowledge, god-like strength, and a undeniable hatred for the hero, and with Agent Smith a hatred for the human race. Now anyone that hates a whole race has to be classified as a uber-villain. Anyone who refer's to the human race as cancer is a diabolical baddie. Smith is an excellent intimidator, complemented nicely by his spooky devotion to perfect annunciation. Consumed by his superiority over humans, he never believed in the prophecy that a savior would come to rescue humanity, and ultimately destroy him. Cool, calculating, and an unrelenting resolve make him a easy choice for my list.  In closing I suppose I will give one last guess at your #1 movie villain. I have to say I am somewhat stumped but for the sake of the website I will go with John Doe, Kevin Spacey from Se7en. I don't think that is it, but I think that is good guess because John Doe is another underrated villain. I look foward to hearing what you have to say on Alonzo Harris and Agent Smith, and I also look foward to you unveiling your #1.   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Judging by the discrepancy between our opinions “Up for Discussion” is bound to be an intriguing endeavor.  First of all I am baffled by your AFI comment.  So what if they put him on the top of their list, a great performance is a great performance.  The fact that this elderly, incarcerated character is so scary is a testimate to Hopkins performance.  Few villains could last matched up to this remorseless, super id of a character who revels in his evilness.  Much of what I have to say about Catwoman/The Joker will be addressed in comments I’m saving until we’ve both posted our villains, but let me make a few points.  One, that Catwomans flirtation with turning good makes her a more compelling villain.  We want good to overcome evil and nothing is more tragic than seeing a character, particularly one as intriguing as Catwoman, come so close only to stay bad.  Secondly Darth Vader is too great to put on your list, but doesn’t he ultimately go good by killing the emperor and saving the galaxy.  If renouncing your evil ways (or even considering it) knocks you down on the villain spectrum, shouldn’t Darth be held to the same standard as Catwoman?  Finally Jack Nicholson’s performance was hammy over acting.  Tim Burton’s dark, moody adaptation of the comic book was full of somber themes on loneliness and loss and the Joker was nothing more than an circus size distraction.  They say there’s an exception to every rule, so if the villain is always the more interesting character to play, than  Face/Off  is the anomaly.  Yes I appreciated the performances and felt they complemented each other, but the villain seemed one dimensional in comparison to the more fleshed out protagonist.  Nicolas Cage brought a great soulfulness and sense of melancholy to the role, so the film lagged every time he was off screen.  Bill the Butcher is a good guess, but wrong.  When formalizing my villain list I thought of Bill but immediately crossed him off.  There is no straight line between good and evil in Scorsese’s underapprecitated masterpiece.  Bill is shown to be a bad guy, a very bad guy, but he’s not the villain.  Scorsese is too brilliant of a director to have a simple hero-villain relationship, which is why he creates individual characters rather than plugging in typical or traditional roles.  I’ll let you chew on that and give you one more guess before I reveal my number one.   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I really like the format that you came out with in your first post. But I think I am going to do something a little different. It is a difficult topic, with all the great performances in the role of the villain, I am not going to rank them. I am going to give my opinion's on the five greatest villains in the history of the cinema. But first, I will air some grievances I have with your post.  I will start with your choice for #2, Hannibal Lector. As you said in your post the AFI named him the greatest villain of all-time, which just on general principle keeps him off my list. I'll concede that Anthony Hopkins was terrifying in the role, possibly the best performance of his career. But he is 60 years old and locked up, therefore, not on my list.   Now you did hit a bullseye with your pick for #3, Darth Vader. For those of you who don't know, I am a huge fan of the  Star Wars  movies. I am one of those fans that got in line 23 hours before tickets went on sale for  Episode I . I have always felt that the two most important characters in the  Star Wars  movies are Han Solo and Darth Vader. Han Solo because he was reluctant to join the rebellion, but once he did, he embodied it. Darth Vader because, like you said, he is an iconic image of pure evil. And that, is what makes him a great villain(he will not be appearing on my list because I feel he is above any list).  She may be one of the greatest female villains of all-time, but greatest villains, come on! Michelle Pfiefer's portrayal of Catwoman was a great performance, but Catwoman was a villain that often flirted with the idea of becoming a good guy. Yes she is sexy, she is seductive, and maybe a little unpredictable, but she lacks that "shiver down your spine" quality that defines a great villain. But the thing is, you mentioned one of the greatest villains in your Catwoman paragraph. Jack Nicholson as The Joker.  The original  Batman  was by the best comic book adaptation ever(I apologize to all you  Spiderman  fans, it's a close second), and that is due in no small part to the man we have simply come to know as...Jack. The idea of The Joker is a little weak, a little 1970's, but Nicholson turned that weak idea into a bad guy that we cannot take are eyes off of. He stole the show, everytime he was on the screen he shined. The conflict between The Joker and Batman had history. The Joker had killed Bruce Wayne's parents in front of him, when Bruce was just a little boy, and he only remembered one thing about the incident. He remembered something the killer said, one of the greatest single lines in the history of movies, "have you ever danced with the devil in the pale moonlight?". One man, one voice, could truly make that line work, Jack is that man, Jack is that voice.  The second evildoer, and last of this post, is a little less celebrated than all the others we have talked about, but is just as fearsome. Castor Troy( Face/Off ) is still to this day one of the most interesting roles ever. Played by both Nicolas Cage and John Travolta, Castor incorporated a conscience-less killer with an astonishing intellect. He was the true equal of his protagonist counterpart Sean Archer(also played by both cage and Travolta). Troy and Archer knew each other so well that they seemed to switch off being one step ahead of each other. One of the things that seems to be lacking in most action movies is emotion, Travolta and Cage brought a phenomenal amount of emotion to this movie. Most villains lack emotion, but in this movie when Castor's brother, Pollacks, is killed by Archer, it seems to fuel the hatred the Castor has for our hero. In my opinion Castor Troy is one of the most underrated villains of cinema.   So there you have it, two of my five, there are three more on the way so stay tuned. As for guessing who your number one is, Daniel Day Lewis as Bill "The Butcher" Poole in Gangs of New York. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Let me begin our villain discussion by laying out my number two, three and four favorite villains and gauge your response before I throw down my number one.  (Try to guess but I don’t think you’ll get it)   #4    Catwoman  in  Batman Returns  So sexy, so devilish, this, in my opinion is the best portrayal of a comic book character on the big screen.  The team of Batman villains, led by Jack Nicholson, were all over the top.  Both Gene Hackman ( Superman ) and Willem Dafoe ( Spiderman ) served their films well, but Pfeifer was unforgettable.  Bursting with equal parts female rage and sexuality the character is so frightening because she’s as unpredictable as she is seductive.   #3   Darth Vader  That Darth Vader has become the iconic image for evil is all the more impressive when you remember the  Star Wars  trilogy is rated PG.  The long black cape, impenetrable helmet and heavy breathing are enough to send a shiver down anyone’s spine but then there’s that voice.  Oh that voice.  Vocal performances get very little credit but without James Earl Joneses perfect authorative delivery  Star Wars  wouldn’t be what it is today.  The character, in wanting to kill his own son, strikes the same Oedipal ruthlessness as other villains, but none made being bad this cool.   #2    Dr. Hannibal Lector  in  Silence of the Lambs  AFI named a 60 year-old character with slicked back hair who spends 99% of his screen time behind plexiglass the greatest villain of all time.  What makes Lector so terrifying ( I think he is the scariest villain of all time) is he embodies what we most want to be-brilliant, refined, cultured- yet without a conscious.  His almost God-like in his intellect, so brilliant that he burrows into our minds and we are unable to get away.  Lector’s power comes from knowing we will never outsmart him.  A hybrid of wild animal and genius Lectors mind covers the breadth and depth of every imaginable evil.  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Adolf Hitler, Osama Bin Laden, Grigory Rasputin, are all great villians of the the last century. But now 'Up For Discussion' is the most diabolical baddies in the history of cinema. I got some ideas on who I am going to speak on, and I look foward to seeing what you have to say on the topic. So get ready, becuase we will be taking Jensen Vs. Jensen to the next level. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After a long, restful break I’m ready to dig back into a discussion and will start by going into territory we’ve been oddly reticent about-directors.  I don’t want this to be dialog mistaking the word ‘overrated’ with ‘sucks’.  I’m approaching this topic by calibrating the general consensus of the director/actor/writer with the talent level I grade them.  Essentially my argument boils down to points, some I feel have a few unearned points in their column, others deserve a few extra.  With that out of the way here are my candidates.  Mood is an aspect of filmmaking I have great reverence for.  Mood adds a great deal to the story and the characters and yet rarely gets its due.  One of the masters (perhaps the master of mood) is David Fincher.  My theory of David Fincher is this- critics comment on the story he’s telling but not the film he’s made.  Perhaps the biggest lapse in critical judgment of the previous century was the blithe dismissal of Fincher’s best work  Fight Club  (with the exception of Peter Travers) because critics were uncomfortable with what the film had to say, though I think they also missed a great deal of the films point.  Fincher has proven to be a remarkably consistent director, a quality my wallet and I adore.  After getting his feet wet with the third  Alien  film he found his style with  Se7en ,  The Game ,  Fight Club  and  Panic Room .  His films look and feel like no other.  Fincher, I suspect, hasn’t received the real credit he deserves because his films tend to illustrate the confusion, darkness and hopelessness we all feel, but his talent and command make him the most underrated director in Hollywood.  The other maestro of mood is Gore Verbinski.  Verbinski doesn’t have Finchers knack for bringing all the elements together, but his visual style is one of the best in Hollywood.  The  Mexican, The Ring  and  Pirates of the Caribbean  are all films worth watching without sound.  His best film,  Pirates , sailed on the witty dialog and Johnny Depp, Geoffrey Rush and Kiera Knightley’s entertaining performance.  With time and experience if he learned to keep up he could become a director worth reckoning with.  Comedy seems to be the hardest and most unappreciated genre in movies, which is why we have so few great comedies.  One of the best directors around is Cameron Crowe, who’s light touch blends films that are as funny as they are touching.  Crowe knows how to handle a younger cast and as a writer and director puts more humanity and truthfulness into his characters than almost anyone around.  Two other unsung heroes in the romantic comedy game are Andrew Bergman and Andy Tennant.  Bergman directed two forgotten gems,  Honeymoon in Vegas  and the funniest movie to flop that should have been a hit,  The Freshman .  Tennant helmed two of the better romantic comedies,  Ever After  and  Sweet Home Alabama , empowering the female leads to give their best performances in this category of films.  Neither Bergman or Tennant is a great director, which Crowe is closing in on, but they are both succeeding in a territory where most are failing.  My final underrated mention is Mike Nichols, a man who appears on the list of best directors but is, in my opinion much closer to the top.  Nichols has an unparalleled versatility, as his credits range from the cerebral  Carnal Knowledge  to the campy  Birdcage .  Nichols has the rare gift of making films that define the times and yet preserve an element of timelessness.  In  Primary Colors  he not only summed up the 90’s political mood, he spoke to the larger on going question of integrity and compromise, whether ends justify the means or if the means are the end themselves.  Recently Nichols has downsized his work to HBO, a shame for the larger movie audience, but his ability remains as large as ever.  My first four overrated directors fall into an over hyped category.  They’re all good directors but particularly their recent films have failed to live up to the wonder the chorus was singing.  Lasse Hallstrom hasn’t made a movie that genuinely touched me since  What’s Eating Gilbert Grape?   Peter Jackson’s  Lord of the Rings  trilogy was impressive but failed to live up to its operatic ambitions and lost steam as it went along.  For me the series had as many holes as it did Oscars.  I hope that this years Alexander the Great film will return Oliver Stone to his glory since he peaked with  JFK .  Finally and I hope I’m not stoned for saying this but I think Steven Speilberg is overrated.   Schindlers List  is an unassailable masterpiece but since then Speilberg has been reading too much of his own press.  The most glaring example is  Saving Private Ryan , a shamelessly manipulative piece of patriotic, nostalgic propaganda.  To understand the true fear, pointlessness and stark realities of war turn to Terrance Malick’s superior WWII drama  A Thin Red Line .  I prefaced this post by saying I didn’t want overrated confused with sucks, (and I don’t) but I forget to preface my preface by stating there is one exception- Brett Ratner.  I don’t think Hollywood thinks Ratner is a world class director, if they do it’s the end of the world as we know it, but they did give him sixty million dollars and Anthony Hopkins, Edward Norton, Ralph Fiennes and Emily Watson.  Hollywood doesn’t hand over that kind of money and talent to a hack, except in this case they did because Ratner is a hack.  And not a good hack like Ed Wood, but a complete and total hack who should never be allowed to film any actors outside Chris Tucker and Jackie Chan.  I look forward to your reply.   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Now it is time for the discussion to turn to those in Hollywood who are over-rated as well as those who are under-rated. I am thinking of keeping the focus on actors, actresses, writers and directors, but if you think of someone or something outside of my focus areas please feel free to express them. I will be leaving Charlie Kaufman off my over-rated list so I hope he won't appear on your under-rated list. I think sometime in the future we might need to spend a whole topic on Kaufman, maybe not ten posts, but I think we could definitely cover the topic in six posts. I look forward to seeing what you have to say. 

						
</post>


<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My very first blog, kinda exciting! First things first, i really enjoyed this movie from beginning to end, I felt it was a solid, well-timed comedy(definitely in a year that has struggled delivering a great comedy). It is just fun to go see a movie that you smile and laugh all the way through.   To be sure, Starsky & Hutch   was not one of the greatest comedies of our generation. It is, as the credits put it, a Todd Phillips movie(Road Trip, Old School), so there is no intracite plot or even a sure-fire concept. But the framework of a cheesy 70's cop show provides the minimal structure that his other movies lacked. With Ben Stiller(Starsky) and Owen Wilson(Hutch) taking that structure and building of it with a combination of dry, sarcastic humor and over the top situations.  Starsky & Hutch is exactly what we have come to expect from Ben & Owen. Perhaps it is not as smart or well written as Zoolander(the other major Stiller-wilson collaboration), but nevertheless the movie isn't about anything other than several funny actors making us laugh.    GRADE: B+   In closing that 70's show that you spoke of being recycled into current times would have to be Charlie's Angels.  Nick Jensen
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Nick! So here it is, our first ever joint blog.  Only two months into the year we've taken in three movies and since I'm kicking off our forum I'll take the liberty of which film we'll discuss first, though in your postings you can steer the discussion toward any film you like.  (The downside is so can I).  Since  Miracle  isn't as fresh in my memory, and    Euro Trip    is scurrying back into the hole it was made in, let's begin with    Starsky & Hutch   . Now neither one of us watched much television in the 70's, you weren't even an idea in the 70's, so we can't compare it to the original t.v. show, but I did like that the filmmakers kept the story in the original decade.  On the whole I'm not a big fan of updating old television shows to current times (I'll give you props if you can name my one exception), they seem to me like a grunge cover of a disco song-odd and unnecessary.  Much of the humor in    Starsky    comes from the decade itself, like when they're putting the wire on Huggy Bear, so I don't see how they could have done it any other way. Have you noticed that Ben Stiller plays the same character in all his movies- a repressed nice guy with anger brewing under the surface who can't loosen up until a free spirited rule breaker (Jen Aniston, Owen Wilson) comes along- and yet I still really enjoyed the movie.  Stiller has really perfected the character in a variety of films, the dry, witty    Royal Tenebaums   , the hilarious    Meet the Parents    and now the absurdist    Starsky   .  We complain about actors playing the same roles over and over again, yet we give Stiller a pass.  I suspect it has to do with his being a comedian, but that's just a guess.  Anyway sorry my post is so long, look forward to reading your thoughts.  Courtney  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In this revenge picture, Denzel Washington stars as John W. Creasy, a heavy-drinking, spiritually bankrupt former military assassin who picks up a job as a body guard for the daughter of a wealthy couple in Mexico City. It is a place, the movie reminds us, where abduction is common and often fatal. Man on Fire is a movie of high ambition, dressed up in jazzy, jittery style. All the flash and dash that director Tony Scott (  Crimson Tide, Enemy of the State  ) brings to the screen apparently is meant to obscure the fact that, minus its artistic cloaking devices and big budget, the movie is really just another rampaging-avenger flick. Deep down inside, it is no more sophisticated than, say,   Walking Tall  .   Not too many R-rated revenge pics depend on   Uptown Girls   star Dakota Fanning for the stronger scenes. Yet once the ten year old star exits the picture,   Man on Fire   starts blowing a lot of smoke. Once on the job, he bonds with the 9-year-old girl in his charge (the brilliant Dakota Fanning) and thereby finds a reason to keep living. So when the unthinkable happens to her, he's happy to devote himself to tracking down and eliminating the gangsters and corrupt cops responsible.  The plot contains several twists and tangents that give it the gloss of a sophisticated thriller, but they are for the most part too predictable to lend much depth. Among Creasy's allies are a former comrade-in-arms called Rayburn, a confusing character played well by Christopher Walken. But despite the phenomenal performances by the stars of the movie, Scott indulges in maddeningly fussy camera and sound-editing techniques that Tony's director brother, Ridley Scott (  Gladiator  ), knows to ignore. I felt this movie could have been another tremendous tale of revenge, ala   Kill Bill  , if only it had been under the direction of someone like Quentin Tarantino.   When it is all said and done. There are too many flaws in this movie for the actors to overcome. Scott's hyperactive style - and about 20 minutes of excess footage - cannot masquerade the same-old story that lies beneath.    Grade: C   Nick Jensen 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Revenge, a dish served cold by the Klingons, has become the specialty d’jour in Hollywood.  From Uma and Bill, to the Punisher and now Denzel Washington in  Man on Fire , the summer blockbuster season is being preceded by the spring pay back season.  Like  Kill Bill ,  Man on Fire  is buoyed by a ferocious central performance.  Few actors today are able to simultaneously emote burning rage and a quiet coolness with the same charismatic integrity as Washington.  The first act and Washington’s scenes with little Dakota Fanning are the strongest.  Fanning is a peculiar child actor, despite her high voice, blond bob and baby blue eyes, she’s the most mature child star to ever grace the screen.  She uses that maturity to her advantage,  more convincing with a performer of Washington or former co-star Sean Penn’s caliber, than with another child actor or even the younger actress, Rhada Mitchell, playing her mother.  Fanning and Washington have a nice chemistry that elevates the somewhat underwritten relationship.  The rest of the film unfortunately is like  The Punisher , big blowups, an implausible plot line, and predictable twists.  Director Tony Scott thought using MTV-like camera work and quick cut editing, similar to that in  City of God , would pass as style but doesn’t.  Unlike  City of God , which used the style to illuminate the rise of MTV generation hoodlums, Scott's direction serves no purpose.  A perfect example is his use of subtitles to translate perfectly understandable English dialog.  Huh?  Where  Kill Bill  and the lovely revenge picture from a few years ago,  In the Bedroom , went right is their characters lost themselves cascading down a spiral of grief and confusion until vengance became the only way to regain their life.  For Creasy and the Punisher, grief was just an excuse to blow a lot of stuff up. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From the co-creators of your favorite movie review website, Jensen Vs. Jensen, comes an innovative look into everything pop-culture. The link should be up in the next few days, so keep checking in.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Quentin's world and we're just livin' it.    Quentin Tarantino has done the remarkable, he's created three great films- the sublime  Vol. 1 , the moving, slyly funny  Vol. 2  and the dizzying masterpiece of the entire  Kill Bill  saga.  The genius of Vol. 1 (and where I feel most critics missed the boat) was in the giddiness Tarantino radiated from behind the scenes.  You couldn't watch the scenes at the House of Blue Leaves without imagining him behind the camera going "This is so cool".  But Tarantino isn't going to repeat himself, or cheat the audience to pay for the same movie twice, so he switches gears, giving The Bride, the storyline and respect she deserves.  Where  Kill Bill  is ultimately a rumination on domestic squabbling,  Vol. 1  was the flashy, juicy argument and  Vol. 2  is the thoughtful understanding of what went wrong and what happens next.  That's not to say  Vol. 2  isn't loaded with those trademark Tarantino scenes where his sparkling dialogue causes the audience to grin from ear to ear, but  Vol. 2  doesn't want to just entertain you, it wants to show the affect the atmosphere, established in  Vol. 1 , has on the character.  "That woman deserves her revenge and we deserve to die" Michael Madsen, in the performance of his career, tells his brother Bill.  "But then again, so does she."  Madsen, in a beer stained sluggishness, is a man who's been slowly broken down by his sins, who's tired of killing but gets that thrill when forced to rise to the challenge.  Budd is the only viper who, like The Bride, has not overcome  his conscious, yet he's the only one she never speaks to.  Trailers have given the cinema two great fight sequences, the battle between Nic Cage and John Goodman in  Raising Arizona  and now the showdown between Elle and B.  The delicious scene, which was second to Bill in anticipation lives up to expectations, and is a testimate to the actresses physical prowess.  I understand your reaction to the final confrontation, but I think on a second examination (as I've had) you'll realize Tarantino gave us the perfect send off.  Too smart to redo or try to outdo  Vol. 1 's finale, Tarantino gives us his most twisted, layered act.  As Bill and The Bride go around and around, Tarantino does something remarkable, he simultaneously moves the story backward and forward.  The ride that got The Bride to that point was long (shot, raped, cut, beat up,slashed, kicked, buried alive, tortured under Pai Mei) and  Vol. 2  pays off with an emotional understanding of the journey.  Perhaps the best scene in both films is when  a never better Uma Thurman removes the truth serum dart from her kneecap.  Her hand quivers and you're unsure if she'll throw it or set it down.  The tension between her emotions, wanting to unleash her rage, and her training, which taught her to use her head and keep her cool is palpable.  Watching this woman battle her way through so much while knowing she could completely fall apart at any time is what made the ride thrilling.  Tarantino uses every weapon in his arsenal-dialogue, music, editing, cinematography, casting- to create a fascinating, emotionally rich odyssey.  In a few instances Tarantino seems to love his own words too much (Budd's dressing down at the topless bar could have been condensed) but this is a small quibble and an indulgence I'm willing to make to a filmmaker so in control of his facilities, so fearless and so utterly in love with movies.  It's Quentin's universe, and there's no other place I'd rather live.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Kill Bill Vol. 1   reminded us all that Quentin Tarantino is still the boldest and most stylish director in Hollywood. What you need to know about Volume 1 is:  1) it is a spectacular film in which Tarantino makes a triumphant return to the cinema by delivering this action masterpiece.  2) it is a completely separate movie from it's sequel, but it works incredibly well with it.    Kill Bill Vol. 2  , though equally stylish, shows the director's fondness for the emotional tones that make his characters so intriguing. While still enthusiastically violent, the film moves on it's key players and away from the brilliant mass gore of the first installment.   Kill Bill Vol. 2  , stands on its own as a self-sufficient movie that works without the viewers even having seen Volume 1 -- or having an obsessive knowledge of the countless obscure '70s chopsocky epics that are the object of Tarantino's homage.  A radically different tone is evident in the opening flashback sequence, shot in stunning black and white, which finally introduces the elusive Bill(played by David Carradine in the performance of his career), who was barely seen in Vol. 1. There is a long exchange of Tarantino's trademark stylized dialogue between Bill and his about-to-be married former lover, The Bride(Uma Thurman) who's name turns out to be Beatrix Kiddo, before Bill and his hit squad wipe out the entire wedding party, and leave Beatrix for dead.  Beatrix has three names left on her list: Elle Driver(Daryl Hannah), who has replaced her as Bill's lover; Bill's brother Budd(Micheal Madsen), retired from killing to a humiliating existence as a bar bouncer; and Bill himself, who we found out at the end of Vol. 1 wonders if she is aware that her daughter is alive and living with him in Mexico.  One of the movie's special delights is a long sequence recapping the way The Bride acquired her deadly skills from reclusive kung-fu master Pai Mei, played by Asian action superstar Gordon Liu. The entire section is a loving tribute to the original -- and unfortunately by today's standards, hokey -- Asian kung fu movies that so influenced Tarantino.  Tarantino creates another masterful fight scene when he pits the two amazonian blondes against one another in Budd's broken-down trailer. But I'll touch on that in a bit, the real classic sequence in this movie -- alone worth the price of admission -- has Budd shooting Beatrix in the chest with salt pellets and then burying her alive in a coffin. Micheal Madsen gives an awe inspiring performance in which he shines in every scene. None more prevalent than the scene with David Carradine at the start of the movie, in which Budd tells his older brother that he sold his priceless Hattori Hanzo katana at a pawn shop for 250 bucks. Every time that Madsen is on screen you can't help but smile, and yes, also the performance of his career.   Now, back to the battle of the amazons. Daryl Hannah plays against type as a conscienceless killer who wants nothing more than to be the one to kill The Bride. At one point, when Budd is writhing in pain from sustaining three bites from the deadly black mamba, she informs him that she regrets that the Bride died at the hands of someone like Budd, and not someone like her. As I said before, this is a masterful creation. It has everything a great fight scene needs to have, including an astonishing shot in which we see Beatrix down the hall holding Budd's Hanzo sword. The music in the background of that shot is what sells it as one of the single greatest shots in action movie history.  After all this, Beatrix is finally on the threshold of fulfilling the title. The confrontation with Bill consists of more talking than fighting, a choice which fits the circumstances. And nothing's quite as funny as Bill's vastly understated explanation/apology for putting such a bloody end to her wedding plans: "I, uh, overreacted." The seated combat scene between the two former lover's is impressive, but short. And in thinking about it, my only real complaint about the movie, like I have said in past reviews, the final fight is a vital piece of any action movie. And make no mistake,   Kill Bill  , in it's entirety, is a action movie.   Grade: B+   Nick Jensen
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I begin to tackle  The Punisher  let me inform our readers (if there are any) of yesterdays behind the scenes happenings.  Shortly after I published my piece on  Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind  Nick called me to defend his position and debate mine. Now in a perfect world all of this back and forth would have taken place in cyber space, but with our emotions high and minds racing, the lag between typing, posting and responding was too much.  The gist of the conversation was Nick stands by his opinion, I am resolute in mine.  (Nick if you want to continue our debate online I'm more than ready to defend my  Eternal Sunshine  until I can type no more)  In the past few years the ante has been upped on the action movie genre.  No longer are audiences satisfied with lots of things blowing up.  We want Johnny Depp's humor or mind blowing CGI.  The wide range of popular culture (internet, television, movies, comic books, video games, ect.) has left 80's style action movies (buff hero, little plot, big explosions) feeling stale.   The Punisher  is a by the numbers action movie that is as banal as it is predictable.  With no plot, interesting characters or atmosphere whatsoever (Tampa?) the film is devoid of any emotional attachment.  After seeing  The Punisher  I happened to come across  Spiderman  on t.v.  There was a film inspired by the comic, that took it's characters and storylines seriously.  Someone needs to understand plastering the Marvel logo before a film isn't enough.  How awful was  Punisher ?  At the end when the Punisher heads out of town he says "This isn't revenge, it's punishment."  No, I thought, it is revenge.  Mindnumbing revenge at that.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am astounded that you and I, who share the same mother, same father, same genetic makeup, could be so far apart in our opinions.  I'm starting to question whether or not we saw the same film.  Before I get to my review of  Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind  and refute yours, let me first make an important disclosure and air a grievance.  Let me preface this posting by saying Charlie Kaufman is my cup of tea.  I understand he is not to everyone's liking, such a widely innovative, peculiar artist can't be, nonetheless I relish his brilliant, tender touch and the unique new worlds he creates with his strangely endearing characters.  That said, I think you were remiss by not stating upfront that you loathe Kaufman's work.   I am achingly perplexed at how you could find the thinking "shallow" and the emotions "tepid".  Of the films we've discussed this year not one of them has had more to say or presented two more honest, realistic characters embodying a true life relationship than this film.  Kaufman doesn't expect us to buy into the relationship because it's Jim Carrey and Kate Winslet, he shows what pulls them together- his taciturn steadiness and her gregarious impulsiveness- will also be their ultimate undoing.  The tragedy, the truth to the story is these characters can't live with each other any more than they can live without each other.  Early in the film, what we think is their first meeting, Clementine tells Joel "I think you're nice, right now.  Later who knows what I'll think."  We all make these judgments on a whim, on a sliver of an interaction and when, in real life and in extended contact, they fail to live up to this standard we hold it against them.  One of the things I love the most about Charlie Kaufman movies is the tender connection the characters have.  From Lotte to Charlie to Joel they possess a fragile almost childlike love.  I'm chuckling you were dazzled by the storytelling because I thought this was the least Charlie Kaufman-like plot to date.  Unlike the twists and turns of his previous films  Eternal Sunshine  never wavered from it's original concept and left out the twists.  Unlike  Being John Malkovich  and  Adaptation ,  Eternal 's Charlie Kaufman plot was underplayed, playing second fiddle to the characters and relationship.  I thought  Malkovich  found the perfect balance between creating characters and a roller coaster plot;   Adaptation , one of the most audacious pictures of the past decade, was at times too clever for it's own good.  Kaufman and director Spike Jonze swung for the fence but didn't get all of the ball, though I admire their moxy.   Eternal  seems to me Kaufman's most nuanced and I hate to say it, mature movie to date.   Eternal Sunshine  is one of the most bittersweet movies I've ever seen and I mean that as the highest compliment.  Joel and Clementine made me smile and swoon, broke my heart and nursed it back together.  When I read your line "(It's) not about how love conquers all but how people can be weak and foolish and waste their lives on stupid destructive relationships" I thought of that last memory Joel erases.  "So go" Clementine says and Joel, his shyness never more acute, tells her he did because she sounded so dismissive.  She of course said it to be flip, to mask that she really wanted him to stay.  A week ago or so I issued an apology and as I walked away I remember thinking how slight it sounded, I truly was sorry yet I wasn't able to get that across.  I was certain the other person didn't understand how I really felt but I couldn't force myself to go back and explain.  I just walked away.  I don't think Joel was any weaker or more foolish than me and I don't think his relationship with Clementine is stupid and destructive.  Love doesn't conquer all, that's part of the problem- we want/expect it to.  Love exists in moments that we capture and collect in our memories.  What Joel and Clementine destroy isn't their love or each other but their recollection of how they felt at a particular moment.   Eternal Sunshine  has lingered in my head for days.  The reason I waited so long to blog is it's taken me all this time to find the right words.  We (mostly me) have spoken at length about Kaufman so let me make a few points on the collaborators.  Michel Gondry's hazy direction gave this story a distinctive look that was never distracting.  Winslet's funny, passionate, vulnerable performance is her best and one of the best of the year.  I've always thought underneath Carrey's manic, elastic mannerisms lies a darker, somber undercurrent.  The role of Joel required an exact performance that could have easily been under or over played, but Carrey, by buttoning himself down and staying within himself, gives a breathtaking performance.  Kaufman and Co.'s captivating, tragic masterpiece is one of the best films of the year. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Keeping with my current trend I will be reviewing   The Punisher   next. At first glance this comic book adaptation is truly gripping, taking time to establish the hero's happy domestic life before the bad guys take it all away. This is something that very few action movies do, it creates a foundation of anger and injustice to build off of. But everything after that is anti-climactic, a problem that director and co-writer Jonathan Hensleigh(the writer of   Armageddon   and   The Rock  ) attempts to solve by jacking up the violence in order to keep the audience in their seats.  Thomas Jane stars as Frank Castle, an undercover FBI agent who accidently killed the youngest son of a Tampa Bay crime lord in a arms dealing sting. When Howard Saint, played by John Travolta, discovers Castle's role in his son's death he orders his whole family to be massacred. Somehow, the wounded Castle escapes the family reunion turned slaughterhouse, recovers his health, moves into a rundown section of Tampa, and begins exacting his revenge on those responsible for the murder of his family.  The bright spot in this movie would have to be it's star Jane, who i felt held the screen nicely in his first headlining role. Jane plays the punisher as a grave, brooding vengeance machine, who stays in abtastic shape despite his daily bottle of wild turkey. Jane was even given some comic moments, having strung up a Saint insider for a torture session, the Punisher sears a steak on the stove as he pokes the criminal with a Popsicle. And convinces the sucker that it is actually his flesh burning.  Bottom line, first time director Jonathan Hensleigh neither makes anything interesting, original or profound out of the vigilante premise and doesn't stop Travolta from outrageously hamming up his every scene. The most important element to any action movie is the final fight, in which there must be some build up, ie. some nameless henchmen meet their demise, but then a big last fight with the big baddie, in which you receive closure. Bad guy dead, good guy wins. One more side note on this movie, though it may be true to its comic source, the film really pushes the envelope with its torture and sadism. Such things can be used in movies, but they need to be used properly, they don't need to be there -- just to be there.   Grade: C-   Nick Jensen 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again I will be doing this out of order, I will be reviewing our most recent venture to the movie theatre,   Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind  . In the last couple of years memory and memory problems have become a popular theme in movies, explored in scripts as diverse as   Memento  (long-term memory loss),   Fifty First Dates  (short-term memory loss), and   Paycheck  (surgical removal of memory). Now, the star-heavy, and suprisingly low-budget   Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind   is another, and on paper it is similiar to   Paycheck   because it also speculates what might happen if science could selectively delete certain troublesome memories from our psyches.  But since it comes from the pen of screenwriter Charlie Kaufman(  Being John Malkovich, Adaptation  ), it bears no further relationship to the entertaining sci-fi film and gradually emerges as another engagingly offbeat comedy-drama. The thinking is shallow. The emotions are tepid. But the creativity is dazzling. If that sounds like a slam, consider that most Hollywood screenplays are predictable, repititious, and functional -- and those are the good ones.   Eternal Sunshine  , at the very least, is an encounter with an imagination and a personality. That my friends tips it toward the positive.  When we meet Joel, played by Jim Carrey, he looks shell-shocked, riding a commuter train from New York into Long Island, lost, lonely and searching. On a train platform in Montauk, he meets a woman who's drawn to him for no apparent reason. This woman's name is Clementine(Kate Winslet), a blue-haired bookstore extremist who's as aggressive as he is withdrawn. The film zigzags through time. The most impressive sequence -- albeit somewhat slow-moving -- is the one in which Joel, unconscious, undergoes the memory-erasing process, while two technicians (Mark Ruffalo and Kirsten Dunst) get stoned and hang out in his bedroom. The movie shifts smoothly back and forth from the activity in the room to the memories in Joel's mind, to Joel's fantasies. Wanting to hold onto his memories of Clementine, Joel scrambles to hide her in remote corners of his mind, such as scenes of childhood humiliation. The filmmaking is adept enough to show, at times, snippets from the technicians' conversation floating into Joel's mind and influencing his fantasies.   The film's missing element is emotion. If we cared about Joel and Clementine as a couple, the movie might inspire a more passionate interest. But I don't think the filmakers were going for that type of movie.   Eternal Sunshine   is not about how love conquers all but about how people can be weak and foolish and waste their lives on stupid, destructive relationships. So many times I tell people to "enjoy the movie for what its worth". This movie was well acted, incredibly creative, but just lacked the emotional attachment to the main characters.   Grade: C+   Nick Jensen   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know this doesn't make much sense but here I go.   The Whole Ten Yards  had a predictable plot, a stupid story, hammy overacting and lots of trying-to-be-funny jokes that weren't funny, but I didn't hate it.  I didn't love it and wouldn't recommend anyone to go see it, but I have an odd well of affection for the film.  The original was  a quirky, off beat experiment that more or less worked for me.  In the original Matthew Perry's jumpiness made sense, he was living next door to a professional hit man, his wife wanted him whacked and his assistant was the whacker hired to do it, and Bruce Willis' steel gaze was the perfect compliment.  The problem with the sequel is neither character behaves in a believable way.  That said my affection for the film can be summed up in two words-Amanda Peet.  This is a bad movie and she knows it and still she crackles in every scene.  Why this actress, so lit up and bubbly from the inside has not become a major star is a blight on the entertainment industry.  For fair disclosure Peet stared in one of my favorite television series of all time  Jack & Jill , and I've been a fan ever since.    Her filmography is an odd dichotomy- there's no such thing as a good Amanda Peet movie (that I've seen, the exception being  Igby Goes Down , but that was a minor role) yet there's no such thing as a bad Amanda Peet performance.  It's a testament to her talent that I'm giving  The Whole Ten Yards  a slight pass on the merit of her performance alone.  Now let's go Kill Bill!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That wooshing sound you hear is my sigh of relief that you didn't think I was totally off my rocker in my  Taking Lives  analysis.  I know I'm behind in my reviews but I still have a few days until Fridays main event.  I have to say the closer  Kill Bill Vol. 2  gets, the harder it is to concentrate on these mediocre movies.  I wish for our first disagreement we had a meatier film to wrestle over than  Walking Tall , but I'm sure down the line we'll find something to really go toe to toe over.  Right now I'm too baffled as to how  Tall  earned a B+ in your estimation.  Like you I am familiar with the story but have never seen the original, but unlike you the changes didn't work for me.  The whole time I was watching the film I kept thinking it would have made a lot more sense if they had kept the setting in the South.  Northwesterners aren't really take back our community kind of people.  Perhaps the Rock wasn't up for a Southern accent  As to the gambling I thought it was a brilliant way to modernize the story and offered a platform for the producers to make a wider, social commentary but instead they caricatured the casino and the villain.  When they get what's coming to them in the end you cheer not because they victimized the town, but because they victimized the Rock.  At under ninety minutes the film felt slight with a by the numbers feel.  Rock gets beat up, becomes sheriff, cleans up town.  End of movie.  Where's the struggle, the emotional conflict.  A nice moment between father and son (which was a little too trite for me) does not a good movie make.  The Rock is a charismatic guy but I want to see him really use it, like Bruce Willis in  Die Hard , rather than just skate by.  The Rock was the only halfway notable thing in Walking Tall, which is a shame because if they'd gotten a lead performance on par with the film, they'd have one of the best awful movies of all time, instead it was just awful.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would have to agree that   Taking Lives   was anti-womem. I felt the same way but decided to leave it out of my blog because I am trying to keep the same tone throughout, trying to focus on any redeeming qualities the movie may have had, and in this movies sake, spend the other 90% of the blog on the negative aspects. One of those negative aspects was the stabbing of the pregnant woman's stomach. I am not a squemish person, but i found myself looking away from the screen in disgust. I just feel that is an image that has no place in cinema.  Now if i worked for a newspaper i would have to title my review of this movie "The longest yard". The 2000 hit-man comedy,   The Whole Nine Yards  , was no masterpiece but it was a clever, enjoyable slapstick that provided a good recipe with Bruce Willis as a contract killer, Mathew Perry as his long suffering neighbor and Amanda Peet as a homicidally ambitious dental assistant.  For the sequel,   The Whole Ten Yards  , Warner Bros. has reassembled the same cast with a different director(Howard Duetch filling in for Jonathan Lynn) and come up with an excruciating sequel that has virtually none of the wit and charm of the original. The first thing the movie does wrong is jump right into its complex set of characters and relationships with no subtle recap of what we saw four years ago. So if you haven't seen the DVD lately, you're in for a 99 miniute struggle to find out whats going on. It also became painfully evident that the original was complete unto itself and the writers have had to strain themselves to come up with a this awful premise in which the stars find themselves threatened by the gangster father of some obscure character from the first movie.  The single bright spot of the proceedings is Peet, whose aspiring hit-woman set the tone of the original and sparked its best scenes. Once again, she nails the character but everything around her is so dismal that it overshadows another good performance by Peet.  Now from the best to the worst, Willis is kept on a sporadic diet of terrible jokes about Jimmy's "erectile dysfunction." He squints and strains through the role, as though he'd taken a laxative to produce comedy. (It doesn't work.) He and Perry have no chemistry; they don't work together for laughs; they get out of each other's way. Their lack of teamwork makes you long for Robert De Niro and Charles Grodin in  Midnight Run   , a far superior comedy about a hit-man and an uptight white-collar guy.   Grade: D+    Nick Jensen
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nick I'm totally digging the tone of your posts.  They have a vibe similar to the back and forth dialog between Lisa Schwartzbaum and Owen Gliberman in Entertainment Weekly, though I'd have to say I'm more like Owen, i.e the harsher critic.  I will now stop digressing and get to the topic at hand which is  Talking Lives .  Let me begin by concurring with you, the film was without one redeeming virtue.  But I hated the film for a different reason you either didn't see or don't agree with, that the movie was misogynist.  Here are some reasons why:  1.)  In the scene where Angelina Jolie is chasing after the bad guy from the art gallery through the Carnival she's wearing pearls.  Pearls!?  Pearls are for First Lady's, not FBI agents.  2.)  When the brilliant FBI profiler learns the identity of the serial killer in the hospital how does she react- she faints and is barely able to utter to Olivier Martinez who to go after.  3.)  The twist.  Woman in jeopardy movies are as old as Hollywood but this movie took it a step farther by setting up the third act as the pregnant woman in jeopardy.  The idea that an FBI agent would keep the baby of a serial killer is ludicrous but the producers don't stop there.  After five minutes of whimpering around, Jolie's agent Scott is stabbed in the stomach.  There are few images regarding women more iconic than a pregnant stomach, and watching the scissors plunge into that belly made me more uncomfortable than all of  Kill Bill Vol. 1  put together.  If that's not enough she then removes padding as to say "AHA! We used the pregnancy as a ploy to fool you."  Now I don't want to sound as if I think pregnant women are sacred and can't be used in Hollywood (I would never give up my Kill Bill), but I had no attachment to Jolie's character so the ploy at the end had no impact, it just felt cheap.  I'm glad you referenced  Seven  a far superior film.  Unlike  Taking Lives ,  Seven  had believable characters you cared about and most importantly had something to say.   Seven , embodied in Morgan Freeman's character, was making a point that apathy is one of our greatest sins.   Taking Lives  says what, be careful of loving one twin more than the other, especially if the favorite accidentally dies in childhood?  (One last note I hope the producers of  Seven  sue over the blatantly copied opening credit sequence)  Sorry my post ran long.  I don't need a detailed response but in your next post let me know if you think I'm totally off base in regards to  Taking Lives  being anti-women.  P.S.- I didn't find  Kill Bill Vol. 1  uncomfortable in the least, I was just trying to reference a film that some professed to have issues with.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next up on this cinematic crossfire between twenty something siblings would be Angelina Jolie's   Taking Lives  . The Hollywood serial-killer thriller genre has been so overworked in the movies that it is all but worn out, and audiences(myself included) appear to be losing all patience with it -- witness the devastating reception that both this movie(just under 28 million) and Ashley Judd's   Twisted  (just under 25 million) received.  At first,   Taking Lives   seems to be just what the doctor ordered to breathe some new life into a depleted genre: it has a new location(Montreal), an innovative visual style, and a fresh idea or two, or so it would seem. It's about a Canadian serial killer who we see launch his career at age 16 in a 1983 prologue, and then (via a clever title sequence) continue it over a 20-year spree in which he not only takes the lives of these young men, but also briefly assumes their identities. When we first meet FBI special agent Illeana Scott (Angelina Jolie), she's lying in a grave. More precisely, she's lying in a Montreal construction site where a serial killer dumped his recent victim, who was horribly disfigured. Illeana is an unorthodox detective who works instinctively and is not well received by local police.  But, agonizingly, it all falls apart, and it is not a coincidence that this all happens once Ethan Hawke makes his first appearence. The audience ends up figuring out the mystery long before the script intended, several intriguing elements of the plot never add up and much of what seemed so different was really only the same old cliches in disguise.    Taking Lives    isn't just a movie title, it's a declaration. Those who fall prey to its marketing campaign will lose nearly two hours of their lives to an unimaginative, and utterly disappointing thriller that is just attempting to pirate ideas from David Fincher's   Seven  , like a cinematic theif who attempted to pick someones pocket but only came up with lint.   Grade:  D-   Nick Jensen   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since our last blog we have seen two movies, and I think I'll start things up a little out of order(kinda tarantino esque) with the action comedy Walking Tall. I never saw the original   Walking Tall  , but I know that in 1973 it came out telling the true story of the crusading Tennessee Sheriff Buford Pusser, and it was a southern phenomenon, kickstarting the "Southern" action genre.  This new theatrical remake makes some big changes to the template. Aside from being updated into current times, it has also been fictionalized(hero's name is Chris not Buford), moved to our own Kitsap County, and reconcieved as a vehicle for the fast-rising action superstar Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson. Not being the biggest fan of remakes, I think it was smart making these changes. So many times a remake is just a sloppy clone of the original that doesn't capture the magic of its predecessor.  In this version, the hero is an Army special forces vet who returns to his small hometown after many years, only to find the lumber mill closed and the main industry a gambling casino run by his slimy high school rival played by Neal McDonough. The villain tries to bring Chris into the corruption, but he resists and -- after a savage beating and mutilation by box-knife (the most feared weapon of our time) -- he is elected sheriff and goes after the crooks with everything he's got, including his favorite 2-by-4 club.  Granted, it s not exactly "Gone With the Wind" and will not be contending for Oscars, but it does have some bite. The script makes a compelling case that legalized gambling can have a devastating effect on a small community. In general, the performances are much better than they need to be for a popcorn movie like this. John Beasley is quietly touching as Chris' father, McDonough makes a splendidly detestable villian and Johnny Knoxville comes off well as the hero's comic relief and sidekick.    Grade: B   Nick Jensen   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cartoons serve an interesting purpose for they simultaneously mollify and civilize children.  Throw in an animated movie and not only will they stay distracted for ninety minutes but also learn valuable lessons, like being true to yourself, finding the inner beauty, appreciating your home and family, etc.  No wonder Walt Disney is the world’s best babysitter.  In 2001  Shrek  broke that mold, and its very funny, very touching sequel has returned to break it again.   Shrek  was the kind of cartoon Disney used to make-one that appealed to adults as well as kids.  The scathing treatment the film gave Disney went over the kids’ heads, but the grown ups, myself included, lapped up every second.   Shrek 2  is every bit as layered as the original.  Our green hero is still as uncomfortable with himself as he is with the rest of the world and his newly ogred wife is still unsure about her new shape.  One of the themes I appreciated in the first film, which is picked up in the second, is how we can be both fiercely committed to ourselves while equally uncomfortable with who we are.   Shrek 2  is the exact opposite of the summer movies seen so far- it not only has something to say, but has a kick ass, jovial time expressing it.   Shrek 2  widens its scope past Disney to take a jab at Hollywood while exploring the difficulties of happily ever after.  The go for broke, kamikaze spirit that so illuminated the first is back, and turned up in the sequel.  The Fairy Godmothers even gayer limo driver has replaced Robin Hood’s Merry Men.  The film references are not only more frequent but less subtle, especially my favorite, the  Mission Impossible  spoof.  Even more than the original the creators really pushed the bounds of a PG rated cartoon, to hilarious results.   Shrek 2  is the second big leap forward in elevating animated voiceovers to the status it deserves.  Mike Meyer’s brogue and Cameron Diaz’s giggles have the tendency to wear thin in live action films (Meyers in the  Austin Powers  sequels especially), but under their animated veneers they infuse their characters with humanness rare in cartoons.  Eddie Murphy once again finds the perfect balance between hilarity and obnoxiousness that takes the stereotype out of the sidekick.  On the other hand Antonio Banderas, mocking his  Zorro  character, throws every cliché he has into his Puss in boots, and delivers his most nimble, charming performances in years.  Every performer brought a gleeful vim to their character but none more than Jennifer Saunders, whose delicious, campy villain capped off the film with a musical number mixing  Post Cards From the Edge  and  Footloose .  Now that’s creative!   Shrek 2  wasn’t as well put together as the first, at times it seemed almost too big for its creators to handle, but it was riskier and funnier.  Sequels are hard.  For a film to be successful it must come to a satisfying resolution, but sequels intrinsically undo that resolution.  A film that not only builds on its predecessor but also deepens the characters while avoiding repetition, now that’s an accomplishment.  Just like Fiona, I’ll take Shrek just as he is.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sequel to the 2001 smash hit   Shrek   is packed with sight gags, puns, jokes and amazingly witty references to dozens of other movies(  Lord of the Rings  ,   Alien  , and   The Wizard of Oz  ), the movie blasts out of the gate like Smarty Jones at The Kentucky Derby. An energetic screwball comedy-action-adventure, that is expertly paced.  Now if you are just getting back from the moon, the story(based on a children's book by William Steig) deals with a big, green, swamp-dwelling ogre who, despite his difficult manner, found love with a ogrette/princess named Fiona. In the first film, Shrek (voice of Mike Myers) and Fiona (voice of Cameron Diaz) were married. Now, immediately after their honeymoon, they are summoned by the bride's parents to a festive welcome. The problem: The folks don't know that Shrek is an ogre; they kept Fiona's ogre-ness hidden for most of her life and expect her to marry the dashing but superficial Prince Charming (voice of Rupert Everett). Complicating matters is Fiona's Fairy Godmother, hilariously voiced by Jennifer Saunders (Absolutely Fabulous) as a cross between Estee Lauder and the Wicked Witch of the West.  The fairy tale characters from the first installment all reappear, but as much as Diaz and Myers earn star billing for their voice talents, they are curiously toned down next to their co-stars. Saunders gets a big part, as does John Cleese, who voices the role of Fiona's father the king of Far Far Away, but these characters get a bit tedious(just a bit) and I feel that they exist solely to drive the plot.  The real humor comes, once again from Murphy, whose Donkey is so genuinely funny and clever that he very nearly steals the film. Except that it's stolen by Banderas as a rogue Puss In Boots outlaw hired by the King to do in Shrek. His Puss is so endearing and charming in his less-than-honorable pursuits and so feline in his self-deluded pride, that the film brightens and magic happens whenever Puss appears on the screen.  Now officially this is the first Disney animated feature that I have seen from start to finish. And yes that includes   The Little Mermaid, The Lion King, Finding Nemo  , and a list that seems endless. But I really enjoyed this movie, the only thing that took away from this movie was the crowd. I expected that, with all the little ones in the theatre, it would be loud and a lot of annoying voices would be coming from all over, but the movie was so enjoyable that it over-shadowed the noise coming from all around me.   Grade: B+ 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a truly divided mind about  Troy .  On one hand the film fitfully executes its undertaking.  It is solidly acted, Wolfgang Peterson guides his film with a steady hand (unlike Stephen Sommers) and the effects are seamlessly woven across the screen.  On the other hand the film is way too long and lacks a pizzazz or sparkle that demands a second viewing.  I couldn’t help thinking afterward if a centuries old poem is the best source for a summer movie?  The film touches on some of Homer’s themes-loyalty, war, fame- but then tweaks the plot to make it more cinematic.  The result is less than satisfactory.  Peterson made a safe movie, smarter than its competition but not too smart to alienate the summer audience.  I would have liked it if he’d conjured up a little of that Tarantino fearlessness, not giving a damn what the audience wants or expects and made a smarter, more political film.  I don’t wish to sound dismissive of  Troy .  It is a solid picture.  Brad Pitt brings an animal masculinity to the role that is appropriate and the older actors (Gleeson, Cox and in particular O’Toole) apply their greatness into underwritten roles.  Orlando Bloom, like in  Pirates of the Caribbean , has the lame duck role that would have been overshadowed in a one-man play, but luckily for most of the film he’s playing off an averagely pretty German model whose bland stare wouldn’t launch a dingy, let alone 10,000 ships.  For $200 million they couldn’t budget in Angelina Jolie?  The real find of  Troy  is Bana, who infuses Hector with an empathetic stoicism.  The film is at it’s most focused when it concentrates on the hesitant obedience of the kingdoms two greatest warriors.  The final showdown between the two is as beautifully choreographed as it was performed.  Because the heart of the movie is the comparison and contrast between Achilles and Hector, the film, with the exception of O’Toole’s lovely speech, putters out after Hectors exit.   Troy  hits all the notes it aimed for, and was exquisitely shot, but never quite excels.  Yes it’s the best in it’s class, but being valedictorian in school of idiots isn’t much of a compliment. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going against the traditional format of the site, I will be the only one reviewing this movie, for my sister did not see it. I saw this movie yesterday and I feel it is my duty to the fans of this site and to fans of the cinema to tell people about this movie. A wild ride that is a brilliant piece of film making.  Watching his team's opponents soar above the soccer field like caped superheroes, Sing (Shephen Chow) gasps "it must be special effects!" This is the just the thing that makes this movie so great, this little inside joke, coming near the end of the movie, that's as thick with cheesy CGI as it is with infectious silliness. Welcome to   Shaolin Soccer  , director/star Stephen Chow's amazingly light-hearted spoof that truly lives up to its ad slogan "Get ready to kick some grass."  Now this movie was actually made in 2001, but Miramax chief Harvey Weinstein delayed bringing it over for three and a half years, and then when he did, he decided to release it to less than 100 screens. I am truly disappointed that more people won't see this movie. It doesn't take itself seriously, it is a one of a kind masterpiece that I would recommend anyone to see. Whether you like foreign films or not, whether you like kung fu movies or not, whether you like soccer or not.  The movie follows Sing as he joins up with older, disgraced soccer hero Golden Leg (Ng Man Tat) and rounds up his old friends and fellow Shaolin kung fu students to apply their martial arts moves to the playing field. The "brothers" from his old dojo are a specialized crew currently down on their luck. Iron Head has, well, a blow-proof noggin. Iron Shirt has the ability to trap a soccer ball in the force-field of his stomach. Little Brother is a tubby bear of a fellow, who nevertheless can float like a balloon when he jumps. And so on, you get the idea.  In a sweet subplot, Sing meets Mui (Vicki Zhao), who makes steamy buns at a food stand using the fine art of Tai Chi kung fu. She's painfully shy and mortified by her bad facial acne, but starts to come out of her shell when Sing, seeing her inner self, insists she's beautiful.  The main course of   Shaolin Soccer   is a series of soccer matches that leads these chopsocky players toward an ultimate showdown with Team Evil, run by the rich, corrupt Hung (Patrick Tse Yin), the guy responsible for ruining Golden Leg's career (and his golden leg) 20 years earlier. Naturally, his Evil players are juiced on illegal designer dope, allowing Hung to gloat, "Those American drugs are better than I expected!" The soccer matches are gravity-defying spectacles, with balls kicked so hard they turn into blazing meteorites. The scenes are completely unbelievable and completely enjoyable. There's something ingratiating about the casual cheesiness of the computer-generated effects. At not quite 90 minutes, the movie doesn't overstay its welcome for one second (when I knew it was about to end I thought to myself "no it can't be over already." And it packs quite a lot of stuff into that brief running time: a recurrent joke about slipping on a banana peel, glances at Sing's adoration of Bruce Lee, even a sudden song-and-dance number in the street, set to "Celebration."    Shaolin Soccer   is a major cause for celebration, it's genial goofiness is so endearing you can't help but fall in love with it. It is the most entertaining movie I have seen in the last four years, and probably the best.   Grade: A+ 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did a fair amount of researching about the Trojan War in the weeks leading up to this movie. I really only have two complaints about this movie. 1) It was a little long, 2 hours and 45 minutes, I would say about 20 minutes could have been cut and then it would have had it's ideal length. 2) The writer's took quite a few liberties with 'The Iliad', the epic Homer poem the movie is based upon. One could go on like this all day. But the amazing thing about all this apparent disrespect is that it doesn't really matter.   Troy   is such an exhilarating piece of epic filmmaking that it pulls you in, sweeps you up and works very much as its own thing. And at the end it has basically taken us to roughly the same place as homer, capturing the pageantry, political complexities, and rich characterization of one of Western literature's great masterpieces.  Set 3,200 years ago, the story deals with the Greek war against fellow superpower Troy that's sparked when Troy's prince, Paris(Orlando Bloom) makes off with Helen(Diane Kruger), the wife of Menelaus(Brendan Gleeson), brother of Agamemnon(Brian Cox), the Greek King of Kings.  The Greeks draft their great but reluctant champion, Achilles(Brad Pitt), raise a fleet of 1,000 ships and sail across the Aegean Sea to get Helen back, but Troy lies behind huge walls that have never been breached and things quickly get bogged down. In Homer's version, the quagmire that ensues is seen from three perspectives: the Greeks, the Trojans and the gods, who take sides in the conflict and keep coming down from Mount Olympus to directly enter the fray as allies of the mortals. Peterson left the Gods out of this movie, which I feel was a smart move, the movie might have been four hours long if he would of included them.   Peterson then faced a question that all film makers face when making a historical epic. To go with the gritty realism of   Master and Commander  , or the romance of   Gladiator  . Peterson went with a little of both. Through it's graceful battle scenes, not one but three romances. And in a most satisfying way it leans away from a movie depicting men in war, and towards showing the spectrum of strengths and flaws that each character has.  The movie's strongest point is it's casting. Brian Cox gave us an incredibly detestable villain in the role of Agamemnon. Brendan Gleeson shined as the brutish Menelaus. And a great performance by Peter O'Toole as the aged, weak, yet undeniably noble King Priam of Troy. Orlando Bloom strikes a chord in the thankless role of Paris, showing us a self-centered softness, but he also gives us a cowardly sense of vulnerability and self disapproval that explains why his family and nation would stand behind him. In the role of his brother, the great Trojan hero Hector, Eric Bana delivers the performance of his career. Bana is so unexpectedly strong and yet so sympathetically human that he all but steals the picture. Brad Pitt also found a character that he could lose himself in. He gave us another incredible performance(same level as his portrayal of Tyler Durden in   Fight Club  ). In Battle he makes you believe that Achilles is an unstoppable killing machine that knows no equal. I could not imagine anyone else cast in this role.   Grade: B+ 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like most films that have claimed the lead-off position of the Hollywood summer movie lineup(  Gladiator, Spiderman, and X-men 2  ),   Van Helsing   has long been regarded as one of the surest of the summer's blockbusters. And rightfully so, on paper this movie has it all: a proven action superstar in Hugh Jackman, a director who has given you three established hits, and the undeniably successful franchise(Universal's classic horror remakes). Not to mention the confidence the studio seems to have in it(creating a video game and soon a TV show spin off).   Granted, the prime target for this film is teenage boys, but I was a fan of the three previous Steven Sommers movies(  The Mummy, The Mummy Returns ,  and   The Scorpion King  ) simply because they were entertaining all the way through. They are the truest form of a popcorn movie, a guilty pleasure that almost anyone can enjoy.     Van Helsing   begins with a black and white reprise of the 1931 movie   Frankenstein   re-creating many of the shots frame-for-frame. In which we discover that Count Dracula provides the funding for Dr. Frankenstein's experiments. But Dracula wishes to use his creation, the Frankenstein monster, as a means to achieve his own evil goals.  Now after the homage to   Frankenstein  , we jet over to 1889 Paris, where we meet the new incarnation of   Bram Stoker's Dracula  's 60-year-old Dutch monster-hunter, Dr. Abraham Van Helsing(changed the name to Gabriel in this movie), as he's in the midst of battling a hulkish version of Mr. Hyde, played by Robbie Coltrane, in the Notre Dame belltower.  After disposing of Mr. Hyde, and a 600 year old stain glass window, he is ordered back to Rome where we find out he is a 19th century James Bond working for the Roman Catholic Church. From there he is equipped with many high-tech(for the times) gadgets, a chatty, cowardly, quick witted sidekick and dispatched to Transylvania. Where it seems Count Dracula, played by Richard Roxburgh, is just about to finish off the last of the family that has been his chief opposition for control of the place for the past 400 years -- a Gypsy princess who dresses like an L.A. dominatrix(Kate Beckinsale) and her brother(Will Kemp). He arrives just as the vampires are making their monthly assault on the population, and from then on the movie is a silly fabrication for one long action sequence: Van, his allies and the Frankenstein monster vs. Dracula, his three brides and the Wolfman.   The movie's also stuffed with enough over-the-top computer effects -- a few of them simply lame -- to choke George Lucas. Jackman does well as the famed hunter, but his strong performance gets overshadowed by hammy overacting by Dracula and his annoying brides, and the directors love for CGI. Beckinsale's lack-luster performance didn't help either. All in all Sommer's fell victim to the same problems that plaque a lot of big budget directors, He got so wrapped up in spending the money on the effects, he lost sight of what this movie should of been, a funny, action packed popcorn movie.   Grade: C-     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There’s one moment in Stephen Sommers laborious  Van Helsing  when it delivers on the fun summer romp it promised to be.  Hugh Jackman, Kate Beckinsale and the obligatory nervous nelly sidekick are trying to escape from a mansion full of vampires when the friar/scientist/tonto/whatever asks how.  “Through that window” our hero and heroine say simultaneously before smashing through a stained glass window.  For that brief moment  Van Helsing  is giddy with it’s own adventure but once they touch down the film returns to resembling a bird trying to carry a 50lb. safe.    Not being a fan of  The Mummy , the film did have a certain campiness I appreciated.  Essentially a homage to the Saturday afternoon matinees Sommers grew up on,  The Mummy  never relented its sense of fun, but it seems a raised budget and higher expectations killed any joy Sommers had to put into  Van Helsing .  Lacking  The Mummy ’s light, breezy touch,  Van Helsing  hits the ground running with its action scenes and never stops, but that’s the problem.  Non-stop action leaves the film with no character development or pacing.  Jackman is a charismatic performer who swaggers around Transylvania with a roguish gleam in his eye that could have been better put to use in another movie.  His character can’t remember his past but Jackman’s having too much fun playing the hero to care.  Kate Beckinsale for some reason has caught Hollywood’s attention (I don’t know why Minnie Driver, a sparkling, pretty Brit with greater range, doesn’t get the push) but she’s too dour and serious for this film.  A good dose of Keira Knightley pluck, ala  Pirates of the Caribbean , would have done wonders for  Van Helsing .  Sommers use of CGI went on ad nauseum, as if he was using it because he had it to use.  The appropriate use of CGI seems to be a line directors are struggling to find (a worthy topic for ‘Up For Discussion’ perhaps?) and in the case of  Van Helsing  the old truth, less is more applies.  Maybe next time Sommers can shave a little bit off his budget, put a leash on his CGI and give us more of what we really want-fun. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out what those twenty-something siblings are up to now. A no holds barred, take no prisoners, crossfire discussion on anything and everything that makes up pop culture. The link has been added, the discussion has begun, find out what the first topic is.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first two  Harry Potter  movies were recreations of the books on a large budget, the third is a film that stands sturdily on its own.  Chris Columbus is a competent, soothing director who makes films for small children but isn't of the caliber to make childrens films that appeal to all ages, like  Shrek .  I enjoyed the first two films, which were too long and too chapter like, not because of the direction but due to J.K. Rowlings overwhelming love and passion for Harry, Hogwarts and her magical imagination.  The third film, by Alfons Cuaron, is darker, moodier and more film like.  Rather that force the audience to sit through the end of the school year, the film ends when it should- after the climax.  The third installment also rewards us by not lingering at Harry's aunt and uncle.  In this installment Harry is angrier, lonlier and beginning to assert himself and the film reflects that.  It took three films but the character is starting to grow.  Like its predecesors the film is still a bit too long, but the performances are enjoyable, David Thewliss brought a nice melancholy to the picture and Emma Thompson lit up every second of her too brief appearance.  As Dumbledoor, Richard Harris left almost unfillable shoes.  Sadly Michael Gambon, lacking the other worldlyness and fragility, opts to play the greatest wizard of all as an eccentric, bumbling old man.  The character needs more authority, like say what Ian McCelan brought to the  Lord of the Rings  trilogy.   I'm not yet a rabid fan, the story needs to find something deeper and more universal to say, but appreciate it's creativity.  Rowlings world and characters are as thorough and personal as you'll find in popular culture.  In a summer of one dimensional characters and half hearted executions that's saying something.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Day After Tomorrow  is a film that wants you to take it seriously.  The creators and screenwriters didn’t want to just make a summer roller coaster ride, they wanted to make a roller coaster ride with a socially conscious, thought provoking message, and I can practically see them at the pitch,  it’s not just a disaster movie, it’s a warning about global warming .  Unfortunately in trying to be two things at once the film fails on both fronts.  The cast is full of talented actors but each seems to be squirming from the bad, clichéd lines they’re forced to repeat.  At one point when the high school quiz kids have taken refuge in the public library from the pandemonium and flooding in the New York streets the rival says to Jake Gyllenhall, our young hero, “Just tell her how you feel Sam.”  I couldn’t tell if the audience in the theater laughed because I was concentrating so hard on keeping myself from throwing up.  You’d think if a company were going to put up the hundred plus million dollars it took to create  Day After Tomorrow  they’d insist such insipid lines would stay off the screen.  Yes the special effects are impressive, especially the Russian tanker floating toward downtown, but good special effects in bad movies are a dime a dozen and lacking the creative visual paunch something like  Pirates of the Caribbean  delivered.  After leaving the theater and gathering my thoughts I took a moment to consider whether I was being too hard on the film, after all it is just a summer movie, but I’m not.  This is a summer movie that asked me, with it’s sober tone and jabs at the current administration, to take it seriously.  Perhaps I would have been less disappointed if the film hadn’t had the germ of a good film smothered beneath the mess.  The world, or at least the Northern Hemisphere is coming to an end.  A scientist, who’s dedicated his life to studying climate and mother nature, is helpless to do anything about it, so instead of meeting his end in the capital with his governmental co-workers he decides he’d rather die trying to reach his son, a teenager holed up in the New York public library discussing life, death and the end of the civilization with a disparate group of people.  Now that’s a movie I’d like to see.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came under some criticism for the prediction I made in my last review. I had stated that the summer movie season would receive it's first big triumph in the form of   Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  . Well, I was wrong, it wasn't just a triumph for the summer movie season it was a triumph for the cinema in general. I mean, I was a fan of the first two installments but they pale in comparison to the epic piece of film making that is   Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  .   Just as J.K. Rowling's   Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban   represents a step in maturity beyond the series' first two books, so does director Alfonso Cuaron's film version improve upon its predecessors. This third   Harry Potter   movie shakes the candy coating off of the franchise without violating its spirit. Chris Columbus, who directed the first two, is skilled at assembling the elements and moving a story along, but he doesn't leave behind ideas that haunt or images that linger. I feel he was a great choice to start off the series, but as Harry grows so must the director. Switching to a more artistic director, an edgier director was the right thing to do.  When I first heard they had hired Alfonso Cuaron to direct   Prisoner   I must admit I was a bit worried, I mean I had never heard of him. So I did some research, checked out some of his work and came up with only one conclusion. Cuaron is one of the most gifted visual storytellers around(he's no Tarantino, but honestly who is), whether he's working with the lavish production design of   A Little Princess   (1995) or the intimate, near-soft core porn style of   Y Tu Mama Tambien   (2002). What those two very different films have in common is that the Mexican-born director goes so far beneath the young protagonists' skin that you virtually can feel their hearts beating.  It's no wonder, then, that Harry (Daniel Radcliffe) comes into his own at last in   The Prisoner of Azkaban  , which has the advantage of being based on an emotionally rich book that begins with him hitting the troublesome age of 13. In the first two movies Radcliffe's Harry was just a little too cute, unruffled and goody-goody. The Harry of the books is far more of a mischief-maker, and Cuaron and the increasingly assertive Radcliffe get the idea. You know you've entered new territory from the opening shot, as Harry reads his wizard books under his bedsheets while flicking his wand, furiously, for light. Using magic while living with Muggles (non-magical humans, in this case the beastly Dursley family) is forbidden, but Harry has had enough of being treated like the black sheep. As in   Chamber of Secrets  , the new film has Harry causing havoc in the household, but Cuaron doesn't play the sequence for slapstick. When Harry casts a spell on his visiting Aunt Marge (Pam Ferris) after she cruelly disparages his late parents, his rage and his relatives' fear become apparent.  Like all of Rowling's books, this episode aims for an incrementally older audience than its predecessor while covering a year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Once again Harry tries to excel in wizard training and the airborne game Quiddich while warding off the increasingly dark forces that threaten his life. This time a notorious killer, Sirius Black (Gary Oldman), is on the loose after becoming the first-ever escapee from the famed Azkaban prison, and Harry soon hears that Black is after him. Making matters worse, Azkaban's cloaked, phantom-like prison guards, called Dementors, are roaming in search of Black, striking our hero with particularly deep fear and dread. Also fresh on the scene are new Defense Against the Dark Arts Professor Lupin (David Thewlis, a warm, lanky presence), who has a habit of protecting Harry at key moments, and Divination Professor Trelawney (Emma Thompson, wearing Coke-bottle glasses in a comic-relief role).  The usual suspects are back as well: Harry's best friends regular-bloke Ron (Rupert Grint) and assertive brainiac Hermione (Emma Watson); the gentle, bearish Hagrid (Robby Coltrane), who takes over the Care of Magical Creatures class with typically unwieldy results; the sneering Draco Malfoy (Tom Felton) of the rival Slytherin house; the acidic Professor Snape (Alan Rickman); the stern but kindly Professor McGonagall (Maggie Smith) and Hogwarts' wise, eccentric headmaster Albus Dumbledore (Michael Gambon, replacing the late beloved Richard Harris does an admirable job).   Film producers rarely receive the kind of recognition that directors do, yet that cast offers a powerful reminder of how well produced this series has been, by David Heyman and, on   Azkaban  , Columbus and Mark Radcliffe (no relation to the actor). Rowling's vast world requires the casting of dozens of key roles, and over three movies there hasn't been a ringer in the bunch, especially now that Daniel Radcliffe's Harry has stepped up. It's hard to return to the books and not have the movies' actors in your head. The same goes for the scenery, as Cuaron has inherited production designer Stuart Craig and his clearly articulated vision of Hogwarts, though the place has never appeared so weirdly wonderful as in our first glimpse of it here, as choir singers grasping fat frogs serenade a banquet hall illuminated by airborne candles.  Most important, the visuals inevitably are tied to mood and feelings. When a power outage hits the students' annual train ride to Hogwarts, there's a beautiful faraway shot of Ron's hand pressed to the window, his flesh the only visible light at that moment of vulnerability. Even more chilling are the Sirius Black "wanted" posters, which show the scraggly escapee raging in a film loop. On a lighter note, when Harry finally rides the winged Buckbeak, the movie takes off with him as he leaves behind his frustrations and ill omens for a moment, at least, of pure exuberance.  Well without giving anymore of the movie away(for those of you that are "hallmark" Harry Potter fans that don't read the books) I will finish by saying that this is an amazingly powerful piece of cinema that has the ability to make anyone a Harry Potter fan. And in case any of you are wondering, they are shooting for a November 2005 release of   Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire  .   Grade: A 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to start out by saying that I do not consider myself a harsh critic. After reviewing 12 movies my average grade has come out to a C+. Now it's not that I think I have been too hard on the movies we have seen, it's just that the movies that have started off this summer movie season have been, all around, average at best. But as past reviews will tell you, there are some diamonds in the rough. I would urge anyone to go see   Shaolin Soccer  ,   Shrek 2  , or   Kill Bill Vol. 2  . And now comes a time for me to make a bold prediction: This so far average movie season will get it's first big triumph this weekend in the form of   Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  . With all that said, onto my review of   The Day After Tomorrow  .  I guess it is finally official, with the release of a big, dopey disaster flick, the summer movie season is in full force. Last summer brought us   The Core  , which is still on my list of the worst movies ever, This summer it is   The Day After Tomorrow  . The disaster in question is environmental. Greenhouse gases melt the polar ice caps, and ocean currents are disrupted, causing all manner of Biblical weather. The chaotic climate change leads to continent-sized super storms that suck air from the upper troposphere, which flash-freezes everything in its path. And  voila ....A new Ice Age.  Along the way, New York City is inundated by a storm surge, from which writer-director Roland Emmerich conjures up a terrific rock 'em-sock 'em action sequence with mobs of panicked city dwellers storming the public library for safety. The people-plot revolves around Washington scientist Jack Hall (Dennis Quaid), who delivers the usual warnings to the usual arrogant government types, who brush him off. Jack's son, Sam (Jake Gyllenhaal), is in New York, stranded in the library, helping everybody stay alive as the temperatures drop. Jack heads out on an Arctic-style journey to find Sam. The lengthy trek has its moments yet is vaguely disappointing. Maybe it's just that ice isn't as gripping as the raging explosions of   Independence Day  , also an Emmerich creation.  Ian Holm turns in a fine picture of a scientist caught in the storms. Poor Sela Ward is stuck with the thoroughly boring role of Sam's mother, a pediatrician who spends the movie talking on the phone or gazing at a patient. The Day After Tomorrow has generated an inordinate amount of brow-furrowing over its underlying message. Don't be fooled. This is not a policy paper, it's a movie - a make-believe yarn that invites you to put your brain in park and not worry about thinking for the next two hours.   Grade: C 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Between Tom Hanks and Steven Speilberg they have enough talent that even their worst movies are better than most actors/directors.&nbsp; The downside to all that talent is we expect a lot of them.&nbsp;  The Terminal  is a well made movie, Speilbergs direction is the steady hand we expect and Hanks keeps his character from becoming a caricature or cliche, but it has nothing to say.&nbsp; There's nothing special or important in the story, nor is the film entertaining enough to get by without.&nbsp;  The Terminal  is like watching Lance Armstrong on a stationary bike- wow he's a good athlete, but what's the point if he doesn't go anywhere?&nbsp; While  Terminal 's creative team doesn't overcome the lack of story,  Dodgeball 's stars manage to get by.&nbsp;  Dodgeball  never soars to the height of lunacy of  Shaolin Soccer , but it gets by with some funny scenes and the charm of its stars Vince Vaughn and Ben Stiller, playing their typical roles.&nbsp; I may not want to watch Hanks/Speilberg in subpar material, but it's not so bad with Vaughn and Stiller. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Passion of The Christ  is Mel Gibsons faithful chronicle of Christs last hours.&nbsp;  Saved!  is a modern satire set at a Christian school.&nbsp; One film left me feeling upbeat and optimistic.&nbsp; One film left me feeling beaten down and dour on the state of man.&nbsp; Even a cliffs notes religious scholar like myself knows that the story of Jesus is suppose to be uplifting, but Gibsons relentless, masochistic film is so brutal and relentless all that reverberates afterwards is the evilness man can enact upon each other.&nbsp; While  Saved!  doesn't completely work as a satire (it finds sympathy for each of its characters) it does work as a religious film, preaching the value love and acceptance.&nbsp; At times funny and thoroughly well acted  Saved!  has the heartlifting optimism, Gibsons punishing film forgot.   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you can find the side splittingly wacky  Shaolin Soccer  or the humerous social experiment  Super Size Me , do.&nbsp;  Shaolin , a zany martial arts/soccer hybrid, has nothing to say but is a fun, frothy burst of absurdist imagination.&nbsp;  Super Size , which follows a month long all-McDonalds diet, broaches the serious topic of obesity with a thoughtful, light touch.&nbsp; The film raises more questions than answers, and those it supplies are a bit weak, but both  Super Size  and  Shaolin  offer a change from the typical, mindless summer fare. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>