<Blog>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been in a relationship with my hunnie for nearly 11 months now (exactly 11 on monday), and yet it seems that my love for him still does not match that of my love for this other twerp i loved before... You might be saying that I am such a low-life two-timer, but no, that is not the case.  There are times I feel I have been to nasty to him -- too nasty that bea my thesis mate had noticed  "as your friend, I have noticed na ang taray mo sa kanya"  and I do have to admit that I have been all that! Mataray, nasty, masungit, matampuhin.. and YET he is still there, still loving me with his all.. EVEN IF. now that is the phrase for the day: EVEN IF. I want to barf at all the times I have been so mean to him.. I want to take back every nasty word that came out of my mouth - but of course I can't do that. All I can do now is to be the good loyal girlfriend he has always wanted. All I can do is to love him more than he loves me. I hope I can do that. Wish me luck.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink hot 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have a new crush.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       michael buble and white boys   this morning, after eating rebisco, I played michael buble's cd on our player, and read nikki's email (nikki friend from dlsu), and learned that *white boy* really did cut his hair. I know that  *white boy* + michael buble = maita's bestfriend + *white boy* = date of the century!!! , but for some reason i am not affected. Sabi nga ni nikki,  we are just not ready to make gaguhan each other so we make gago other people (hey i beg to disagree since I don't  REALLLY  make gago my hunnie mejo lang hahah!) pero honestly, kinilig tlaga ako over the -- *white boy*  mo-- he he he!! Definitely something to perk up my day =) thanks niKKi i owe you one, see the big wide smile on my face and  HEY!!!  my mouth is still smaller than jobert's mouth!!!!  quote for the day: the beautiful cannot be held responsible for the havoc created by their looks. - that 70's show last night. just not sure if that was "by their looks" or "by looks alone" heheh anyway you get my drift =) arg ang gwapo ni ashton puñeta! sana kami na lang! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       valentine brou-ha-ha-ha   I curse. And I get 2 dozens of YELLOW roses from my bf, and my bf's mom. How cool is that! Better start cursing noW! ha ha ha!  Last saturday, I went to PASAS Gig (sorta school gig) where my bf's band played. Do you know where the gig was? NAKAMPOTAH! it was somewhere in QC (God help them)!!! ask me where exactly... well we went down GMA-Kamuning (I think) station and took a cab to Millenia! No offense to all bloggers living there but for me, it was too damn far. Makes you think about long distance relationships.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's stay together   I, I'm so in love with you,  whatever you want to do, is alright with me,  'cause you make me feel so brand-new,  I want to spend my life with you, they say it seems, baby, since we've been together, loving you forever, is what I need. Let me be the one you come runnin' to, I'll never be untrue, Ooo baby, Let's... Let's stay together, loving you whether, whether, times are good or bad, happy or sad,   Whether times are good or bad, happy or sad.   Why, somebody?, Why do people who break up, oh, turn around and make up? I just can't see. You'd never do that to me (would you baby)?  Being around you, is all I see.  Here's what I want us to do: Let's... we oughta stay together, loving you whether, whether, times are good or bad, happy or sad. (come on) Let's... Let's stay together, loving you whether, whether, times are good or bad, happy or sad. If you never need me you can set me free woman 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things I love to do early in the morning  1. take a long hot bath 2. eat rebisco butter sandwich (erk! hate the peanut butter version!) 3. listen to alicia keys (ha ha ha! got the first album as monthsary gift, will make parinig for the new one) 4. open my inbox and see emails from numerous important persons in my life =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      crack open.  I want that to happen to my head so I can get rid of the little monsters wrecking havoc inside. Prior to this I had a fabulous meal at Congo Grill - is this karma for gluttony or what?   Today is Feb. 10 and it's the bday of my boss, and unfortunately for her, the stall I used to buy leche flan from (a close replica to what my boyfriend cooks heheh) ran out of the damn thing! *boo-hoo*  KAKAHIYA!   makes you think of how the world is punishing you for being so happy   you can't be too happy ven, or else everyone will get jealous at youuuuHMmmmmmm   By the way, welcome to my new blogsite on the web, I sorta "pirateD" sand in my shoes coz I looooovVVee that song from Dido's new album (buy it! buy it! Buy it!). Hopefully this will become a permanent one since I can't have my writings all over the web right? But then again....  Hopes for the new site 1. permanency 2. free forever 3. tools tools and more tools!  See you all soon =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       aLoha!   I am migrating to this new site, and hopefully it will be more user-friendly than my old blogsite (if you call that a site? he he he). Finally, I have the universe to myself ha ha ha!  Friends, keep on dropping by =)
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe it took me this long to write a new entry, I am in fucking limbo. I can't write, I can't read, I can't even type correctly!!! Good thing there's spell check - but even my words baffle it. I am in a state of seclusion - everything I say is apparently HIDDEN so badly, I am becoming the queen of secrets!!!! And that is WAY WEIRD!! because I am not one to hide something! (hello have i ever been not so blunt about things??)  Though I am not asking a problem to burden me this summer, I am asking our Lord for the strength NOT to outbore myself, and my peers. I am becoming a problem, a menace to society. I am becoming BORING.  When normally, I would pass time writing a letter or a poem, NOW i am EATING. YES, I have developed  an uncanny habit of eating, and not just eating, STARING. Yes, my eyes are sometimes fixed on a certain subject for a long period of time - not a word comes out of my mouth.. ARG!!!!  I am not inspired enough. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ARG!   tang--- nya! Nyeta! ang kapal ng muka ng mandong yon! feeling nya tlaga! arg!! sobrang kiss and tell! huhuhu... what a dork he is. and i thought he wouldn't betray me anymore after that ThIng... but guess what? he opted to tell a story to his equally dorky and desperately maniac friend OMAR. arg! Now everybody knows. except my hunnie. and I fear that the most.  I hope he doesn't learn about it forever.... my life might be ruined by it... not now when i love him so dearly... =(
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe it took me this long to post ...  And while I'm posting this, my peripheral vision is blocked by two horrible individuals feigning concern for the environment and their  (wrinkled)  itsuras!! feeling sosyal, mukang tansan naman ng beer ng beer (i feel sorry for beer na beer)..... using the office mobile phone for their business concern when they can in fact call using their own phones! making parinig that they buy their makeup at rustans (well hindi obvious sa muka nya), and just about doing inane things that make me go wacko!   OPus? what's opus? as in opus dei?  Are you blind madame?? arg! shempre plastic smile always wins the game!!! Yey. Labo!  I'm having a rather complicated time nowadays.. no time to go to my fave hangout "sm department store", no time to eat my favorite inihaw na bituka ng baboy, no time for my boyfriend or my family.. it has always been work.. work.. work.. thank God I don't have to work during weekends.. or I might just have a breakdown.  my insomia is acting up again, making me sleep in the wee hours of the morning, giving me not enough time to rest my computer-eye-bags. All day at the office, I'm responsible for editing the catastrophic pictures of several modelong charing! it hurts! I can't take it anymore!  I need a break. a real long long long long long long loooooooong break from it all.  cynic-ven is starting to gain power again, because happy-ven is no longer in control of her life.   no longer.  so sad.  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I had an incredible friday night. Read on. This is going to be a long   May 31, 2004   Mrs. Nora Suarez President, Laitrans Association  Re:  Disrespectful attitude of Dispatcher Last May 28, 2004  I am writing to you today to complain about one of your dispatchers I encountered last May 28, 2004 at around 10:30 PM on my way home.  My boyfriend and I went to the terminal in Park Square for a ride home, while lined up, we saw that the blue URVAN had some space left at the back, but due to the things we had, we felt that we would be more comfortable to ride the following shuttle. For some reason, the dispatcher identified as Allan Tumarles, opened the rear door and motioned for us to go in, and when we informed him that we had already mentioned to the other dispatcher that we were going to ride the following shuttle, he shouted “Pinapagod nyo naman kami eh!” and he went to the table situated behind us, and started defaming our character in front of his comrades, and the people also lined up. Lines like, “Isa lang sa harap hah!” and “Pinapagod nyo kami!” only made me shout back “cno ba nagsabi sayo na buksan yung pinto! Wala naman nagsabi na magpagod ka”.  Such attitude is not befitting of a PAYING customer, much more importantly, of somebody who actually rides the service 4-5 times a week.  It does not end there, another dispatcher said to my face, “hindi pede maingay sa harap”. Tell me, is that correct? He is also the person who had been very obnoxious and disrespectful to me even before this incident.  I was mortified by such attitude, and what has happened to me is beyond embarrassment. I have never encountered such an obnoxious bunch of people ever before in my life. If it was a joke, it’s not funny.  I am appealing to you, as a young citizen of the Philippines that this kind of outrage should be stopped, and that proper orientation should be given to all drivers/dispatchers in your terminal. I have never encountered a disrespectful employee of the Ayala system, should it start now? I suppose I have proven my point.  Also, I would like to commend the attitude of your other dispatcher, the young one, who defended me by saying “ano bang pinagaawayan nyo jan, nagbabayad naman yan”. For someone so young, he has bested his co-workers by showing the right attitude towards customers.  I hope I have made my point, if you would have any questions, or clarifications, please do not hesitate to call me at the office at (02) 8129412 or thru my mobile 0920-9120904. Please tell me any updates regarding this incident; I am sure I would feel safer riding your shuttle afterwards.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       puñemas hah!!!   akalain mo! my song - well sorta feeling lang tlaga ako today - HANDS DOWN ay pinapatugtog na sa MAGIC! ANO BA!!! lahat na lang hah!!!!! nakakaasar! kelangan ko na naman maghanap ng song ko. You know the feeling right? when you like something so much you tend to be selfish,.... kakainis ng feeling. Need to find a new song.  Palpak for the day: was supposed to meet up with friends for a movie, but was notified that today may 26 is the bday of coi's older sis thus cannot come with  my friends, because feeling sis-in-law ako, have to attend dinner.... im so sorry!!! i love you all :) naxx feeeling sttarrrr
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Vanilla Vodka Party,  pansin nyo lahat nakawhite? except me? pasaway eh! :) that's me, mar, "lesley", niki, and trixietot. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Loser girlfriend tlaga. grabe na toh.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    It's been in and out of the cinemas but I still have not managed to watch it. LOSER tlaga.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sabby's birthday last May 15. Diane, beautiful kulot me, and my nephew Diego bebe!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      caught up with  vavavvoooom  adoptive sisters Maita and Trixie last night. Was supposed to go to Ruins, but instead had unlimited coffee at Maita's place. Coi dropped by after his classes thereby making me a happy girl =)  BTW, Maita does not know that you have to put in the coffee/sugar/creamer first before putting water.. WAAAA!!!!! Spoiled kasi! :P
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh... it's a wednesday (sheesh i thought it was a tuesday!) and i'm such a lazy dope-ass here at the office (for writing this blog, a resounding YES)  watched reality bites last night and it hurt a bit to see ethan hawke.. he's such a cool gwapo guy, i melt in his gaze (ok perhaps he wasn't really looking at me and he was looking at winona but then again, its my imagination at play)... haay, if there are a lot of guys looking as badDd and as handsome as he is in LONDON, I'd be on the first flight tom morning (if I do get my visa fixed hahaha)  my mother is in a weird mood today - could it be because I've been going home early for the past few days? - so i try to steer clear from her sight.  The sun is out - summer has ended but it's back? weird. I wanted to go to Puerto but I cancelled since it started raining - now it has stopped!?    "i love her, and she breaks my heart again and again, but i still love her" 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im so hungry. it's 10:58 am and i haven't eaten anything. well except for a few potato chips. a couple of days more and it's may 10 na, the D-day for all politicians. I hope the one I'm rooting for wins - a miracle indeed! and I hope the Filipinos vote for someone with integrity, wit, sincerity, and respect for humans because if he/she ain't that, then what a catastrophic country this would be...  a very known astrologer has predicted that after elections, there will be a bloody revolution, and afterwards, the Philippines will be going up the ladder of success... im hoping this would happen (ok it's a relatively short bloody revolution.. sorry the end justifies the means ba? yuck lagot ako kei Lord.), so I don't have to go out of the country and work my sorry ass. Yes, i will be an OFW. The one Gary V. sings "babalik ka rin" to, the one western union courts.. the one earning the dollars or better yet the pounds. And though i would love to earn pounds, I just can leave the Philippines behind - even if most of the time, my life is a laughing strinkeroo.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    cutie cat! this cat is owned by Jay Alonzo -photographer-extraordinaire, BUT he did not take this pic. His wife did :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im sick!  and no, it'ss not a psychological thing, it's a physical kind of sick. its so sad.  and that twerp of a flirt of a guy, didn't even call!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi darlings, for someone so depressed during the weekend, i am profoundly happy this monday morning - or afternoon for that matter.  1. my  crush-flirt-buddy  dward is single again. meaning. you know. hahahha!!!!  for some people, my life might sound a little shallow, but believe me this shallowness makes me sane most of the time. I just don't choose to dwell on the sad parts of my life, maybe because i'm not a masochist like most people are. I don't make it a really big issue. Now, don't go telling me I don't like confrontations, because if you really know me, you know I do, I just don't want to.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stages of infatuation:  extreme glee stalking depression denial  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ....for my classmate Cel....   And you never would have thought in the end How amazing it feels just to live again It's a feeling that you cannot miss it burns a hole through everyone that feels it   its from the used, titled blue and yellow =)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I acted like an uber-infatuated highschool girl a couple of hours ago, and I'm still floating!!!  Ever had a crush wherein you actually tried to STALK him by tracing his friendster account, looking up any neat looking girls in  his friends' list and just assuming that the neat looking girl is actually the girlfriend?  Yes I was that stalker.  ARG! I hate it! even my boss teases me! I can't look at him straight, nor can I stop my self from smiling when he's here. kakahiya!!!! anu ba toh!!!  haay. that's my wednesday.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there are so many jerks in the world  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    cool&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haayy friends =)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is one of my&nbsp;favorite songs in her album     &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Sand In My Shoes    by Dido     Album  : Life For Rent   Submitted by  :   urlLink  Maja Petersen      Corrected by  :   urlLink  Liz        Two weeks away it feels like the world should've changed  But I'm home now  And things still look the same  I think I'll leave it till tomorrow to unpack  Try to forget for one more night  That I'm back in my flat on the road  Where the cars never stop going through the night  To a life where I can't watch the sunset  I don't have time  I don't have time   [Chorus:]  I've still got sand in my shoes  And I can't shake the thought of you  I should get on, forget you  Why, why would I want to  I know we said goodbye  Anything else would've been confused but I wanna see you again   Tomorrow's back to work and down to sanitation  Run a bath and then clear up the mess i made before I left here  Try to remind myself that I was happy here  Before I knew that I could get on the plane and fly away  From the road where the cars never stop going through the night  To a life where I can watch the sunset  And take my time  Take all our time   [Chorus]  I've still got sand in my shoes  And I can't shake the thought of you  I should get on, forget you  Why, why would I want to  I know we said goodbye  Anything else would've been confused but I wanna see you again   I wanna see you again  Two weeks away, all it takes to change and turn me around I've fallen  I walked away and never said that I wanted to see you again   [Chorus x2]  I've still got sand in my shoes  And I can't shake the thought of you  I should get on, forget you  Why, why would I want to  I know we said goodbye  Anything else would've been confused but I wanna see you again   I wanna see you again  I wanna see you again   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i have reason to believe that there is no such thing as   YOU LEARN FROM YOUR MISTAKES    when it comes to love.   For some time now, i have been going in and out of sheer depression -&nbsp;I'm more likely to think i have become stupid as my age progressed.  Let's take for example, MYSELF. I have been in 3 " serious " relationships, and just recently (like the first monday of the month),  my boyfriend of 15 months broke up with me  - or rather wanted to be friends. It's such a duffus of him to do this since he was the one who made a big mess up in our relationship - that i do not want to discuss lest i hurl myself at the monitor.  Due to this sudden tragic loss, I am experiencing extreme emotions-&nbsp;crying spells in the night, and weird brittonish attitude in the morning - happy brittonish attitude. My friends have all taken up to themselves to tolerate me in this phase, and I am so happy about that. I get to be legally crazy YahOoOOoo.  wait, where was is?  Ok, since he did break&nbsp; up with me, I cannot believe that I am back to crying my eyes out. I have experienced this during the past 2 relationships, and since I thought I knew better, I would have no problem with the 3rd one, but this last one really did break my heart. It sucks! I thought I would easily get over him, or if not get over him, not entirely have a nervous breakdown ala mariah. But NOOOO.  I can't believe it, I'm crying again. It's sad everytime a relationship ends but not this sad - making me believe that Yes indeed there is no such thing as learning from your mistakes. We just make them.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am pain!  why does it have to end this way? can't you see you're leaving me... for an ugly girl... :(  isa lang masasabi ko: wala kang kwenta, i hate you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i kinda always knew i'd end up your ex-gurlfriend 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I may not be completely over coi, but i am starting to move... an inch away from him! i mean hello, you have to congratulate me because for today (well so far that is) I have only browsed his page for like 3 times! and that's really minimal for me! I am happy.  I may never get over him, but that's ok, you never actually get over any of your ex's, i think you just forget or something better comes along (or someone) that would make you forget about those things - and you know what? it will appear shallow 5 years from now and make you laugh your ass hard.  I do love him, i care for him, but maybe we really aren't meant to be. Now maybe we'll get back together, maybe we won't, at least we were together for a while, thats cool.. its all good.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    hay na ko si dad tlaga lahat ng pictures nakapikit! ano ba yan! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    of all the boys in the group, i have to say that mr. silent giant in the middle has got to be the most fixated of all BOYS i've met in this lifetime! At least dale doesn't pretend to be straight, and baggy still hasn't changed from his casanova days, i mean look at his mouth! tempting? uh, not for me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    padla natin kaya kei she-who-must-not-be-named-because-of-our-drama-queen-friend?? would she still consider making out with this guy/girl/bakla/tomboy? heheheheheheh!!! kaka turn off jusko. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You have got to love this Kodak Moment!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    aren't we cuties? hehehe&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cockster rupert in his REDDEST EVER! Is he blushing because of his ka-cockster maita? nyahahahha!! I had a blast that night, save for the lost earring which really pissed me off, and few other things. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the beautiful people&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ang ganda ni maita! could it be because of cockster rupert?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mar and trix (women in black! Gawd!)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    rupert, nikO, and Marikring&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    one cool pic! one cool night! one cool birthday (?), ah basta cool kaming 3! me, nix, trix during pepperees bday party. This is was a  couple of days before the breakup. This is so fucking depressing me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       shitty monday.   this is for my ex-boyfriend.   Always And Forever  by Al Green   Album :   Submitted by : Nan  Corrected by :     Always and forever each moment with you Is just like a dream to me that somehow came true And I know tomorrow will still be the same 'Cause we've got a life of love that won't ever change and  (Chorus) Everyday love me your own special way Melt all my heart away with a smile Take time to tell me you really care And we'll share tomorrow together I'll always love you  Forever, forever  There'll always be sunshine when I look at you Something I can't explain just the things that you do And if you get lonely phone me and take A second to give to me that magic you make and  Chorus  Forever, Forever Loving you is the thing that I plan For a very long time Me and you, you and me, we as one     
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       shitty monday.   this is for my ex-boyfriend.   Always And Forever  by Al Green   Album :   Submitted by : Nan  Corrected by :     Always and forever each moment with you Is just like a dream to me that somehow came true And I know tomorrow will still be the same 'Cause we've got a life of love that won't ever change and  (Chorus) Everyday love me your own special way Melt all my heart away with a smile Take time to tell me you really care And we'll share tomorrow together I'll always love you  Forever, forever  There'll always be sunshine when I look at you Something I can't explain just the things that you do And if you get lonely phone me and take A second to give to me that magic you make and  Chorus  Forever, Forever Loving you is the thing that I plan For a very long time Me and you, you and me, we as one     
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        to him who must not be named        I'm missing your laugh, How did it break? And when did your eyes begin to look fake? I hope you're as happy as you're pretending.    I've tried so hard to tell myself that you're gone, But though you're still with me, I've been alone all along    You were everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it , And all of our memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending  See me jump through hoops for you, You stand there watching me performing, What exactly do you do, Have you ever thought it's you that's boring, Who the hell are you!!!  Thought you'd come around when I ignored you, Sorta thought you'd have the decency to change, But babe, I guess you didn't take that warning' Cause I'm not about, to look at your face again  At this point you’ve realized, Life is but a joke,  and the laugh’s on you, Its funny right   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME!!!!     HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME!!!!     HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME!!!!         so what the fuck have i learned in my 23 years of existence?   um..      ..   ...         ...      joke lang. of course i learned a lot - but the most valuable of them all is TRUST. No it's not the condom.      You can't trust just anybody   Trust your CLOSEST FRIENDS   Trust your PARENTS MOST OF ALL    Trust in the LORD TOPS IT ALL             
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was supposed to have a nice day today - but it got ruined when I remembered coi.  for 3 weeks now, I have been nursing a broken heart, and though that sounds a bit joe d mango-ish i have to say it,   I AM WALLOWING IN MISERY.    My ex is having fun with his life - I mean fucking look at his friendster profile - so many girls so little time! ang saya saya. He's such a fucking good friend to everyone, everyone except the girl he told "friends muna tayo", except friggin me!  ha ha ha! he's such a nice person! sarap kasama! tangina nyong mga kaibigan nya! except si erika (i have found a kindred in her)! tangina nyo! gnyan kayo kasi hindi pa kayo nakakagrad! mga immature! kala nyo pag naging boyfriend nyo si coi sasaya kayo? HAYOP! magisip isip muna kayo bago kayo gumawa ng ikababagsak nyo leche! tapos pag naging ex kayo ng gagong yan, SIGE LUMAPIT KAYO SA KEN HAH! AT TATAWANAN KO LANG KAYO MGA UGOK!  woW! thats really nice! i should vent out my anger more often!    ikaw Coi, KUPAL KA!   kala mo cute ka! well, yeah cute ka pero wag ka! mas madami akong cute na makikilala ka! kala mo ngayon bitter ako, HELLO malamang noh iniwan mo ako eh! pero give me 3 months, MANIGAS KA, gaganda ako lalo, iimprove ko life ko WITHOUT YOU and then you'll realize what cheap jerk you are for letting me go! BY THAT TIME, madami na akong boys na pinapaiyak! fuck you kayong mga lalaki kayo! pero ayoko pang maging obit just to remind you. Kaya ikaw COI, HUMANDA KA NA!! Ayus ayusin mo sarili mo gago! Kung dati, you can ignore my calls, ngayon AKO NA ANG IIGNORE NG CALLS MO! at kahit cute ka pa ren, at kahit LOVE na LOVE KITA, kakayanin ko yon, kasi dati kinaya mong gawin sa kin yon...        
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         At My Most Beautiful    by REM  I've found a way to make you I've found a way a way to make you smile  I read bad poetry into your machine I save your messages just to hear your voice. you always listen carefully to awkward rhymes. you always say your name. like I wouldn't know it's you, at your most beautiful.  I've found a way to make you I've found a way a way to make you smile  at my most beautiful I count your eyelashes secretly. with every one, whisper I love you. I let you sleep. I know your closed eye watching me, listening. I thought I saw a smile.  I've found a way to make you I've found a way a way to make you smile 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in a few days, i'm celebrating my 23rd bday, and it fills me with sadness that nobody will be sending me flowers on wednesday.. ahhuhuhu! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA  it's slightly depressing me, and i've been playing all those sad sordid songs for the past 30 minutes in an effort to further depress me even more. its so sad.  Hmm. . . maybe i should read up on melanie marquez again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stupid.  I found myself in a horrifyingly strange position for a date proposal - from me nonetheless.   YAK!!!!!!    Ok, so the guy wh0's being a very nice diversion from it all has been chatting with me again (after 3 record days of not calling me BABE), and I for some   INSANE   reason asked him to be my "boyfriend for rent" on friday. AND IT TOOK HIM SO LONG TO REPLY.  I sorta figured out he didn't want to go so I just said (after yelping silently - you try to do that! hehhe!!!) "  haay never mind, forget i asked  "   to which he answered  " i cant, my brother's leaving the country  "    YEAH RIGHT!         Of course I wanted to eat my hair to try and choke myself to death, but then again, there are only few pretty people in the world, why should i get rid of myself. I answered in typical  kabit  way "  no it's ok, I shouldn't have asked anyway  "         GEEZ the life of a kabit tlaga!      
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's our 16th monthsary yesterday, august 1. 9 more days and it's my birthday na, august 11.  I cant stop thinking about him and I cant stop singing that " ill never get over you getting over me " song. Takte yan. nakakaasar na tlaga.  I am plagued by reminders (genesis bus line, my passwords - that I havent changed due to laziness, our fave song, etc etc), and so do the songs that keep bugging my head.  Last saturday, my friend Mytz and I went to quiapo to witness   heaven dvd on earth  . Yes they were pirated dvds but for us striving working girls, it's ok! hehehe!  Bought  fahrenheit 9/11 (really good but too long), cheaper by the dozen, something's gotta give, ranma 1/2 OVA 1 & 2,  and more. I forgot actually. I also bought 2 pairs of earrings. Really cheap.  Of course we also asked for divine intervention from The Black Nazarene, and I really prayed for grace that day - for me, my family and my friends and the whole Philippines. We needed more than the holy water showered on us - we needed a POOL of that. If only it were easy to get blessings by showering ourselves with holy water - it would probably a commodity that would be uber expensive - and naturally, it's always the rich who get it. Geez, wala rin palang silbi.  I love the song   summer sunshine   and I've been singing it for a week now - except when I get that whiff of sadness in the air, and start singing "and where are you now? now that i need youuuuu". I particularly love the line "i kiss you and nobody needs to know" and it's dedicated to the   punkin  (acdg to nikki) - who hasnt messaged me in the past 2 hours!!!!  arg !  anyway, back to reality, because he hasn't called me BABE in like 2 days... tapos nalaman ko lasing lang pala sha - ehem TIPSY - nung friday kaya I figured out na ganon sha kagago. bwiset.  hay nako MEN.     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>