<Blog>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright this is my first time trying this, so bear with me.  The last few months have been  chaotic, exciting and quite frankly frightening.  The list of what I've gone through is long which includes but not limited too knee surgery, moving, and starting a new job.    Lets start off with knee surgery.  Ahhh  yes.... Good ole Las Vegas. To say the least it made that trip unforgettable.  For those who know how it happen, I need not say more.  For those who don't, well what happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.  The good news is my knee since then has healed up quite nicely.  Luckily the damage wasn't that bad.  I was able to walk out the hospital the same day.  I was in crutches for a couple of days and had to wear a knee brace for about a month.   Things have been going quite well for me at my new job.  Though I do miss my old job.  Casadei(old job) for all it's problems and drama it was home to me for the pass six years.   I grew up in that place.   I miss the entire crew even Eletra(boss) who drive me nuts.  She called me last Friday.  I should really call her back but I just been dreading having to drive over there.  Kelly(friend and partner in crime) started a new job, last week.   She's only been there a couple of weeks so she's still trying to get situated.  She seems to miss the old place too when I last talked to her.  At my new job I'm still trying to find my place.  I've met some cool people.   I love my office.  I have a nice view, plus I got a pimpin new computer with a bad ass flat screen.  The best part of the my office is the door which I can close at my discretion.  I want to move myself into the engineering department were the real money is made.  We will see how that works out.  Unfortunately there is no eye candy to speak off which blows.  I'm starting to think my boss has no emotions.  He is worst than Ben Steins.  It's like talking to a robot.  I've been at the new place for about a month now.  I have to say I have really cool roommates.  I love the place.  I never realize how far away from everything I was until I moved.  Everything you can think off is now only within a short drive or walking distance.  Plus I like the house we live in.  We had a bit of an issue with the heat but that was solved last week after Erika(roommate) had to lay law with our landlord.  Erika is this way cool fashion designer.  We finally got our DSL hooked up yesterday.  I was as having serious DSL withdrawal been on dial up for almost a month.  She has this really energetic dog named Apple.  He has no off switch.  The other roommate is Julie, she's this hair dresser/hotel worker/bartender.  I rarely see her, she works very long hours when she's not home she's usually with her boyfriend Kevin who I just met yesterday.  I started Yoga last week.  I love it.  It's right around the corner from my place(so I have no excuses). It's very intense to say the least.  Basically it's 1 1/2 hours of yoga in a room heated too 105 degrees and 60% humidity.  Plus the eye candy is great.  Last but not least is the good old love live.  I still haven't found anyone worth while however there are a couple of women I have interests that I'm dating.  We will have to just wait and see.    Last few dates from women I met in bar's have been awful.  Your eye-balling you watch before the date even begins.  I've had better dating experiences dating women I've met elsewhere.   Including the internet which has been an experience (good and bad).  I guess that's pretty much it... I don't know how many people are going to read this nor do I care but what the heck...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I avoided getting a real job for years out fear that it would make me miserable, despite that I have a degree from top school and great promise. So instead I had a very fun but safe(no chance of getting fired) job that paid halfway descent money. I was wrong. The reason being I was already miserable to begin with. I would deny it to myself and everybody else around me. At times I would believe it. Last year I finally gave in. I finally put my degree to good use. I found a job in my field that pays very well, with the potential of growth. So instead of just being miserable, I'm miserable with money.   I'm going to have a few drinks with co-workers after work today, then I'm going to have more drinks with friends tonight. I'll go out again tonight with high hopes of having a great time but half way through I'll be drinking just trying to drown out the fact that I'm not. I go out with friends, I'll meet women hoping to find something will fill this inner void. It's not sadness as it us utter boredom, or maybe a mixture of the two with some disillusion throw in. Finding happiness in the little thing is difficult, to say the least. I don't feel as though I really have anything to say to anybody. The funny part I end up saying a lot about nothing. By meeting me you would think I was the life the party I laugh, tell jokes, keep everybody entertained. Popularity or lack of friends or potential mates has never been issue. It's finding joy in these things that has been the struggle.   Like I said, you would never guess I feel this way. I don't talk about it much if at all because I know people don't want hear it. Nobody wants to listen to that, it's depressing. The funny part is I feel that most people can relate to what I'm saying but nobody is brave enough to actually come and say it(myself including). Let alone hear it from someone else.   So instead we all go out. Put on costumes of fancy and we all stand around, posturing, canvassing the room trying to find something better that will break us from this funk. Or at the very least find some distraction so we can it make through this singular moment in hopes that next one will better, but it never does. We make-out or take home some stranger to fill some immediate need only to feel empty the next day all over again.   See I realize something it's not about that one moment were everything turns around. This dullness will continue even if all my material and social wishes come true. I will never be truly happy all the time with what I have. It's the search that for something better that drives all of us forward. The second we are content we look for the next thing. Because as much as we hate to admit we need something. A goal to keep us going. Basically to give us meaning, a reason to keep living. We are defined by what we do, not who we are.   So instead we cherish those fleeting moments of pure bliss. You know what I'm talking about. Five seconds after you cum, eating ice cream on hot summers day, a first kiss, winning, etc..... Those few fleeting moments that we engrave in our mind to help us through the long extended periods of utter boredom.   So this is my life. Every now and then I have these introspective moments of brilliance. Sometimes my cynicism gets the better of me, other time my hopeful optimism leads me down a road disappointment or utter joy. I've learn to accept the world we live in. I'm trying to find happiness fleeting as it is. Though the rebellious side of me every now and then tries to break free from this cycle only to be slap down to reality.   I'm sorry if this depresses you but It's like I said I have these moments. I really am a fun person, really. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's March 1st.  I've just finished up a very short and expensive month. Sooo.... I'm broke until friday.  On the bright side I've had an excellent weekend.  Erika and I finally finish watching Twin Peaks.  Very dissapointing.  The one thing we didn't want to happen, happened.  It totally sucked, to be fair it wasn't David Lynch's fault the show got cancelled.  However, that doesn't give confort to the terrible dissapointment.  So much so that we were in need of alcohol afterwards.    I'm convinced that apple(Erika's dog) is a ecstacy loving, panty sniffing, foot fetish, bi-courious dog.  It's ok we love him anyway. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I talk to my old friend Jenny from Casadei.  I haven't talked to her since we got layed off back in November.  It was funny I completely called her by accident.  I was trying to call Jennifer a girl I met a week before to ask her out and I ended up dailing the wrong Jennifer from my address book.   I didn't even realize it until I heard her voice.  She seems to be doing well she just got engaged with her longtime BF.  It's about time Jenny. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dating in LA at very least is an adventure.  I've learn so much about human behavior over the last year since my break-up.  I have 3 dates this weekend and I'm only really excited about 1.  Which makes me wonder, why? Why I'm going out with the other two to begin with?  I probable spend between $300 and $1000 a month on dating and going out.  I didn't realize this until last night when somebody mention that the average guy who dates spends about $280 a month.  I did the calculation I realize spend well above the average.  For two reason.  First one I live in Los Angeles, everything is so much more expensive here.  Second I date far more than most men.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today's has been a rough day at work.  I have several people coming at me from different directions.  It's just one of those days.  This is the first real time I've had to gather my thoughs and survey the damage. I guess I needed to vent a little.  It's just frustrating.  A nice dinner and video rental sounds awesome right about now.   I had a pretty good weekend.  I went out with friends on Friday.  It was fun.  Hung out with Erika and her crew at Three Clubs. I flirted with a few girls, had a few drinks, I guess all in all just had a good time. Saturday I mellowed out and friday got a chance to watch Troy with my friend Vanessa.  She's pretty cool.  She made lunch for me today, that was nice of her.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmm.... I'm starting get the cold shoulder from Parker which is not good.  Too bad too I was really starting to like her.  I just hope I'm overreacting.  We met up this weekend.  I though we both had a great time and I though that it was implied that we would continue seeing each other.  However I've called twice and she's yet to return my phone calls.  It's been a week.    I'm still dating other people.  However, I was really starting to focus my attention on Parker.    This sucks!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok here is the deal.  Her name is Parker.  I've been dating her for about a month (a new recent record..lol).  We only get to see each other on weekends because she lives in Irvine.  I met her through a friend of a friend type of situation.  We always have lots of fun our conversations are great.  BUT their is more than one problem.  First off she still lives with her boyfriend which is not good.  She tells me it's over and the only reason she has moved out is that she can't afford it.  Which understandable because she is strapped for cash right now.  BUT that's a big BUT.  I went to visit her a couple of weeks ago in Irvine.  I picked her up had a great date.  We had sushi, walked on the beach and had a drink at a local bar but when I went to drop her off.  In the apartment that she shares with her ex(so she says).  We kissed right in front of their apartment.  All kept thinking while kissing her is what if this guy catches in a total lip lock?  Is he really going to be ok with that?  I know she likes me because she's told me this much and has given every indication that she likes me.  However, deep down inside I keep thinking I'm setting myself up for disappointment.  She has a lot on her plate right and the last thing I want is to pressure her into an uncomfortable situation.  Aside from the BF situation their are a couple of other issues she's got deal with.  If things weren't complicated enough I'm starting to really like her.  I just don't want to get my heart broken.    I got to slow things down in my head.  Take a deep breath and see the situation for what it is.  Far easier said and then done.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, I've decided no on Amsterdam.  However, I want to go to Barcelona and/or London. I'll have to rework my reservations but it shouldn't be difficult.  I'll take care of travel arrangements once I'm there.  Flights are cheaper if I book them in Europe plus I can always take a train.    Erika should be back from Japan tomorrow and blake came back from Europe yesterday.  Seems like a lot of my friends are taking, taken or will take trips this summer.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Erika just left for Japan.  I have to say I'm a bit envious.  Don't get me wrong I'm happy for her but I really need to get out of L.A. even if just for a little while.  Maybe I'll go to Vegas this weekend.. That's an idea.  I've got my trip to France next month. That cannot come any sooner.  That should be awesome.  I love France.  I'll be in Paris and in Nice.. However, since I'll be there for 17 days... I have time to go to other places. I might just have to do that? Maybe Amsterdam???? Maybe... We will see...  Until then I'll just chill and wait.. Should be a boring weekend.. I should change that.. I'm going to start making plans now.... Do something... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did this 10 day cleansing fast.  All I consumed was this lemonade with maple syrup, cayeanne pepper.  In the mornings I had to drink this this huge glass of salt water.  Before going to bed I had to drink this dieters tea.    It was not very fun.  I'm suprised I was able to make it til the end.  I do feel better after coming off it.  I lost about 12 lbs.  Plus my body feels so much better.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Most of the drama has been cleared away at work.  Today is probable the first day in about 3 weeks were I've had a chance to breath.  It's scary how one little thing can screw shit up.    I don't know I'm in a wierd mood today. I'm not depressed but I'm not happy either.  I'm not lonely or anything like that.  In fact I'm quite content.  I just don't care today.  All I want to do is sleep.  I just don't care today.    The whole Parker thing has come and gone.  It's probable for the best.  I feel like I'm living a very selfish exsistance.  I want someone to share something special.  Everything else in my life is going great for once.  It's just that one thing that I'm missing.  My friends seem to think I'm destined to stay a bachelor for a long long time.  I can't really blame them(behavior dictates perception).  They see me date woman after woman with liitle or no interest other then sex.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is my last post before leaving.&nbsp; My flight leaves in a few hours and I'm killing time at the airport.&nbsp; I'm nervous and excited, though I can't tell which&nbsp;emotion is which.&nbsp; This my first big trip by myself.&nbsp; The last few times I've taken big trips I've always expected life changing experience and to an extent they were.&nbsp; I always came back with greater understanding and acceptance of the world.&nbsp; However each time, it didn't hit me what I've learn until months if not years afterwards.&nbsp;   I'm at a crossroads and I've been stuck at this crossroads ever since my breakup.&nbsp; I made a&nbsp;choice at that time of&nbsp;a life of immediate satisfaction over substance because at that time it felt right.&nbsp;&nbsp; It help me get through the pain.&nbsp; Though I'm not proud of what I've done over the past year, I'm also&nbsp;not a shame of it either.&nbsp; This is who I am and it help mold me into the man I am today.   I had recent scare after taking STD test.&nbsp; Luckily everything came out fine but in the five days of uncertainty I came to a conclusion.&nbsp; The time for change is now.&nbsp; I try to fool myself in my Vegas trip.&nbsp; I had an&nbsp;opportunity and I took it.&nbsp; As I was with that stranger in that ladies&nbsp;restroom at The Rio.&nbsp; I remembered those five days.&nbsp; I didn't want to go through that again so I stopped it before it&nbsp;went to far.   I'm leaving on this trip with the understanding that I need to make a change for the better.&nbsp; The timing could not be any more perfect.&nbsp; Sure I'll see amazing art and architecture.&nbsp; Meet new and interesting people and come back with a great appreciation of the cities I had the&nbsp;honor of visiting.&nbsp; However, I hope I will come back with a greater understanding of myself.   I need this time&nbsp;to myself away from Los Angeles and the non-stop partying.&nbsp; Quite frankly I'm tired of it, maybe that's why I finally acknowledge that I am at a crossroads and need to make a decision.&nbsp; every time I go out now, it's not like it was before.&nbsp; I'm starting to see the down falls of&nbsp;my lifestyle and it's not pretty.&nbsp; I dodge a bullet but&nbsp;how long can I&nbsp;go dodging bullets.&nbsp; Lets say, got forbid.&nbsp; I do catch something how&nbsp;will I be able to look my mother in the eye and tell her.&nbsp; How will be able to find the love my life.&nbsp; I won't.   It's funny&nbsp;everyone I know expect me to comeback with tales of conquest.&nbsp;&nbsp;They expect me to go out every night and get hammered and&nbsp;come home with some stranger.&nbsp;&nbsp;Honestly I don't give a shit what they think.&nbsp; I'm tired of these &nbsp;false expectations.&nbsp; Sure you get a good chuckle out my stories and say "oh that's just Carlos" but it's my life, my health and I'm not going to live up to someone else expectations.   I have no expectations of this trip.&nbsp;Self discovery as I've learned a long time ago is on going process that last an entire lifetime.&nbsp; I have a new found appreciation for my life, for&nbsp;the people around me,&nbsp; for all the things I've been blessed with&nbsp;and the opportunities I have ahead of me.&nbsp; I'll be getting on a plane soon with an&nbsp;appreciation of this wonderful voyage I'm about to embark on.&nbsp; I'm just going to take it all in and let the chips fall were they may.&nbsp;   The world is quite beautiful when you learn to appreciate what you have instead of what you don't.&nbsp; I don't need to go looking for something else.&nbsp; I have me and that's more then enough.&nbsp; I don't drown out my sorrows in alcohol, because I have no sorrows.&nbsp; I don't need to fill the void of loneliness by sleeping with some stranger, because I'm not lonely.   Well I guess this is&nbsp;goodbye for now.&nbsp; I'll try to post when I'm away.&nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got back from Vegas this weekend.&nbsp; It was supposed to be a great trip.&nbsp; Which to an extent it was.&nbsp; It just didn't feel right.  Last night I had the best dream.&nbsp; One of those dreams you just don't want to ever wake up from.&nbsp; In this dream&nbsp;I'm having dinner with my mom, &nbsp;sister and girlfriend.&nbsp; The food tasted so good. &nbsp;I didn't have a worry in the world.&nbsp; We are just laughing enjoying each other's company.&nbsp; My girlfriend and I said our good byes and end up at some street fair.&nbsp; Here we are in this crowded street fair&nbsp;but somehow&nbsp;it's like theres no one around us.&nbsp; We're laughing, talking, playing, teasing each other. &nbsp;I felt completely and utterly happy and in love with this woman who love me the same way.&nbsp; Moreover, in this dream I can see her face as clear as day.&nbsp; I knew her every contour, her every expression, her&nbsp;every slight impefection that made her human.&nbsp;&nbsp;She was so beautiful..&nbsp; I knew her and she knew me.&nbsp; I didn't have to be somebody else I just could be myself.&nbsp;&nbsp;My&nbsp;fictional dream&nbsp;girlfriend she felt so right&nbsp;I&nbsp;couldn't help but&nbsp;feel so&nbsp;completely heartbroken when the dream was over.&nbsp; If I could of stayed in that dream forever,&nbsp;I would.&nbsp; But alas here I am awaken fighting to find that happiness.&nbsp;   For me when I make life a decision it usually takes many weeks if not months or years&nbsp;of thinking and weighing the consequences.&nbsp; I've been thinking of slowing down my lifestyle for a while.&nbsp; It's just not&nbsp;healthy and it's leading me down the wrong path.&nbsp;&nbsp; I want to feel like I did in that dream and it's not going to happen I continue to self-destruct.   I had a great weekend but I still felt like something was lacking.&nbsp; It wasn't like previous trips either.&nbsp; We usually all did things as a group but not this trip&nbsp;we kind of all did our own thing.&nbsp; I guess we are all growing up and growing apart.&nbsp; I guess I need to except this.&nbsp; I need to start&nbsp;focusing in&nbsp;on myself and what's right for me.   I need to grow up and accept the fact&nbsp;that I can't be a kid forever.&nbsp;        
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First this girl who is living with us has turn into a nightmare.&nbsp; It's not what she did (although she never washes dishes, take out trash and always parks on the lawn) its what she said.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Sunday night I'm chilling in the livingroom watching TV and she's in the kitchen on the&nbsp;computer, talking on the phone.&nbsp; She's talking to her boyfriend and I could hear everything because she's right in the next room.&nbsp; She could see I was there for god's sake.&nbsp; When she's starts talking how everybody here is shallow and fake.&nbsp; Then she goes&nbsp;onto comment about how Erika should not be&nbsp;going&nbsp;out with a&nbsp;married man.&nbsp; Keep in my that&nbsp;this married man she talking &nbsp;about has been a friend of Erika's since they were kids and the friend (Skip) was in town. Then she starts ripping into&nbsp;me...  &nbsp;  Dammit I should of said something.&nbsp; At that point I walk out and she goes into Erika's bedroom and I proceed to leave.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I told Erika what happen and we were ready to kick her out.&nbsp; Unfortunately we felt sorry for her so&nbsp;now we are stuck with her until Sunday.&nbsp;      
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My itinirary is finalize.&nbsp; I'll be in Paris, Nice, Barcelona and Paris again before coming home.&nbsp; I'm&nbsp;excited, it's less then three weeks away.&nbsp; Plus I'm going to&nbsp;Las Vegas in less then two weeks.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  There this girls staying with us for the past few days.&nbsp; She seems to be cool.&nbsp; She just moved from Ohio to start a new job.&nbsp; She's a friend of a friend of Erika's.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't know why I torture myself. A few days ago I emailed Parker. I know, I know bad idea. It was a nice email friendly email, though. I asked her how she was doing, told her I was doing good and that I wanted us to be friends.   She email me back. Told me she was doing good. I mentioned in my email my trip. I guess that started our conversation. We been emailing each other back forth everyday since. The conversation is light friendly.. Mostly talking about movies, books, music and politics.&nbsp;   I don't want to read into it.&nbsp; We'll just see were it goes.&nbsp;To be honest I don't want to be 'just friends.' I have no idea what's going to happen.&nbsp; She's cool but she's flaky so I'm not putting much stock in anything.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One other thing I wanted share.  I met this girl.. Umm, woman.  I met her a couple of days before my trip.  We had 2 awesome dates and we've been emailing each other back and forth since then.  She's in buffalo right now visiting her parents.  She'll be back a week from today.   She's been incredible so far.  We'll see how it works out.  I have a feeling this one might last while.  I don't want to read to much into it this early, but still I can't help but smile when I think about her.  Her name is Sarah.  I can't wait until I see her next week.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK... It's about 1Pm... I got a phone call yesterday while I was in Barcelona.  It was my boss.  They needed me at work right away it was an emergency.  Next thing you know I'm at the airport booking a last minute flight back home.  I got in around 7:30 AM I went from the airport straight to the office.  On my way I ran into Erika on the freeway... It's kinda of funny if you think about it.  I'm awfully tired I haven't slept at all in a couple days.  I tried to get some sleep on the plane but it was useless....  The worst part is that I'll be here late... When I get home I'm probable just going to crash...   The trip was awesome.  I fell in love with Barcelona.. I have a new favorite city.  My only dissapointment is that I had to cut my trip short.. I really didn't buy anything.. I was going to do some shopping this weekend but thats never going to happen.  I was quite dissapointed.. My boss said he would make it up to me...  Oh well... It was fun while it lasted... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>