<Blog>


<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Heres where i'm gonna keep my stuff to add on to bentzou.blogspot.com. its gonna take a lotta coding but i can do it
     
    
</post>


<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dude i'm gonna get m y licence nex month its gonna be sweet, i cant go to the A1(like the dmv but hella easy) cuz my dad is makin me pass the dmv test which is crap cuz i'm crapptasic at parellel park 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Fall Back Down" _RaNCiD_  Dont worry about me Im gonna make it alright Got my enemies cross haired and in my sight I take a bad situation gonna make it right In the shadows of darkness I stand in the light Ya see its my style and Ill keep true I had a bad year but I got through Ive been knocked out, beat down, black and blue Shes not the one coming back for you Shes not the one coming back for you   If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  It takes disaster to learn a lesson Were gonna make it through the darkest nights Some people pretend to make a reason But that one make everything alright  Well the rest of times they dont faze me Even if I look and act pretty crazy On my way down she betrayed me Now my vision is no longer hazy See Im very lucky to have my crew They stood by me when she flew Ive been knocked out, beat down, black and blue Shes not the one coming back for you Shes not the one coming back for you   If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend  If I fall back down  Youre gonna help me back up again If I fall back down Youre gonna be my friend 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am the master Bull5H!+3R
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      People should listen to rilo kiley they're good  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      couldnt write yesterday had to work. today i almost got in a fight with a magic corner kid,( if you dont know what that is, its a kid that hangs out in the southeastern corner of our lobby and they tend to like the rpgs,anime,comics,card games, to an extent and scares most people, as for me i like the comics rpgs comics, but not like these kids, it gives me the willies) any way i slap the kid with fly paper, then my friend keleio slaps him with fly paper, and i sneak a piece of fly paper on the back of his jacket and i go up to him and smack the back of his head with fly paper,and keleio hits the side of his face with another piece of fly paper. the kid rips off the fly paper and smacks both pieces on my face i call him a bitch and  i kick him in the ass, the hortaculture teacher mr berberich sees this and the kid and me have to stay after class 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Watching invader zim. just got done eating dinner, nothing happened today. i found my ps2 cord , havent played in a while. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      just got back from anchorage i'm tired i had a lot of pizza a lot. it was good eatin
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at work. i need new shoes, my pumas are all jacked up. i think i'm going into anchorage tomarrow, i dont think we can stop to by some stuff though. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at work. i cant find my ps2 cord i think i left it at skool. im still sick i think i'm getting better though.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just got back from neon bowlingwith my cousin ronald, it was sweet i got beat by a drunk dude
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ITS FRIDAY, and i didnt get my licence. here at work, i gotta get outta mrs thompsons science class, shes driving me crazy. i didnt take my drivers test. couldnt my parents couldnt come. but its all good my cousin ron might take me neon bowlin if he gets outta the house.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and so is marcelle foxley, vanessa arno, britney vaughn, tiffany vaughn, alexis gotzler, amanda piatt( except i heard she chews and smokes and thats gross), ashley dickerson, jenny comer,leslie berberich,sam hunt, steph carlson, elisa overby, kenny psenik,  and thats about all i can think of 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      krystal cantu is hot
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool lookin up info on the temple mount. i finished the last part of the hsgqe reading it was easy. i brought my ps2 today i played marvel vs. capcom2 and silent hill 2 atv off road fury and kingdom hearts. we also watched swat. the library people are scaring me 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at work i finished part two of the hsgqe. math i think i did pretty good. after the test my friends jake and mitch went to taco bell, but not before we had to help the shop teacher mr lords move lumber. the truck had a bed that tilted like a dump truck and wood boards were sliding off. a board slid off and it was about six feet way, another board slides off and pushes the other board which catches my shoe and crushes my toe. its ok though i think my fungus saved my toe. any whoo the people at taco bell are stupid. the total was like 9.80 and i give him 15 dollars to see what the dude would do. he uses the calculator on the cash register, he puts 15 in the register and takes out my five again and hands it back to me. and he screwed up my order dumb bitch. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      did the high school graduation qualifying exam. atleast the first part ,writing, it was bs, so long, except if i fail this test i dont graduate. i watched once upon a time in mexico at skool, it almost got taken away, i should bring all of my movies, yea that would be tight.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      didnt write yesterday went into anchorage (biggest city in alaska) for some shopping, watched once upon a time in mexico today it was sweet. finished my spanish movie yesterday, jc forrester snorted wasabi, and ate a hot pepper, after that he got on his old football stuff and we went down a hill in a shopping cart.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      !!GAME LIST!!: games i wanna get silent hill 3 ,2: restless dreams,4 Bloody roar 4 fatal frame 2  ICO Kingdom hearts 2 Metroid:zero mission onimusha 3 zelda:windwaker mario and lugi: superstar saga mario cart double dash 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      watchin sienfeld saturday night live is next. this night was so busy we made $2000 thats good enough for two nights, its crazy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my little brother just made a blog it should last a day or two still work its calmed down a bit i am so tired my feet are swollen larger than they usually are. my sister just got back from basket  ball she lost both of her game.loser
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My little brother bernard is an idiot
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      still working still sick nothing has happened today i gotta pee, but there would be no one to watch the cash register my little brother is outside playing in the snow i hate him he's been pretty useless this whole day
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at work still sick some dude and his kids are here theyre friends of my mom and dad gotta work the whole day today 10 maybe 11 hour shift...:( most people dont do that but i do. i gotta do my spanish movie tomarrow it gonna be good first theres gonna be a jackass segment then a sinfeild segment then a baywatch segment i'm the lifegaurd i'm gonna need to learn how to run in slomo 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just got done with my spanish, score now i gotta shovel my drive way, damn
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HOLY CRAP I MODDED MY BLOG
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DAmn some people can really mod their blogs i really need to learn how to do taht 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      happy valentines day 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friday the 13th still sick, i have to work tommarow all day it's valentines day and that means it gonna be hella, its gonna suck, by the way i work at a chinese resturaunt, i donno how romantic chinese food is but it must be romantic enough cuz we alaways get a huge crowd on valentines day and it sucks. i donno  how many people lookat my posts maybe its just me i need to get my profile on my blog  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
           here at home writing  a plot diagram on MACBETH 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool again lookin up info on aspartame. keiths thuggin it on the computer. i donno what to do theres a Canadian lookin over my shoulder. theres a kid named joey in my class he isnt too bright he got electrocuted and he has a smell to him its b.o. he STANKS
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      O MY GOD my favorite web comic mallmonkeys.com is gonetahts depressing it was hella funny. now its gone*tear*watchng mc battles this blind miget dude is whoopin up on this big black dude whoop never mind hes gettin rallied, i gotta new car subaru forester its bad ass i need to get my licence i'm gettin it next week cant wait to go out again 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
          get the new blink 182 album its good i command you go get it NOW
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i'm sick, the link to mall monkeys is jacked it goes to hot topic i myself do not shop at hot topic if you were to catagorize me i guess i'm a nerd/prep, weird combo. i need nyquil lots of nyquil. i'm watchin the oc many people dont like the oc i donno why its a good show. i need to get once upon a time in mexico, johnny depp looks bad ass in taht movie well thats all the ranting i'm gonna do for now later 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool hangin with my canadian buddy gellin like a fellon
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First post of the day nothin much happening just   livin in a small town in AK there was a fight today big ass kid named jake kicked the shit outta kid named gabriel. gabe stole his truck and according to werd on the street gabe sold his truck i donno how it is in the lower 48s but in the AK you just Fd your self
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so sleepy i only got 5 hours of sleep last night, i saw school of rock it was pretty good, jack black is tyte.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HOLY SHAT AND A HALF I GOT MY LICENCE
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      XD :D ^_^  SPRING BREAK XD  :D ^_^  GETTIN MY LICenCE TOMArrowXD :D ^_^ XD :D ^_^ XD :D ^_^ XD :D ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool again. in math doing a geo packet its ghetto, trisha is hot thats all i gotta say 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool with spencer tyler austin and tyson doin sum math its ghetto tylers mom is a trapazoid tyson just left and i gotta finish my math
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      once upon a time there was a kindergarten boy who needed to bring in something or tell something exciting to the class. when the teacher called the little boy to show or tell what he had, the little boy said ''i wanted to tell you about a period'' the teacher asked '' whats so exciting about a period?'' the little boy said '' damned if i know but this morning my sister missed hers and my dad had a heart attack, my mom fainted, and my sister's boyfriend shot himself in the head.''
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      damn i never right any more. yesterday i went over to my friend andrews house with everret. we went over to fred meyers and bought 15 dollars worth of candy and played the ps2 until everret and andrew got a sugar high and wrestled me to the ground. it was sweet, after that andrews parents came home when we were watching retarded animal babies that sht is funny. after that we played diablo, and ate tacos. taht was my yesterday 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday night i watched starsky and hutch, it was good.  I give the perm a 8/10  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I might go see Starski and Hutch today with my friend Everett and Andrew I heard it was funny. I haven't written in a while been busy Im goin to Japan in August I gotta find sponsors to go though. Yesterday I went on a field trip with the horticulture teacher it was great we had pizza hut I got the buffet and ate 16 pieces only 2 kids beat me though they ate 17 apiece it was crazy
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at the library and this blows. i'm looking for information on wong fei hong, and everrets complaining a lot and alexis on rubberfaces.com
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      66 points for my xbox SCORE!!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HORROR MOVIES THAT FREAKED ME OUT  1. THE EXORSIST 2. DAWN OF THE DEAD 3. JEEPERS CREEPERS (1&2) 4.TEXAS CHAINSAW MASSACRE  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just watched kill bill volume 1 it was great, my favorite part was the origin of o-ren. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at skool in the computer lab derae is lookin at my blog, i need to do my science project, derae says you all suck
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CRAP! i got a thirty hour flight in august in japan . its gonna be crazy i wil have to kill some one at 15 hours and i will have to take over the plane at 15.01 and if they hold me down god help them all 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i'm tryin to come up with a rap its not coming along very well
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i'm gonna get a xbox with the mountain dew dew codes i got 3 so far i'm goin dumpster divin
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im watching the miss usa pagent i dont know why AK didnt show up so i dont care any more. i need to do home work, last week i went on a savenger hunt with some mormans it was good, i was  pimp, we lost though
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ben Tzou's X-Men Team  wolverine cyclops pheniox gambit  colossus storm beast angel havok juggernaut iceman emma frost nightcrawler professor x 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      TOP 25 FAVORITE TOONS  1.The Simpsons 2.Batman: the animated series 3.Batman Beyond 4.X-men 5.Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 6.Samurai Jack 7.SpongeBob SquarePants 8.Tenchi-Muyo 9.X-men:Evolution 10.Dexter's Laboratory 11.Invader Zim 12.Spider-Man:the animated series 13.PowerPuff Girls 14.King of the Hill 15.The Family Guy 16.Furturama 17.DragonBall Z 18.Cowboy Bebop 19.Sailor Moon 20.Speed Racer 21.Looney Toons 22.G.I. Joes 23.Transformers 24.Animaniacs/Pinky and the Brain 25.The Justice League
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      its 604 do you know where i am ?
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      happy memorial day everybody. here at home i just got done eating lunch i had hotdogs and hamburgers, yesterday i went to my friend andrew's new property, we hung out for a while had had a bbq, it was fun, i got 50 dollars mowing the lawn yesterday,score, i never should have brought my brother to wasilla, he was acting like  a dumbass, no school today i was, dang i gotta go to work now.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i got my graduation pics!! and i'm watching your friend andrew wk hes sweet. i met a freshmen chick named teah at graduation, she was hot, i cant wait til next. i was juss jokin about bustin a mack on her, and acted like a dumbass, but i think she took it seriously, and i think she was a little creeped out by me, :( . o well i think i can change her mind. dang shes hot, shes gonna be one of the reasons why i think next years gonna be good. my friend keith and i are gonna go to the american idol in anchorage, i think he has a chance, atleast he can sing
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home tonights graduation night. i was gonna go to the grad blast but it starts at 10 and goes to 5 am, and that sucks cuz i have work and a curfew, damn you rules and my moral sense! its gonna be the last time i can take pictures cuz my photos came out like crap. well it starts soon so i gotta go
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i'm working on my english collage, and it looks of crizzap, its all good though, i am so tired from football practice, i havent worked out in several months so as you know i wasnt at the top of my game, eh so tired. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just ate dinner and took my friend keith home he was here for a while and we played resident evil for a while after that i helped him make a profile for msn. today was the first day of football training it wasnt hard i made a 7.19 in the 40 meter dash, but what was crazy is my friend jake huen ran it under 5 seconds, and for jake's size that is hauling like crazy.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home watching rockos modern life im close to finishing my 7 page essay, man taht thing sucks,dang i am a sad sad man. ha 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i'm writting my english final, i'm listening to new found glory they do a pretty good job of remaking songs, i like their take of my heart will go on(the titanic song) they do a sweet job of juvinille's back that thang up. i'd better finish my final ms, thomas is already on my case about not doing it
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just got back from wasilla it was great i brought my sister to go shopping while me and my friends walked around fred myers and wal-mart. we still have a week and a half of school left which is ghetto... its all good football is starting soon !! that should be fun fun fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here at home i just got back from anchorage and i finally saw mean girls! it was good i liked it, even if it was a chick flick, the only bad part was there were some crazy ass b!tches, this crazy little 13 year old comes up to us and starts talking, i know she was on something or drunk and i had to explain voodoo juice to a little girl, and a little girl takes a drink of her soda and spits on me i'm like what the hell and they leave it was Fd up, but the movie was good i give it a B. i also got my pic of me vanessa and kyle it turned out great except i have a green book cover on my head and kyle kinda looks like a old crack addicted frodo, only vanessa looks great and thats what matters, damg that was corny.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just got back from work, today was the last day for the seniors. i'm gonna miss them, Chris, Junoir, Nick, Justin, Vanessa, David, Sean, Tiffany, Oland, espcecially vanessa mmm vanessa, shes great, shes perfect, smart hot and great personality, i just hope her mom (the art teacher) doesnt read this that would be awkward
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DAMG its hot!! its 71 degrees! that may not me much in the lower 48s but remember i'm in alaska its hella hot. i dont think i'm gonna pass science its close to impossible now. which sucks, today wasnt a great day. i forgot my wallet at home, i tore my pants, i had to work alone today, and i'm gonna most likely fail science
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      at home its wednesday, its the last night of angel, and the season finally of smallville. i get to go to anchorage on saturday twice!! i gotta do my english final and my science final, and study for my spanish and math final. not good, not good at all.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here in my motel, i'm writing my essay that was due last week X_x. i need to get more organized. this keyboard kinda sucks. i dont know why its sorta less than responsive. anyway today kinda sucked i had to finish my forensics final, and i have til friday to do my final science project, my english final was due today, but i didnt do it. i dont know why its not really lazy. its more like hating to write about something i dont really care about, but i gotta do it anyway to get a grade. damn spyware i hate spyware,viruses, worms, adware, and all that other crap, i wish there was a free program to get rid of it all forever.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home yesterday i watched van helsing, it was pretty good i dont know why the critics gave it a bad review, it was pretty good. my friend keith is gonna come with us it anchorage on saturday hes gonna see van helsing and me and jj are gonna watch mean girls
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just woke up. its sunday, last nights snl was good, the only bad thing is that epidsode was jimmy fallon's last =(. i wonder who they're gonna get for the weekend update. J-kwon was pretty good. the olsen twins werent bad either.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home watching seinfeld. its saturday night live on next, ashely and mary-kate olsen are hosting =D. J-kwan is the musical guest he needs some braces, he has some messed up teeth. its snl's season finally, so it should be good. tanners over at our house hes small. and i dont think he sleeps much. saturday night live is gonna be on soon!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just ate dinner,i'm watching xplay. its the golden mullet awards, its all the crappy games man there are alotta crappy games. im gonna stay at home today. work wasnt difficult today, there werent any costomers, my little brother is playing with his friend, now hes gonna spend the night, i found the snl skit online for downloading at http://www.mugglenet.com/fusion3/fullnews.php?id=1122. i gotta warn that it can sometimes the server is down and you cant download.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just got off work it was busy, i cant go to mean girls on friday cuz my sister amy has to babysit on friday, as you can see theres a girl of the month in my sidebar every month i'm gonna put up a new pic and her site every month
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      at home watching the simpsons, i think i might be able to go to van hellsing on saturday
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      at home i just got done eating, i had to unearth the garden today it was hard work even if my sister helped me i donno if i can watch van hellsing on saturday or friday. i may have to work and my parents might not let me. i'm watching a preview of day after tomorrow. damn it doesnt look half bad, i'm problably gonna see it
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here in mr. berberich's room i'm doing inventory for the plants i just sent zack to look at the trees. we gotta lotta trees, i need to find out how to put pictures into my background. i might go to see van hellsing this friday or saturday it should be sweet.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here at home i had to work tonght the hostest was sick i cant figure out how to change the background on my blog, i need to figure out how none of the copy and paste codes work, hey jj if your reading this the site the site were you get the html code is http://wvrocker.tripod.com/codes.html ,  and may 21st baby thats the day were gonna see mean girls o and you can get jj's blog in my links section.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just go back from my friend andrews house. we watched the matrix:revolutions, and we ate skittles everret and andrew tweeked out again, today my class went to my resturant to eat, shay hall was a dumbass as usual. we had a lotta food. i need to find out how to freakishly modd my blog
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home watching malcolm in the middle and harry potter(her her her hermionie!) nobodys on msn at least no one to talk to, hey look its hilary duff   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home watching ebert and roeper, i dont really pay attention to the two thumbs up or down crap, i have to work today and its mothers day which sucks because its gonna be really busy
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn IT I cant go to mean girls nex week cuz jj has to go to some church thing in hope, but after that week jj doesnt have any other plans, so i can finally get a ride to anchorage, dang i wish mean girls can come out to the valley
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      watching viva la bam its great, i'm tired, the big snoop dogg is hosting tonight on saturday night live and i heard that the olsen twins are hosting next week, Yippee mary kate and ashley olsen! avril lavine is the musical guest, my sister is babysitting tonight if she wasnt i could have went to go see mean girls, its gonna suck if mean girls disappoints me, which is unlikely cuz i heart lindsay lohan
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i'm so BORED! its ok though nex week i'm gonna go see Mean Girls, yea i know i sound a little obsessed, but it is all good cuz lindsay lohan is hot, and tomarrow night the big snoop dogg is hosting saturday night live an d avril lavine is the musical act,
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DAMG IT!! i cant go to mean girls cuz my ride had to go watch his little brother's basketball game. DAMG you christian look at what you did
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      tonite i'm going to muldoon to watch mean girls
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at the computer lab keith is practicing boxing and james is lookin at flowers jenny is worthless
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If every thing goes at planned i can go to anchorage to watch mean girls with my gangsta buddy jj and his bro  !! LINDSAY LOHAN!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Top 6 Actresses Under 25 that i think are hot and if you dont then thats too bad  1.Michelle Trachtenberg  2.Hilary Duff 3.Lindsay Lohan 4.Mary-Kate Olsen  5.Ashley Olsen 6. Amanda Bynes  You may think they're young but i'm 16 damn it and i think they're hot. Plus Michelle is already 18, Lindsay is turning 18 in a few months,I loved Lindsay in Saturday Night Live, she was HOT, Hilary and the Olsen twins, i can wait for them, and Amanda i donno how old she is but i think its really close to 18 or she is 18, thats all i gotta say about this.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i'm in mr. berberichs horticulture class with my buddy monique this class is boring i  need a guest book i'm so sad i'm gonna cry softly in the corner.Just kidding
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ronald spent the night last night, and today i went with him my sister amy my brother bernard and his friend JT to harry potter, i had already seen it but i think i'll change my grade for a B-/C+ to a B+, i dont know why it just was it was just better the second time around.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i worked til 5 today. then i went to everret's house with andy and yet again we played halo, i'm watchin snl janet jackson is the host, its a rerun. i cant get the vcr to record anything on the tv. and i'm trying to tape the snl next week because i think the olsen twins are hosting.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i dont have to work til one. good times, i should have up a new girl of the month soon, but i dont know whether i should have hilary duff or lindsay again. hilary because she was the girl of the month for june but she was changed out for the olsen twins because of their birthday. and lindsay because she turns 18 on the second of july
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i might be able to go to white chicks on sunday with ronald and my brother bernard, it looks funny, i worked today again and i have a full day tomorrowl and that sucks, but at least it's money. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i didnt have to work today so i went to everrets house again. we played halo for 3 hours dang i am one worthless p.o.s. its midnight, and i found out that vanessa arno found out that i put to get a picture with her at #1 on the things to do before i die, and i am embarrassed, i also finally talked to her on msn today, damg i am a sad sad man. ha
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      today i had a day off and on my day off i went to everrets house and played games for 3 hours. it was fun. i was going to bring my little brother bernard to around the world in 80 days, but my mom said no.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just got off work, a few days ago i rented timeline. 50 first dates, and Elephant. the 50 first dates was funny and timeline was mediocre. but elephant was crazy. the movie starts out like a ordinary day in a normal high school, but it goes to hell i won't tell what happens but it was crazy i give it a A-.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i bought a new cd player, and its decent. yesterday i told amy that my best friend everret was now living with us and that he was going to be adopted into the family because his mom threw him out of the house, everything is going good, and hopefully amy wont read this
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home its friggin hot out, i just got off work i worked a 10 hour shift, i am tired, watching reba, its a ok show so far. outta the 3 movies i rented last night grind was the best one. my babys daddy was ok and along came polly was just dumb, and grind was like roadtrip crossed with a skate video, and i got a pg-13 rating but it was still funny and the skating was sweet. i give it a B-. my babies daddy i give it a C, and along came polly i give a D- cuz jenifer aniston saved it from a F.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i got home and hour ago, i'm watching the mtv movie awards, and i am tired i had to wash dishes all day. it was ghetto. i met a new girl at the library i never got her name, she looks like the skinny white girl on degrassi. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i got off work a little while ago i saw shrek 2 today with everret and bernard, it was better than the first one and i really liked the first one so i give it a B+. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i watched you get served and in america. you got served was crap but in america made up for it, i give you got served a D+ i would have given it a F but the dancing was tight, and in america a A, it was a really good movie. volenteered at the library earlier today it was hella boring, 70 something people signed up tahts alot. i got the mtv movie awards from jj but i let my friend jason borrow it because he never saw it 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i have to go to work today and volenteer at the library. after volenteering at the library i have to work at the resturant, then at 5 i will be bored outta my mind.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happy birthday to the current girls of the month mary-kate and ashley olsen. they turn 18 today,and theyre still hot
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home it was busy today at work, i taped the snl with lindsay lohan last night, it was tight. jj was able to tape the mtv movie awards so he should be able to get it to me tomarrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home it was busy today at work, i taped the snl with lindsay lohan last night, it was tight. jj was able to tape the mtv movie awards so he should be able to get it to me tomarrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday was so busy at the resturaunt. i taped the saturday night live with lindsay lohan as the host, it was good. the hostest was "sick" yesterday and i had to cover for her, it sucked mainly because i was up at 7:30 and i had to go into anchorage
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home it was busy today at work, i had to work all day today. yesterday i went to everret's house to watch the mtv movie awards, and i think that starsky and hutch (ben stiller and owen wilson) were robbed when they lost best onscreen duo. and lord of the rings won best movie. again. the only good part was seeing lindsay lohan, but it seemed that they didnt show a lot of her. o well she was hot any way. i think britney murphy smoked some gonja before the show cuz she was messed up
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home yesterday i stayed my cousin ronald's house, we watched roadtrip, and we went to day after tomorrow, it was pretty good i give it a B. and roadtrip was halarious i give it a B. i thinking of getting out of the Mtv.com community, cuz the members are not very bright. at all. i ask one question on the message boards and it takes several days for a Bull$h!t answer, WORTHLESS is the first thing that comes to mind when i think of the message boards.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home, i have to work today and i have to find everret so i can watch the MTV movie awards. the community at mtv.com isnt very good, no one has relpyed to my post in the forums and all the other posts have people replying, which sucks so if anyone knows when the mtv movie awards are gonna show on mtv2 please comment on this post
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home today was hot, so very hot, i couldnt take the heat.i worked the morining shift as usual today, i think i found someone with cable, at 5 o'clock (alaska time) the MTV Movie Awards are gonna be showing 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday my sister left for the foreign exchange program, she'll be gone for 2 weeks a that means that i have to work, alot, o well it has its perks, i was able to get that pic of lindsay lohan without getting caught, and i can look at porn for 2 weeks without worrying about my sister catching me, although i never look at porn anymore, and the pic of lindsay does not count. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      if you read my blog you will know i have a thing for lindsay lohan, and whats great is i found one of THE hottest picture of her you can see it above my past girls of the month. if you like women in bikinis or lindsay lohan or both you will love this 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i just got back from home. yesterday i saw harry potter and the prisoner of azkaban, in my opinion it was the worst of the 3 so far. so i give it a b-/c+, because the movie was more of a coming of age movie the movie was too short they left some stuff out. i also saw eurotrip, jebus michelle trachtenburg is friggin hot, lil skinny but friggen hot, too bad there werent any boobies.of her. i give the movie a B-, due to the fact that they went to a nude beach, but it was full of guys, only guys, and a dude gets tortured in a amsterdam kinky way ew.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      damg ronald has to work tonight, i jus i'll juss go with everret and andrew, o well its all good.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i dont have to work today!! its friday harry potter opens today, and i have to see if my cuzin ronald is working or not, he also works at a restaurant.as you can see i changed the girl of the month mainly because i remembered that the olsen twins turn 18 this month.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home today was a great day, i got all my classes i wanted, and today i chilled with my favorite cuzin Ronald,and my best budds everret and andrew, it was great. today we went to the video store to find eurotrip, but they didnt have it, dang michelle trachtenberg is hot! too bad the chick working there was stoned, she had some mad incents burning. it was good, if everything works out im going to see harry potter with ronald, it should be tight
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey i gotta new blog i like this its green it works for me and its better than my old one
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here at home i could write yesterday i was watching movies with my brother, we watched Freaky Friday and Scary Movie 3.Today is the last day of school and it is good,i got pulled over by a cop today, i got off with a verbal warning thank god. i have a new girl of the month up it's hilary duff, tomarrow i have to go register my classes,and i need to get classes i failed, i'll have engilsh 2 science 2 english 3 math 2 and team sports, what suks is my sister is gonna be in some of my classes. o well
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       here at home, oh my god i gotta see the village, it looks F'ing awesome, on saturday i'm gonna watch harold and kumar go to white castle with my cousin it looks halarious, and i'm gonna watch the village on monday, and i'm gonna watch bourne supremecy the week after, today was kinda boring, i worked again, my sisters gonna be back in a few weeks, and on the 15 of august i'm goin' to japan!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       here at home i think i'm gonna use italic today, its classy, i have to watch the exorcist beginings, it looks f'ing tight, i'm gonna watch harold and kumar go to white castle this weekend and on monday i'm gonna go see the bourne supremecy, watchin' leno theres a dude singing, i didn't catch his name, but hes good, i think its ricky or something like that. its getting late and bernard has a cold so i'm gonna be working alone tomorrow, dang i like writing in italic  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i watched a cinderella story, it was pretty good, atleast i liked it, hilary was great, i give it a B-, it was kind of a chick flick, but at least it was a good one. yesterday i stayed out the latest i've ever stayed out, 12:30 yeah thats right i'm a badass, ha, i have to worked today at 1:00 and next week hopefully i can go see bourne supremecy, it looks so sweet 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at h0me i had to clean out my parent's closet today, tomorrow i'm gonna go to the movies with my cousin ronald, were gonna see a cinderella story, mmm hilary duff, it should be tight, i got the avril lavigne cd, its ok, there are a few good songs, but some of the songs are a little too "folky" for me  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here at home, watchin leno, julia stiles is on, i so gotta watch Bourne supremacy. bourne identity was sweet, and having julia stiles in there isnt bad either. i finally cleaned my room, its great cuz i can see the floor again.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i gotta get ready for work in little bit. yesterday i watched i robot. it was pretty good, i give it a B. i also bought confessions of&nbsp;a teenage drama queen, it wasnt one of lidnsays best, but watching lindsay preform for the movie was worth it so i give it a C. i'm gonna add some things to my blog like audio and video clips 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home, my sister and mom went to california , my mom's staying for 3 days and my sister is staying for 3 weeks, damg it, i have to work, it was busy today at work, mainly because my mom wasnt there and i had to do her job, or atleast part of it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home today was boring yet again. i went to a teacher's house and met some deligates fr0m japan. it was so boring. i was going to watch i,robot, but i had to go to meet the delegates, damg, on tuesday i'm goin to watch a cinderella story, and buy confessions of a teenage drama queen. good times  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home, the best of will ferrell part 2 wasnt as funny as part 1. i have to go to a dinner with my dad, were going to the ELP teacher's house to meet some japanese people. its gonna be ghetto. i'm problably gonna miss my friend andrews birthday, damn.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home, i cant play football, didnt make grades, it sucks, next year i will play. i will play football in palmer alaska! tonight its the best of will ferrel its gonna be tight.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home, these past few days havent been very eventful ,i went to ronalds house again,my cousin miron is moving out, and i saw the butterfly effect, it was good, a little messed up but i give it a B-. i didnt have to work today. good times, and i also gotta new pic of hilary duff on the girl of the month section. i also modded my blog, hmm i guess a lot more happened than i thought 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home lindsay is offically 18 and i read shes going out with wilmer, fez from that 70s show, what a lucky man, hopefully lindsay is not going out with him, or lindsay is abstinant. i worked today, im still poor, everret got $323 in his pay check lucky s.o.b. tomorrow is the 4th of july yippie fireworks! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home i have to go to work in a hour, i got a hair cut, its no longer the shag but  a slight mohawk, its lindsay lohans b-day today, i wonder whos shes going out with, who ever he is he is one lucky mofo
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      here at home. i was chilling with ronald there past few days, it was fun but i am so tired... i have a new girl of the month up YAY its Hilary! but its gonna be different tomorrow Cuz its lindsays birthday!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       here at home , i gave my password to my friend everret cuz he needed to to email a friend, now hes messing with my profile, so i have to change everything. damg, yesterday i watched the village, it was the worst movies i've ever seen this summer, no story no plot, good acting though, there was good storytelling but with no story, so i gets a D-,  god it was  disappointing movie 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>