<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, we left Older Son at his new school yesterday, and I feel like crap today.  He threw a couple of massive tantrums, one at the doctor's office and another when I wouldn't let him get into the school fountain butt-naked.  The sister who serves as school administrator walked up in mid-tantrum and said she knew I was occupied but that she wanted to give me and Older Son a hug.  I thought, "here, let me give you a hit in the head," but I didn't say so.  DW said her good byes while I went out to unload the car; I didn't insist that Older Son come back for me to say good-bye.  By then, he was walking around the campus with a very large man who had been called in during tantrum time.  He reportedly was doing much better by the time we left yesterday, but this morning I called and was told that he hadn't slept last night.  However, he perked up some after breakfast.  Knowing that Older Son is having such a hard time hurts me deeply.  I like the residential side of this place.  It's very nice.  The day school, which is public, is a joke compared to our own public school system.  However, I think Older Son's preacademic skills and his self-motivation are sufficient to overcome that.  What he gets in the residential side should be sufficient to allow us to bring him home in 18 months or so.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a very moving spiritual experience last night.  Older Son was already lying in our bed, when Younger Son wanted me to take him in and put him to bed.  We spoil our kids rotten, and putting them to sleep is part of the spoilation.  Anyhow, Older Son was still awake when we went back to the bedroom.  Younger son got into bed right up against Older Son and nuzzled his head against Older Son's chest.  We listened to a CD of soothing music and I stroked both of their heads until they fell asleep.  I was misty-eyed, but not out of sadness about Older Son's upcoming boarding school placement.  I felt real joy for the first time in a while.  These moments are rare and I savor them.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow and Friday are big days for my family.  Tomorrow we drive to Alexandria, Louisiana, with Oldest Son, and Friday we enroll him at his new school.  It's not something I really want to do, but it's the best I can do for now under the circumstances.  So now the President is jumping on the Constitutional amendment bandwagon, knowing full well that the thing won't even get out of Congress until after the November election.  Pretty cynical, but it may backfire.  A lot of conservatives are uncomfortable with constitutional amendments of any kind, particularly ones that give more power to the Federal Government.  Also, while Middle America might not be all that comfortable with gay marriage, I don't know whether Middle America is so outraged by it to tinker with the Constitution over it.  IMHO, this is a matter for the states to decide, without interference from the Federal Courts on the one hand or those who would amend the Constitution on the other.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I woke up and it was raining hard.  I had looked at the paper a couple of days ago and saw a great extended forecast.  This is New Orleans, however, and the paper always lies about the possibility of rain during Mardi Gras.    This month has been surreal.  DW and I reversed ourselves regarding placement of our oldest son in a residential school for mentally retarded and autistic children.  We agreed on a temporary placement, which will give us time to get our youngest son's autistic behaviors under control while the school does the same for our oldest boy.  I'm uneasy about the whole thing, but it seems like the best we can do under the circumstances.  Oldest son looked terrific in the suit we purchased for him to attend Sunday mass.  He didn't care much for the Yankees and Hornets caps I bought for him.  I've been browsing on the Internet for statues of the Buddha to use in my nascent meditation practice, but I can't quite bring myself to purchase one.  I'm fascinated by the Buddhist philosophical approach to life and the meditative techniques, to the extent I understand them, but there's something about using a little statue, as opossed to a picture, that seems so ritualistic somehow.  Nevertheless, I purchased a Buddhism-in-a-box deal today to help with meditation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DW rode in a local Mardi Gras parade last night.  I didn't go, and was in bed by 10:30.  Two of the members of the kids' classroom staffs came by to babysit last night, so I went out for a bite to eat and a trip to the coffeehouse with a book.  Yeah, I'm really boring.  Anyhow, DW rolled in around midnight, totally sore from standing and throwing beads for several hours.  She didn't drink anything along the way, contrary to the tradition in which riders get rip roaring drunk.  I used to attend most of the New Orleans parades when I was single.  I lived right along the Uptown parade route, which is where the most famous parades roll.  I lived on the edge of an overwhelmingly African-American neighborhood, so I usually watched parades with black people.  I used to gripe about the Rex parade throwing one set of beads every block, then I watched that parade from a predominantly white area one year.  Hmm, I thought, they throw more stuff here.  Enough negativity, though.  My favorite Mardi Gras was in 1989, when I flew down from law school with my friend Maurice.  We got a bit rowdy, though neither of us got laid in the street (or anywhere else, for that matter).  Maurice did grab ahold of an attractive woman at one point and plant a huge kiss on her lips.  I got a great picture of hundreds of men looking up at us, hooting and hollering, when we stood on a balcony next to a woman who was baring her breasts (showing her tits, in the Mardi Gras vernacular).  At the time, I had an extremely homophobic roommate named Bob.  As Maurice and I walked past a place called the Club My O My, I chortled, "wouldn't Bob love it if we went in here."  Maurice was behind me at the time, and I turned to see him going inside the club.  I followed, and we were seated.  After several minutes, Maurice commented to me that if he didn't know better, he would think that the dancers and waitresses were men.  I had to break the news to him.  We had fun watching the act, but were a little skittish when the waitress, Seth, asked me to put a dollar in his garter.  I handed him the money instead, then told him that my name was "Jim."  Or maybe I stuck it in his garter, I don't remember.  We discovered that the best place to watch the parades was right at the end, when they unloaded all their junk.  There we were, scrambling for plastic trinkets with preteens.    And that's Mardi Gras.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of my kids got me up at 3:30 a.m., so I had some time for some goofball ideas this morning.  Here are some ideas for episodes of some favorite TV shows:  Six Feet Under -- David and Keith are married on the steps of San Francisco City Hall, with Father Phil Intitola presiding (or is that Ryan Chapelle from "24"?)  Meanwhile, Nate begins psychotherapy with a former supermodel turned psychiatrist who has a thing about showing her legs during sessions.  As this is SFU, Nate makes a move on the shrink, who says she has a patient who is a paisano and can squash Nate like a bug.  When Nate's therapy fails, Brenda calls in the Fab Five for a lifestyle makeover.  Brenda uses her ketchup-and-pickle fortune to fly the five to L.A.  Nate emerges with his shirt tucked in, his hair combed, and all that body hair waxed off.  He does well for a while, then falls apart again.  The episode ends with Nate selling his body for money in airport supply closets.  24 -- Who cares?  They make it up as they go along anyway.  Sopranos -- The omniscicent ghost of Ralphie Cifaretto haunts bowling alleys all over North Jersey and, for some strange reason, a certain funeral home in Pasadena.  People begin taking Raphie's friendly, ghostly advice.  Ralphie is still Ralphie, and his advice results in everybody getting whacked.    My wife just said "imagine what you could come up with no sleep at all." 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm all discombulated about politics this year.  I generally agree with the Bush Administration on national security and terrorism, although I'm leery about the idea of preemptive war as a general principle of our foreign policy.  I was for the Iraq war, and I'm still not convinced that it was wrong.  The lack of WMDs does make me wonder.  Also, I think the Administration has been reckless with fiscal policy, and I'm not in favor of tinkering with the Constitution to keep gay men and lesbians from marrying each other.  However, my main beef with the Bushies is their apparent arrogance, their slavish adherence to ideology, and their obsession with secrecy.  On the other hand, Kerry's voting record on military and national security issues makes me uncomfortable.  And the guy kind of gives me the willies, even though I can't put my finger on why that is.  I could be for Edwards, but I don't like his position on trade.   Heck, it really doesn't matter in the end what I think.  Bush will carry my state unless Kerry wins in a nationwide landslide. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's interesting to note the banner ads at the top of these blogspot blogs.  Mine started with commercial garbage equipment, only to transform into anti-anxiety treatments.  I suppose I should determine what types of ads I want up there, then repeat certain keywords ad nauseum.  My kids would want me to advertise Krispy Kreme, Krispy Kreme, Krispy Kreme, Krispy Kreme, or Target, Target, Target, Target.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was waxing philosophical over the weekend for some reason, and I thought about the question, "what is the highest truth?"  Of course, the answer depends in part on how one defines "truth."  Moreover, the answer is -- or should be -- entirely subjective depending on who is providing the answer.  For me, the highest truth is found in my love for others, especially my wife and children.  I like to think that everything I do is somehow rooted in my love for them.  Paul's poetic description of love ("charity") in the New Testament is a great definition of the love I feel for my family.  Spirituality also is important to me.  However, for me spirituality is subjective, experiential, and experimental.  I find more spiritual meaning in nature, music, art, and meditation than I do in more formal settings.  I have total respect for people who find spirituality in other ways.  I'm grateful that DW's parents, who are devout, by-the-book Mormons, appear to respect my less formal path to spirituality.  I hope it stays that way.  Honesty and integrity are important to me as well.  I love a good debate, and I'm a big free-speech advocate.  I'd rather have someone disagree with me honestly than agree with me dishonestly.  I realize that people make mistakes -- I know I do -- and the best policy is to own up to those mistakes and move on.  I also realize that part of my nature wants to put a positive spin on my actions; I assume that we all have that tendency.  That's not necessarily dishonest.  As for integrity, to me that means acting consistent with one's values and being honest in one's dealings.   Maybe I'll come back to this broad philosophical topic later.  Now I've got to finish taking down the Christmas tree.  It's only February 16!   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My anxiety level has been pretty high the past couple of weeks with the boarding school thing coming up all of the sudden, and it seemed that a blog would be a good way to deal with the anxiety.      I'm worried about how and when to tell my mother and sister that we are placing their favorite grandson/nephew into an out-of-town institutional environment.  They freaked out when we first went to look at the place.  My mother has visions of gross abuse and mistreatment of children.  I doubt that even the nun who runs the place could convince her otherwise.  We might even wait until after we get older son up there to break the news.  I worry that 1) they'll try something to stop us from taking O.S. there (they would fail, but still); 2) they'll attack DW's mothering abilities; and/or 3) they'll never talk to me again.  I'm probably more worked up about this than I ought to be.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I watched an episode from the first season of "The Sopranos" over my lunch hour today.  Geez, it was funny.  That show has mophed over four seasons from a brilliant dark comedy with dramatic aspects to a brilliant drama with comedic aspects.  I love that show because it is amazingly intelligent but not the least bit condescending.  For instance, the most grusome ep. of the whole series interspersed lyrics from the Stones' "Sympathy for the Devil," but you didn't feel like you missed out if you didn't get it.  I can't wait for Season Five to begin in March.  DW and I have spread the gospel according to Tony and Carmela via DVDs to Mapleton, Utah, where SIL and her husband have become addicted to the show.  It's been therapeutic for them as they deal with a family trauma.  HBO as therapy -- now there's an idea!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel better today than I have in a while.  My natural optimism is showing through, I suppose.  DW and I can focus like laser beams on our younger son's violent and self-injurious behaviors while our older son is helped by the boarding school.  They've got a good program there.  We'll reintegrate our older son into the home once we're on top of our younger son.  Ah, the joys of parenting!  I'm conflicted about the upcoming presidential election.  I really shouldn't be --my state will vote for Bush, unless Kerry wins in a landslide.  I really wanted Lieberman, but that wasn't meant to be.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please allow me to introduce myself.  I am a middle-aged, happily married American man with two boys, ages 5 and 7.  Both of my boys are autistic and mentally retarded.  I'm currently dabbling in Buddhism -- I enjoy meditation and the idea of training my mind to eliminate afflictive emotions and strengthen the more positive aspects of my mind is appealing.  I have mild/moderate depression and am being treated with medication and therapy.  I'm also an attorney in the employ of the Federal Government, and I live in Louisiana.  DW and I recently made the difficult decision to place our older boy in a residential school for autistic/MR children for a period of around 18 months.  During that period, we will get on top of our younger boys violent, self-injurious, and odd behaviors, while the school does the same for our older boy.  It's a big risk; let's hope it works out.  This is a depressing thing for me -- I've really put all of myself into raising my boys, only to fall short.    Oh yeah, "Dumpster" is my handle on various Internet bulletin boards.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I've arrived.  I've got a BLOG of my own.  I feel special.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just voted online in the election of national Sierra Club board members.  That organization is having a rip-roarin' internal dispute between the powers-that-be and an unusual coalition of vegans, animal-rights extremists, and anti-immigration types.  There are a number of "petition candidates" in the running, some of whom are part of the coalition and some of whom are running to warn members against voting for the coalition.  For instance, the Director of the Southern Poverty Law Center, Morris Dees, is a candidate.  Dees isn't asking for any votes; he just wants S.C. members to vote against the anti-immigration people.  The ballot contains an "urgent election notice" from the current board, indicating that certain nutjob organizations are intervening in the election.  There are even some white supremecist organizations on the list.  Boring old Randy voted for the establishment candidates.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I suppose that most well-adjusted TV watchers are interested in who will be the next person fired on "The Apprentice" or who will be the next American Idol.  Me, I'm more interested in who's gonna get whacked next week on "The Sopranos."  The preview makes it appear as if one and perhaps two people meet their maker at the hands of members of Tony's small-f family.  However, the previews for the show sometimes have midirected viewers into expecting things that never materialize.  The shot in the preview of Christopher firing a pistol with tears in his eyes suggests that Adriana is found out and eliminated.  That would be a shame.  I've actually grown fond of Adriana ever since the FBI started squeezing her.  I wouldn't be surprised to see Chrissy dreaming that he was shooting Ade on Tony's orders.  It seems to be dawning on him that her demeanor has changed and that she is strangely curious about his activities.  Having him realize that his girlfriend is a rat and dealing with the angst and conflicted loyalties of the situation would make for a great Christopher storyline.  OTOH, Drea de Matteo will star in the "Friends" spinoff, so Adriana may not be long for this world.  Johnny Sack is another prime candidate to take a dive in the death pool.  He started an internal war in the Lupertazzi family by whacking Lorraine the loan shark last week and pissed off Tony by working with Feech on that deal to steal all the cars at the Jewish wedding.  Tony didn't look happy when Feech let him know that Johnny was doing business with one of Tony's underlings without Tony's knowledge.  Also, Johnny has made it clear that he hasn't forgotten how Tony stiffed him when he wanted to kill Carmine.  Tony may want to launch a preemptive strike on Johnny.  I dig Johnny Sack, so I hope he hangs around.  Uncle Junior's senility has got to have Tony concerned.  Who knows what information he'll give up when he isn't lucid?  And it was Junior who ordered the hit on Tony back in Season 1.  However, he is still the titular boss of the family.  If Junior is whacked, I hope he gets to sing first, like he did at the end of Season 3.   Finally, Paulie Walnuts spent a good part of Season 4 talking out of school with Johnny Sack.  Also, Paulie and Chrissy have been at odds off and on since Paulie got out of jail.  Either Tony or Christopher could whack Paulie.  However, Paulie is dearly beloved among viewers of the show, so to whack him might invite noisy protests outside HBO headquarters.  And then there's A.J. Soprano.  His conduct towards Carmela merits at least a mock execution.  I think he's cruisin' for a bruisin' with Tony but is too stupid to realize it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Inaccurate reporting of judicial decisions is a pet peeve of mine.  The WWL radio morning show host was agitated this morning about a recent decision of the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Fifth Circuit that he claimed now allows police to enter homes without warrants and conduct searches.  According to the morning host, all the police would need was some suspicion that they might find something.  That sounded a little odd to me, partly because such a holding would pretty much directly contradict the Fourth Amendment.   I printed out the Fifth Circuit's opinion this morning and read it over.  The court did not hold that police can barge in without a warrant whenever they think something untoward is going on.  Rather, the court held that police must be in the residence legally (in this case, someone in the residence opened the door and allowed them in even though they didn't have a warrant); that there must be reasonable suspicion that the area to be "swept" harbors an individual posing a danger to police; that police may only conduct a cursory inspection and not a full search; and that police are limited to whatever time is necessary to dispel reasonable suspicion of danger.  The court did not require that any arrest occur before the search took place, contrary to language in an earlier opinion.  There were dissents, so the result is debatable.  I have no idea whether the Supreme Court will take the case or how that court would decide the case.  However, the radio station got it totally wrong.  I didn't think the opinion was a hard read, so somebody over at the station might have read it before going on the air.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see Older Son on Saturday with my mother and sister in tow.  In the space of one month, he's gone from looking like an overgrown toddler to looking like a seven-year-old boy.  Autistic kids are pretty utilitarian in their view of people, and my O.S. is no exception.  He smiled and ran over to me when we arrived.  I handed him a new toy bus, which immediately got his full attention.  He then took my hand and said, "french fries!"  when I asked what he wanted.  No showing anybody around the place -- McDonald's beckoned.  We had fun there, then went back to the dorm.  O.S. was teary about going back, but he led me by the hand right back to his dorm area.  He then requested a Blue's Clues video in his VCR.  I noticed that the weekend trainer referred to him simply as "T" and not by his full name -- a sign to me that he's got everybody charmed.  There must be an intangible charming quality that some people possess and most of us don't.  I had a roommate in law school who got away with all manner of things, yet everybody loved the guy, including me.  My O.S. has the same ability to charm that my old roommate has.  Kind of scary when you think about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As part of my ongoing rebellion against my inherent wussiness, I walked across the street today and ate several pieces of sushi for lunch -- with chopsticks, no less.  Mmm, raw eel!  Next time I see my mother, I'll make sure to mention my sushi feast so I can hear all about intestinal parasites.  Recently I've had an urge to go diving again, maybe due to that silly Zen diving article.  I doubt I'll be able to do that anytime soon, but it's sure nice to think about being 90 feet underwater, swimming with the marine life around some sunken bridge span.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I deleted my earlier forgiveness post.  I decided it was too personal about people other than me.  Sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray!  I got my vipassana meditation course in the mail today.  It looks very good, and should make various relatives worry even more about this boy.  Last night I chose to mediate on empathy as suggested in one of the Dalai Lama's books.  It was actually kind of wrenching as I tried to imagine how some of my friends and family members must feel in the difficult situations they face.  Next time I'll meditate about scuba diving or something else pleasant.  I stumbled onto a coworker's blog the other day.  I envy this guy's enthusiasm about reading and dissecting legal and philosophical writings.  These days, I'm lucky if I can get throught the letters section of the "Atlantic Monthly" and can figure out whatever it is the letter-writers are talking about.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My 24-year-old brother-in-law recently split with his girlfriend and then bought a new motorcycle.  Hmmm, dumping a significant other and buying a shiny new toy.  Is it possible to have a mid-life crisis at age 24?  I got through my first MLC a couple of years ago with no split, some scuba gear, and a kayak.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I was unable to get my meditation thing going on, so I lay down on the floor and thought about the latest big-family politics in DW's extended family.  However, I was soon mediating about meditation.  Is there such a thing as meta-meditation?  In my ongoing search for sources of new-age-y enlightenment, I occasionally come across things that are novel and even silly.  Here's something I got a chuckle out of:  "As Master Fwap notes, when you are under water in the ocean, you are in a place that still remains pure and clear.  Water acts as a filter.  The thoughts and impressions of the people across the globe are filtered out by the vast amounts of ocean water.  As you dive deeper you notice that your mind becomes sharper.  The thoughts of daily life recede, and a clarity replaces it.  You can solve problems more readily, not by thinking hard about them, but by seeing into the essence of the issue, and intuiting the answer.  You experience a deep peace and immediate sense of being awake and present."  I enjoy scuba diving, though I go infrequently.  I agree that it is calming and peaceful underwater.  However, the notion of underwater meditation strikes me as downright silly.  I'm too busy checking my air supply, no-decompression limit, depth, and dive time; keeping track of direction and distance; looking after my buoyancy; and watching my dive buddy to clear out my brain and meditate.  Also, were I to take sufficient time to get into the mediation zone, the nitrogen would build up in my tissues and I would run out of air.  That wouldn't be too fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My father died 27 years ago yesterday.  I was thinking about my memories of him -- both positive and negative -- yesterday as I was jogging.  My dad had a genius IQ, but refused to join MENSA.  He considered it a snob organization.  Dad was a reverse snob -- a snob about snobs.  He was well-read, well-rounded man, with a large home library he had pretty much committed to memory.  He was conversant in art, literature, history, and science.  He was a scientist by profession (analytical chemist) and loved to ask questions.  He had a smart-alecky, intellectual sense of humor which got passed down to yours truly.  He was vaguely Christian, but I now suspect he was something of an agnostic, or maybe I'm just projecting.  He had no use for organized religion and was excommunicated from the local Presbyterian Church when my mother became a Mormon.  He was proud of being from Louisiana and the South.  I remember having a rebel flag over our treehouse.  However, he strongly favored the civil rights movement and Dr. King.  On the flipside, my father could never remember how old I was or what grade I was in.  He wanted a son who could play football and other team sports; I had bad knees and loved swimming.  He wanted a son who loved fishing, an activity that still bores me to tears.  I was, however, willing to paddle the canoe while he fished, as I love paddling.  Anyhow, that was my dad.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We visited Older Son yesterday at his new school.  He looks fabulous after losing a few pounds due to dietary modifications (he was a little fat going in, so it's all good).  We took him to McDonald's for fries and a coke, and he climbed to the top of the playland tubular thingy and all around it.  This was a first and a big accomplishment for him.  We took him back to the school, and he was brave until I turned the engine off and DW said the word "school."  "SCHOOL!" he bellowed, then he started crying.  He had pooped his pants at McDonald's, so his school trainer took him for a bath and a change while DW and I went to a big pow-wow with the behavioral staff.  Older Son was brought over after his bath and was weepy for a few minutes.  He said "bye bye car!" loudly, which made me feel sad and a little guilty.  He got happy again when he saw his icon book and used it to ask for orange juice.  I got him singing our version of the "Sopranos" theme song, which made DW cover her face in shame:  Randy:  Woke up this mornin', got yourself a OS:  GUN! Randy:  Momma always said you'd be the chosen OS:  ONE! Randy:  You know you're one in a million, you've got to burn to shine, You were born under a bad sign with a blue OS: MOON! Randy: In your eyes.  Whatever works.  The visit with OS was too short; I'll have to get back up there soon. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am on a Sunday afternoon in the back of the house, parousing the food and drink section of the "Queer Eye" book when DW announces that we have visitors.  When I get to the front, she tells me it's the LDS missionaries and that she would rather they not come in.  I didn't really want them in either.  We're usually nice to missionaries, but we didn't feel like it today.  Anyhow, younger son gave me an assist getting rid of the elders first by pushing the door shut, then by scooting himself out the door to get into the car.  I gave him a big kiss once I got him in the car.  I wonder how the mishies would have reacted had I told them that I was reading the "Queer Eye" book when they arrived and was trying to decide whether to fix DW a champagne cocktail or a margarita as a nice little surprise next weekend.  Maybe I should have -- it probably would have got us put on the do-not-visit list.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We took our younger son to the Mississippi Gulf Coast today.  The water was cold and it was windy, but he didn't care.  He loves going to the beach, no matter how cold it is.  He stood in the water and watched the foam and surf come ashore for over an hour.  He was so blissful that he stiffened his whole body and jerked his arms around like a little robot.  He reminded me of a mad Leonard Bernstein, directing the surf back and forth like an aquatic symphony orchestra.  It was a totally ecstatic experience for Younger Son.  I thought a little about how we adults seek ecstatic and/or spiritual experiences from gods, gurus, shamans, meditation, drugs, sex, and rock and roll.  It sure would be nice to feel the joy and ecstasy that my boy felt watching the shiny gloss on the top of the surf before it turned to foam and came ashore.  Older Son is adjusting well to his new school.  We will see him Tuesday, when we go up there for a conference.  I'm looking forward to seeing my boy again.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I read something on Lance the Leftist's blog yesterday that brought to mind my one and only motorcycling experience.  It was in Utah on Easter weekend, in 1997.  My wife's BIL (BIL1) is a huge motorcycling enthusiast.  He wanted to take DW's 17 year old brother (BIL2) to the Little Sahara for the big Easter weekend.  Even though Little Sahara is in Utah, Easter weekend sees thousands of bikers converge on the place to ride up and down a hill known as Sand Mountain.  BIL2 wanted to stay in Logan and play video games, but he agreed to go to humor BIL1.  DW suddenly chimed in and said that I ought to go too.  I was a little reluctant at first, but BIL1 talked me into going along.  We got to Little Sahara and set up camp.  The group next to us looked like, well, total white trash.  As the evening wore on, they acted that way too.  They "tested" their bikes all night long, and at one point were dangerously close to BIL2's tent.  As I lay freezing in my sleeping bag (it started out that day in the 60s, but dropped into the 20s), I couldn't help but hear the very loud conversation going on in the camp next door.  Every other word was an f-bomb, even when it made absolutely no sense.  Cussing always has been a bad habit of mine, even when I was a very active LDS.  The woman in their group showed up and started talking about doin' the nasty with various guys.  The bikers next door at one point smoked a doobie 'round the campfire.  They also tossed in the names of a few of their hometowns.  The next morning, BIL1 commented to me that the people in the next campsite must be from Colorado or something, but they probably weren't from Utah.  No, I told him, they're from Cache Valley.  Places like Newton, Hyrum, and Logan.  BIL1 went over to talk to those guys.  I was afraid there would be some type of confrontation, but BIL1 surprised me by complimenting their motorcycles.  Those guys dug BIL1's old dirt bike, which evidently was a prized model.  I came out of the tent and BIL1 introduced me as a big city lawyer.  The biker dude asked what the hell I was doing out there, as I might wipe out, fall off the bike, and hurt my brain.  We were yukking it up at that point, when BIL2 came out of his tent.  He was very annoyed at us for socializing with the f-bomb crew.  "They don't even cuss right," he told me.  Yes, I said, that's how I knew they were Mormons, or had been raised as Mormons.  Too many cuss words used inappropriately is always a giveaway in that part of the country.  I suppose Jack Mormons try a little too hard to differentiate themselves from their more observant neighbors.  Later on, just before we took off back to Logan, a couple of guys showed up on their Harleys and asked if they could park their hogs in our campsite.  We said sure, and I watched the big bikes as my BILs rode around one last time (we only had two bikes, so one of us was always back at the camp).  The Harley dudes came back after a while and were pissed off because there was sand and dirt on their bikes.  I thought, "uh, you're in the EFFING DESERT!  Of course there's dirt!"  Anyhow, that's my Utah motorcycling experience.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had a nice televisual feast on Sunday night.  I put Younger Son to bed while DW watched her guilty pleasure -- "Charmed."  I get a kick out of that show sometimes because it's so silly.   Then the big event -- "The Sopranos," season five, episode one.  I enjoyed the show, but I thought they tried to cram too many plotlines into one episode.  The opening was fabulous, however, and I loved the idea of a grizzly bear roaming around North Caldwell, New Jersey.  Can you tell that David Chase and some of the other brains of this show worked on "Northern Exposure"?  I thought Tony approaching Dr. Melfi for a date was a little jarring, but it gave her the opportunity to think about the morality of associating with a mob boss.  I really look forward to what looks to be an upcoming civil war inside the Noo Yawk family, and Steve Buscemi makes his debut next week.   After "The Sopranos," we caught "Curb Your Enthusiasm" for the first time.  I busted a gut laughing at one of the tackiest things I've ever seen on TV.  Larry David's rabbi asked if he could invite a survivor to a shindig at Larry's.  Larry called his Holocaust survivor friends to tell them that another survivor would be at his party.  The rabbi brought a former contestant from "Survivor" to the party (Cody, I believe is his name).  At dinner, the "Survivor" contestant and one of the Holocaust survivors had a shouting match about what was worse -- being on "Survivor" or being in a Nazi death camp.  DW sat in stunned silence, but she managed to laugh later on as she caught the groove of the show.  Only Larry David could get away with putting something that tacky on TV.  Older Son reportedly is doing very well in his new school.  I spoke with the automation person up there yesterday.  She's going to get Older Son to the computer lab now that I've told her what a powerful tool it is for him.  Now I'm going to poke around a little and see if I can get some new computers donated to the place.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really need to pay more attention to the local news.  This morning I cut through the French Quarter to get to work.  I saw two 20-somethings walking the street with a John Kerry sign.  I waved politely and drove on.  At noon, I jogged to the riverfront on my usual route.  As I turned the corner at the Aquarium of the Americas, I saw an armed coast guard boat in the river and barricades in Woldenberg Park.  People were streaming into the area.  I asked what was up, and was told that John Kerry was speaking at 1:15.  I'm a political junkie, so I briefly thought about hanging around, but I wanted to finish my jog and I've got too much work to do today.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a very nice mediation experience last night.  I placed a tiny Buddha at eye level on the kids' table, surrounded by tiny paper prayer flags.  They prayers are in Sanskrit, so I have no idea what they say.  I then sat in the lotus position and focused my vision on the statue.  I closed my eyes and drove out all thoughts except for a generalized feeling of compassion, which is what I had decided to meditate on.  No great thoughts, just a kind of general notion.  I stretched my back and neck, opened my rib cage, and did some deliberate breathing.  Whenever my mind strayed, I opened my eyes and refocused on the little statue and prayer flags.  I did all of this twice, and I felt very, very good afterwards.  I could only describe it as a spiritual experience.  The last really spiritual experience I had at church (not direcly involving my own wife and kids, of course) was in the early 1990s.  I was in an amazingly diverse little ward in the inner city.  We had one fast and testimony meeting that blew away everybody who was there.  We opened with "The Spirit of God Like a Fire is Burning" -- and we meant it.  There was a series of deeply moving testimonies.  I suppose that the heavy influence of the African-American church remained with many of the members of this ward when they became LDS, and they in turn influenced the white members of the ward.  It was almost as if we were going to be translated like the proverbial City of Enoch.  At one point, a black man walked in and sat for a minute, then went to the podium.  He said that he was a Baptist and would remain that way, but that he was standing at the bus stop out front and felt a special spirit coming from our building.  He felt compelled to come in and be a part of it.  It was a truly amazing example of group spirituality.  I held onto that experience for years as I sat through countless boring meetings in which the right rote things were spouted over and over again with no passion of any kind.  It's as if the Mormon Church institutionally has had an emotional lobotomy.  Is that a consequence of correlation?  Whatever, they've pretty much squeezed away spontaneous spirituality of the kind I experienced last night.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't see any banner ads atop my blog today.  So I'll throw out a few words and see if they generate any ads.  Sopranos.  Six Feet Under.  Tibet.  Buddha.  Zen.  Yoga.  Yogurt.  Pizza.  Capicola.  My blog is naked without ads.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw our own Slidell High School on Fox News this morning.  Some bats flew into the school gym during a basketball game, and somebody filmed the incident.  Slidell is mostly Suburbia, USA, so we only make the news when something quirky happens.  Older Son is doing better in his new surroundings.  I've already started my first little crusade up there.  The kids have virtually no access to computers during the regular school year, yet the computer is my kid's most powerful learning tool.  I'm already negotiating how and when to get him access.  I'm even thinking of taking our newest PC up there and placing it in their computer lab, where access can be limited and the machine can be secured.  DW and I use a laptop, and our really old Gateway machine will do for Younger Son, who isn't even on the computer yet.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took a brief walk at noon today.  I walked through the newly redone Piazza d'Italia, which is one of the few interesting outdoor spots in New Orleans.  There's a colorful, faux-Roman columned wall, from which juts a marble fountain shaped like Italy.  The New York Times once called it America's first postmodern ruin, and it long was a camping ground for homeless men.  It's been cleaned up and repainted, and I hope people will return to eat their lunches there.  Then I walked through Harrah's casino, with its Mardi Gras-themed interior.  Some people think it's tacky, but I like the look of the place.  I've spent about $1.25 there in the two or three years the casino has been open, but I do like walking there every now and again.  I was watching the news about Haiti this weekend and was reminded of something I've never really understood.  What is it about Jean-Bertrand Aristide that has kept him so popular with the political left in this country?  Yesterday John Kerry said that he would have used American military force to keep Aristide in power.  Why?  It seems to me that Aristide is no better and no worse than the thugs who started the current rebellion.  He used terror tactics and rigged elections to keep his people in power, and the country is no better off than it was when he was elected.  The United States shouldn't take sides between left-leaning thugs and right-leaning thugs when our vital interests aren't implicated, but we can take steps to ensure stability and humanitarian relief once a winner has emerged.  In short, Bush got this one right.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I put some links on my blog this morning.  I linked to all of your blogs and a few sites of interest.  I linked to the Burning Man site because I secretly would like to do something like that just once.  And to think -- my voter registration card still says "Republican" on it.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the heck is up with my banner ads?  Early this morning I logged on from home and was happy to see ads for commercial dumpster rental services.  Now I'm back to having "help for seniors" displayed up there.  Damn!  How humiliating!  Well, maybe it's not that inaccurate.  I have had a false-alarm cardiac scare and a false-alarm cancer scare in the past three years -- and I'm only 41.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dangit!  I want to go diving.  Now!    I last went underwater last summer, when I was at a conference in South Carolina.  I had a kayaking tour scheduled for the built-in day off, so I was forced to play hooky for a day to go out on the dive boat.  I was kind of stoked because I had just picked up the items I had purchased on lay-away.  I had my Zeagle buoyancy compensator, my Dive Rite computer, and, best of all, my Poseidon regulator.  Poseidons are Swedish and expensive.  I like them because they have a powerful, easy airflow, and I'm a heavy breather underwater.  Anyhow, I hooked everything up to the tank and -- low and behold -- the Poseidon was leaking air.  Fortunately, the captain had a spare regulator onboard, so I just used it.   The dives that day were kind of a bummer.  I lost a lot of dive time due to an informal diving protocol requiring snorkels.  I didn't bring my snorkel along; they really aren't used in the Gulf of Mexico.  Then my dive buddy, who was even less experienced than I was, panicked when he couldn't see the anchor line running from the boat to the bottom, so he surfaced and went back to the boat.  I had been descending free-form about 2-3 feet from the line, something that isn't done there.  Again, I was following my training in the Gulf.  The second dive went much better, and I saw some pretty little fishies.  The previous summer, I dove in Lake Powell, Arizona.  That was interesting.  Lake Powell is a desert canyon that was dammed and filled with water.  Diving there is kind of like hiking, except you're underwater and there are fish.  It was neat swimming inside little mountain canyons and ravines.  Anyway, I've got a hankering to go down again.  But I have neither the time nor the money right now, so I'll have to content myself with taking that kayak in the garage on its maiden voyage.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came across something interesting in my meditation workbook last night.  The author was discussing how sleepiness interferes with meditation practice.  According to the author, some people cannot stay awake during meditation because they have feelings they are unable to face head-on.  When their minds start to calm and those feelings emerge, they simply fall asleep.  My wife thought this was obvious, and she reminded me that she occasionally sleeps off the blues.  I know that some depressed people sleep long hours, but I hadn't made the connection between depression and sleep as a subconscious avoidance mechanism until last night.  Recently I've reflected some on the topic of anger.  A relative is going through a period of intense and totally justifiable rage at the moment.  My instinct here is totally the opposite of how I tend to be.  I try to smooth everything over with everybody and keep things calm, pretty much at any price.  In this relative's situation, however, my instinct is to be a sounding board and to help him vent vicariously via sending videos of my favorite televeision show.  I may even drop my copy of Fight Club into the next care package.  Reflecting on this, I realize that there are times we need -- even deserve -- to be angry with others.  Of course, I love everybody who reads my little blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went jogging along the riverfront and through the French Quarter at noon today.  Tied up at the dock is a gorgeous 4-masted sailing vessel from the Spanish Navy.  The ship is steel and not wood, but it's still a sight to behold.  One funny moment -- I overheard someone asking what country the ship is from.  There is a huge Spanish flag on the stern.  Oh well.  The sailors were in their dress whites and disembarking for shore leave when I went past.  Woo hoo!  Sailors on leave in the Quarter.  Lock your doors; hide your women (if the occasional reader of this blog who lives down there is reading this post, beware!).  Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum!  That sounds kind of good on a Friday afternoon, come to think about it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another year, another prostate exam.  Well, actually, it's been two years and a blown-off PSA.  So I get to the clinic and the nurse looks at my chart.  She moved me to the ultrasound room, "just in case."  Great!  Cattle-prod time!  I had a prostate biopsy in August 2001 for what turned out to be a benign growth.  Eight slices into the prostate through the anal wall -- and with no anasthetic.  Soooooo painful.  After it was done, the nurse brought me one stinking Tylenol.  So the new urologist comes in.  He examined me and found nothing at all unusual.  I don't need to do any more PSAs or prostate exams until I'm 50 years old.  Hooray!  Middle age kind of sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I have google banner ads for LDS online dating services.  To hell with that, I say.  If I'm going to sign up for a dating service, I want someone who will put out on the first date.    What's that, hon?  Oh, I'm just discussing the Iraq situation with my fellow bloggers here.  Nothing interesting.  Wait, don't read that.  Uh, no, I'm not thinking of signing up for anything.  It's all hypothetical, you see.  Why are you throwing books at me?  Owww!  That's my head! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find myself feeling conflicted about a political tug-of-war that will affect my children.  On one side is the residential facility my oldest son attends (which is a good place) and all other residential centers (most of which are bad).  They've historically had the upper hand with the state legislature.  On the other side are the advocates of community-based care, who want to empty the residential facilities and provide supports for the MR/DD population to live at home.    I have one child in each situation right now.  There is a bill in the legislature that would phase out all of the facilities and move the residents into community-based situations.  The bill also would also open more "slots" for kids on the MR/DD services waiting list (it's about 8-9 years long now).  Between medications, respite care/personal care attendants, and other costs, raising autistic kids is extremely expensive.  We get very minimal state-supported services at home for our younger son right now; the full array of MR/DD services is probably about 6 years away.  Older son's residential services, OTOH, are fully funded via the Medicaid program.  We had anticipated a 4-6 year wait to get him into his facility; however, their waiting list suddenly moved.  They have a long waiting list there too, as there's a moratorium in place on expansion of residential treatment facilities.  My concerns about the bill are these:  1) it would close down the good facilities along with the bad ones; 2) the legislature would commit to opening slots for kids on the waiting list, but as the kids coming out of institutional care would suck up all the money, the new slots would not be funded, making the wait even longer; 3) the community-care agencies are already understaffed and their employees are poorly paid, and there would not be adequate assistance available for everybody to have their needs met; and 4) local school systems will be unprepared to provide educational and ancillary services to the wave of MR/DD kids that will hit them.  Fortunately, my fourth concern is inapplicable to my own local school system.  I have always leaned towards community-based care so that we can keep our kids at home.  However, I see my oldest son doing well in his new setting.  Moreover, my suspicion is that the groundwork hasn't been done here to really make that work and that the community-care advocates are seeing pie in the sky as far as funding goes.  On the other hand, the advocates of facility care need to realize that the national trend is moving in the opposite direction and that many families would like to have their loved ones out of the institutional system.  I would hope that some kind of compromise could be reached that would keep the good facilities open and allow those who wish to transition back into the community to do so.  We should know in the next few weeks how this political battle will shape up and shake out.  I'll probably be writing to my legislators about this.  They'll be baffled, as I've already taken both sides of this issue in letters to them in previous legislative sessions, albeit with qualifications.  Politics.  Shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Just when I thought I was out, they pulled me back in."  So said Michael Corleone in Godfather III.  Anyhow, I've found myself posting in the Foyer again.  I went there last Monday after General Conference to see whether any wacko remarks were made at the semi-annual LDS pow-wow.  I also paroused some of the odder GC addressed on LDS.org.  I find myself wondering whether I'm what I like to call a tribal Mormon.  No matter how apostate and non-practicing I may be, I suppose it's possible that I'll always identify myself as a Mormon.  To allay any fears some of you might have, my vipassana meditation is going well.  It's interesting to notice how much is going on with the human body when you're mindful of it.  That's where vipassana starts.  It's also a nice reality check to realize that many of the things I worry about are merely thoughts, like all other thoughts, and that they can just come and go.  Other things, obviously, are hard realities and must be addressed.  This Eastern stuff seems to fit me fairly well.  Time will tell.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had quite an interesting Easter weekend.  DW and I decided that our boys needed to see each other after 6 weeks apart, so yesterday we packed up Younger Son and a load of Easter presents and drove to Alexandria, LA.  YS and I played hard in the motel pool and at McDonald's last night.  This morning we drove to Older Son's school for Easter Mass.  I expected that YS would be ga-ga over seeing OS again, but that OS would ignore YS.  I was half right -- they both totally ignored each other the whole time we were together.  YS really wanted to put his hands on the crucifix that was carried in the processional.  He ran over to the door before the processional began, then tried to run up the center aisle during mass itself.  Nobody minded him running around, as the service was designed for MR/DD children.  YS also tried to get to the keyboard, but DW stopped him in time.  OS stayed quietly with me the whole time.  The reading for the service didn't come from the scriptures, but from a large picture book about Easter.  As the nun read from the book, I could swear I heard OS say "Jesus" a couple of times during a string of his jargon.  My favorite part of the service was when the priest walked up and down the center aisle with a mic, letting the kids say whatever they wanted.  The music was nice, and one of the female students sang a couple of simple solos.  It was the first church service we've been to together as a family since May 2001, and maybe the first one ever to hold the kids' interest the whole time.  After church, we went to WalMart and McDonalds, then back to the school.  OS sobbed and cried when we got back, but he put my hand on the seatbelt buckle and said "bye-bye, car!" to let me know he wanted the separation to go quickly.  I really hope that the crying and sobbing phase goes away quickly.  He's fine 10 minutes after we leave, but it kind of leaves a hole in my heart to see that.  The dorm mom thinks our departures are a little harder for OS because he's much closer to us than some of the other kids are to their parents.  She's nice, that gal.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A group is doing something akin to the stations of the cross outside my window right now.  We just watched Jesus surrounded by Roman centurions, standing on the back steps of the U.S. Court of Appeals building.  I wondered if someone was going to deliver some kind of anti-judicial diatribe, but I didn't hear anything like that.  I only heard singing about Jesus and peace.  My impression was that the courthouse steps were just a convenient place for the group to do their thing.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As part and parcel of my meditation practice, I have been working towards experiencing sensations and thoughts for what they are, disconnected from past or future events.  One of the authors of my meditation course writes that the only experiences we have of the past or the future are thoughts that we are having now.  I read somewhere that the Buddhist concept of the self is essentially that the self only exists in the mind here and now.  I could be understanding that wrong, so please correct me if I'm mistaken.  Anyway, I find myself more aware of sensations involved in everyday things, some of which have become more beautiful and amazing then ever before.   Also, I've thought some about how what I understand to be the Buddhist concept of self appears to differ from the Mormon concept, in which the self is a spirit that has existed in some form since the beginning of time -- albeit as an "intelligence" at some point -- and that will exist eternally.  Under the Mormon view, we are placed on the Earth in order to earn our way back into God's presence through our works and our faith.  The Buddhist self exists in the here and now, and is different from the self that will exist 10 minutes from now or at death.  That concept, it would seem, decreases anxiety about the future and recognizes the past for what it is.  The Mormon self has always existed and will always exist.  That makes it difficult, if not impossible, for Mormons to live in and for the present moment.    I don't know that I entirely buy the Buddhist concept as I understand it.  However, it's something to think about.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I was having a relatively pleasant drive into work when I was struck by a stark reminder of world affairs.  The sky is cloudless and blue; the swamp is greening up; and traffic wasn't too bad.  I had to bail from the Interestate and cut through the funky Bywater and Marigny neighborhoods, then through the French Quarter.  I was in the midst of a neighborhood known for its laissez-faire attitude towards sobriety, sexuality, and a whole host of other issues (btw, not everybody who lives in N.O. is a besotted libertine).  I turned from Dauphine Street onto Tolouse Street and looked straight ahead.  Moving parallel to the river was a parade of sand-colored armored personnel carriers onboard rail cars, heading east.  Presumably those APCs are destined for service in Iraq.  Behind the parade of APCs was a festively decked-out riverboat.  The contrast was striking to me, anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a great snippet of politcally related dialogue from last night's Sopranos:  Christopher:  What do you got to be stressed about? That bar?   Adrianna:  War, Christopher? The Middle East?   Christopher:  You don't listen to the president? We're gonna mop the floor with the whole fuckin' world. The whole world's gonna be under our control. So what are you worked up about?   Randy:  So why can't I buy gas for less than $1.65 a gallon?  Can't we just take all the oil we want from Iraq?  Whatever happened to pillaging and plundering?  Kofi Annan:  But that would violate international law.  And nobody has kicked up to me with oil-for-food money since you guys invaded Iraq.  David Chase:  Get these two idiots off of my set! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DW and I made an emotionally draining visit to our Older Son yesterday.  The ride up was unpleasant due to Younger Son's tantrum after we left him with the sitter -- his behavior was so bad that we turned around to go back.  However, he calmed down in time for us to turn back around again.  All the turning around made for an unpleasant ride for the first hour or so.    We arrived in Alexandria, LA, after 4+ hours in the car, only to find that O.S.'s dorm was on an outing.  We hung around for an hour or so before somebody explained exactly where they were and when they would be back.  We drove to the restaurant, only to find no kids.  We went back to the school and the kids were being unloaded from the van.  O.S. saw us and began crying.  The crying didn't help us feel any less guilty for placing him there, which might have been his point.    O.S. looks pretty good, but he's lost enough weight that he actually needs a belt now.  Neither of the belts we sent with him were in his closet and his pants were falling down.  I made a hoo-ha about the situation and the trainer who came on after the shift change was apologetic.  She got busy looking for a belt right away.  Meanwhile, I dug out some shorts with a drawstring and put them on O.S.  O.S. began crying again when we got back to the school after our little outing.  I had to change his clothes due to a poopy incident at McDonalds.  DW told me that while I was in the bathroom trying to figure out what to do with the dirties, some of the other boys in the dorm came over and hugged O.S. to help calm him.  One misconception about autistic children is that they are incapable of showing affection and positive emotion.  I've not seen that with my boys, and we're seeing quite the opposite in the dorm at the St. Mary's school.  Another example -- yesterday, one boy who is considered to be extremely autistic walked up and shook my hand when I called him by his first name.  Meanwhile, back at the ranch, Y.S.'s sitters took him to the beach in Mississippi.  We had taken him there Saturday, so he's getting bronzed for summer.  One of the sitters told us that they took Y.S. to his favorite beach spot, then took him for french fries at a Burger King that's right on the beach.  When they finished there, he made it clear that he wanted to go back to the beach, so they took him to a different spot.  At first, they wanted to take him to the park on the way back to our town, but when one of the sitters noted the time and said it was time to go home, Y.S. reportedly said "home!"  If that happened, it's a miracle.  He's been totally nonverbal up 'til now.  Got back just in time for "The Sopranos."  Nobody got whacked, unless you count Tony's cars.  Tony himself totaled one, and Christopher shot the other one up in a fit of rage.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The blogosphere sure is an interesting place.  One of my blogging coworkers recently discussed the statistical significance of some poll numbers that a political blog posted to demonstrate that a certain Senate Minority Leader is in political trouble.  My coworker is apolitical, from what I can gather, so he had no ax to grind.  His discussion was more mathematic than political, and was sparked by a law professor's claim (on the professor's blog) that the poll numbers posted on the political blog were insignificant.  The political blog is citing my coworker's discussion to make the point that the candidate's poll slippage may be significant.  So it's a closed-end loop -- blog 2 questions blog 1, and in turn is questioned by blog 3, which is cited by blog 1 to support blog 1's original point.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I watched next week's Sopranos preview again, read some posts in the Television Without Pity forum, and looked at the HBO website today and I think I've got next week figured out.  Christopher leaves town on business and whacks somebody we don't even know.  A rumor about Adriana floats around the family and Tony has a dream in which he executes Chrissy.  That dream drives Tony back into therapy with Dr. Melfi.  Nobody big dies.  This is the first time I've gone to so much trouble to figure out what's going to happen on a TV show.  It was kind of fun but I doubt I'll do it again.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, time for a little parental bragging.  As is true of many autistic kids, my boys are obsessed with water.  My Youngest Son also is obsessed with fish.  He has watched the fish at the local aquarium for many hours in the past few weeks, and last week at the beach he was imitating other children as they let themselves be washed ashore by the surf.  Yesterday, I noticed YS putting himself underwater in the backyard swimming pool and holding his breath for as long as he could.  Our pool is about 2.5 feet deep, so he can float in it for a while.  He's very nearly neutrally buoyant, something I envy.  Anyway, he was doing some floating today.  Then he started pushing himself off the side and bottom of the pool.  Then he started using his hands and feet to propel himself in the water.  Not much, but I saw a rudimentary stroke or two.  Sua sponte swimming lessons!  Very, very cool, and a proud moment for yours truly.  In other news, Older Son got up the courage last night and this morning to use a regular swing at the park instead of a handicapped one.  He used to go on regular swings routinely, until he fell off of one and went splat into a gigantic mud puddle a couple of years ago.  We're planning to hit the beach tomorrow.  It'll probably be in Mississippi; our last drive to the Alabama coast with the boys was a complete fiasco.  Mississippi is much closer, so I won't be pissed or depressed if things don't go well.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As some of you know, I've had a crummy week.  Yesterday, however, was so singularly bad that I could only laugh at the ridiculousness of the situation.    I took yesterday off to go fetch my O.S. in Alexandria, Louisiana, which is about a 3.5-hour drive from home on a good day.  I woke my Y.S. at about 7:15, processed him (meds, diaper, clothes, etc.), and put him in the car at 7:35.  I realized I didn't have any money, so I went to the nearest ATM.  Y.S. started tantruming on the way back, as we passed Toys R Us, Chuck-E-Cheese, WalMart, and Target.  I realized that I had left the gate open, so I drove us back home, which got Y.S. even angrier.  Finally, we got to Interstate 12 and headed towards Baton Rouge.  About 10 miles from Baton Rouge, traffic came to a complete stop.  The bridge into B.R. was closed by an accident.  Now, my boys are on a medication schedule, and I didn't bring Y.S.'s meds in the car because I already had built in 1.5 hours or so of delays and assumed we would be back in time.  However, it seemed like this delay would be 3-4 hours, which would mean turning around and going home, and not bringing O.S. home at all.  I went into panic mode, pulled onto the shoulder, and drove a few yards.  A cop popped out from behind a car and directed me to stop.  There was no escape, as traffic was totally stopped.  So I got ticketed.  As he wrote the ticket, I thought about my strategy for getting it dismissed.  It may work, I don't know.  I then got back into the traffic lane.  It took us 1.5 hours to go 1.5 miles.  Suddenly, the bridge into Baton Rouge reopened and we were able to move along.  But my mood wasn't the greatest.  I picked up my sister in B.R., and we headed north.  She wanted to gossip about various family members, but I was not in the mood.  I brightened up when we arrived at the St. Mary's school.  Y.S. was strangely curious about O.S.'s dormitory, and he wandered around while O.S.'s trainer showed me what she had packed.  I collected the boys and went back to the van.  I let my sister drive back to B.R. while I played in the back with the boys.  We had fun.  Rush hour in B.R. was a bitch, which darkened my mood somewhat.  B.R. is way worse than New Orleans during rush hour, so I try to time things to avoid it.  Anyhow, we got home about 2 hours after I had intended.  We medicated the boys and let them splash around in the pool I put up Wednesday night.  They fell asleep around 8:30.  Oh well, they'll sleep in and we can breathe easy in the morning.  Nope, O.S. was up at 3:10 a.m., wanting to watch Thomas and Blue.  He let us sleep while he turned on the t.v. and watched informercials.  Y.S. came in at 5:00 a.m., wanting to drink Coke and go play in the pool again.  And that was my day off.  Work isn't so bad sometimes.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I went onto the Foyer BB to back Jo & Schmo against some undeserved criticism.  This morning I went there and made a comment favorable to Bill Clinton, who was being attacked as a "scumbag" despite the no-politics rule of that board.  I saw in the response that the "p" in Dumpster was replaced with a "b," and by one of the nicer people on that board at that.  I never got what it was about Clinton that makes conservatives go postal.  I'm actually quite conservative on a lot of issues myself, but I try to have some objectivity about politics and politicians.  Anyhow, when I have a few minutes, I'll go on aimoo and unregister from the Foyer.  It's something I've been meaning to do anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From "The Late Show with David Letterman:"  Top Ten Things Never Before Said on "The Sopranos"   10. "You don't have any money? That's cool" (Dominic Chianese)  9. "Screw this home cooking -- I'm going to the Olive Garden" (Aida Turturro)  8. "In addition to disposing of bodies, you'll need to know how to use Powerpoint and Excel" (Steven Van Zandt)  7. "Wasn't that the guy from Springsteen's E Street Band?" (Robert Iler)  6. "I just hooked up an illegal cable box. Now I'm getting free HBO" (Jamie-Lynn Discala)  5. "Tony, I'm gonna need to leave early today for Rosh Hashanah" (Tony Sirico)  4. "I want a bigger part -- what are you gonna do, kill my character?" (Drea de Matteo)  3. "Hey Paulie, how about you and me going up to Massachusetts and getting married?" (Michael Imperioli)  2. "I can't go to prison -- Martha Stewart will eat me alive!" (Edie Falco)  1. "I just whacked myself" (James Gandolfini) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         President Bush is Louisiana today, to deliver a speech at LSU and to raise money. &nbsp;I got to thinking about the upcoming election the other day, and I don't know if I can vote for either Bush or Kerry. &nbsp;In my opinion, Bush does not deserve reelection. &nbsp;He took the country into a war on flawed intelligence, then underestimated the aftermath. &nbsp;His reckless fiscal policies have contributed to massive deficits. &nbsp;His administration is arrogant and secretive, and everything with this White House is ideological, not practical. &nbsp;Finally, I'm opposed to amending the Constitution in the way Bush seeks to do.      Bush has done a few good things. &nbsp;His response to 9/11 was nearly perfect. &nbsp;He raised morale in the aftermath of that event and justifiably went to war in Afghanistan. &nbsp;And his reckless fiscal policies put more money in MY pocket.      On the other hand, John Kerry is the quintessential Eastern establishement liberal, a type I just can't listen to for more than five minutes at a time. &nbsp;Morever, I fear that he suffers from the Vietnam syndrome in foreign and defense policy. &nbsp;Iraq showed that the US should not plunge headlong into military adventures without a parachute, so to speak. &nbsp;However, &nbsp;the US is the US, and should not be hesitant about using force and supporting bad regimes when it is appropriate. &nbsp;I agree with Samuel Huntington that in order to protect our liberal, open society, we must be willing to behave cynically abroad. &nbsp;I don't know whether Kerry shares my views. &nbsp;And Kerry is boring, too.      I take some comfort in Craig the Philospher Lawyer's theory that individual votes don't matter. &nbsp;Maybe I'll vote for the Natural Law Party this year. &nbsp;That would be in keeping with my Eastern outlook. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's Daily Zen:  Your notion that thoughts arise Leads to a notion that you  Must prevent them From arising.  These conflicting ideas Are both wrong.  Look well at the source  Beyond mental activity.    - Daito (1282-1334)  What do you think this means?  My meditation manual discusses the notion that thoughts just come and go, and that much of what we view as realities are nothing more than mere thoughts.  But what is the source of our thoughts and why would anybody want to stop them from being generated?  Do thoughts arise from reality, via perception and consciousness?  Is that dangerous? 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry, Dave, but I couldn't resist the urge to bring up this week's Sopranos episode.  It was either brilliant or terrible, depending on your point of view.  Tony's 21-minute dream sequence was one of the most surreal things I've ever seen on television.  However, the way it was done reminded me of my own more vivid dreams -- totally disjointed, fast-moving, seemingly illogical scenes dredged up from my subconscious to try to tell me something.  There was a ton of symbolism, some of which is common to dreamers (DW, for instance, has the same thing with teeth falling out that Tony had in his dream), and some of which was unique to the Soprano situation.  What I got out of it is that Tony is deeply insecure about his position as a mob boss (particularly now that he's in deep shit with Johnny Sack); that he is insecure as a father; that he is somewhat disillusioned about his career choice; and that he knows he's got two specific issues that must be resolved quickly but that he is unprepared to deal with emotionally.  All this internal angst and insecurity after an episode in which Tony was a complete jerk to everybody.  My first reaction was "what the hell was that?"  However, after thinking through a little, I think I liked it.  I'll have to take another look at it.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to follow everybody else and redecorate.  I also decided not to use the Haloscan comments, which evidently lost everybody's previous contributions to my little corner of the Internet.  Sorry about that.  I just like this format better.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A few minutes ago, I had a hallway encounter with a coworker that got me thinking about how people define themselves.  It seems to me that most people start with their occupations, then move to concepts like gender, race, religion, ethnicity, sexual orientation, and so on.  I'm an attorney by profession, but I've never looked in the mirror and seen a lawyer.  The whole L.A. Law thing never has been for me; I'm just in this because it's an agreeable way to make a living.  I'd rather see myself as a good husband, devoted father, and loyal friend than as a stereotypical lawyer.    Buddhist teaching warns against becoming attached to concepts of oneself.  That can lead to limitations in your ability to experience phenomena as they arise and limitations in your ability to think outside the proverbial box.  For instance, I can call myself an overwhite white male, a Southerner, a father of autistic children, a married guy, a heterosexual, a disaffected Mormon, a borderline Buddhist, and a lawyer.  If I get too attached to any of those concepts of myself, it limits me.  Still, I am all of those things and probably more.  So how do people define themselves?  How should they define themselves?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took my Youngest Son to the Aquarium of the Americas this morning.  He knew exactly where we were going once I turned into the Canal Place parking garage, so he gladly got out of the car without the plastic doo-dads he's been obsessed with lately.  We spent about two hours in the place, running from tank to tank.  He shouted with glee the whole time, so loudly that one girl covered her ears and ran to her father.  He didn't seem to care; I certainly didn't.  YS is definitely my son -- he loved the sharks, big and small, and he pent more time at their exhibits than anyplace else.  He has no idea that they are ultra-efficient killers; I suppose he just thought they looked nice as they swam.  He climbed into (and up) the concave window on the big shark tank and watched the killer pelagics swim up only inches away.  He tried to touch some large Brazilian fish in the Amazon exhibit that swam to the surface, and he loved watching the penguins eat.  Later on, we went to PetsMart to look at dogs.  Ironically, in light of his fondness for sharks, he was very much afraid of the small dogs on display at the store. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes inspiration comes from the strangest places.  I had a brilliant idea a few minutes ago, inspired by a car accident on Interstate 12.  Coastal erosion is a serious issue along the East Coast and Gulf Coast of the United States, particularly in Louisiana.  The southeastern portion of the state was created by the silt left over from Mississippi River flooding and now that the river doesn't flood anymore, there's no more silt.  Also, global warming appears to be causing some encroachment of salt water.  There may be other factors at play, I don't know.    A few years ago, the State came up with the idea of building dykes using old Christmas trees, placed in wire pens.  This has helped the problem somewhat, but more needs to be done.  On the way home tonight, DW pointed out a car in the ditch.  I joked about just pushing the car into the woods instead of wasting time and money pulling it out, and then my inner environmentalist had another idea.  Why not use junked cars instead of Christmas trees to slow coastal erosion?  Imagine how much more effective a wall of old Suburbans would be than a bunch of Christmas trees!  Marine life would flock to the structure, and the resulting reef would be an environmental boon.  Why, tourists might even flock to Port Fourchon to view this wonder of the Gulf.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This post is from legal eagle Dan, in response to my post about spirituality.  It was too long for the comments section, so I'm posting it separately:  First, I think spirituality definitely can and should be separated from religious teachings and practices.  Many religious traditions (especially the ones we would call "primitive") are experiential religions--the focus is on having spiritual experiences, not on formulating doctrines or on interpreting the spiritual experiences.  This is real religion in my opinion.  The Native Americans were good at this.  Meditators are taught to have mental stillness in order to reach a higher consciousness.  How can the mind truly be still if we are attempting to interpret what we are experiencing while in the altered mental state?  The minute you try to interpret what you are experiencing, it begins to vanish.  The experience of pure religious ecstasy does not allow one to ruminate over meanings.  Here's a novel thought: maybe the purpose of religion--if organized religion is necessary--should be to teach more people the techniques to achieve spiritual transcendence and not to answer the big questions like where we came from, why we are here, and where we are going.  Counterintuitive, eh?  Why not leave those questions to empirical methods?  Eastern traditions, with all their attention on technique, posture, mantras, etc., seem to have an advantage over Western traditions, like Mormonism, that teach to pray and read scriptures (ad nauseam), but never have much to say about specific meditation techniques, except for vague generalities like "you should listen for a few minutes after praying to hear an answer".  (shallow)  Perhaps, too, religion should not concern itself with answering questions of morality.  What is right and wrong?  Is sex outside of marriage wrong?  Is abortion wrong?  These questions should not be left to a religion that is to be thought of as experiential.  They should be left, once again, to empirical methods.  In my opinion, basic empiricism in the first place led to many of our moral traditions--traditions which were then co-opted by religion and given a moral flavor.  For instance, when mankind realized that unbridled sexuality can lead to the spread of diseases and unwanted pregnancies, and emotional turmoil, it would have been an obvious decision to curtail that sexuality.  Once that norm became deeply ingrained in the culture, it would have taken on a sacred character.  Now that we have better mechanisms to prevent the spread of disease and unwanted pregnancies, should the norm not now be changed?  The question ought not be left to religion, but to logic.  It should, of coure, take into account all factors, including emotional factors.  But the point I am trying to make is that perhaps religion has been given too many jobs.    Bare spirituality without a religious paradigm is superior to contextual spirituality for the reasons discussed above, and also because bare spirituality does not require one to pin his hopes and dreams on teachings that may or may not be false.  To contrast: one who experiences enlightenment while meditating knows that the feeling of enlightenment was good and satisfying.  He doesn't need to know why it was satisfying.  As long as he can still meditate, he will always be able to feel good.  But one who experiences enlightenment while contemplating deep doctrines of an afterlife, a savior-god, resurrection, etc., is pinning his hopes on something that will fluctuate according to the varying strengths and weaknesses of his belief in those doctrines.    This understanding has been one of the most fascinating aspects of my journey out of Mormonism.  I have discovered that spiritual experiences are not dependent on doctrines, can occur in many different contexts and can be triggered by many events: music; frequency patterns that alter brainwaves from listening to  Tibetan singing bowls, a didgeridoo or a hand drum; chanting; rituals; meditation; nature walks; dancing; simple conversation; art; science; or hallucinogens (check out the fascinating documentary on the History Channel called "Ancient Drugs".  It implicates drugs such as peyote, hashish, ayahuasca, ergot (among others) in the formation of early religion.  I think drugs played a major part in the development of religion, especially the rituals and visions.  It is very likely that many of the rituals practiced in modern religion (such as eucharist or the sacrament of bread and water/wine or baptism) are deformed copies of rituals that were originally designed to accompany the drug-taker's trip into the "other realms," or at least to symbolize it.  The psychelic journey can be very sacred, but is also fraught with peril as one perceives his own self in all its splendor and ugliness and perceives the dance of life from a cosmic angle.  It is truly a death/rebirth experience.  With this new point of view, I don't see how any discussion about the nature of religion and spirituality can be complete without a discussion of how hallucinogens have had their influence.  Because of our cultural context and the way drugs have come to be thought of, this is not something that would occur to most of us.)  Many of us live our lives periodically hearing those "mystic rhythms," at times spontaneous, other times sought after.  But, as this discussion demonstrates, spirituality to us is like a river, the source of which we know not.  Well, in my opinion, the sacred plants that inspired much of ancient religion are essentially a method of going upstream and finding the source of the river--the wellspring of spirituality.  I have gone to that wellspring and seen personally where my spirituality begins.  Only by seeing the fountain up close have I been able to put my mind to rest about Mormonism and why I used to feel so powerfully moved while participating in Mormonism.  Now I see where those experiences were coming from.  They were indeed powerful, but what I have realized is that those experiences were being filtered through the Mormon lens, and thus corrupted.  I have seen that even without Mormonism, that fountain of spirituality is still there.    Why do we even have spiritual feelings in the first place?  In a simplistic way of saying it, I believe it is because we are conscious beings in a universe filled with powerful phenomena:  Stars; planets; animals and plants of all colors, shapes and sizes; rain; thunder and lightning; wind; hurricanes; tornadoes; earthquakes; floods; comets; meteors; solar flares; oceans; black holes; galaxies; incomprehensible distances and time spans; and, the most enigmatic of all--the human brain and consciousness itself.  We humans are the conscious thoughts of nature--nature becoming aware of and observing itself for the first time in all history in awe and confusion.  We are not above or outside of nature, but we are nature itself, in its (to-date) most complicated manifestation.  In us, nature has arisen from a deep sleep, dusted herself off, opened her eyes, and perceived her own majesty.  Thus, when we ask whether the universe is aware of us, we are missing the point.  Yes, the universe is aware of us--but in the sense that we (as the conscious part of the universe) are aware of us.    Perhaps spirituality is a by-product of consciousness.  A supercomputer powerful enough to be conscious of itself, it seems, would also be powerful enough to have strong spiritual feeling.    Another way of looking at this is to think about the idea of there being a reducing valve in our brains that allows only enough information to get through to our conscious selves as is needed to survive.  If we were constantly aware of every sensory impression being received from sight, sound, smell and touch, and every memory, there would be an overload of information that would prevent us from functioning.  Through evolution, nature built into us a reducing valve that filters out unnecessary information and allows only the most important information to come to the fore of our consciousness.  What if there are times, when, for whatever reason, our conscious selves become aware of all sensory stimulation--when the reducing valve is bypassed?  Many people (Aldous Huxley for example, in "The Doors of Perception") think this is what is happening when spiritual enlightenment is achieved.  When we become so aware, colors grab our attention like never before, there is an eternity of fascination in a single sight, sound, or thought.  We perceive the world around us in a 100% sense, instead of the usual 10%.  Because we are so unaccustomed to experiencing life from this enhanced angle, all that we experience is strange and overwhelming to us--so overwhelming and ineffable that we have traditionally come up with religious doctrines to attempt to explain it.  Basically, I think life could be a lot more interesting on a continual basis if it weren't for that pesky problem of survival.  We made a trade-off when we "installed" that reducing valve--we traded constant awareness of all sensory input for the ability to survive.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been thinking a lot lately about spirituality -- what it is and how it is attained.  Last week I discussed the topic with a couple of people, and some of the comments in response to one of Ann's postings discussed the topic.  I think of spirituality as a connection of the individual's mind and soul with an external, perhaps universal force that lifts and motivates the individual to live, love, and exercise compassion.  I personally need to feel that kind of connection to something larger than, and outside of, myself.  I've come to believe that there is not just one way to achieve individual spirituality and that the spirit speaks to different people in different ways.  Lately, of course, I've been attracted to Buddhist thinking and meditation practices.  Some folks -- including skeptics -- cannot separate the concept of individual spirituality from the institutional church and its dogmas and doctrines.  What do y'all think?  Is there an innate human need for spirituality?  How is it achieved?  Can spirituality be disconnected from religious dogma?    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I returned my Oldest Son to his school today after his first visit home since being placed at the school at the end of February.  I stopped off at Pie Capital of Louisiana on the way home, but, alas, it is closed on Mondays.  I went to the gas station and got a moon pie.  Not quite what I had in mind, but it did the trick for this redneck.  O.S. loved his long weekend at home, but I think he was ready to go back.  We took him to all of his favorite places, bought him 3 or 4 SpongeBob notebooks, and bought him gobs and oodles of french fries and pizza.  Yesterday he kept pestering me to go in the car and wasn't satisfied with anyplace I took him.  I thought he wanted to go to the park next to the local train depot, but I didn't dare do that solo with Younger Son in tow.  So I took him there this morning, but he just wanted to look at the Amtrak Crescent City Limited and go to the potty.  I suspect he was trying to tell me yesterday that he wanted to return to his school.  Maybe, I really don't know.  DW and I weren't sure what to expect on the ride back.  I insisted on taking it on myself and leaving DW back here so I would be the only one who saw O.S. tantruming and crying.  I feared I was in for 4-5 hours of hell, counting potty breaks.  Anyhow, this morning I let O.S. ride the bus to his old school, then got in the van and raced over to meet him there.  I think Y.S. must have seen me there because I could hear him screaming up a storm before the buses were unloaded.  A para brought O.S. over to where I was trying to hide.  O.S. wanted nothing to do with that para or with his old teacher, both of whom were near and dear to him.  I put him in the van and drove to the train depot park, just in time for the rain to start.  And what a rain it was!  Good thing we drove out of it and to a whole other part of the state.  O.S. was happy as a clam all the way to Alexandria, something that stunned me.  O.S. has an uncanny sense for landmarks and geography, so I have no doubt he knew exactly where we were going.  He did great until we made that last right turn onto Louisiana Hwy. 1, which leads to the school.  He cried for that last 5 minute stretch, something that has torn a little piece out of my heart every time we've gone to see him up there.    When we got back to the school, there was some confusion over where O.S. should go.  I took him from the clinic to his classroom, then to the school office.  Three women surrounded O.S., and he dropped to the ground.  I heard him say "BAY-AITCH!" loudly, and I couldn't help but laugh.  The school people weren't as amused as I was, so I quickly chided O.S.  We went back to his classroom, and his dorm trainer took him to find a toy.  I could hear him screaming as I left.  Of course, he was fine when I called an hour later.  I suspect that O.S.'s ideal world would consist of DW and I moving to his school.  I think he wanted to be back there but didn't want to be separated from me.  I really have no way of knowing, other than by observing his behavior and his moods in the car.  The structure at O.S.'s school seems to have done him a world of good in the 8-9 weeks he's been up there.  He was very well behaved and took direction much better than I've ever seen.  His speech is much improved over what it was a few months ago.  A part of me -- a fairly large part -- wanted this setup to fail miserably so we could bring O.S. back home.  However, a larger part of me wants to see my boys in a situation where they can develop to their fullest potentials.  I hurt when O.S. cries about going back, but I rejoice in knowing that he is improving.  Y.S. was a holy terror the whole time O.S. was home.  Jealousy, jealousy, jealousy!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I thought about Dave today when I stopped off in the town of Lecompte, known in these parts as the Pie Capital of Louisiana.  I stopped off at the renowned Lea's Lunch Room with my Oldest Son and picked up a couple of pies on the way home from his school in Alexandria, LA.  I'm going to eat a piece in a minute.  Mmmmm, floor pie!  I was actually anxiety-ridden all day long about bringing OS home for the weekend.  Is it too soon?  How will Younger Son react?  Am I up for running around non-stop like I used to do on weekends?  Will my sister quit talking in the car?  Also, I think there was a bit of an aftereffect from the last time I went up without DW along.  I had a few heavy-breathing episodes, but fortunately nobody else seemed to notice.  I don't understand it -- my overall anxiety level has gone down since I went on a mental-health regimen, but I have more anxiety attacks.  Fortunately, they're easy to manage and get over.  I stroked OS's head as he fell asleep a few minutes ago.  Putting the boys to sleep has always been a high point of my days, at least when they're actually going to sleep and not just making a play for attention.  Anyway, it was a very nice moment tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I called it right about the disabilities legislation I mentioned a couple of weeks ago.  Today the MR/DD systems-change bill died in committee.  I still have mixed feelings the issue -- my oldest son appears to be adjusting well to his residential school, but that school is an exception.   And I'd like to have the resources to bring him home.    I was pissed off yesterday because I got a note from an advocacy group urging support of a scaled-back version of the systems-change legislation; the new bill would have merely created a one-year pilot program to allow 100 currently institutionalized kids to move back into the community.  I immediately shot back with a nasty little stinkbomb that basically said that it's time to shit or get off the pot -- the pro-community activists need to get serious about dealing with a Legislature that doesn't take them seriously.  Our state is in pretty flagrant violation of the Americans with Disabilities Act, and the MR/DD legal advocates need to take that into court.  Maybe they will now.  The nun who runs my oldest son's school is extremely passionate about keeping her school operating.  The pro-community activists don't come close to matching her passion.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wrote a thank-you note to the head coach of the New Orleans Saints.  He and four of his players paid a visit to my oldest son's residential school this morning.  I knew that the "Saints Caravan" was in that general area this week, but I didn't know it planned to stop by the school.  I need to remember tomorrow to ask my son's trainer whether he got any autographed photos.  My oldest son loves to catch balls, run at people, and be tackled, so who knows?  Go Saints Go!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was thinking a little about psychotherapy this morning and about Tony Soprano's dead-on metaphor in the most recent episode of that show.  Here's a description of the relvant scene (which should nail down Gandolfini's next Emmy) from HBO.com:  Having finally gotten this lie off his chest is an emotional - and physical - relief. When Dr. Melfi likens the process to childbirth, Tony asserts his own metaphor. "Trust me," he tells her, "It's like taking a shit."  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't commented on my favorite television show in a while, so here goes.  Last night's Sopranos was one for the ages.  Good gosh, it was funny.  The overarching theme seemed to be lies and excuses, with many bad events being blamed on "Unidentified Black Males," which was the title of the episode.  Tony S. repeats the lie about black guys killing Joey Peeps.  Even Meadow repeats the lie that black drug dealers killed her ex-boyfriend, Jackie Jr., whose sister accurately portrayed her brother's assailant as "some fat fuck in see-through socks."  The kicker is when Tony S. reveals to Melfi his long-secret lie about something he has always blamed on a couple of unidentified black guys.  The truth is far more interesting.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a poignant moment regarding my Younger Son in the park yesterday.  Fortunately, it came after a sort of high-point moment, so the net effect wasn't too negative.  I took YS to PetSmart so he could look at the SPCA dogs and pet them if he dared.  The SPCA ladies know him by name now, and they know that he is MR, so they encourage him to play with the animals.  To my surprise, YS assertively petted (word?) one of the dogs, and he tried to pull the ears of a massive German Shepherd.  YS adores dogs, so the realization that he could pet them without being hurt made him a little giddy.  I needed to keep YS out a little longer (DW has a stomach flu this weekend and she was napping), so I took hiim to a large public park.  YS's current obsession is magic marker caps.  Not the pens, just the caps.  He dumped his caps at the bottom of a curvy slide, then climbed up the slide and came back down.  He arranged his caps again, climbed again, then came back down.  A boy approached me with a toy gun and asked about the caps.  I conversed with the boy for a few minutes.  He told me that he is 5 years old and that he was born in December.  "Oh," I said, "his birthday is in November."  Okay, this boy is one month younger than my YS.  "Why does he cry like a baby?  Is he some kind of baby?"  asked the boy.  I debated how to answer that.  I didn't want to ruin a 5 year old's afternoon in the park by trying to explain that my son has severe brain disorders, so I just said, "oh, he's still a baby in a lot of ways."  Fortunately, that answer satisfied the boy.   YS collected some of his caps and ran across the park to another slide, then came back, grabbed some more caps, and ran across the park again.  I schlepped the remaining caps over for him.  The other boy asked me if I would do him a favor and let him shoot me with his toy gun.  Sure, why not.  I did death throes and falls to the ground worthy of an Academy Award.  I even pretended to bounce off of a tree after being shot multiple times.  I saw the boy's mother and grandfather busting a gut on a park bench as I played the dramatically dying victim.  For a moment, I felt what it would be like to have non-disabled, "typical" children.  DW feels that frequently and deeply.  She worked as a nanny for several years, and she has much younger siblings, so she knows what it's like to be around typically abled children.  I really have no basis for comparison, so I guess I'm kind of lucky.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I studied and fiddled a little with the "five hindrances" to meditation practice this past week.  Attachment, aversion, sleepiness, restlessness, and doubt.  The first four are pretty obvious, but I had some trouble wrapping my brain around the notion that doubt can hinder effective meditation.  After a Heineken and and episode of Six Feet Under put me in a properly warped state of mind last night, I think I kind of got it.  My meditation workbook defines doubt as "an inability to make a commitment, or to take the risk of finding out for yourself where a certain path might lead."  The workbook warns in particular against skeptical doubt, something I've always tended to see positively.  Because of my preconceived idea on the subject, it took me a while to see it in a new light.  Anyhow, the author explains that "because we're unable to commit or take a risk, we remove ourselves from the process of discovery.  We stay at a safe distance.  Instead of letting something speak to us, we obsessively analyze it; perhaps we disparage or judge it.  We haven't actually experienced it fully or deeply because we haven't allowed ourselves to.  That is how doubt functions in the mind: we remain immobilized at the fork in the road."  According to the author, doubt is a "very jumpy state.  You hop from one thing to the next, considering and wondering and judging and assessing."  The cure is to let the mind settle, "even on a simple object in the moment."  It's a concept labeled "sustaining attention."  I think a certain amount of skeptical doubt is good, and I like at least reading deep intellectual discussions even if I don't always feel qualified to participate in them.  However, at some point, one has to take a leap of faith in some direction.  Try something out and see if it works.  If not, try something else.  I see rather a lot of the less positive side of skeptical doubt on the Foyer, quite honestly -- good people bashing their heads against the proverbial wall because they can deconstruct and disparage all of the contradictions in the belief system about which they formerly were passionate.  However, they are unable to take a leap of faith from purely rational analysis to something positive and spiritually affirming.  I suppose this is to be expected to some degree, given the harsh anti-intellectual, follow-the-prophet rhetoric from the pulpit in Salt Lake City.  However, a leap of faith and ignorant, blind obedience are different animals.  It's taken me a while to grasp that.  Thanks for the great comments, Doug.  I've gone back and edited some things.  Thoughts?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this certainly is shaping up as a weird weekend.  I feel absolutely no motivation to do anything, and this morning it was as if I could feel my noreprenephrine and seratonin levels dropping by the hour.  I took Younger Son to Petsmart to play with other peoples' dogs, then to the park for a while.  That actually helped with the brain chemistry thing, but I still don't feel terribly motivated.  On the brighter side, I will be heading up to Alexandria, LA, later this week to bring Older Son home for his first weekend visit since we placed him at St. Mary's in late February.  I'm looking forward to playing with him, though not looking forward to the jealousy Younger Son is sure to exhibit.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's daily zen is that I've signed up for a meditation class at the New Orleans Zen Temple.  I previously had the impression that those folks were too churchy for my liking right now, but I gave it a second thought and decided to do the class.  I was comforted to find that the NOZT has moved from a nice, comfy building downtown to a dumpy old marine-supply warehouse in the Bywater, with the marine-supply logo still on the front of the place.  Maybe they aren't so churchy after all.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm feeling very depressed this morning.  YS had a difficult, violent weekend, and I was the recipient of most of his violence.  Also, a couple of other big issues I've been juggling recently came crashing down last week.  I thought I had gotten over the gloom yesterday, but it's back this morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday the Supreme Court unexpectedly plopped a turd into the punchbowl of criminal jurisprudence.  The case is Blakely v. Washington, and it could have a dramatic effect on the way criminal cases are litigated.  The case also could gut the Federal Sentencing Guidelines, but that remains to be seen.  Under Blakely, in the absence of a waiver, all facts relevant to a sentence must be found by a jury (instead of a judge, as is the common practice), or must be articulated as part of a plea proceeding.  Whatever the ultimate effect, Blakely will keep me and my coworkers busy for years to come.  Now what you've all been waiting for --    Yesterday's Daily Zen:  Good deeds stand tall Like a green pine,  While evil deeds Bloom like flowers It seems the pine is not As brilliant as the flowers.  When the frost comes,  The pine will still stand tall,  While the flowers, withered,  Can be seen no more.   - Anon 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From the Daily Zen:  You are a seeker.  Delight in the mastery Of your hands and your feet,  Of your words and your thoughts.  Delight in meditation and in solitude.  Compose yourself, be happy.  You are a seeker.    - Buddha in the Dhammapada  The first thing I thought of was Harry Potter, the youngest seeker in over a hundred years.  Actually, I wish I had mastery of words and thoughts.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dangit to heck!  The recent conflagration got me hooked on Internet bulletin boards again.  It was fun doing undercover detective work to come up with a theory of the case in that situation, even if it did end up getting me labled untrustworthy and uninvited from returning.  However, I had already cancelled my account when all that mess got underway and was looking forward to being aimoo-free.  Now I'm addicted to reading those dang boards again.  Stop me before I lurk again!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's Daily Zen:  Worldly ups and downs Should be treated As lightly as clouds Gathering and breaking up.    - Anon  This is a great attitude to have, even if it does seem a little naive.  Come to think of it, that's exactly how I used to view life.  I'm working back to that, so I guess I'm really just going 'round in circles, or maybe it's just my nature.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, now that the lastest bulletin board controversy is drawing to a close, I thought I'd say something blogalicious.  The other night, DW purchased me a package of Zen cards.  Today I have selected a card marked "truth" on the front.  On the back, it says:  What is, is. What is not, is not. No amount of wishing or wanting can change that simple fact.  Well, isn't that obvious?  On the other hand, don't we use our powers of perception to filter through things and events?  I'm a little better at understanding that filtering process, but it's always going to be there, so my "truth" will always be at least slightly different from yours.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I was huffing and puffing up a storm while I was jogging in the heat.  I took a rest stop next to the Aquarium and did something I've been meaning to do for quite some time.  I took a close look at the New Orleans Holocaust Memorial.  The memorial consists of nine acrylic pillars painted with what appears to be stained-glass patterns in the center.  The edges of the pillars facing the river are painted different colors, while the edges on the other side are painted black.  When you go to the plaque explaining the memorial and look at the pillars, you see a yellow star of David on a black background.  Walk around slowly, and the star of David disintegrates, eventually into blackness.  Continue walking around, and eventually a multicolored menorah appears.  Continue further, and rainbow colors appear.  I found the memorial moving.  Despite the darkness of the Holocaust, Jewish culture and faith has survived.  Also, I love the way the memorial was put together.  It's very cool and not dark and depressing.  I think we need to be reminded of that terrible chapter in 20th century history; this is the kind of thing that can't happen again.  I say that knowing that we've had the killing fields in Cambodia, ethnic cleansing in the Balkans, and the slaughter in Rwanda.  Also interesting was that the Archdiocese of New Orleans contributed money to build the memorial.  Yesterday I read an article by Elie Wiesel praising Pope John Paul II for improving Catholic-Jewish relations.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I attended a group for men to talk about dreams.  My therapist put the group together and invited me to join it.  As my dear readers know, I've had several unusual dreams in the past year or so.  I just don't know about this group thing.  The guys who were there last night all seemed intelligent and articulate, and my therapist obviously knows what he's doing.  I like the fact that he's open to anything and doesn't want to impose his own interpretation on our subconscious thoughts and images.  However, I wonder whether it's worth $50 every two weeks to sit around and shoot the shit about archetypical symbolism.  Maybe I should just have a better attitude and try it out a few more times.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's Daily Zen:  Cold night, no wind, bamboo making noises, Noises far apart, now bunched together,  Filtering the pine-flanked lattice.  Listening with ears is less fine than Listening with the mind.  Beside the lamp I lay Aside the half scroll of sutra   - Hsu-tang Chih-yu   I like this for three reasons.  First, it serves as a reminder that hearing and listening are distinct.  In human communications, it's all too common to formulate our responses while the other person is speaking.  Second, it suggests that the mind can benefit from letting down its filtering mechanisms and actually listening to "white noise."  I suppose that goes for experiencing other phenomena that we filter out routinely.  Third, it suggests that at some point we must stop reading about philosophy, religion, ethics, etc., and go experience life.  It reminds me of the commonly expressed LDS thought that one must live one's religion to truly understand it.  There's doctrine, then there's practice.  Any thoughts?  Am I full of it or what?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just redid my settings to allow anonymous comments.  I hadn't realized that I was only allowing registered members to comment.  Not that anybody else is reading and wants to chime in, but those hypothetical teeming masses now can snipe at me without giving themselves away.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was Family Day at the St. Mary's school.  DW, YS, and I drove up on Friday afternoon.  The only room I could book was at a fancy downtown hotel, so that's where we stayed.  It was a singularly inappropriate place for an autistic 5-year-old, but oh well.  YS loves little adventures, so he was bouncy and giggly Friday night.  We took him to the local Chuck E. Cheese, where he had a grand time climbing around in the sky-tube, which supposedly was closed.  Some other kid had removed the cardboard barrier, and YS was at the top before I could do anything to stop him.  I decided I didn't care about the wobbly lower part of the slide, so YS played away.  Can you tell I grew up in the '60s and '70s, before child safety was a big issue?  We went to St. Mary's on Saturday morning, where the administration had 8 or 9 activities set up, with each age group to rotate on a 15 minute schedule.  YS ran straight past OS's dorm and to a large slide/play station he's been lusting after for months.  OS was already out on a tractor ride around the campus, so DW waited in the shaded pavilion while I went out into the blazing sun to watch YS.  DW and OS eventually came over to the playground with us.  YS wouldn't budge, and OS only wanted to swing, so it was farewell to the activity schedule for us (we weren't the only family to blow off the schedule).  I discovered that I've still got it going on with high-speed merry-go-round pushing.  OS loved that.  Let's see how fast a 41 year old can get a merry-go-round going and jump onto it without falling off and breaking something.  Again, can you tell I grew up in the '60s and '70s?  Eventually, we took the boys to Target and McDonald's.  It was a nice family time, for the most part.  YS threw a few nasty little tantrums to mess things up a little.  I think he's jealous of OS now for getting to live in a place with so many playgrounds, horses, and such.  DW and I were talking last night about what a fine boy our OS is becoming.  He's always been sweet and happy, not to mention cute beyond belief; now he's making progress with speech, behavior, and demeanor.  The Family Day was a good thing.  I hope good things keep going on with OS.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Daily Zen is on a roll.  Why do I like this one so much?  What does it mean?  No form, no sound.  Here I am;  White clouds fringing the peaks,  River cutting through the valley.    - Daito 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I was just told that my O.S. is attending Vacation Bible School this summer. &nbsp;I don't know why that surprised me, but it kind of did. &nbsp;Slap my hand, but I didn't know Catholics did VBS. &nbsp;However, I read about VBS being a part of his school's summer program; I must have just forgotten about it. &nbsp;Hey, I'm all for them using Catholicism in O.S.'s program, if that helps him with in any way, shape, or form. &nbsp;I was stunned by O.S.'s good behavior during Easter mass a few weeks ago. &nbsp;Sr. Mary, who runs the place, apologized to us in advance for the service, which was a little rowdy by Catholic standards. &nbsp;However, those autistic kids behaved far better than children -- or some adults -- in your average LDS Sacrament Meeting.      Only in America could you have a family with an apostate LDS/crypto-Buddhist dad; an inactive LDS mom; a Catholic O.S.; and an unchurched Y.S. &nbsp;Gotta love it!     
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's daily Zen:  If you understand the first word of Zen You will know the last word.  The last word or the first word,  Is not a word.    - Wu-men  Have you ever had feelings and thoughts that you could not articulate using language?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The latest brouhaha on the Foyer led me to cancel my aimoo account entirely.  It's something I've been needing to do anyway.  When it comes right down to it, I really don't care about most of the topics of discussion on those boards, so I shouldn't spend any mental energy on them.  Last night I was reading about the role of sexual desire in the Buddhist philosophy.  Some schools view sex as something to be avoided.  Others, however, go so far as to incorporate sex into meditation practice.  Even the Dalai Lama -- a Tibetan monk and presumably celibate -- writes about how sex can serve as an advanced form of meditation.  I don't think I'll ever try to meditate in that fashion, as I don't much like the thought of being sent out to sleep on the couch.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DW and I saw the new Harry Potter movie Friday night at the Aquarium of the Americas' IMAX theater.  It was great on the IMAX screen, even if the chairs there are amazingly uncomfortable.  Anyhow, I thought it was the best of the three films.  By cutting some of the scenes from the book, Alfonso Cuaron ironically managed to come closer to the spirit of the Harry Potter books than Chris Columbus did when he crammed every little bit of the books into his two films.  The movie has a great flow to it and kind of captures the breeziness with which one reads the Potter books.  Also, the film was colored with a dark pallet, in keeping with the spirit of the third book.  Oh, and Draco Malfoy has bangs in this one instead of slicked back hair a la Macaulay Culkin.  But enough of that.  Tonight is the season finale of "The Sopranos."  Who's gotta go?  I expect a bloodbath, but we shall see.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I picked up the current issue of "Tricycle" magazine today, which contains an article about Buddhist themes in HBO's "Six Feet Under."  I'm a fan of that show, but I had never thought of it in that light.  Nevertheless, it makes sense.  Because the family at the center of the show runs a funeral home, the characters are always having to address the inevitability of death and the impermanence that implies.  The author writes:   The show's foundation is the interplay of the Fishers, as each family member struggles toward the core of his or her identity amid an ever-changing caravan of corpses.  Friends and lovers fill out their circle, each seeming to embody a classic obstacle (or ally) in the path to liberation.  David Fisher's companion, Keith, is a black L.A. cop with anger issues; Nate's lover, Brenda, is a hungry ghost, plaued by an insatiable appetite for sex and sensation.  Young claire wrestles with the blithe ignorance of her high school peers.   The characters themselves are not Buddhists -- indeed, David and Keith met at church.  Alan Ball, the creator of the show, is not a Buddhist either.  However, the author writes that   their individual encounters with samvega -- an urgent desire for liberation, inspired by visceral encounters with samsara [cycle of death and rebirth] -- are enormously moving and instructive.  They illustrate Ball's conviction that "for a lot of people, a life that's filled with mistakes and tragedy and random messiness can be way more spiritual than a life of simple piety."   I'm hopeful that the author of the piece will address Buddhist themes in "Deadwood" in the next issue, but that might be a really big challenge.  But you never know -- there is a book out there titled "The Tao of Bada Bing," after all.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         A couple of weeks ago, I got a quasi-promotion at work -- with no corresponding raise, unfortunately. &nbsp;This quasi-promotion entails me occasionally reviewing other attorneys' work, in addition to writing up my own caseload. &nbsp;Three or four other attorneys are in the same position I'm in. &nbsp;In the past week I've reviewed two memoranda written by other lawyers, and I find myself being more heavy-handed than I would have thought. &nbsp;However, I can't think of any changes I wouldn't suggest if I were to look at those two cases again. &nbsp;Moreover, I've been told that the ultimate readers of these memoranda look to see who reviewed them in case of screw-ups, and I'm cognizant of the need to establish my bona fides as a reviewer with them. &nbsp;Additionally, this is my new boss's first big change since taking over the office at the beginning of the year, and it would help his standing (and, therefore, my own standing) if this works out. &nbsp;Finally, we're looking at the possiblity of a RIF due to budget issues in the near future, and I want to be keep my job.      Craig, a couple of your neighbors may have my picture on their office dart boards right now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I feel like shit today. &nbsp;We took O.S. back to his school yesterday. &nbsp;He was high-strung all day Sunday, and he stayed that way most of the way to Alexandria. &nbsp;Still, he was cheerful enough until we got about 50 miles away, when he started crying and sobbing. &nbsp;He tantrumed when we got to the school and took him into his dorm. &nbsp;Y.S. ran into the dorm after him, laughing with a malicious cackle. &nbsp;Y.S. made himself at home while enjoying his brother's misery. &nbsp;That boy sure can be a mean SOB. &nbsp;I've noticed that he deeply resents O.S.'s abilities, limited though they may be in our eyes. &nbsp;On the good side, O.S. was fine a few minutes after we left.      O.S.'s speech, deportment, and behavior all have improved dramatically since we placed him at St. Mary's in late February. &nbsp;However, there's still a long way to go, and I want to see O.S. continue to make progress. &nbsp;That hope makes moments like yesterday's bearable. &nbsp;Also, Y.S. has much further to go than even O.S. does, and things seem to work best when they are apart.      This parenting business sucks out loud. &nbsp;Still, I wouldn't trade my boys for anything or anybody. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally, another decent Daily Zen:  A temple, hidden, treasured In the mountains cleft. Pines, bamboo such a subtle flavor: An ancient Buddha sits there, wordless The welling source speaks for him.   - Yuan Mei (17161798)   The notion of wordless communication, of course, is classic Zen thought.  What do you think?  Can you tell me without using words? 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Seinfeld" had the soup nazi; McDonalds now has the shoe nazi.&nbsp; We were in Alexandria, LA, earlier today to visit our oldest son.&nbsp; We went to the McDonalds closest to his residential school.&nbsp; We've been there several times before, and the boys have always worn their shoes in the playland.&nbsp; Today, however, an elderly employee shouted at the boys as they climbed into the play structures.&nbsp; She then barked at me to take the boys' shoes off.&nbsp; I ignored her.&nbsp; The boys were up at the top anyway by that point, but the hag continued to gripe at them.&nbsp; She left the playland area before DW came in with the food.&nbsp; I thought we were done with this strange old bat, then I noticed her staring at the boys from the main dining room.&nbsp; She went and told the manager on us, and he came in and told us that kids are not allowed to wear shoes because they might scuff up the plastic on the slides and climbing towers.&nbsp; OS was seated at the table right then, so I took off his shoes.&nbsp; He couldn't understand why I did that, and it totally ruined the experience for him.&nbsp; He got upset, and DW took him to the car.&nbsp; I had to pull YS from a tubular slide and take him to the car, kicking, screaming, biting, and scratching.&nbsp; YS has put some nasty bites on me in recent days, so this was not appreciated.&nbsp; Damn that shoe nazi!&nbsp; Damn her straight to hell! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We watched the pilot of&nbsp;"Entourage" last night on HBO.&nbsp; It's a show about wretched excess in Hollywood, with a young movie actor and his hanger-on best friends.&nbsp; The show has promise, but it hasn't found its legs yet.&nbsp; Marky Mark Wahlberg is one of the executive producers, and one would think he would know all about the subject matter of the show.&nbsp; I'll keep watching this one, at least for the next few weeks. &nbsp; I think "Six Feet Under" may have gone six feet under with last night's episode.&nbsp; Most of the episode was devoted to David Fisher picking up a hitchhiker and being forced to drive him around Los Angeles.&nbsp; The psycho hitchhiker ultimately poured gasoline on David, then drove off in David's van.&nbsp; Along the way, the guy made David withdraw money from an ATM; dumped the corpse from David's van (David is a mortician); bought crack cocaine; made David smoke crack; had sex with David (who is gay); and made David help him catch a dog who turned out not to be his.&nbsp; David had several obvious opportunities to escape or summon help -- most notably when the psycho hitchhiker left him tied up inside the van to go into a store, then he managed to untie himself&nbsp;-- but he either did nothing or blew his opportunities.&nbsp; Give me a break!&nbsp; It was like we were watching the first two seasons of "24" and David was the dim-witted Kim Bauer.&nbsp; "24" is pure pulp and doesn't pretend to be anything else; "Six Feet Under" purports to be a drama with a touch of dark humor.&nbsp; Or at least it did until last night.&nbsp; I don't know if I'll be able to watch this turkey again, at least not this season.&nbsp;&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oy, such a morning!&nbsp; I took YS to Chuck E. Cheese this morning.&nbsp; Everything went fine until I made him let another kid go down the slide he was climbing up.&nbsp; He went totally nuts, and I had six fresh bite marks on my wrists by the time I fastened him into his carseat.&nbsp; Masochist that I am, I took him directly to PetSmart.&nbsp; We followed a dog back into the grooming section, and YS gently petted the animal.&nbsp; When the dog went back behind the door, YS went nuts again.&nbsp; I had to pick him up and carry him from the store, with his head and arms wildly flailing around, trying to make contact.&nbsp; I got his arms crossed and firmly immobilized, but he was able to bite me.&nbsp; He got my entire left thumb into his mouth and bit down so hard my thumb briefly went limp.&nbsp; I took him to the neighborhood playground, then home.&nbsp; He's been fine ever since.&nbsp; I've got a few bruises and bite marks, but no major damage. &nbsp; Yesterday was a very good day.&nbsp; We did PetSmart, Target, and a large local playground without incident.&nbsp; YS is very good with dogs, and he loved PetSmart yesterday.&nbsp; I'm thinking he was just terribly overstimulated yesterday and this morning and what I tried to do was just too much. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of the fringe benefits where I work is free parking for about half of our employees.  We have to pack in the cars and frequently have to move other peoples' cars to get out.  That's cool with all the employees except one, who has made her parking privileges a 10-year personal jihad.  The latest is so funny as to be blogworthy.  This employee parks in the so-called 4:30 line, where everybody leaves at 4:30 p.m.  The past few days, she has been placing a note on her steering wheel informing the rest of us that she does not consent to her car being moved before 4:37 p.m.  The note explains that she turns off her computer at 4:30 when the computer clock says that it's 4:30, then she needs time to clean her desktop, gather her belongings, and get across the street.  There is an allowance made for anybody who needs out during the day.  The note is a full page long.  The first note was taken from her vehicle and turned over to the the boss so he could deal with it.  There is another copy of the note on her steering wheel today.  This coworker had been waiting until 4:45 or so to leave the garage, so as to miss the traffic from other parts of the garage at 4:30.  Thus her vehicle often was moved into inconvenient places.  Never dented or scraped, just moved.  It doesn't affect me, as I park in another part of the garage.  Still, it's damn funny.  Evidently I'm not the only person around here who needs to see a therapist.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Has anybody else been watching "Six Feet Under?"  It seems that they've decided to make everybody except David and Keith either stark-raving mad or amazingly stupid.  Nate is as nutty as a fruitcake, following a dog to a psychic, who led him to believe that Lisa is still alive.  Uh, Nate, you buried Lisa yourself.  She's dead, okay?  Brenda and nice-guy Joe suddenly got into kinky sex, and it was funny to see Nate show up at the door while Joe was handcuffed to the bed.  Then there's Brenda's mom, who is always good for a laugh.  Now she's bonking the pretentious art teacher who previously slept with her own son.  And why is Claire such a bitch all of the sudden?  The individual plotlines are quirky, much like Season 1, but yet, something just doesn't seem right with the show.  I can't put my finger on it.  I will be watching this coming Sunday -- it looks like something bad is going to happen.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a confession of sorts.  I've been fighting off an attack of depression the past couple of weeks.  I seem to have bottomed out yesterday and today, and I may be pulling out a bit.  A few good "Sopranos" episodes helped, and I've been very busy playing with Younger Son.  I just ate some sushi from Sav-a-Center just for the hell of it, and doing stuff just for the hell of it is always a good sign.  I like Sav-a-Center because they make a point of carrying Louisiana products, some of which are very difficult to find.  I was more excited than I should have been to see New Orleans Nectar Soda at the checkout.  Next thing you know they'll be carrying cream cheese ice cream.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Younger Son and I are having a very busy weekend while DW is in Utah/Idaho.  Yesterday we spent two hours at a McDonald's playland, two hours in our backyard pool, and an hour running around PetSmart.  YS got to pet a nice black Lab at the pet store, and ran around looking at fish and birds as usual.  We just got back from the Mississippi Gulf Coast, where YS spent three hours in the Gulf of Mexico.  He is working on his dog-paddling technique and on his diving technique.  He started diving down to the bottom to grab handfuls of sand.  Other parents have their kids in floaties and tubes; I was tossing YS into the air and getting maniacal laughter once he came back up from under the water.  Lest you think I'm totally negligent, we were never in more than three feet of water.  I'm not sure what we'll do with the rest of the afternoon, but I'm sure I'll think of something.  YS's transitions are problematic right now.  I had to drag him from McDonald's and PetSmart yesterday kicking and screaming, and I've got a long scratch mark on my face from when I gently placed him into the car.  I don't know why the people in the drive-thru line were looking at us like that.  DW, of course, would like me to be putting together some bookshelves she bought last week.  Oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got this in the mail recently:  Dear Friend,  I don't want to believe you've abandoned the Republican Party, but I have to ask . . . Have you given up?  Our records show we have not yet received your Republican National Committee membership renewal for the critical 2004 presidential election year.  . . . .  So I am surprised and concerned because I know how generously you have supported the RNC in the past and how instrumental your help was in electing a Republican President and Congress.  [yada, yada, yada]?  Sincerely, Mike Retzer Treasurer  I was telling Craig just yesterday about receiving a similar fund-raising letter from my law school.  The difference being that I had actually donated money to the law school in the past, and I was pissed when I got a letter saying that they were concerned because they hadn't heard from me.  I have never given a dime to the Republican Party or the Democratic Party either, for that matter, so imagine how surprised I was to hear how generous I have been in the past.  At the office, I get stuff from the DNC and I somehow was on John Edwards's mailing list.  My magazine subscriptions or whatever must create an interesting profile -- am I an Edwards Republican?  A Demopublican?  A Republocrat?  Just plain fucked-up? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DW is on an airplane bound for Utah.  She will be attending a family reunion while YS and I hold down the fort here.  YS is driving me nuts already, and we only got home from the airport 45 minutes ago.  Last night he decided it would be fun to pour liquids onto the carpet and place little plastic things inside the resulting stains.  So we've had two bottles of bubble bath, two cokes, and a bottle of carpet cleaner poured onto the run in the last 14 hours.  I bring in the rug shampooer whenever he pours.  The machines scares the hell out of him, and I want him to associate spilling with the machine.  Meanwhile, I'm going through and putting any and all liquids out of reach.  That's a really tall order when you think about it, so I'm sure I'll have more floor care opportunities this afternoon and tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this certainly was a fun day.  I was moving in slow-mo this morning, so I was about half an hour late leaving Slidell to go pick up T. for the weekend.  I forgot to take any wipes, which I usually take just in case.  I needed gas too.  So I got off in Covington, LA, got gas, and went to Target for the wipes.  I had planned to hit Alexandria around 11:30; instead I got there at 12:00.  No big deal, and we were on the road by 12:20.  Okay, so if we stopped at my mother's house in Baton Rouge, we should still be home by 5:30.   T. needed more potty stops than usual, I supsect so he could manipulate me into buying snacks.  After two potty stops, I bought him French fries in Opelousas.  30 miles later, in Henderson, he shouted "potty!" again.  Of course, there's a McDonald's in Henderson, and he knows it.  Okay, what the hell.  Another potty stop and another order of fries.   We got back to the Interstate and traffic problem number one.  There was a wreck 10 miles or so ahead, and we moved at a crawl for several miles.  We got to about 15 miles outside Baton Rouge, where we hit traffic problem number two.  There was a wreck somewhere inside Baton Rouge, and it had traffic pretty nearly stopped for 20 miles or so.  There are no alternate routes, so we just had to move along at 15 mph.  We got across the river into BR, and I took the first exit.  We cruised through LSU and came out right by Barnes & Noble at 5:00.  I took T. into B&N for a potty stop.  The escalator totally freaked him out.  I managed to get him to pee, then we went to the car.  We crawled along in BR rush hour for a few minutes, then T. shouted "pizza!"  Okay, I thought, I'll find someplace after BR.  Nope.  T. has an uncanny sense for geography, and he remembered exactly where to go in Baton Rouge for pizza.  He started screaming and kicking my seat when I passed that exit, so I had to backtrack and go to Pizza Hut.  So we got our pizzas and came out shortly before 6:00.  Well, the pizza didn't quite do it for him, so he shouted "French fries!" as we neared an exit where there just happens to be a McDonald's.  I thought I could get away with driving to the next town, but traffic came to a standstill.  I maneuvered over to the left lane, which resulted in a big stinking tantrum.  So I got back over and went to the Golden Arches.  We went inside and to the bathroom.  T. went, then I bought him fries and a root beer.  T. wanted to play in the outdoor playland, which was locked up for the night.  He started tantruming again, and I had to drag him to the car kicking and screaming.  Once we started moving again, T. threw his French fries at me, first one at a time, then the whole box.  Then he threw his coke at me.  Then he threw several Matchbox cars that A. had left in my back seat.  He kept it up until we hit Walker, LA, where he said "potty!" insistently.  So I got off on the Walker exit.   Wouldn't you know it?  There was another freaking McDonald's!  I pulled into a Shell station and waited for T. to settle down.  I gave him his nighttime medications, then took him into the station to use the bathroom.  The toilet was amazingly filthy, so I took him right back out.  I drove him to a Wendy's down the street, where he finally went poop.  We got back in the car and he said "French fries!  Coke!"  Not what I wanted to hear, but I was way into bribery by this time, so he got what he wanted.  We got back to Slidell around 8:20, and we didn't even stop at my mother's house.  So what is usually a 4.5 hour ride (including potty stops) was an 8 hour ordeal.  And the weekend is just beginning!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just made the rounds on the blog-o-rama.  Everybody looks like they're doing fine, but I kind of miss the legal and philosophical musings of my downstairs coworker.  With the Supreme Court acting like it's on crack, this would be a great time for some commentary.  Anyhow, I'm off to fetch Oldest Son for the 4th of July weekend.  I'm going by myself -- he loves having one-on-one time with me, and me picking him up alone is a great way for him to have that.  We'll go to Target and McDonald's, like we do on local visits up there, then I'll surprise him by turning south instead of north.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This Sunday morning was a little different than most. I drove into the city today for an introduction-to-Zen class and not to take my kids to look for freight trains. Because I needed to be out before A. awoke, I headed to the funky old Bywater neighborhood and arrived around 6:45 a.m. for my 8:00 class. Bywater is quite a mix of people -- hippies, contemoporary bohemians, upper middle-class gay/lesbian couples, blue-collar black families, and active-duty Naval personnel. Strangely, perhaps, suburban me felt very comfy in the funky neighborhood coffeehouse, where I sat down and started making my always-A/R to-do list for the week. Rather incongruous, now that I think about it.  Yesterday saw A., my ailing sister, and I head up to Alexandria, LA, to visit T. We fetched T., then made our ritual trip to the nearest McDonalds. A. ran in and started climbing, fully shod. T. sat down and ate French fries. I removed his shoes as he ate. Sure enough, the shoe nazi appeared and walked through the playland, checking every kid in sight for shoes. She even bent down to look under tables to ensure that all of the kids were unshodden. Fortunately, A. was deep inside the intricate maze of plastic tubes and slides and could not been seen with his felonious footwear. Unfortunately, A. became overloaded and completely freaked out inside the climbing tower. We had to leave immediately. My sister followed with T., and was more upset by the way some of the other diners looked at us than she was by A.'s obvious neurological/psychological issues. She kept on about how those people looked at us, so I just said "fuck 'em. You develop a thick skin pretty quickly." We then went to Target, where the kids behaved very well. We then made a spur-of-the-moment trip to my aunt and uncle's house 15 or 20 miles from Alexandria. A. & T. went straight upstairs to the playroom that my relatives keep for their own grandkids. The boys had a great time up there, so I stayed there about an hour or so longer than I had anticipated when we decided to go there. On the way home, A. discovered that Lea's pie store has a kids' play area in back. He attempted to steal some of the toys, and our struggle over that ended in another tantrum that ended when we got to Burger King.  The Zen course this morning was fascinating. Of course I've been sitting all wrong, but that didn't surprise me. We had a quick class, then helped set up for the lunch we would have after the actual Zen session. Once the session started, we sat facing the wall for half an hour; did walking mediation for 10 minutes, then sat for another half an hour. You're supposed to focus only on your posture and your breath; if you do that, the mental aspects of zazen are supposed to take care of themselves. Physiologically, proper posture alters the bloodflow to different parts of the brain, allowing underused parts to get worked out. Anyway, keeping the position was difficult for me, so it was good to have a disciplinarian in the room to straighten me out. It was all very Japanese, with lots of bowing, incense, and lying prostrate. We also did some chanting, in Japanese, that was designed to teach us proper breathing technique. Afterwards, we had a great lunch that a resident student at the facility prepared for us. The lunch included pepperoni slices and wine, two things I had thought were off-limits. I guess they aren't at this dojo. I can't go there for zazen terribly often, but I do plan to make it there several times a year anyway.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A reliable source informs me that some of my coworkers have discovered my little corner of cyberspace, I assume by clicking my profile link on another coworker's blog.  If that's so, welcome, hi there, and I'm not as whatever-it-is as I appear to be.  At least I hope that's the case. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Harumph! I just saw some coworkers in the hallway poking a little fun at Craig's frequently changing facial hair. People have gotten so accustomed to my indecision about beards and goatees that they don't seem to notice anymore. Anyway, I think it's kind of fun not knowing what someone is going to look like from one day to the next. You go, Craig! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just spoke with my 7-year-old son on the phone.  It was our usual conversation:  T:  Hello.  R:  Hi, T  T:  Dad-dy!  R:  Have you got a notebook?  T:  Book.  R:  Do you watch Thomas?  T:  Thomas.  R:  And Blue's Clues?  T:  Blue.  Clues.  I then did a monologue about his favorite shows.  He didn't respond, but he didn't push the phone away either, which is what he does when he's tired of listening.  It was sweet to hear his voice; I hope he feels the same way about my nasaly twang.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had an exasperating tug-of-war with my therapist this morning. I started off talking about having some sadness on Saturday over my younger sons long-term prospects and how it would feel like total and complete failure were certain things to happen. My therapist started to push me a little and I said "I dont want to go there." He continued pushing me. I told him again that I didnt want to go there.  My therapist said that what was going on was a tug-of-war, with him trying to get me to articulate feelings and me shutting him down. He had been reviewing his notes on me, and he noticed a clear pattern of minimizing, rationalizing, compartmentalizing, and cutting off discussion of, strong emotion and the subconscious. That tendency was apparent even to me at the dream-interpretation group last week. I had been able to move the discussions to a more comfortable, intellectual plain in the past, but not today. He tweaked me a little by telling me I say I "dont want to go there," then pointing out that I keep going back, which means that I do want to go there. Just before I left, I told the therapist that I usually felt agitated leaving his office. He told me that I need to bring that up and talk about it.  I hate it when people wont allow themselves to be outmaneuvered. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>