<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aw, shit.  I wanna make a comic.   Again.  Anyone want to help?  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've started driving on my own recently, and I've noticed how bad traffic really is.&nbsp; My parents say it looks like what downtown Portland used to look like 25 years ago.&nbsp; It's absolutly crazy.&nbsp;   I read an artical in The Columbian the other day saying by&nbsp;2005 (or 6, can't quite remember), every city (with the exception of Yacolt, heh heh) in Clark County&nbsp;will be expanding and recieving almost double the traffic of what they are seeing now.&nbsp; The article also says that Vancouver and Battle Ground will see the most change.  That's insane.&nbsp; I cannot imagine driving in worse traffic than what we have now.&nbsp; Then again, we'll all be in College (except for Felix, that lazy bum.), so I guess it doesn't really affect us.  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think welfare is a system of total CRAP. Here we are, spending our hard earned money for taxes, taxes which go to programs like welfare, promoting the American way of life (sucking the blood outta the guys who've got cash!)&nbsp; &nbsp;  Though the concept is novel, people out there are vampires! Though I don't think that we should totally wipe it off of the face of the USA, much like a smudge on the face of a hugely fat baby, there needs to be definite change.  &nbsp;  I'll be first to admit it, and I don't know much about the program, besides that it hands out money and food stamps (do they still have those?) to lazy-ass "citizens" who do nothing but drink booze and have babies, so they can get more welfare! Though I'm sure there is a silent minority that actually needs it, like families on hard times, there is the overly disgusting majority (I think it's a majority) that suck our blood and wallets  dry , just living off it!  &nbsp;  What I want to see are stricter time limits, huge background checks, and checks on the recipients that come often, to look at progress. The program probably has these already, not too sure, but if they do, I'm thinking they aren't strict enough!  &nbsp;  Correct me if I am wrong on any of these facts! Let's see some blood spilt!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uhhh I like Hair bands. I intensly dislike music like usher and rap rnb and all that stuff. I pretty much like older Rock in General, a lot of new bands too. Yeah thats prety much it, oh and I like Christina Aguilera too, cause4 she can actually sing, unlike some other slut who is out ther. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This topic is bound to come up eventually, so we might as well get it out of the way now. &nbsp; What is your favourite kinds of music at this moment? &nbsp; How about this,&nbsp; Favourite Type of Music, Favourite Band(s), Favourite Song.&nbsp; Note: They don't have to be the same. &nbsp; For me, it would be:&nbsp; Classic Rock, Aerosmith, Dust in the Wind(Kansas) 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, time to lay down The Law.  &nbsp;  1. Keep profanity at a minimum.&nbsp; Please refrain from using it if you can while arguing.&nbsp; I guess you could use it to make a point, but it does kind of take you away from the opinion. 2. Racial/Sexual/Homosexual slurs will not be tolerated.  3.&nbsp;No name calling&nbsp;unless you're intending it to be friendly.  4.&nbsp;Do not post an opinion without reasoning if you hope to discuss it.  &nbsp;  If you follow those simple guidelines, I have no beef with you.   &nbsp;  -Praise or Haze-  &nbsp;  I've developed a good way to make a fun arguement when you want to.&nbsp; If you chose to make&nbsp;a topic in which you can post something that you want people to argue with you or say how much it sucks or something, put "Praise/Haze" in the title.&nbsp; Simple.&nbsp; Deliciously simple.    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't really see why we need people to critique movies and things. I don't see what significance they have. Different people look for different things in movies and music, so how can we have one person saying what's good and what's bad about movies and junk? I missed the boat on that one. This topic sucks. Blah blah cookies. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's ask a better question.&nbsp; &nbsp; How long does everybody think Felix will live after questioning the power of an opinion board? Any predictions on what might happen?  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How long does everybody think this will last? Any predictions on what might happen?  &nbsp;  I don't want to be negative, but I think this won't go on for long, as it needs to be a highly collaborative project, and with one or two people slacking off, it'll be more reliant on the few people who do actively post. The crevice will get further larger, until we all forget about this.  &nbsp;  But the future is bright and all etc. etc.  &nbsp;  I was going to end my first post with my highly offensive and politically incorrect assessment of all races of the world, but I was forbidden. Impedement of my free speech.  &nbsp;  Since when was this&nbsp;thing a&nbsp;FASCIST STATE? HM?    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I asked it once before on my other blog, and I'll ask again. &nbsp; Nintendo DS or the Sony PSP? &nbsp; I'm partial to the Nintendo DS, soley for the first party games.&nbsp; The PSP is pretty sexy, though. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anyone see Micheal Moore new film Farienheit 9/11? whaat u think about it? (bias, truth, slander, whatever) I think it rocks and I love Michael Moore.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really likes socks. To me, they are the most efficient, comfortable, portable and affordable way of keeping your feet dry, clean and blister-free. Not only that, but theyare multi-functional! For one, you can make sock-puppets. And another thing! You can make sock-monkeys. Also, you could use them as a wind-sock. I tremble in fear to think of what the world would be without socks. 
    
</post>


<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another note: It's Pulalup!  Who would have thought?  -  Did you ever notice that the lead guitarist of Metallica walks like a crab?  That is very amusing...
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Acadamy Awards only sucked because Mystic River lost and The Lord of the Rings won.  What crap!  They ALWAYS WIN!!!  -  Bleh, I've been trying to put the stupid Red Vs. Blue Episodes on a DVD so I could store them, but the stupid recorder keeps screwing up five minutes in, ruining a total of five DVD-R's.  -  Band trip went wrong in so many different ways.  1. I forgot my mouthpiece. 2. I forgot to pack snacks. 3. I was crammed next to Kyle and Taco for the first half of the trip. (Also on top of heater!) 4. Quiznos sucked in that location. 5. I was thirsty. 6. We lost through a series of bad calls. 7. It took us WAY to long to find the bus. 8. Still hot on the bus. 9. Lost my voice from singing and yelling. 10. Very thirsty. 11. No vending machines at the goddamn rest stop. 12. Couldn't sleep. 13. Couldn't sleep in car on way home. 14. Couldn't sleep when I got home. 15. Oh so thirsty!  Well, the trip from hell is over with now, good.  -  In other news, I'm having second thoughts about the dinner idea....  Note: Old School really wasn't that bad.
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a pep band game tomorrow that I just learned of today.  It is up in...okay...lets see if I can spell this right....Pueolp....no, thats close, but no cigar.  Anyway, up north.  That means long bus ride.  Now, long bus ride is okay, because I have people to talk to, but it would rock if...oh, I don't know...Katie was in pep band, maybe.  Heh.  But, you know, long band trips always turn out fun in some way in the end, even if I just get stuck talking to Kyle the whole trip, won't be too bad.  -  In other news, I now have heard the worst Starwars Joke EVER...I MEAN. EVER!  Ask me if you want to hear it.  -  Dead baby joke count: 9  SO TWISTED!  SO WRONG!! SO...funny...ew...now I feel dirty...  -  I've changed my drink from Dew to Pepsi, because of that music contest.  I feel so deprived...
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Layovers suck.  First layover in LAX, THREE HOURS.  Second layover, TEN MINUTES.  Fucking crazy.  Anyway, I'm back home, and I'm going to sleep.
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's been a really long day.  I'm so tired.  I got up at five, got up to the airport, took a flight to LAX and waited for three hours there.  Had a funny experience in the little McDonalds there.  There were about 15 employees crammed into the place which, if you've seen airport restaurants, is really freaking small.  We then took a puddle jumper (small plane) into "Yuma International Airport"!!!  It has six gates, and is roughly the size of the mini terminal in LAX.  Got Rally burgers, drove a golf cart, and saw AWC get their asses kicked in Basketball by the Gauchos.  Now, I must sleep.  More later.
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got my shots.  Hepatitus shots suck really hard.  -  Wow, I've posted a lot today.  Then again, I went to sleep after my earlier posts, so it's like a new day.
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God, it's been like what...ten?  Twenty minutes?  I'm bored as hell, though, and I feel like ranting.  -  I noticed I've been recieving a lot of mail recently.  Both in Email and U.S. Mail. About college.  I get information about every small college that I've never heard of.  Thats why they mail me this crap, because I would never know about them otherwise.  But it's like fucking spam, all the time, 10-20 emails a day, 3 to 5 letters a day, the occasional giant envalope with about 80 pages on the college I don't care about.  Getting on my goddamn nerves.  It's like those internet CD's you don't ask for.  If I want an AOL disc, I can grab one at just about every store.  And last time I checked...I was already a member to AOL!  Christ.  -  Note: Quesadias are delicious.
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oooh...creepy things keep happening to me this morning.  So, there I am, walking down the stairs, not much light.  All of a sudden... *Thud* "What the hell!?"*Thud Thud Thud*  Just the dog, still creeped me out.  -  Anyway, on to a little less creepy thing...  Somebody was signed onto my name.  Apparently, somebody's ping got through the firewall.  Here's how it happened.  ::I sign on:: *IM - AOL advisor something*:Your screenname is currently signed on in three locations...etc.etc.etc. Me:!?  I always have the computer signed on upstairs, however, combined with that computer and the one I'm currently on, unless I've forgotten how to count, is two.  This really freaked me out.  *I IM my own screenname*: Listen, asshole, get off my name!  I sign off.  Sign back on.  No more alert.  I changed my password to a completely different one, and plan on changing it regularly for a few weeks, I should be fine.  (It's the caffiene that's freaking me out...)  -  I have a lot of crap to do to me, preventing me from going out with my friends to the mall.  Damn, this sucks.  But, hey, I get to spend a couple days in Yuma, so all the better.  -  Cool thing - I just figured out how to put files other than music onto minidiscs....  I feel all...spylike.
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, absolutly nothing interesting has happened over break.  I'm leaving for Yuma early tomorrow.  I saw Runaway Jury.  Worth the three bucks rental.
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Well, I finally asked Katie out.  Apparently, she cannot date until she is sixteen (in mid march), which means I will have to play the waiting game (dammit).  I shouldn't complain, though, at least she said yes...sorta.        The Band headed up the 'Bay for a girls basketball game.  It was scary.  We were on these dilapidated bleechers, way up high, and across the gym from where the dance team was (again, dammit).  Very frightening.  We won, though, so it was turned out well, I guess.         All in all, the day wasn't really that bad, but I can't think of anything to do tonight.  Looks like it's back to the old TV for comfort!
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a total asshole.  I have been for so long.  I need to confess to something.  There's one trait about me that really bugs me.    I'm a compulsive liar.  All the time, every day, I'm lying.  I even lie to people I don't even know, who don't even care if I have a boring life, or that I'm just a fucking moron.  It's a terrible habit, I do it even without thinking.  But I feel as if nobody would like me or even care about who I was if I didn't make anything up.    It's hard to stop, though, I'm so used to it.  But I'm getting so tired of putting on a show for everyone, being fake.  It's not fun.  I hope none of you hate me for this, but I'd understand if you did, and didn't want to ever talk to me again.  I'm going to start over.  No more lies.    Please forgive me.
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To everyone who thinks I've been a total asshole these past fews days,  I'm sorry I've been this way.  My mood's been really sour from all kinds of things.  Beyond realizing that I had no chance with you know who, and that I've been swamped with schoolwork, I also haven't had much sleep.    And now, I will address to people who need to listen to me.  Brionna - Please stop correcting me, arguing with me, insulting me, or attacking me every chance you get.  I am really vulnrable right now, and I don't need to put up with that.  Felix - Please stop humiliating me in science, it really hurts.  For once, keep your goddamn mouth shut and let things go, it's not helping anyone to act the way you've been acting.  Jason - Stop being so hostile.  You act like we're not friends anymore.  Ian - Enough with the annoying physical harm, it's getting on my nerves.  Alicia - You keep talking condenseningly to me.  It's frusterating.  Please stop acting as if you are superior.  To anyone I didn't mention above - Leave me alone once in awhile.  Those things are just adding to an already overwhelming amount of stress.  If you guys think it's fun, it really isn't.  It's hurting me, and I'm feeling more and more antisocial everytime this shit happens.  -  I am so pissed off at Deus Ex: Invisible War.  I have been playing it upstairs, on my piece of crap computer.  No problem, just choppy.  So, I figure I'll bring it downstairs and see the glorious splender that is DEUS EX.  My fucking graphics card is incompatible!!  ARGHH!!  -  For those of you who were overly interested in why I was wear my shades all day, why don't you try not asking in a public place.  I don't want to openly talk about it.  -  In other news, I'm collecting Dew U points, so if anyone has some, give them to me.  -  Here's something thats bugging me.  Question - Would you be mad if somebody gave your name to somebody else?  I don't really think it matters, I mean, seriously.  With so many ways to ignore people, I figure if they want to know my name, fine, but thats all they get.  I know some people who freak out if their name is given away, even if the person it was given to really doesn't care what his name was, and only wanted to say hi.  Besides even that, your name will always be passed around anyway, besides people telling people.
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, Felix, you goddamn asshole, you asked for it.
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh.  When I ask people to leave me alone, why won't they?  It's really annoying.  -  I've been playing this neat little online game, called *gag* Kings of Chaos.  It's nifty.  If anyone feels like helping me out with it,  urlLink click here .  It will give you a number, and you click the corresponding number.  Really simple.  Don't click "Join the War", unless you wish to try the game out yourself.  -  I'm tired.
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crap.  So, I see this little flashing number at the bottom of my browser (Avant).  The number is 42.  So, naturally, not knowing what it was, I click it.  BAM!  I am bombarded with popups!  FOURTY TWO OF THEM!  Thats the last time I click ANYTHING in this fucking browser!
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another reason I kinda dislike Xanga, they're too pushy with their Goddamn premium service.  Dunno, just not for me.  -  Spring break is so close, just one more week and then we get another week off...
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bah, failed excursion into Xanga.  I dunno, just too much to get used to.
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've moved over to  urlLink Xanga , I kinda like the interface better.  So, yeah, look for me there.
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      drunkbuzby (12:10:36 PM): I am sure this is your fault somehow.  We all love you, Burnie.  -  Oi, I snuck out of my house at about 12 last night and got some snackage at the MinuteMart up the street a ways.  Good bike ride.  Some scary old dude, possibly freeloader, possible just eccentric, very creepy.  He kept telling me to come over to where he was.  So, naturally, I sprayed him with mace and then ran.  Nah, just shook my head and tried to be non-confronting.  It was very nice outside.  65 degrees or so.  Odd breeze.  Very different.  Felt good.  It took an hour, and I almost got caught doing it.  Totally worth it anyway.  -  I'm pissed that I was a week off in my mind.  Dammit, this was supposed to be spring break!!!  Ah, well, no problem I guess.  I hate doing group projects, and it seems like every teacher wants to do it now.  It's so fucking annoying.  I work much more efficiently alone.  That is the sole reason I hate Algebra class, Mr. Morris keeps forcing me to work with my teammates.  They're fine on their own!  When they need help, they ask me.  Simple!  I don't need to go through every single problem with them.  None of us want to!  ARRRGHH.  Okay, steam blown off there, felt good.  -  Smooth move on my part, I wore a black shirt today.  It was like a fucking oven!  That shirt came off fast when I got home.  Not very sexy.
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nobody wanted to get the group together, so now I blame all of YOU for making me sit on my ass and sulk!  (Yes, thats it, just pass the blame my puppet!)  Nah, it's no problem, because I beat Deus Ex and that new James Bond game.  But, yeah, next weekend, we're doing something, and none of it during Spring Break, because I may be going on vacation.  -  In other news, I am confused.  If somebody (by somebody I mean Zak, Kyle, or Felix) could explain to me how it's possible to have Paul Denton and Jock come back in Invisible War?  Oh, look, a quarter.
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been moping around my room last night and today, trying really hard to forget that I've been shot down.  So, I got a ton of snacks and Mountain Dew and watched the El Mariachi series again.  Those movies are so great.    I'm pretty much over it, and I figure I'll swear off of girls for a little while, no sense in jumping in again.  -  In retalliation to what someone said in their blog...  FUCK YOU!  I DID NOT COPY YOU!  -  In other news...there is something I haven't said before in public, but here it goes.  Flibby jangly wonk wonk.  Thank you.
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is no such thing as "drama" in High School.  Now that I have stated my position, here is an example of how melodrama is blown extremely out of proportion.  So, awhile back, a friend of mine asked another friend of mine to that Sadee Hawkens dance.  We will call them Girl 1 and Guy.  Anyway,  another friend, Girl 2, tells me that she has liked Guy 1 for God knows how long.  So, naturally, I see it as the classic, two girls after one guy, and it doesn't seem that important.  Flash forward a week or two (or three, anyone's guess).  I get up to school, early release, feeling okay, though I had the remince of a killer headache from the night before.  Anyway, so I get up to school, and apparently Girl 2's whole "secret" got out, and for some reason, Girl 1 was really pissed off at her.  Something about wanting to be a seat buddy with Guy.  Now, Guy doesn't like Girl 1, and has told her that, and that seemed to make everything worse.  They talked it over, Girl 1 and Girl 2, and made up.  Is it just me, or is this something that didn't need to be enlarged like it was?  Dunno, might just be me.  -  In other news, early release was thwarted by the fact that I had to put up with a five hour band festival.  -  And in relation to being sick yesterday, three things happened.    Number 1, while the class corrected the quiz they took yesterday, Sara, Jill, and I got to sit out in the hall and talk the whole period.  Not a bad deal, better than doing spanish I say.  Number 2, Cranny didn't really care that I was gone yesterday in the relation to the project that was due (Which I had finished on Friday of last week).  Which brings me to...  Number 3, Mrs. Klaas wen't super bitch on me today, claiming I skipped class because the persuasive paper was due, which is total crap, seeing I did it on Monday night.  But, you know, Uber bitch Santa wives will be Uber bitch Santa wives, I say. 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was busy all weekend.  After getting home, I did my homework, ate, and then cleaned for seven hours straight.  Pulled out 25 bags of garbage out of my room.  On Saturday, went to aunt and uncle's garage sale, helped out, made a few bucks.  Had a really nice dinner.  Went home, worked four another four hours, thus cleaning up my room.  Sunday, woke up, mowed the lawns, went to Quiznos, came home, ate, and worked for another four or five hours, vacuming and moving my bed and other various possesions into my new room.  -  Mom came home today.  I'm kinda pleased.  However, I kinda liked just having one parent bugging me, then again, whenever one leaves, the other forces us to work to death.  Double edged, so they say.  -  I enjoy living in this room.  It is bigger, the computer's here, there are some chairs, TV, balcony with a great view.  All I did was add my bed, and it was perfect.  -  I am sooooooooo ready for an easy week.  Except for Monday, in which I must write that paper for Klaas and do that newsletter for Cranny.  I have a lot of tests, but those go by fast.  Wednesday is early release, which pisses me off because the band festival is then, and it usually works as a great way to miss class, but instead we're going right after school ends, and then we come back at about 2:30!  ARGH.  No school on Friday, pretty sweet deal, because then we've got spring break, unless I'm off by a week.  -  Spring break will be all about laziness for me.  I will sleep in, rent a few games I've been meaning to play, sleep some more.  Eat some fast food, etc, etc, etc.  It will be so awsome.  -  I should be sleeping right now, but, as usual, insomnia clicks in when I need to get to sleep, so I'll most likely be awake 'til about three or four, if not the whole night.  I need a snack.
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever been called "useless" or "inferior"?  Hurts, doesn't it?  -  This past few days are going by like they didn't even happen at all.  It's really different.  I mean, not really quickly, and not really dragging.  Just...unreal, maybe.    -  I had a really bad episode with myself during English Class.  I was looking at the forcasting sheet, and I realized that I need to crunch things in and I really don't know how the hell I'm going to do it, especially after stupidly failing English.  I don't know if I can take much more of it, before I'm just going to explode.  -  Mrs. Klaas can really be a bitch.  I mean, if she's not teaching, she's really nice, easy to get along with.  But when she's teaching, oh man, she's a fucking nightmare.  Since failing, she and my dad have been emailing back and forth, so I don't screw up again.  And now she's using it against me.  "I'm sorry, Mrs. Klaas, I swear, I got it signed, I just forgot to bring it today.  I forgot my whole English binder."  "Oh, well I guess your dad will be hearing about this."  (What a bitch.)  And the worse part is, she says it so the whole class hears it, and it's really embarassing.  I don't think ANYONE should have to deal with that.  -  And in dealing with that stupid dilemma of mine, I don't think I'm quite over it.  The problem lies in the fact that they're not both in the same classes...  -  You know, my life has been so fucked up this year, I need to take a serious break.  Not talk to anyone, not go to school, just lie back in bed, and have nobody barge in and bother me.  It would be paradise.  Some peace and quiet....
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am truely stuck in a dilemma.  It is really screwing with me.  I don't want to put it on here in case people who I don't want to know find out, so ask me about it.  Lets just say it has to do with Science Night.
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am in an Offspring phase again.  They seemed to stick to me, never left.  Besides, they tricked me into buying seven albums.  -  I should try to get some sleep, I might just be sucessful this time around!!  -  I leave you with this line...  "IIIIIIIIIIIIIII am an antiCHRIST YA!"  We LOVE The Sex Pistols!!!!
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I tweaked my knee the other day, and it's still causing me problems.  I think I'll need to have it checked out.  -  I'm having a slow week.  Really long nights, and even longer days.  My sleeping habits have gotten worse, I'm falling asleep at about 3 or 4 in the morning.  School feels so long, and after dealing with those annoying projects, it just gets longer by having to take notes in just about every class.  To compound that, I do work during lunch, and that prevents me from eating lunch.  Other than that, I'm great.
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Video Killed the Radio Star - Presidents of the United States  -  Well, today was a gloriously boring day.  First period, band, had the most going on, which is really sad.  Second period, algebra.  Mr. Morris seems to have cooled down from that little terror spry I had the other day.  Thats good.  He was wearing a shirt that looks like he took from my closet.  Third period, biology.  Boring test, then watched five minutes of Gattaca.  Lunch, boring, played thirteen, thats about it.  Forth, Spanish, the only other cool class today.  We finished up our fasion show.  It was hilarious.  Fifth, History, semi amusing.  Cranny ranted about nobody helping out for nothing.  I found out I had four unexcused absences in his class.  (WTF, I haven't even been gone four days!)  Sixth, stupid fucking English.  Finished Julius Caesar, and then made a rubric for our papers.  We had to fill in what a paper would look like in six different catagories for 8 points and 6 points, following her 10 ones (I am NOT kidding.)  What a stupid fucking idea.  You can tell she had nothing planned.  Meh, hung out with Brionna, Michael and Kaylee for 45 minutes when we were supposed to be doing the assignment.  Whatever, win win.  -  I finally have Video Killed the Radio Star's first part down.  I'm pleased, it's kinda hard.  -  For some very odd reason, the OC pulled me in.  My sister had it on, and I just sat down and started to watch it.  All of a sudden, I start getting interested!  Holy crap!  It really is like a soap opera!  It's insane. 
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Finger?? What the hell?"  -  Listening to: Angel - Darling Violetta  -  Finally, the goddamn WASL is done.  Two weeks of torture.  Actually, it really wasn't that bad.  -  For anyone who is still confused, I was blue for Spanish Class.  -  Update:  Wei is a G7. Felix is a Bm.  -  I've been stuck doing manual labour at Grandparents' house.  Not so bad.  Get's my arm strength back, and I'm getting paid for it pretty well.  -  After doing the Reading WASL the other day, I have decided to seriously train now.  Not just for track anymore.  I want to run the Boston Marathon when I'm 18.  I'm going to have to train really hard, but it will be so worth it.  -  4.7 seconds, man!
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OCD, the most painfully annoying mental problem out there.  -  So, yeah, I'm tired of the WASL now.  I'm about ready to explode, it's so damn boring!  -  I've been slacking off on my guitarring, as usual.  I need to learn a few new songs.  -  Geez, where did all of this wind come from?  I mean, sheesh!  I start walking from school, and the wind's blowing me all over the place.  -  I skipped fourth period last Friday.  Weighed Spanish and a second lunch, and it really wasn't a hard decision.  Plus, I didn't miss anything important, so, it's cool.  I just need to make up the time with that stupid Language Tutor.  Damn I wish Algebra came after lunch, if you catch what I mean.  -  I've started training again.  I have decided that I am going to run in the Boston Marathon when I'm 18.  I guess the WASL is good for something.
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why are people so against washing their goddamn hands?  It's not like it's hard!  Christ, man.
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been sitting at home more than once this week, alone, making a pizza, eating snacks.  Yeah, I need to do something.  -  My mood is seriously influenced by other people.  It's like I'm a radio or something, recieving all of their emotions and retransmitting.  This can be easily seen in history class.  Any mood I was in changed while being around Kaylee, who's been silent recently.  My mood just dropped to depressed.  Then she left early, and being around others who were chipper changed my mood again.  -  Odd, my posts are usually longer.  I'll have to follow up later.
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heheh...   Felix: Man. Felix: How do you describe the sensation of pain after getting hit in the mean bean machine? Me: Oh, I know. Me: I've been hit there so many times. Me: It's a pulsing ache. Me: Like, it echos. Me: Like they're hollow or something. Me: What happened? Me: Get wacked in the tool? Felix: Nah. Felix: Just wondering how you'd describe it to a girl. Me: Oh. Felix: Because it's hard for me to... Me: I'm gonna quote this.
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: About Her - Malcolm McLaren  -  I saw Vol. 2, better than the first, they feel like two completely different movies.  -  Songs learned recently  Seven Nation Army - White Stripes What it's Like - Everlast  -  WASL is gonna be sweet for two reasons.  No homework, and Mrs. Klaas only three times a week.  Then again, there are some bad points.  -  Okay, so hey, listen, I have my cell number on there if anyone really needs to reach me.  Please do not call or IM my phone just to say hi.  Please.
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Idioteque - Radiohead  -  This week has been a joke, nothing more.  All the teachers as scrambling to finish a unit before WASL, in which we will forget everything we have learned.  Easy week, filled with movies (October Sky, Beauty and the Beast and Babe en espanol, Gattaca, and that frustratingly dramatic Julius Caesar we all love!), annoyingly boring WASL prep, and neat 50's tune's in Cranny's class that I haven't heard in awhile.  Just another excuse to get my groove on in History.  That groove and good spirit carried over to English, where Mrs. Klaas crushed it into the ground.  She is the only woman I know who is evil enough to destroy the good feeling I get from 50's music.  Damn her, she's inhuman!  -  After school, I checked out Room 210, where Mr. Allen confessed to have missinformed me about a meeting which is next friday.  So I walked to Gramms' house.  -  We took Bridget to the Pet Wash where, like always, my allergies attack in full force.  Not fun.  Bridget looks cute now, though still really fat.  -  Afterwards, psycho grandmum was conviced we needed to get her new computer tonight, even though I was really freaken' tired from washing that damn dog.  Whatever, I got Wendy's and Kill Bill out of the deal.  Win win.  Plus I got rid of that damn Wal-Mart gift certificate that has been haunting my wallet since Christmas.  -  I need to try and get some more sleep.  I may or may not be seeing Kill Bill Volume 2 tomorrow, but I will see it one way or another. 
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Knives Out - Radiohead  -  Day went by really easy.  Most of it was boring WASL prep, movies, and, get this, a free period!  Sight read and tried a groovy new game in band today.  It's a real toe-tapper.  Bored out of my goddamn mind in Morris, where we just sat there talking about the future, per usual.  Nightengale was really dull WASL practice tests, not much to say.  We started watching Beauty and the Beast in Spanish, which is eating up two days, score.  Cranny had a sub, who apparently does not know how to run a VCR, and ended up making it eat the movie we were supposed to watch.  So it was a free period, which is neat.  I was able to read my Julius Caesar cliffnotes (heh heh heh), get updated on my sports scores, talk to Abe and Alicia, and wonder why the sub was so interested in us.  Klaas ruined  a perfectly good day by actually giving homework.  Argh, so close to a free day!  -  I was stuck at Grandparents' house today, which is fine, because they're cool.  I did some manual labour, earned some cash, saw Steve and Aunt Robin, who I haven't seen since Christmas (Even though they live in Fisher's Landing).  We tried to get Bill running, only to find that the coil was pretty much done for.  -  I got ANOTHER gift card as a late birthday present.  What ever happened to cash?  I'm only joking, I really appreciate it.  (Unless it's to Wal-Mart, that's inexcusable...)  -  I leave you with this....  Roses are red, Violets are blue. It's I against I, And me against you.  Violets are blue, Roses are red. The way we are living, We're already dead...
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: What it's Like - Everlast  -  Easter was okay.  Familly drove around for awhile around Portland.  Got some Peeps.  Came home, and then cleaned.  Fucking typical.  -  Of course, once I mention that Red vs. Blue is finally keeping on schedual, they start to lag behind on Episode 29.  Damn.  -  I like this new look.  A bit fuller, plus I decided to put a little picture of my guitar in there.  -  And to all of you who want to see that Alamo movie, I hate to spoil the ending, but they all die.  Sorry, I like that joke.  -  My DVD collection is growing, thanks to grandmum.  -  Wow, those above entries are really short.  Here's another one.  -  I'm so not looking forward to school tomorrow.  I might have to take a mental health day.  But, then again, I've missed enough school as it is.  My grades are accually doing well this semester, but I need to really raise my grade in Cranny's class.  I could do an extra project, which could boost me up a letter or two.  Or, I could accually do my homework.  But thats unheard of!  -  I'm really angry at my mother.  I need to get to River City Music because I need to replace some pads on Nikita (clarinet, long story), get some nylon strings for my Mexican guitarra, a slide, a stand, and a new hard case.  Some new picks would be nice too, I've already broken four of my five.  -  Everyone questions why I'm attracted to American Idol.  Well, I won't be once the two hot chicks are sent away.  I started to watch this, and there were a lot of them.  Now it's down to two, and one of them came awfully close to getting voted off, but instead, the unattractive one left.  Neat.  -  Songs learned recently:  A Wolf at the Door - Radiohead Good Riddance - Green Day Blister in the Sun - Violent Femmes  -  Wow, time flies when you're screwing around.
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo, middle of the night, changed my screenname!  So, yeah, my new Screenname is ElectricMariachi.  Okay, cool, bye.
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Changed things around a little.
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Pop is Dead - Radiohead  -  1:15 in the morning, and here I am.  -  Yo, so I'm back in my Radiohead phase.  They are so cool.  A few bands that I listen to that came and never left.  The Offspring Pink Floyd Radiohead The Beatles Jimi Hendrix Experience Green Day Led Zeppelin Aerosmith  Wow, that list grew a little.  -  So, yeah, blogger felt like being a BITCH for a day and didn't let me publish until recently.  But hey, still better than Xanga!  -  I can't believe this goddamn vacation is almost over with.  I'm pissed off, I didn't get any real down time.  -  Everyone, Everyone is so near. Everyone has got the fear. It's holdin' on.  -  I think the Blazers are pretty much screwed.  I think they have to win every game up to the playoffs to be in the playoffs.  My teams always get screwed over.  Just look at the Mariners' opening game.  -  The guys at  urlLink Red vs. Blue  were slacking off for awhile, but surprizingly, they've been able to crank 'em out once a week.  For anyone who has no clue what I'm talking about, go there.  Go to the season 1 archive, and download the first four episodes.  The series is hilarious, but you kinda have to watch it from the start.  -  I now leave you with something different...  Drag 'em out the window, Draggin' out the dead, Singin' I miss you, Snakes and Ladders, Flip the lid, Out pops the cracker, Slaps you in the head, Knifes you in the back, Kicks you in the teeth, Steel-toed caps, Takes all your credit cards, Step up, get the gunge.  Get the eggs, Get the flan in the face, The flan in the face, The flan in the face, Dance you fucker, Dance you fucker, Don't you dare, Don't you dare, Don't you flan in the face Take it with the love it's given, Take it with a pinch of salt, Take it to the taxman.  Let me back, Let me back, I promise to be good, Don't look in the mirror, At the face you don't recognize, Help me call the doctor, Put me inside, Put me inside, Put me inside, Put me inside, Put me inside.  I keep the wolf from the door, But he calls me up, Calls me on the phone, Tells me all the ways, That he's gonna mess me up. Steals all my children, If I don't pay the ransom, And I'll never see him again if I squeal to the cops.  No, no, no, no No no, no no, no no no!  Walkin' like giant cranes, With my X-ray eyes, I strip you naked, In a tight little world, Are you on the list? Stepford wives who are we to complain?  Investments and dealers, Investments and dealers, Cold wives and mistresses, Cold wives and sunday papers, City boys in First Class, Don't know we're born just to know, Someone else is gonna come and clean it up, Born and raised for the job, Someone always does always pick it up, I wish you'd get up get over, Get up get over, Turn this tape off.
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Double Gulp.  64 ounces of pop.  Delicious.  -  We headed out to the surprise activity, which was the rhododendron garden in southern Portland.  It was actually pretty neat.  It was full of ducks and Canadian Geese.  Ducks are very interesting to watch.  Afterwards we walked up to a Seven Eleven and got some chow.  Then we went home, thats it.  -  I haven't been online that much the past two days or so, because we were hit with an annoying trojan.  And, through the combined effort of my dad and myself, it got worse.  However, five minutes alone looking at it's behavior and digging up some stuff on it, I found out what it was and how to kill it.  ----------------------------------------------------------  CWS (CoolWebSearch) Infection  How you get infected - Certain porn popups from ANYWHERE, including clean sites, still unknown which ones, that exploit a hole in Java.  From what I've seen, this hole is only found in Windows XP.  Charateristics - Constant pop-ups, hindering activity by sucking virtual memory dry, the prefix "nkvd.us\1525" placed onto your default browser everytime you try to visit a site, and an attempted opening of ports for the attack "Newtear" through random masked IP addresses.  How to treat - Download "CWShredder" which can be found  urlLink here .  You then run it, do what it says, and it should treat the problem.  You can see the difference by using  urlLink HijackThis  (I suggest you ask an expert to look at the findings from HijackThis, because problems can be caused by deleting things that you shouldn't).  How to avoid - Well, if you don't have XP, I'm unsure if you can get it.  XP users, the hole can be closed manually, but if you have applied the Service Pack 1, it's been closed for you.  Also, use a program called  urlLink Ad-Aware .  It's a free program that scans for Adware, such as the infamous Gator crap we've all put up with.  ---------------------------------  Anyway, thats about enough for today.
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is now 4:30 in the morning!  This is what I absolutly love about the night!  Insomnia!  Isn't it just the greatest thing someone could have?  Who wouldn't want to lay in bed for hours on end trying so hard to get to sleep, but to no avail?  Who wouldn't want to be in an endless state of half-awakeness?    Who wouldn't want to be physically fatigued aall the time?  Who wouldn't love to have viciously disturbing nightmares everytime they accually get to sleep?  I have put up with insomnia since I was really little, and I'm fucking sick and tired of it.  The nightmares are terrible.  The worst of them being this reoccuring nightmare, where I kill and mutilate with a knife anybody I care for.  I keep cutting them, I can't stop, and I'm smiling, while they're screaming in pain.  I sometimes awaken from that dream to find my house empty, familly being gone somewhere.  Many of my friends have recieved late night phone calls from me.  My doctor says it's probably a fear of seperation or lossing the ones I love.  That makes sense.
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can anybody say "Hella boring Spring Break"?  ::Hella boring Spring Break!!::  Good job!!  This has been the number one dullest Spring Break I have ever had.  Ever.  So far, I have either done insane amounts of yardwork, watched TV for hours on end, tried to endure my annoying cousins, or spaced out while playing my guitar.  What a great way to start my spring break.  Look at this, it's already Thursday!!  Yippee!  I am going to see The Whole Ten Yards on Friday, that will be cool, followed by this "Mystery Activity" Brionna has planned for the group, and she refuses to tell me what it is (You're TEARING ME APAAAAART!!).  Oh, I did go and hike Beacon Rock with the group, alas, Alicia and her asthma slowed us down, so we went over to her house and watched some movies.  Win Win, I think.  -  I have started to write my script for that updated Julius Caesor idea I had.  It's going pretty well.  Kinda hard to get anything done on this, because I go all psycho into the details of the settings and camera work, so I estimate a total of four years to get this done.  -  As the world does turn, And if London burns, I'll be standing on the beach, with my guitar. I wanna be in a band, When I get to Heaven. Anyone can play guitar, And they won't be a nothing, anymore.  -  I don't know why, but the '96 version of Romeo and Juliet is one of my favourite movies, up there with Pulp Fiction and Fight Club.  Funny.  -  I don't know, I'm kinda at a loss on the subject of my love interest.  I think she may already know, so I'm really not sure if I should even go for her.  I really like her, though.  -  I'm about to konk out at the desk.
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Nothing, I've got a fucking migrane.  -  Yeah, I went home early today, I couldn't stay focused, my head hurt like a bitch.  Sorry to my group in English Class, I wouldn't have been any help anyway.  Besides, wasn't fun going home anyway, because I cleaned.  I cleaned while I was sick.  Fun times, eh?  Well, it's my dad's birthday today, and he wanted a clean house.  So, I came home, drugged myself up with asprin and cleaned.  And cleaned.  And fucking cleaned.  For about four hours.  Then my dad came home, and pointed out everything I  didn't  do, and there wasn't a lot I hadn't done.  Uhg, just pisses me off, he's never satisfied with anything.  Acted like I didn't even attempt to clean.  -  Met the new band directors yesterday.  They're nice people, the only reason everyone is pissed off at them is because they're replacing Siess and PC.  It's not their fault.  Besides, they're trying really hard to convince a few people (You know who you are, clarinet buddies) to stay in band, which is good.  -  Due to Band/Choir trips and Senior Skip Day, there were only around eleven people in my math class.  So we basically did absolutely nothing.  Oh, we (Jason, Elona, Jenni, and Jessica) made a mural using markers on the white board.  It was great.  Jason got a picture, though his camera had no flash.  So no idea how that turned out.  -  Well, I'm gonna go sleep.
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to:  Last Kiss - Pearl Jam   Oh where, oh where, can my baby be? The Lord took her away from me. She's gone to heaven so I've got to be good, So I can see my baby when I leave this world.  We were out on a date in my daddy's car, We hadn't driven very far. There in the road straight ahead, A car was stalled, the engine was dead. I couldn't stop, so I swerved to the right, I'll never forget the sound that night. The screaming tires, the busting glass, The painful scream that I heard last.   When I woke up, the rain was pouring down, There were people standing all around. Something warm flowing through my eyes, But somehow I found my baby that night. I lifted her head, she looked at me and said; "Hold me darling just a little while." I held her close I kissed her - our last kiss, I found the love that I knew I had missed. Well now she's gone even though I hold her tight, I lost my love, my life that night.  -  I'm a little depressed, but I think I'll hold out.  -  This headache is killing me, it won't leave me alone.  I've tried everything.  -  I saw Shrek 2.  Totally worth it, I think.  -  Shit post, sure, but I'm going to sleep. 
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      F kusu:           You people and your American Idol. F kusu:           Slobbering masses running to instant entertainment. F kusu:           Leading lives of quiet desperation. ElectricMariachi: It's funny when you try to make sense. F kusu:           Your outwark mask to the world belies that spark of intellegence. F kusu:           Hidden, like a seed. ElectricMariachi: Oh, I'm gonna have to quote you trying to be intellectual. 
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Sheena is a Punk Rocker - The Ramones  Well the kids are all hopped up and ready to go, They're ready to go now. They got their surfboards and they're goin' to the discoteque au go go. But she just couldn't stay, She had to break away, New York City really has it all. Oh yaaah oh yah!  Sheena is a punk rocker, Sheena is a punk rocker, Sheena is a punk rocker now.  -  I'm very pissed off at a few people who seem to think I skipped the past two days.  I've been ill, for chrissakes.  I've got a horrible sore throat, I can't talk, and a evil fucking headache.  So, to the next person who say's I've been skipping, prepare to have your stomache gouged out with a large garden pitchfork.  I'll be back to school probably tomorrow.  -  I'm not getting to sleep tonight, because I foolishly fell asleep at two o'clock and woke up at eight.  Silly me.  -  Well, I'm going to go lay down and watch American Idol.  Go Diana!! 
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: A Girl Named Tex - Trocadero  Have you heard the story of  A girl named Beth, now known as Tex  Her life's tale is a bloody trail  Her name fits like a glove   Her daddy sighed as she slammed the door  She'd said to him I'm Beth no more  My life's dream is to kill for green  But first I'll join the Corps   Her daddy said, you're just a girl What makes you think that you won't sink My name is tex and I'm like a hex My playground is the world  Basic turned her gun to gold  Soon had it made, she'd hit by trade  Amassing kills, she proved her skills  Make your blood run cold   I once saw texas at a bar  Sippin rye, with some apple pie With a distant stare, like she didn't care  She said what's with the guitar  I must admit my lips went numb Some butter bar said, his face all red She's too good, you're driftin wood Said boy you'd better run  Texas said sir keep your peace My heart is free, and so is he I'll give it to, any man who's true The safeties were released  He drew before he replied But Tex was hot, and he was not He lay dead, While texas bled Crimson on her side  Texas said This could be my last I guess I gotta go, and now you know I want a song, to live for long It's a fair request  Texas made it out I heard But her one need, I did heed I think of Beth, while mocking death Like a mocking bird  To listen to this song, or to hear more, check out http://trocadero.net/  -  I woke up this morning with a sinus headache and ten minutes to get ready, so I was like,  "There is no way in hell I'm going to school today."  I still need to go to band practice. I'm gonna have to skip it, my head's killing me. -  My minidisc player has survived so much, it's amazing what kind of abuse it can take, from simple roughing up to being dropped 20 feet to the floor of a lake, it's still ticking.  -  I'm gonna lay back down.
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Grease Soundtrack  -  So, yeah, I'm kinda emptied of feelings right now.  To whoever doesn't already know, ask me about it.  -  I watched Grease to make me feel better.  That movie ALWAYS makes me feel better.  I also watched Paycheck, which was really fucking awsome.  -  I got a new X-box controller, so now I finally have two, and I've been trying to get someone in my house for target practice in Halo.  I need to get back in shape for that Lan party tomorrow.  -  I actually bought a Pokmon game, and I was impressed on it's translation to the GBA. I'm still dissapointed in the fact that there's not an aventure one for the GCN.  -  My graphics card has been throwing a fit since we got it, so now it's yanked untill we can find some cheap RAM.  Yeah, I'm pissed off.  -  Got new headphones too.  They're huge, so I'm never gonna be seen out of the house with them.  -  To anyone who insists on calling my house and leaving a message, It would be a whole lot easier if you'd just call my cellphone.  Not only will it be on my person at all times, but you can call at anytime.  -  My dad's on an eating healthy frenzy.  I've been eating good things at school, but I do so I can eat junk when I want to.  -  I'm gonna go practice killing other humans in a virtual ring world.  Bye for now.
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Landslide - Fleetwood Mac  -  I successfully fell asleep in Klaas today.  First time I've been able to do that.  It's weird she didn't notice, because I'm in the front row.  She was reading some poem when I konked out, and I woke up in an instant, but everything was silent.  Scared the hell out of me.  Apparently we were supposed to respond to the poem I slept through.  Can somebody help me out?  -  Over the weekend, I finally got back into Fleetwood Mac.  Good stuff.  -  I've been so pissed at my computer.  I don't even wanna get into it.  -  Thunderstorms are the most frightening weather pattern ever.  I mean, Christ, the rain is fine, it's just the large rumbling sounds and large streams of static electricity I'm nervous about.  It's not unreasonable.  -  Cranny is getting slowly more and more intolerable.  It's fucking incredible.  And his class is boring right now, because, well, you all know.  Oi.  -  Now that I took that goddamn nap in Klaas, I can't sleep, this sucks.  -  For some odd, odd reason, one(or more) of my teachers nominated me for Link Crew (I refuse to call it "Thunder Crew").  Apparently, they're trusting me with the fragile psyches of a group of incoming Freshmen.  Ooh, this is a perfect opportunity to be mean to a few freshies (Just kidding, I'll be good...)  -  Salad!
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Stray Cat Strut - Stray Cats  -  I've been getting into my odd 80's/90's pop song phase again.  Here's a list of recently rediscovered songs:  Stray Cat Strut - Stray Cats Still Rock and Roll to Me - Billy Joel Uptown Girl - Billy Joel Song 2 - Blur Lust for Life - Iggy Pop Sabatoge - Beasty Boys I Smell Sex and Candy - Marcy Playground The Freshmen - Verve Pipe  Etc, etc, etc, etc, etc.  -  I had a crapload of homework this week.  And you will all be proud to know, I finished ALL OF IT!  Woo for me!  That, and Mrs. Klaas moved the paper to Monday.  -  Career unit was pointless this year, just helped make worse that sinking feeling I get when I think about college.  -  I found out it's really easy to peal stamps off of letters.  I guess those college information letters have some use.  -  I took the bus home the past two days, it felt weird.  -  And, to the many people I promised that I would see Hello Dolly on Opening night,  I'm sorry!  -  I've been trying to eat healthier, having salads or sandwiches at lunch and for snacks, eating a full dinner.  I figure it's about time I take care of my body.  (Not that I won't still eat junk crap.  I don't have that kind of willpower.)
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Uptown Girl - Billy Joel  -  The weekend didn't go too bad, just hella boring as usual.  Friday, afterschool, went to Grandparent's house, and decided I didn't wanna do yardwork.  So my Grandpop said I can do it sometime next week.  So we played Cribbage, I walked to dog, ate, pretty boring.  Dad picked me up and we went home.  I played guitar for about 5 or 6 hours, and then went to sleep.  Saturday, I woke up too late to see the parade on Mcgillavray, so I was kinda disappointed.  Then I heard it rained the whole time, and then I didn't mind that I slept through it.  Sat on my ass all day, played more guitar, went over to Gramm's house, came home, watched Matchstick Men (Good, very, very, good.), and then slept.  Woke up and cleaned for Mothers Day.  Thats basically it.  -  And, to please a friend.  Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe!  -  Aw, Friends is over with!  -  I put a little chat box on my blog!  Over to right.  Post something in it!  -  I've attempted to start writing some music.  The thing is, no matter how bad the song is, after you finish, you still feel a strong feeling of acomplishment.  It's also kinda fun.  -  I've had an odd attraction to Tribes, a game I haven't played in about three years, again.  -  I need to do my homework.  Will probably post later.
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Israel Kamakawiwo'ole - Somewhere Over The Rainbow/What A Wonderful World  -  For anyone who hasn't heard or seen by the many pissed off Band Nerds, Band is going to hell.  We're losing Mr. Siess and P.C. to middleschools, but the real kick in the head is we're LOSING THE GODDAMN FIELD SHOW!  I can't fucking believe it.  I was so psyched for it, so looking forward to it, and it get yanked from us.  That's not cool!  -  For everyone who's taking the AP test: STOP STUDYING SO HARD.  Seriously.  It is really unhealthy to study 22 hours a day, seriously.  -  As for teachers, I am THIS close to mashing Mr. Morris's head in with a garden spade, for chrissake!  He's such a goddamn jackass!  Cranny is becoming more and more intolerable each day, but still not enough to ruin History Class for me, heheh...  -  Did I mention O.C.D really fucking sucks?  -  I need to spend some serious time with my guitar and get my pentatonic scale down.  Yes, I do scales in my free time.  My friend's teacher called it "playin' the fish".  Cute at best.  -  I've been addicted to two shows I really shouldn't be, American Idol and The O.C.  However, once my hot chicks are all gone, I'll stop watching.  -  I'm really pissed off at the Mariners, they haven't started this bad in a long, long time.  More ranting on that later.
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Do I look high in this picture?&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Aqualung - Jethro Tull     Sitting on a park bench -- Eyeing ittle girls with bad intent. Snot running down his nose -- Greasy fingers smearing shabby clothes. Drying in the cold sun -- Watching as the frilly panties run. Feeling like a dead duck -- Spitting out pieces of his broken luck. Sun streaking cold -- An old man wandering lonely. Taking time The only way he knows. Leg hurting bad, As he bends to pick a dog-end -- He goes down to the bog And warms his feet. Feeling alone -- The army's up the rode Salvation  la mode and A cup of tea. Aqualung my friend -- Don't start away uneasy You poor old sod, you see, it's only me. Do you still remember December's foggy freeze -- When the ice that Clings on to your beard is Screaming agony. And you snatch your rattling last breaths With deep-sea-diver sounds, And the flowers bloom like Madness in the spring.  -  School is FINALLY OUT!  Goddamn, it's about time.  Then again, I have to go back up in a few days anyway.  What kind of shit is that?  Fucking Summer School.  My fault, though.  -  It's amazing how slow a week can move while waiting for school to end, and Thursday and Friday, even though half-days, were no exceptions.  Slow, EXCRUTIATINGLY slow.  Painful, almost.  Wednesday,  I realized I still had an unexcused.  Very lucky I remembered then, because it was the last day to make them up.  Only problem was I had to stop by Mr. Bannow's room and get class information for next year, which was across the school from the gym.  So, I had to run from that room over to the small gym, and the door was locked.  So I was thinking "FUCK!", and run around to the back side, where the was a big group locked out.  I'm standing there, thinking "I'm screwed, I'm screwed.", however, some very kind aid let us in.  Another hour or sitting there with my math book propped open, spacing out.  Came home, went to Wal-Mart.  Came home, dyed my hair.  Went to sleep.  Thursday, I had Band, Math, and Science, which all went by fairly easily, but allow me to describe what stretched it all out.  Band, played cards and signed yearbooks, the best class I had the whole week.  Math, had to indure Morris for one more day.  Luckily, we had our MULTIPLE CHOICE FINAL (Hell yeah!), and so it was very easy and he didn't talk.  Cool.  Science, presentations.  Jason and I kicked ass.  Afterwards, I went to Klaas's and spent THREE HOURS doing makeup work.  Uhg.  UHG.  Friday went basically as slow as thursday, only without the extended Klaasness at the end.  Afterwards, however, I went shooting with Grandpop.  It was great, because I haven't been to the 'Pits in a year or so.  I only shot a .223, because I was sick, and couldn't hit anything.  But was still fun.  -  Driv3r is fucking awsome.  Period.  -  And let me direct something to Jason for a second.  Hey, I'd teach you this song, but it has a Barre in it!  -  My dad and I checked out yet another car, this one was a '92 Tracer.  Ugly as sin, those things.  Manual, 80 thou on it, and it was really showing it's age.  Thumbs down.  -  I'm gonna be so bored over break, I have decided to play entire series of games.  I am going to start with Mario, playing every one of those games I can get my hands on.  Then I'll do Zelda, and then I'll do Final Fantasy, etc., etc., untill I run out of good games and/or school starts again.  I really am that bored.  -  Good part about summer school: It starts at 10. Bad part about summer school: It's at fucking Heratige.  -  Sleep time.
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Maggie's Farm - Bob Dylan   I ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more. No, i ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more. Well, i wake in the morning, Fold my hands and pray for rain. I got a head full of ideas That are drivin' me insane. It's a shame the way she makes me scrub the floor. I ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more.  I ain't gonna work for maggie's brother no more. No, i ain't gonna work for maggie's brother no more. Well, he hands you a nickel, He hands you a dime, He asks you with a grin If you're havin' a good time, Then he fines you every time you slam the door. I ain't gonna work for maggie's brother no more.  I ain't gonna work for maggie's pa no more. No, i ain't gonna work for maggie's pa no more. Well, he puts his cigar Out in your face just for kicks. His bedroom window It is made out of bricks. The national guard stands around his door. Ah, i ain't gonna work for maggie's pa no more.  I ain't gonna work for maggie's ma no more. No, i ain't gonna work for maggie's ma no more. Well, she talks to all the servants About man and god and law. Everybody says She's the brains behind pa. She's sixty-eight, but she says she's twenty-four. I ain't gonna work for maggie's ma no more.  I ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more. No, i ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more. Well, i try my best To be just like i am, But everybody wants you To be just like them. They sing while you slave and i just get bored. I ain't gonna work on maggie's farm no more  -  I took a bunch of little quizes while I should have been working.  Interesting stuff.  -  Here's a good question for everyone:   Your mother asks you to watch her poodle, Muffy, while she's visiting your aunt Jenine in Ontario, Canada. While Mama is away, you never feed Muffy, and, malnourished and starving, she dies. Do you:    a.replace Muffy with a similar poodle, in hopes Mama won't notice  b.fake your own death so Muffy's seems inconsequential  c.bury Muffy in the backyard, and say she ran away  d.take Muffy to a taxidermist to immortalize her  e.burn the house down in a fit of rage, and when Mama asks, it was Muffy who did it, Muffy, that little bitch  -  Argh, stupid Mrs. Klaas.  -  This is a great time of the year to watch people, because it is without a doubt the most hectic time ever.  My favourite thing to watch is the classic "Due Date Mixup" which is followed by the "Fuck, I'm Screwed" which is soon followed by the "Rush to Get the Goddamn Paper Done".  Just amusing.  -  I just found out today that I'll have CATON for Honours Am. Lit. next year.  FUCK!  -  Next person to make a crack about homework to me is getting stabbed in the eyes.  No warning then, just one now.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Do You Wanna Dance? - Ramones  Do you wanna dance and hold my hand? Tell me baby I'm your lover man Oh, baby, do you wanna dance?  Well do you wanna dance under the moonlight? Squeeze me baby all through the night Oh baby, do you wanna dance?  -  See, shortness to compensate for that really long Outkast song last post  -  You know, some interesting things have been happening to me concerning a certain other person.  I dunno why, either.  A lot of it are some really funny coincidences.  -       urlLink take the "what's your dark secret?" quiz   | courtesy of  urlLink mewing.net.  where darkness and secrecy abound.    That is SO COOL!  Though, taking another look at it, it's kinda tasteless.  -  Well....okay!  That's my post.  I hope you have enjoyed this brief time we've had together!
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Humble Mumble - Outkast  Ahhhh I stank I can, I stank I can The funky engine that could  Oooo oooo yosky, wosky, pisky, wisky All aboard the Stankonia Express The underground smell road Everybody's lookin' for an excuse to let loose What's your locomotive, the chatter and the choo choo  Humble as a mumble in the jungle Of shouts and screams That's the way the cracker crumbles So I guess I've got to re-route my dreams  Back on the microphone, your number one controller I rock the microphone like a blizzard;  I'm so cold I'm tryin' to hold ya Life is like a great big roller coaster Everything in life don't happen like it's suppose to Trials and tribulations make you stronger live longer You wanna reach the nation nigga start from ya corner Everything in life don't always happen like you plan it Demand it; over stand it then you handle it Fuck wishing you, you missing the ambition on your mission Now you switching why you quitting 'cause it's heated in the kitchen Sloppy slipping in your pimping nigga You either pistol whoop the nigga or you choke the trigger You've got to follow through, struggle to complete your dreams "No Weapon Formed Agains Prospers" 54:17 From Isaiah lay a nigga down and spray 'em If the dealer dealt a fucked up hand of cards you've gotta play 'em  Too Democratic, Republic fuck it We chicken nugget, we dip in the sauce like mop and bucket Blue-collar scholars, who'll take your dollar and wipe my ass wit it You living for the lotto never hit it, I met a critic I made her shit her draws She said she tought Hip Hop was only guns and alcohol I said "Oh hell naw!" but yet it's that too You can't discrimahate because you done read a book or 2 What if I looked at you in a microscope saw all the dirty organisms Living in your closet would I stop and would I pause it "whoo" To put that bitch in slower motion, got the potion and the antidote And a quote for collision the decision Is do you want to live or wanna exist The game changes everyday so obsolete is the fist and marches Speeches only reaches those who already know about it This is how we go about it  I'm wild just like a rock, a stone, a tree And I'm free, just like the wind the breeze that blows And I flow, just like a brook, a stream, the rain And I fly, just like a bird up in the sky And I'll surely die, just like a flower plucked And dragged away and thrown away And then 1 day it turns to clay It blows away, it finds a ray, it finds its way And there it lays until the rain and sun Then I breathe, just like the wind the breeze that blows And I grow, just like a baby breastfeeding And it's beautiful, that's life and that's life And that's life and that's life  -  Now, you may be asking, "Why the hell is he listening to a rap song?"  Well, this really isn't all that bad, Outkast is one of three rap groups I can tolerate.  -  "I've got a disease, and the only cure is MORE COWBELL!"  -  My minidisc software decided to throw an attitude at me today.  It wouldn't convert any of my songs.  So, I get the CD, reinstall it (took twenty minutes on my piece of shit computer) and try again.  Same problem.  Finally, it asked if I want to do something with backing it up when I was doing something COMPLETELY unrelated to it.  So I did.  Works fine, now.  -  I was kinda preoccupied on Friday to post everything that happened.  My parents went to Seaside Wednesday afternoon, so my sister and I were held up at the Gramms' house.  I was out in the trailer (Yeah, I was sleeping in a trailer, big deal, it was privacy.), and I was able to do anything I wanted outside of setting something on fire, so, naturally, I snuck out.   Painfully simple when you already are technically outside.  I went to Taco Bell and took a very long walk about some places, woke a few people up, and it was raining the whole time.  Felt like goddamn Florida, walking through water and whatnot.  Nobody wished to venture with me, which kinda sucked, but, you know, gave me alone time I guess.  Thursday came along, boring school day, went over to the house again, and did nothing.  Took a nap, woke up at nine, and snuck out again, this time went to blockbuster and got a movie and got a bunch of snackage from a convienience store.  Went back, and, thats about it.  Friday.  Woke up to Grandpop screaming into the intercomm and what not.  Normal start.  I get ready, get out the door, don't get too far and then I realize with a look at my watch that I would be late.  Well, luckilly for me, I've got a load of driving-age friends on McGillivray, so it was only a matter of time before Erin, who lives across the street from my Grandparents (and pretty hot to boot.), pulled over and asked if I needed a lift.  We were at school in no time, thanks in part to her insane driving.  We were going between 35 and 40, weaving between cars and what not.  Scary.  Got to school, and the day has already been commented on in Friday's post.  Came home on the bus, which I do so sparingly now, it's like an adventure.  Got home, parents were back, got two posters, a Beatles one and a 'Vett one, neat stuff.  Kim's birthday was then.  So, I just watched The Office upstairs, naturally.  Cheesecake, though, couldn't miss that.  Went to bed at three Friday night, while unbeknownst to me, my parents were planning to attack me in the morning with an ungodly amount of chores.  So, I wake up at ten, to my dad yelling something about lawn mowing.  Worked all day, ate, and watched movies. Went to bed at three again.  Woke up at ten again on Sunday, only this time, I was able to get back to sleep, my comatose state I have when I sleep after being sleep deprived saved me for any work untill, get this, 3 PM.  Three in the fucking evening!  I wasted my day!  Kind of.  Ate Chinese food, and watched Game Four (Suck it, Lakers, you're getting your asses kicked in so many ways.)  Thats about it.  -  It's weird.  I finished some T.V. a little while ago, came into my room, looked at the clock, 4:20 on the dot.  Funny.  -  I'm gonna be so tired for school, I really do wanna go.  But my parent's will use the classic "You've missed too much school" which is bullcrap because, from what they know, I've only been absent a total of four and a half days this semester.  In truth, there's countless skips you have to count, but they didn't know that.  -  Summer school is going to fucking suck.  That plus a job is gonna kill my summer leasure time.  -  Did you ever notice a lot of the gum like Ice Breakers and what not are packaged like medication?  What's with that?  -  Damn, it gets light out earlier and earlier.  It's 4:41 as I type this, and the sun's rising.  -  I watched this thing on T.V., called "Crossroads"(No, not the Britney Spears flick).  It's thing thing where they take two bands, one rock, and one country, and mash them together on stage.  The one I saw was ZZTop and Brooks & Dunn.  It was really neat, especially the guitar work.  -  Here's a kinda gross little anictdote I'm sure we've all been through.  I'm mowing the lawn, right, and I thought I had stepped in dog crap.  So, I look at my shoe while walking, you know, kinda hop and glance.  And, in the process of that, I actually DO step in dog crap.  Frusterating.  -  Something that sounds frightening:  Use two Eclipse Mints cases as slides on the guitar.  -  I have like, five 365 calanders I got from my Aunt who knows how long ago.  I now remember why don't like them.  I glanced over at the one on my desk.  Yeah, the date says March 18.  -  Okay, so, there's this bag I brought back from Gramms' house, right?  It was full of stuff I had over there.  I had, among my clothing, four bottles of Mountain Dew, a box of Ritz Bits Sandwitches, two cans of Pringles, a half eaten box of Mike 'n' Ikes, and a bag of Jet Puff Marshmellos.  Somehow, I mangaged to eat everything in that bag on Friday.  -  I think I should make a sculpture out of the AOL CD's a recieve and take from various places.  They seem like they're going to waste.  -  I've had these script ideas, four of them, floating through my head for a couple weeks.  And then, last night, just like that I was struck with an idea.  I shall combine them into one script!  More details later.  -  I have this pack of No Doze I lifted from my mom about two weeks ago.  I looked now at what I have left.  Two.  Just two.  -  I was rumaging through my pile of trash the other day, and came across something.  A pig, made out of a Hawiian Punch bottle and some Tippex.  I think I named him, shit, what was his name... well, I can't remember.  -  There's a double gulp cup that has been sitting on my desk for so long now I don't think I even remember where I got it from.  -  GEORGE.  GEORGE THE TUMOUR PIG!!  I remember!  -  I want a Hat FM. 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: The Trickster - Radiohead  Lost in the mountains Rust in my brain The air is sacred here In spite of your claim  Up on the rooftops Out of reach Trickster is meaningless Trickster is weak  He's talking out the world Talking out the world Hey, hey, hey, this is only halfway Hey, hey, hey, this is only halfway  I wanted you so bad That I couldn't say All these things fall apart  We wanted out so bad That we couldn't say These things fall apart  We're talking out the world Talking out the world Hey, hey, hey, this is only halfway Hey, hey, hey, this is only halfway  Truant kids A can of brick dust worms Who do not want to climb down from Their chestnut tree  Long white gloves Police check carefully Escaped from the zoo The perfect child facsimile is Talking out the world Talking out the world Hey, hey, hey Hey, hey, hey   -  The Condom Dance.  Think of somebody shaking and walking like they have a giant condom over the top half of their body.  Exactly.  -  I'm devistated, Ray Charles died yesterday.  -  School was slow but awfully interesting.  First period, just watched Regan's funeral the whole period.  Second was too boring to even bother explaining.  Third, took an extremely easy quiz, and did more genetics stuff.  Fourth is where I saw something I never expected to see.  Kasey in pantyhose and other womens clothing.  It was so fucking hilarious, and Sarah even got a picture!  Fifth, watched more of "The 60's".  Sixth, free work period.  -  Will post later, maybe. 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Lust for Life - Iggy Pop  Here comes Johnny Yen again With the liquor and drugs And the flesh machine He's gonna do another strip tease. Hey man, where'd ya get that lotion? I've been hurting since i've bought the gimmick About something called love Yeah, something called love. Well, that's like hypnotizing chickens.  Well, I'm just a modern guy Of course, i've had it in the ear before I have a lust for life 'cause of a lust for life  I'm worth a million in prizes With my torture film Drive a GTO Wear a uniform All on a government loan I'm worth a million in prizes Yeah, I'm through with sleeping on the sidewalk No more beating my brains No more beating my brains With liquor and drugs With liquor and drugs.  -  Starlight Parade was a blast.  Rain made it even better.  Best parade I've ever been in.  First off, I get there a little early, but I got to miss a bit of the practicing due to something with my uniform.  Next, this simple, easy busride.  Listened to some tunes.  Arrived in downtown portland (we parked in front of a porno arcade) and walked to our warmup spot.  Where we waited.  We were supposed to have waited for about a half an hour.  That half an hour turned into an hour, and then an hour and a half.  All fine with me, I just talked with people, had some fun.  When the parade actually got going, I saw my parents came!  I'm like, "No way!  They actually made it to a parade!!".  Definately cool.  Parade starts for us, so, of course, it starts raining.  Rain felt very, very, very good.  It was great.  The whole parade just went well.  Bus ride kinda sucked, I was crammed in with a bunch of people.  -  I'll post later.
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Dancing with Myself - Billy Idol  On the floors of Tokyo  Down in London town's a go-go  With the record selection  And the mirror's reflection  I'm a-dancing with myself   Oh, when there's no one else in sight  In the crowded, lonely night  Well, I wait so long for my love vibration  And I'm dancing with myself   Oh, oh, oh dancing with myself  Oh, oh, oh dancing with myself  Well there's nothing to lose  And there's nothing to prove  And I'm dancing with myself   If I looked all over the world  And there's every type of girl  But your empty eyes seem to pass me by  And leave me dancing with myself   So let's sink another drink  'Cause it'll give me time to think  If I had a chance, I'd ask one to dance  And I'd be dancing with myself  -  I've been in such a poor mood.  For all of you who tried to make me talk about it, I appreciate that you care, and I'll talk about it later.  -  For everyone else who decided to act like a total fucking asshole to me, don't be the least bit surprized if you wake up with a pitchfork in your chest and a horsehead in bed.  And you wish I was fucking kidding.  -  I haven't slept in two days.  Well, that was the case untill I got a four hour nap, which sucked.  -  This stupid migrane keeps coming back, and I had to indure marching practice with that.  Okay, if you don't think thats a big deal, imagine you're trying to pay attention to your rank in the hot, hot sun, with Dr. Beat beeping it's infernal death cry, Julie being super bitch (which is redundant to say.), no food or water, no sleep in two days, and you've got a fucking migrane to deal with.  Yeah, sleep was glorious after that, even if it was only four hours.  -  A good midnight snack.  Make a quesadilla (for those of you who don't know what that is, it's cheese melted in a tortilla) and put pepperoni's in them.  Oh, it's fucking good.  -  A lot of people in my house could tell there was something wrong with me, because I was eating marshmellows, my comfort food.  Anyone who's seen I Am Sam, remember when Michelle Phifer was chowing down, thats exactly what I look like.  -  I'm gonna try for some more sleep.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "My goal in life is to harm you.  Severely.  Come here."  -   Listening to:  I Don't Want to Miss a Thing - Aerosmith   could stay awake just to hear you breathing Watch you smile while you are sleeping While you're far away dreaming I could spend my life in this sweet surrender I could stay lost in this moment forever Every moment spent with you is a moment i treasure  Don't want to close my eyes I don't want to fall asleep Cause i'd miss you baby And i don't want to miss a thing Cause even when i dream of you The sweetest dream will never do I'd still miss you baby And i don't want to miss a thing  Lying close to you feeling your heart beating And i'm wondering what you're dreaming Wondering if it's me you're seeing Then i kiss your eyes And thank god we're together I just want to stay with you in this moment forever Forever and ever  Don't want to close my eyes I don't want to fall asleep  could stay awake just to hear you breathing Watch you smile while you are sleeping While you're far away dreaming I could spend my life in this sweet surrender I could stay lost in this moment forever Every moment spent with you is a moment i treasure  Don't want to close my eyes I don't want to fall asleep Cause i'd miss you baby And i don't want to miss a thing Cause even when i dream of you The sweetest dream will never do I'd still miss you baby And i don't want to miss a thing  Lying close to you feeling your heart beating And i'm wondering what you're dreaming Wondering if it's me you're seeing Then i kiss your eyes And thank god we're together I just want to stay with you in this moment forever Forever and ever  I don't want to miss one smile I don't want to miss one kiss I just want to be with you Right here with you, just like this I just want to hold you close Feel your heart so close to mine And just stay here in this moment For all the rest of time  -  Well, fuck, where to start.  -  Well, for those of you who haven't heard my rather colourful story about Friday night, it was quite a tale.  Well, no, not really.  Basically, my parents and others got really drunk, so this South African chick named Michelline and I went out back, talked for about four hours, and ended up making out (Cha-fucking-ching!).  Then I attempted to actually drink a whole beer.  I still can't fucking do it.  I'm fucking Canadian, and I can't do it.  Then again, I need a good import if I expect to down one.  -  I was flipping through channels the other day, and noticed that the Hallmark channel had been showing Westerns.  I'm like "WTF?!  I've been missing this?!"  I mean, damn, you wanna talk about a good genre of movies, look over at Eastwood, Autrey, and hell, Jack Nickleson did one.  -  I saw the Bourne Identety the other day.  Now that's an action movie.  Whew!  -  I love the 90's rocks.  Except it's made me download "Can't touch this".  Oh, shit.  It's hammer time...  -  My drive test is on THURSDAY.  Fuck, I'm soo not ready.  -  Life is a 24 cube of Mountain Dew, waiting for you in the fridge.  -  To whoever hasn't played Prince Of Persia -  WTF is wrong with you?!  -  I relapsed and ate tuna on Friday.  -  Who knew Ice Cube could act?  Shit.  -  Aerosmith, like the 'Stones, will never, EVER, die.  -  Spent lighters are disapointing.  You try for about five minutes to get it lighted (and see the magical fire they show within), only to be crushed by the lack of fuel...  -  Sleeeeepy time.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Hey Boy (feat. Swing Fly) - Teddybears Sthlm  Who's the bum cuzzin' along in your hi fi Stackin' do hittin' the bong, it's the Swing Fly Teddybear sound is the bomb and you know why None of this ill can be wrong and the beat's thight  Hey boy, get your rocks off, move boy, we put the clock on you boy You can't miss, my friend you get knocked down, get up again  You can smell some of the funk when we breeze by We got nuff shit to go round, hit the peace pipe We can do the dunkedy-dunk, and it's all night Yeah baby the dunkedy-dunk and it's all thight  Hey boy, get your rocks off, move boy, we put the clock on you boy You can't miss, my friend you get knocked down, get up again  All we came to do is raise hell and just have fun You can take the skinny girl, cos I want the fat one You better raise the base, leave the treble on plus 1 Can you put me on the guest list - 20 girls plus 1  Hey boy, get your rocks off, move boy, we put the clock on you boy You can't miss, my friend you get knocked down, get up again  I have a lot of problems, but I'm here to discuss one Well pass another bottle cos I won't settle for just one Get ready for the chourus, cos I'm just about done Get ready for the du, the du, come on  Hey boy, get your rocks off, move boy, we put the clock on you boy You can't miss, my friend you get knocked down, get up again  T.E.D.D.Y. yo, the bears are here and this is Swing Fly T.E.D.D.Y. yo, the bears are here and this is Swing Fly   -  Behold!  The Blog is reborn!  Yeah, they really overhauled the features.  So, yeah, I took off the chatterbox for awhile, it was starting to frighten me.  I did, however, notice that they allow comments now, so comment away!  -  Does my profile pick make me look high?  -  Well, I'm done updating, I need to try and sleep.    Seacrest, out.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Beautiful Car.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What day is it now?  -  Listening to: Band on the Run - Paul McCartney and Wings  Stuck inside these four walls, sent inside forever, Never seeing no one nice again like you, Mama you, mama you. If i ever get out of here, Thought of giving it all away To a registered charity. All i need is a pint a day If i ever get out of here.  Well, the rain exploded with a mighty crash as we fell into the sun, And the first one said to the second one there i hope you're having fun. Band on the run, band on the run. And the jailer man and sailor sam were searching every one  For the band on the run  Well, the undertaker drew a heavy sigh seeing no one else had come,  And a bell was ringing in the village square for the rabbits on the run. Band on the run, band on the run. And the jailer man and sailor sam, were searching every one  For the band on the run, band on the run, band on the run, band on the run  Well, the night was falling as the desert world began to settle down. In the town they're searching for us every where, but we never will be found. Band on the run, band on the run  And the county judge, who held a grudge Will search for evermore For the band on the run  -  Dear God, I'm gonna crack.  Summer school moves so slowly.  I cannot stand it.  It's so easy, it's basically an A and time to read Dracula for $110.  -  I failed my written today.  They ask really mean questions.  I mean, seriously, how many people know that a bicycle's headlight has to be seen 500 feet away?  Exactly.  -  We got an insurance quote.  Lower than I expected, but still insanely high.  So I'm taking this "Steer Clear" program to recieve a safe driver discount.  Easy and boring.  -  I am so bored around the house.  Seriously, I'm playing through all of my videogames again.  I even pulled out my N64!  Somebody call me or something!  -  I went to that Fleetwood Mac concert on Monday.  Rocked!  -  I'm noticing just about every song I create sounds like the others.  Dear God, I'm turning into the Offspring before I even have a band!  -  I noticed that summer school is the only way I get up in the morning.  Still don't want to go.  -  I fell asleep at seven last night.  SEVEN.  Actually, it's because I fell asleep at seven the night before that.  Only the former was PM and the latter was AM.  I fell asleep because I was studying for my written.  Go figure.  I actually slept twelve hours, though, which felt good.  -  That five speed's a killer, but I'm finally getting good at starting and stopping with that clutch.  I'm almost ready for the street.  -  It's great, when we were getting my quote at the insurance office, the woman asked for my birthday, and it actually took me a bit to remember.  -  Watch Arrested Developement.  It is the greatest show I've seen in a long time.  -  I've recieved calls from about four different area codes outside my own.  That's creepy.  Well, then again, I did post my number.  Who cares, I don't answer a number I don't recognize.  -  I miss my CD's ::cough cough jessie cough cough::.  -  My watch decided to lose another link, so now I'm watchless.  I feel so naked.  -  My shades broke too!  -  When a younger sibling goes out more than you do, there is something wrong.  -  Why the HELL doesn't Heritage have a freakin' pop machine?!  I NEED MY CAFFEINE IN THE MORNING! THEY CAN'T TAKE THAT FROM ME!  ANYTHING BUT THAT!  -  I wish I could have the house to myself once and awhile.  I wanna crank my music up without annoying anyone and having them retaliate with some crappy modern country song.  You know, ME time.  -  When you're bored, movie channels become your friend.  I've seen so many more movies by just turning it on.  Plus a few channels have long running sets of movies.  Stuff like that.  Good stuff.  -  My alarm's a bitch.  -   We had to write an essay about someone in summer school.  I chose my thesis about how SOMEONE (Not naming any names, because you know who you are) is EXTREMELY lazy, and how they passed up that concert for some more goddamn sleep time!  -  When I was taking my written test, the guy asked me if I was an identical twin.  I jokingly said yes, and he actually wrote it down.  I don't think he was very happy with me when he had to go through this long system of erasing shit.  -  I was playing Pandora Tomorrow online the other day.  I have so much fun grabbing the Mercs and whispering in their ears.  I'm much more entertaining than those stupid fucking Chapelle quoting guys ("I'm Rick James, bitch".  Fuckers.)  I say useful facts and such, like, for example.  ::jumps down and grabs Merc:: Me - "Did you know that a person can die from being shot in a limb due to the shock of bullet entry?" Him - "No, I didn't.  That's actually pretty intere- ::knocks out Merc::  ---  ::grabs him again later:: Me - "Did you know crashing your car at 25 miles per hour has the force of landing, face-first, on the ground after jumping off of a three story building?" Him - "....Actually, I think I've heard that somewhere bef- ::knocks him out::  ---  ::grabs him again:: Me - "Yo, did you kno- Him - "Just knock me out!" Me - "Hazaa!" ::knocks him out::  ---  Sometimes I just get bored and feel like listening.  ::grabs him again:: ::Drags him in a shadowed corner:: Me - "So, how have you been?" Him - "I'm a twenty-two year old who lives in his mother's basement." Me - "You lie, so, watch any good movi- ::gets shot by a taser:: Me - "Argh, you fucker!" Him - "You were getting on my nerves." Me - "Once I get feeling back in my legs, you're dea- ::gets shot in the head:: ::respawns:: Me - "Now what the hell was that for?!" Partner - "I've got him." Me - "Really.  Ask him how he's been.  He wouldn't tell me." Partner - "He say's he lives in his mother's basement." Me - "He lies, knock him out." Partner - "Dammit!  He hit me with a taser!" Me - "He's in for a big surprize, I'm right behind hi- FUCK!" Partner - "What?!" Me - "His partner just bashed me!"  eah, that's how it usual goes.  Those assholes, all I wanted was some friendly conversation!  -  Double the listening, eh?: Vera - Pink Floyd  Does anybody here remember Vera Lynn? Remember how she said, That we would meet again, Some sunny day.  Vera! Vera! What has become of you? Does anybody else in here feel the way I do?   Yeah, that one's a short one.  -  Nintendo's new portable looks very neato.  Probably the last system I'll end up buying.  -  Check out bash.org.  Not only is it a good way to kill time, but it's hella funny.  -  I need help.  Who is the last band they show on that new "iPod your BMW" commercial.  The one with three people, two guys and a girl, and the guy in the middle has a skeleton glove.  I MUST KNOW.  -  My room is so Goddamn hot!  The air conditioning is on, the windows and blinds are closed, the fan is on, but the room will not cool down!  -  I was in the kitchen, and I took a drink out of a can of Mountain Dew, and it somehow missed my mouth.  You know how it is.  My dad looked over and said you have a real drinking problem.  Heh.  -  WTF?  What the hell happened to my Bjrk?!  For some reason, my computer recorded Jason and I talking while we were ripping his Bjrk album.  And I pronounced "Tupac" like "Two Pack".  Yeah, that was a loooong time ago.  We sound like idiots talking.  -  I guess I should be doing my Am. Lit. homework.  SHOULD is the key word.  -  I'm considering getting another Game Pass from blockbuster.  I did it last summer and I once the year before that.  It used to be really cool, because you could rent two games at a time, but now they cut one of them off.  Still pretty good, except I can sometimes take my time with games.  Or maybe that Movie Pass, it's cheaper.  Then again, I don't want to drag my sorry ass up there all the time.  Besides that, Blockbuster hates me ever since I did what Seanbaby did and rented every game on the shelves and hung about the store doing odd things, like staring at posters for 15 minutes at a time.  Or returning the tree's worth of recepts the gave me.  Or going there close to closing time and then taking a long, long time.  They wouldn't bother me, because I looked absolutly mental when I did it.  Just stupid things.  -  I hate being at home when I'm bored because if I sneak out there's nowhere to go.  I live about three miles from everything except Jason's house.  It's better when I'm staying at my Grandparents' house, because then I can bother people, go to stores, eat and stuff.  Plus, it's getting harder to sneak out of my house, my mom keeps falling asleep on the couch.  I once used the emergancy fire ladder on my balcony to get out.  I get desperate when I'm bored.  -  Why doesn't some channel do something nice to insomniacs and put stuff other than infomercials on at night.  I'm up at three in the morning with nothing to watch except that damn toaster oven that you can "Set it and forget it!".  Even that Girl's Gone Wild infomercial got boring for me.    I'm losing it.  -  I drank a whole carton of soy milk.  That stuff is pretty damn good.  -  And to my friends that play Tactics Advance:  I GOT AN ASSASSIN!  AND THE NOSADA, BABY!  Wow, assassis haas two "ass"'s in it.  Wait, I'm sure thats not right.  -  Wow, hella long post.  I've finally run out of things to say.  I leave you with a thought.  Tired of stupid people?  I am.  We should just remove all of the safety and warning lables off of things and just let the problem work itself out.
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: TNT - AC/DC  See me ride out of the sunsetOn your colour TV screenOut for all that I can getIf you know what I meanWomen to the left of meAnd women to the rightAin't got no gunAin't got no knifeDon't you start no fight  'Cause I'm T.N.T. I'm dynamiteT.N.T. and I'll win the fightT.N.T. I'm a power loadT.N.T. watch me explodeI'm dirty, mean and mighty uncleanI'm a wanted manPublic enemy number oneUnderstandSo lock up your daughterLock up your wifeLock up your back doorAnd run for your lifeThe man is back in townDon't you mess me 'round'Cause I'm TNTOi Oi OiTNTOi Oi OiTNTOI OI OITNTOI! OI! OI!  -  ::looks around::  Did they score a goal or something?  -  Yeah, sorry about the long delay of posts.  I had to wait for interesting things to accumulate.  That, and I'm lazy.  -  94.7 finally got good again.  -  I was getting some sexy shades at G.I.Joes, and I found out Erin works there.  To Erin:  I saw your car.  It is hot.  -  I went to McDonalds for breakfast this morning, and I go in there after the rush, and it was completely filled with "old people!"  I exlaimed.  Out loud.  -  Stairway to Heaven gets hard when you attempt to play it correctly.  -  When McGillivray was getting sealed up, people were stuck in their homes.  I went to my grandparents' house (on McGillivray) and visited for awhile (Early in the morning).  They kept wanting me to help out with stuff, and I came to the slow relalization that they were attempting to trap me with them.  Crafty old people.  -  Those damn SNEAKER PIMPS!  -  Car's battery cable was loose.  I was scared I ran the battery dead.  -  I cry to everyone:  GET ME OUT OF THE HOUSE!!  -  My cousin's wedding tomorrow.  I am so excited!  I love weddings!  And remember, I like GIRLS.  Please try to remember that.  -  I watched bunches of movies.  Donnie Darko - Very enjoyable, however it is hard to decipher without the website.  Regardless, it makes you think.  Full Metal Jacket - My favourite Stanley Kubrick film now.  Very, very intense.  Bubba Ho-Tep - Woo-hoo!  25th Hour - Need to re-watch, kind of drifted off during it.  Mystic River - Better than I expected.  Worth seeing.  Open Range - Good western.  Good, good.  The Doors - Long, but tolerable.  True Romance - Brad Pitt has a very convincing stoner role in that.  Saving Private Ryan - I will never tire of this movie.  The Professional - Hehe.......  Taxi Driver - Damn...  -  I finally got a chance to play through Call of Duty.  Now THERE is an intense game.  Holy crap.  -  I'm watching this infomercial about Ronco Knives.  I have seen it four times.  I am praying something will be different and the old guy will cut his finger off.   Yep, that's what it's getting to now, folks.  -  !!!  I was able to go over to Felix's house and not throw up!  Maybe those days are over!  -  Can you believe Rick James is gone?  Damn.  I hope nobody does the Chapelle impression of him at the funeral.  Damn.  -  Why the HELL do I enjoy Maroon 5?!  I SHOULDN'T, but I do!!  ::weeps::  -  Ice-cream is the fixer of any bad emotion.  It's truely amazing.  -  I still can't drive my 5-speed.  Still!  Christ!  -  I've been putting in applications everywhere.  Now let's hope Brian get's a job!  -  To Brionna:  Why do you enjoy TORTURING me so much!?  One day, I'm going to get you back.  -  Jason and I have had this parody RPG in the works for what, two years?  We keep forgetting about it.  We've now decided to ditch RPG toolkit, and turn it into a picture book.  You will be amazed by the vocal stylings of DJ Krackley. 
    
</post>


</Blog>