<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       &nbsp;I invited Thomas over yesterday to help me clean out the part of the garage that's going to be my room by the end of the summer, and he did indeed come over. We moved many heavy and sharp objects and played air hockey, and watched "Lord of the Dance." I swear, there were tears of joy in Thomas' eyes that joyous day. I must agree with Thomas, his legs DO move independantly from his body! *glee* .. After Thomas left yesterday I babysat Oliver and he drove me insane [short trip] hah i love puns. okay, im going to stop using punctuation because im lazy and its hurting my fingers. pooey. nothing at all exciting happened yesterday after thomas left, i read. for  hours , just like the last two nights or so. im reading "The Last Herald-Mage" series by Mercedes Lackey, a wonderful author whos books everyone should read. they are SO good.&nbsp; anyways, on to today. i got out of bed at about 10:50 am [obviously], and went to have a bath. that bath lasted until 2:45pm. i swear, i was a bloody prune, but it was worth it. i havent felt this clean and relaxed in months. unfortunately, i forgot the effect hot water has on my hair at the moment (its still dyed) and i accidentally made the ledge of my bathtub blue. *woops my bad* sigh..&nbsp; oh well could be worse right? then i drained the tub and had a nice hot and then cold shower. it felt sooo good. anywho.. uh oh yeah. lots of the colour came out of my hair, but now it looks more blue than it did before. i guess it was more a teal-bluey green before, its lighter now but the blue is more evident anyways. mmm my mum just got back ffrom getting oliver from daycare, and she bought her and i mcdicks triple thick shakes.. mmm. chocolate. weee.. im going to go see The Village tonight with steven, and most likely chris [forman] whoever he is, because i dont know, and uuh. damn. i think jesse and possibly this kid named.. mark! thats the one. yegawds im horrible with names. well i gotta jet, the brat is screaming and im going to go do something about that. ta-ta dahlings!  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       well today i did absolutely nothing. i drank pop, craved chocolate, comtemplated eating mcdicks then didnt, watched people build my porch, and spend three hours downloading music onto my parents computer only to find that my dad took out the cd burner to put into  MY  computer! but my computer is as of yet not hooked up... *je ne vas pas jurer, je ne vas pas jurer..&nbsp;* damn it im really hungry and i really am craving chocolate.. sigh. i want to hang out tomorow, but the person i REALLY want to hang out with lives too damned many provinces away at the moment. :'(&nbsp; boohoo.well, just one more year. thanks to aaron (lambert) i now am obsessed with bikini kill, the voids and the devotchkas. thanks to a kid i knew over a year ago, ive been listening to the clash, sex pistols, dead kennedys and the buzzcocks and am thoroughly into punk. minus the pop. no pop. i need some new shoes.. oops gotta go, someones at the door!  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       That girl thinks she’s the queen of the neighborhood   She’s got the hottest trike in town  That girl she holds her head up so high
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        well hello readers of blog-opia. yes faithii, im blogging surprise! heh.. not very often though, because my summer isnt so very eventful. ive been at taylors house the last week, and i just got home today.. on thursday night i dyed my hair blonde so that the blue i put in after would stay and look better. one half of my head is teal-blue, the other half green-blue. im happy to be home, nothin like sleeping in your bed in your own room with your own cd player with kick ass music like Out Of Your Mouth playing! *drooool* i looove that band. steven the padleyster is telling me what songs to download, i hope i still have winmx. 0.0 sigh. i think this summer is addicting me to pop.. i love pop. root beer, pepsi, anything but coke..thomas, andrew and amanda, thanks for stopping by my house even though i wasnt there, my mum told me when i got home today, thank you! it made me feel so non-forgotten... on that tangent, weve all got to hang out!&nbsp; ^__^ well thats about it, i cant think of anything else.. so ta-ta for now!     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        la dee dee da leee laaa.. today i went into town [courtney] with tay and her friends alesha and jasmin who are very funny if overly psycho. but anyways, it was lots of fun. we walked around, made noise, i bought tay an un-birthday present, ($14!)&nbsp; i drank lots of pop and ate cookies and we hacked a bit and i bought some hair stuff but i gotta fix my hair first so yeah. when we got back we were pretty tired so i layed down but tay fixed up her hack and hacked a bit. we ate dinner and took into (tays dog) down to the ocean for a walk and we got really soaked in the hing of water when we tried to make a bridge and succeeded. it was fun. i found a 'private property no tresspassing sign', taylor tried to break a branch and managed, but not before it smacked her and made her bleed her own blood, like when i fell on a small prickly shrub thing earlier today when i climbed down a wall. anywho... uh. thats about it bec ause it was fun and my memory blurs it all together and i suck at typing. im about to be really mad at the computer.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         wowie. ho humm.. well i just read a couple of the comments on my site.. interesting, to say the least. heh. i suppose i needn't say that i havent posted here in a long while, seeing as its obvious. i stopped going on the computer just a little while before exams in june, and this is the first time ive spent more than ten minutes on the computer in a really long while. lets recap.. the main things are i passed all my classes, (note that im not telling any of this in chronological order) billoted a very quiet scottish rugby player at my house for three days named David who thought i was boring.. poor child. uuh went to a BC lions game, climbed a tree in front of the train/bus station in vancouver. met a "stick connoiseur" with my comrades jamie and cayle, hacked on a sky train, went camping, went swimming, bridge diving, 'played' (?) improv on an ampitheatre stage and hacked alot more. ran through a forest and around vancouver. drank ALOT of pop, and really didnt swear all that much. played rugby one day, two games and got harsh burnt. made money, spent money, made ridiculous comments, watched bloopers, cleaned and organized and re-arranged my room.. yeah, so sums up the things that stand out in my mind right now. talked to thomas for a while today on the phone.. i miss my friends!!!! :sigh: oh well. by septembermy room willbe in the garage because thats where i want it and i get to paint the floor and walls and its gonna be crazy! when i get back from vancouver island, im inviting people here for a bbq! movie nights, theyre at your house thomas!! haha.. yeah. well, i think thats all for now folks, ill try to be more regular in updates, but summer is more fun than blogging. so ta-ta!     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       so i dont remember much of the last four days in any particular order, so im just gonna say what i remember the most and it will most likwly be inorder. so i went to value village with my mum while i was babysitting my neighours offspring and i got some shirts and stuff and i wanted to see this watch that was in the showcase, so the lady called someone up, and of all people it was josh hyde. so we talked abit, and i called him the next day i think and we went out for coffee, but i just had a jones soda, and we walked to " a cup of italy" by the memorial park plaze, or rather, the gazebo, and we hung out witha couple of people there, i didnt know them. i went to take the bus home, i got home at 10:35 or so, about half an hour past curfew, stupid busses. taylor came over on thursday, coincidentally when i posted last, she was there. she spent the night at my place uh i think friday and saturday night, and she went home today.  we went to playland yesterday, it was good but it was kinda boring because weve pretty much conquered every noteworthy ride there, and even the drop zone isnt as much of a thrill as it used to be. (yesterday was my sixth time on the drop zone). i hung out with josh yesterday, i gave him a call and i went down to his place and we sat and talked while we waited for his clothes to dry. then he walked me to haney place for the bus after buying me a drink from a nearby corner store. ooh i skipped stuff. sunday was my grandmas birthday party and there was good food and cake. monday as in yesterday was her actual  birthday, 65th, tay and i went to playland. dad picked us up and took us to the grandpeoples house, and they took us to the frogstone grill. dinner was sssooooooooooooooooo soo good. i had a hawaiin pizza to myself, then i had this really big peice of chocolate truffle cake with this really yummy bavarian type cream on the inside. oh man. yyuummmy. and today i suntanned for three hours, after getting out of bed at 12:30 or so. heh. my grandparents came over and now here i am. bye bye  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so my computers being an idiot, and the internet has been on and off at my place for the last two days. but on to more trivial matters. ah-ha. i went to value village on wednesday, yes i am a poor bum, and i got a bunch of shirts. i then went home and whatever i did i dont remember.  uh yesterday being thursday, i only left the house once, around 8pm to go for a walk. i did nothing other than draw after that. i actually drew a picture that i really liked to. the drawing was of a girl and actually looked somewhat real. yay me. today i uh woke up and laid in bed until 11 because im excrutiatingly lazy. so i got up, showered and went to lunch with mine cousine and mine grandma to the austin fish and chips place. you know, i speak good. haHAhaHAaaaa. "I'm gonna get ya with mah floppy wrist!" .... "You suck big time!" fuck you. shut up. sorry. blah. blha im going now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        um yesterday i went to thomas' house and we left to go rent a movie and we rented dreamcatcher and the whole nine yards. we took the movies to julias house and ended up only watching dreamcatcher, which was really good. thomas had to leave for his house, his grandmas 85th, so he came back at ten to ten when he SAID he would be back at quarter after nine! the fool. late. tar-D! so we never watched the second movie. weve got them for a week though, so weve got an excuse to hang out again. uuh. so yeah, dad picked me up at sometime before 11. so yeah. thats really all, 'cept i got home after, surprise, and i think i went to bed right away. i may have read. i couldnt go on the computer, so meh. yeah im babysitting today from 1:30-5pm, just my luck. anywho, im off. anything new to post, ill do that.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>