<Blog>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well this is my first post here today. At the moment, I'm a little busy with work and all so I really should get back to that, but before I go let me just say that I'm really excited about this blog thing, and you should check back through out the day for updates. I should be going now.   CONGRATS to Chad and Deonne on their engagement!!!!!!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        This day has started out to be a day from hell. First off I hate to get up in the morning..period!!!!! I have to roll over and beat the fire out of the alarm clock at least 4 or 5 times each and every weekday morning. My husband can sleep through a tornado I believe.  He's such a hard person to wake up. If you've ever heard of a person that can take a shower with their eyes closed, it's me.. My eyes didn't seem to want to function properly so I just kept them closed. Good thing i know where things are at in the shower otherise I probably would have been washing up with my shaving cream. Ok, so after the shower comes the the ironing of the clothes. Since i'm such a lazy grouch at night, I put off this horrid task until the morning. I don't know why i do this, it's not like it going to be any better in the a.m than the p.m. The whole time keep in mind i am still yelling at my husband to get his skinny rump out of the bed so he won't be late for work. When i'm done with the clothes, and he hears me shut the door to the clothes room, he will drag himself out of the bed and hurriedly try to get to the bathroom  before i get in there and catch him still in bed.  Managing to crash into every piece of furniture we have in the bedroom, he finally makes it to the tub with a loud bump, alerting me that he hasn't had time to put his contacts in before he got in the tub.  I get dress and start on the unwanted task of drying my hair. No mousse or gel makes for some frizzy, nappy, fro-like folicles i call hair. Ok, skipping to the end, I am dessed and ready to roll out  when i remember tha ti dind't let the dog out...or so i thought. After what seemed like hours, i finally remember that i DID let the dog out, BUT forgot to close the garage door, thus, letting the varment escape into the neighborhood. (he's got a girlfriend..go figure). Ok, so i'm off to work and the members of the "i can't drive worth a damn club" have decided to have a meeting, making me a member of the "stuck in traffic club". So i turn up the jams and through the tears of anger and aggrivation, i manage to sing a tune along with the radio. Finally making it to work, i enter our office only to find that for some reason the heater isn't on and the place feels like the North Pole. In my imagination i picture many little eskimos running around. This place sucks! So now here I sit half frozen, waiting for the minute that i can go to lunch just to escape the fridgid innerds of this office. I hope yor day goes better! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WOW... What a fun weekend. Friday, Kevin and I went to the movies to see "50 First Dates". That movie was pretty funny. I like how Adam sandler has some of the same people in every movie that he makes. I think it makes it kinda interesting to see who is gonna play what part next. Anyway, before we went to the movie, we went to Schlotski's Deli and ate. I love that place.. So we went to the movie and went home.. Saturday, we went to get the oil changed in Kevin's truck then headed down to Louisiana. On the way we had to stop off by my mom's house to get their 4-wheeler, then we had to go to McComb and drop off a deposit at my mom's bank. We stayed Saturday night at my sisters house and Sunday Morning we got up and met Chad and Deonne in New Orleans at Loyola Drive McDonald's before going down to the parade route. We got down there and parked out trucks then headed up the  intersection of St. Charles and Julia to get out standing spot for the parade. Chad's Dad and step mom and some more of chad's family stayed at the intersection to kinda keep our spot. The 4 of us (Kev, me, chad, deonne) headed down St. Charles on foot in pursuit of Bourbon St.. What an interesting walk.  We went about half way down Bourbon St. And then came back up so we wouldn't get caught by the barricades blocking Canal St.. Once NOPD closes the street... there's no crossing..  So anywho we made it back to our spot and waited....and waited... and waited... and waited.. Meanwhile the sun is roasting my skin like I were a chicken in a 400 degree oven.  FINALLY the parade arrives. There were 2 parades in the same spot back to back, then a third about 2 hours later and then a fourth about another 4 hours later. We hung around for the first 2 which was Okeanos and Thoth. Mid-City and Bacchus were the other 2 parades later that day. After we had out fill of the parade scene,Kevin and I struck out on foot, Bourbon St. bound and the others returned to their vehicles and headed home. I didn't eat anything but breakfast Sunday because I wanted to go to my favorite grub shack on Bourbon. Don Roger's original "Papa Joes" at Bourbon and Toulouse. We had a rather close view of Bourbon St.. The food at Papa Joe's is sooooo good. I recommend the Gumbo and the sloppy roast beef Po-boy and the bread pudding with whisky sauce(yum yum). Kevin and I had the same waiter that we had last time and the funny thing is, he remembered us. How weird! After we got out tummy's full of some good food, we decided to go walk about a little more then go home.  Ok, so here we are strolling down the street and all of a sudden what do I see.... some dummy with a SNAKE wrapped around his arm. Me being scared as hell of snakes, freaked out and said a few choice words amidst the hysterical giggles from Kevin. He walked me right in to that ON PURPOSE! What a punk. I wasn't the only one that had a few things to say...This older lady cursed that dude like there was no tomorrow.  After all that excitement we decided to turn around and head back toward the truck. We'd had enough of the Carnival season for one year. :) We made it back home around 10 or 10:15 Sunday night. Monday morning rolls around and I am in some kind of terrible pain. My sunburn hurt so bad, so I called in sick to work and sat at home with Noxzema on my face for most of the day. If you have never been to New Orleans during Carnival season, you really should go at least once. Mardi Gras is something that you will never forget.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heck yeah!! I am so glad it is finally friday. I have quite a weekend ahead of me. Today i have an appointment at 1:30 to get my hair cut. Then tonight i'm gonna rest cause tomorrow is gonna be F-U-N! Jody is comming to the house around 10. We are going to go to get our nails done and then go shopping. Kenny Chesney is comming to jackson TONIGHT and we are going to the concert tomorrow night at 7. He's bringing that hot aussie Keith Urban and Dierks Bently with him. Dierks looks like Monty, one of kevin's buddies from work. Any who.. I'm pretty excited about the concert. I hope this years concert is as fun as last years concert. We were able to get right up to the front and I got some AWESOME pictures. Kenny is such a cutie. Guess i am gonna go for now. Hopefully i'll post again before the concert but if i don't, I'll be back after with some great pictures. I'm Out--
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YO!  It's been quite some time since i been here. So much has been hapening and i don't know where to start. Let me pull out the old day planner and flip bak to March to see what went down...hmmmmm not much to talk about in the early part of the month.. ont he 26th which was t-dale's birthday i finally got to meet her boyfriend, which is not her ex-boyfriend...don't know what the deal is there...On the 31st i came in to work and started hurting like super bad. I worked about 30 minutes and then  went to the see Dr. Sheeley. He did some tests and mad a few phone calls and pulled some strings and i went to the RAD group for sonagram.. Turns out i had to have my gallbladder removed. i was in pre-op by 3pm the same day. It wasn't a life of death situation but Dr Voyles said he could do it that same day if i didn't wanna wait till the next week, so i said lets roll!!! I was hurting really really bad. I had to stay the night in the hospital cause my heart rate wouldn't come back up like it should have. Some of Kevin's Co-workers came by and brought me flowers and goodies.. Thanks Guys! I went home on April 1st and went back to work on the 5th. I'm feelin good as new! My sister and bro. in law's anniversary was on april 8th. On the 16th i struck out for Denver Colorado to stay with my folks out there for the weekend. My cousin Angie lives in Denver and we got to go up to Pikes peak with her and her soon to be Hubby. The trip was fun. That's about all that happened, worth talking about, in April. May however has been a busy month. Me, Heather and Ashley took momma to get a pedicure and a manicure for Mother's day. We had a ball. All of us had a manicure and a pedicure. After the beauty treatments we went over to Ruby Tuesday for some grub. We all ate kinda lite so we couls have Desert. A chocolate Tall cake!!! WOW.. that thing is a monster. All 4 of us ate on that thing and still didn't finishe it off.. Not far from being gone though. Mom and Heather and Ashley all left to go to the races and i went visiting. I went to see Ms. becky and Ms. Gwen and i went to Jody's House. I finally got home abuut 10pm only to find that my husband wasn't home yet.. He finall called about 10:30 or 11 to let me know that the was leaving the deer camp and hour from home where he and soem of his friends went riding early that morning.. Mothers day was a good day. Kevin and I got to see both of our Mothers that day. We went to Jean and Pop's around 1 or so and visited for a while then we went to Utica to check on a burning tree for Pop. After we put out the fire some we went to My parents house where fried fish and the fixins were waiting on us.. Yummy.. wWe hung out there for a while then came home. We were exhausted! T-dale's high school graduation was on the 11th. I can't believe she is already outta high school. Dakota had to go to the vet on the 13th. He got checked for heart worms,turns out he had no worms and in good health with the exception of a cold. :)  Kevin and I joined the Baptist health plex on the 14th. I am excited about going too. I need to loose a lot of weight. :(   Well last sunday, we decided we needed a new dishwasher so we  went to sears and got one. It wasn't in stock so we had to go back on Tuesday (yesterday) to get it.. The weather has been horrible for the past week and a half and yesterday was no exception.. It stormed for about 2 hours but luckily cleared up right before we went to get the dishwasher. I went to Ms. Glenda's to get a tarp just in case but turns out we didn't need it. Allison came with me when i left from there. She was in a M-O-O-D yesterday. They came to get her around 9ish. Nikki had a SR. banquet last night and allison didn't wanna go so i offered for her to go with me. Ain't I so nice ;) Kevin got the dishwasher installed and in working condition. I'm so proud of him. He did and excellent job. Reckon it's time to go. I'm Out--
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last time I posted it was friday may 21st. The day before the Kenny Chesney concert. Jody came to the house and we went and got our nails dont Saturday(22nd) morning then we went to the coliseum cause tam called and said that kenny and keith were laying out! How hot is that???  Any how when we got there they had already went in. We got to see Kenny a few times and Keith Urban a few times, but we saw Dierks Bently the most. He was such a nice person. He came out and signed autographs and took pictures with the people. I didn't have a single thing for him to sign so I let him sign the battery on my cell phone. He even brought his dog, Jake, out of the bus. What a pretty dog. Ok moving on, Jody and I went back to my house and gathered up some  things tht we needed and some clothes and went back to the coliseum. When it got tome to go to the concert we changed our clothes in her car. Good thing she has some very dark tinted windows :) We went in and had a pretty good time. Our seats were no where nearly as good as last years seats though!    Last saturday (memorial weekend) I went tubing on the river with my aunt and her crazy friends. That was an adventure. I lost my sun glasses and a flip-flop throughout the whole ordeal. My total loss was an estimated 5 bucks, 4 for the flip-flops and 1 for the shades I bought at the dollar tree. Sunday I went to my parents for a lil while to visit before they went on vacation. Their anniversary is monday i think. My sister went and got them a cookie cake and we ate it. I love being at my parents house. After I left there I went to Hammond to see Mandi and the kids. I stayed the night and got up and went to her moms with her to eat. After we got back to the hotel from Ms Cheryls i got my things and went to my sisters house.  When i got there she said that my folks were on the way there so i waited for them to get there before i went and got a snowball. Me and my sis and my mom went and got a snowball then went to the dollar store shoppin. Mom and dad needed some lil things for their camper, and the dollar store is the best place to get them. Any who ashley had a ball game at 7 and i stayed around to go to that. It was the first time i'd seen her play this year. I feel like a bad aunt but it's kinda hard to drive 2 hours watch and hour and a half ball game then drive 2 hours back home, Not to mention that gas prices are way over the top.  Well that pretty much sums up the last 2 weeks. Reckon I'ma go now....  I'm Out--  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey there! I gots me a puppy!!!! He's so cute. He's a Great Dane pup. His name is Brutus. It took us quite a few days to come to that decision. Kevin and I could NOT compromise on a name. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>