<Blog>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi!  It's time to make some changes around here.  So, as you see, here is my blog to keep you up to date.  Since 1999, this spot has been evolving into a news service reflecting independent, creative analysis of world events and trends with a focus on art in technology.   As the idea of  urlLink social networking  catches on, it becomes less important to maintain an anonymous online identity. It just seems nicer to be an individual first and an organization second.  I am partnering with several writers to continue bringing you a service worthy of the Urbanstar name.   While we are working in the background, please reveiw the first digital project from Sophie, age 3.  Find the following objects in the picture below:    3 kittys   9 dinosaurs   a turtle   2 jokers   4 bugs   2 cell phones   a little lamb   3 ducks   a panda bear    Click on the image to enlarge. Have fun.     urlLink       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today George W. Bush visited Concordia University in Mequon, WI.   urlLink Click here  for images from today's not-so-welcoming committee.   urlLink    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Things You Should Know (and Some Things You're Not Allowed to Know) About Virtual Voting    By J.R. Engeriser, Milwaukee Urban Star    Six months from now Americans will cast their votes in what some are calling the most important election of their lifetime.  With all of the critical issues involved this time around, and with all of the questions the 2000 presidential election left in our minds, you may be thinking, “someone had better darn well make sure that the right people end up in office this time”.  A new breed of machines manufactured by a private company called Diebold, Inc. is on the job.   You may be acquainted with Diebold machines from other things they do for you from day to day, such as spitting out cash from your checking account, or transporting that amazing plastic tube back and forth between you and the drive-thru pharmacist at Walgreens.  In November of this year, computerized Diebold machines and others like them will take over the collection and tallying of the votes of 50 million Americans.  The age of virtual voting is here.  Recently we had the opportunity to interview DRE, a Diebold voting machine.    STAR:  Please tell us a little about how electronic voting machines will benefit voters.     DRE:  One of the benefits the machines will provide Americans is to rid them of obsolete voting systems. Who can forget the debacle of hanging chads in the  urlLink Florida 2000 recount ?  Diebold machines will not cause such problems because we do not work like punch-card systems.  In fact, beyond our on-screen interface, users are not allowed to know how we work.  It is a trade secret.    STAR:  What would you say to people who feel the system of tallying votes in America should be an open book to us and that election officials should definitely have complete access?    DRE:   That’s a good question.  In reality, humans are no longer needed in connection with auditing and recounting because the machines are automatically executing these tasks as they operate! I would invite the critics to just sit back, relax, and let us do our job.  Computers don’t make mistakes, humans do.   STAR:  Haven't there been more than 20  urlLink documented problems with electronic voting  in 12 states over the last two years, in some cases resulting in the wrong candidate being picked by the machine as the winner?   DRE:   Whether or not the wrong candidate was picked is a matter of opinion.  I happen to like the candidates that were picked! (smiles)   STAR:   That brings up my next question. In an invitation to a Republican fund-raiser last year, Walden O'Dell, the CEO of Diebold said he was "committed to helping Ohio deliver its electoral votes for the president next year." Do you think it is a disservice to American voters that the CEO of a company that makes voting machines has such close ties to the campaign to re-elect George W. Bush? ( urlLink more on this )   DRE:   Not anymore a disservice than when Katherine Harris acted as both Florida's Secretary of State in charge of elections and as chairperson of Bush's 2000 campaign in Florida. ( urlLink more on this )    STAR:   Why is it that an ATM can issue a paper receipt for a banking transaction, but an electronic voting machine cannot create any type of printed verification or paper trail? ( urlLink more on this )   DRE:   We can.  We just don’t want to.   STAR:   It would seem that, unless we start speaking out about what we want from electronic voting, the American people are stuck with you the way you are.   DRE:   Bingo.   For more information on electronic voting and fraud visit Bev Haris's site,  urlLink Black Box Voting .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Since the  urlLink Google link to this article  has been overloaded with traffic, we have reprinted the entire article here.     By Anwar Iqbal    WASHINGTON: US Secretary of State Colin Powell has admitted that the information he used in his UN Security Council address for justifying invasion of Iraq was false.   The admission, in a dramatic interview to NBC television, has assumed an added importance because of his aide's attempt to cut him off. Mr Powell, however, brushed off his deputy press secretary, Emily Miller, and went on to acknowledge that the CIA and other US agencies had received false information from their sources.   Mr Powell, who was in Jordan during the interview, was heard saying that NBC anchorman Tim Russert was "still asking me questions," to which a woman's voice answered, "No, he's not".   Mr Powell, still off camera, said: "Tim, I'm sorry, I lost you," and added: "Emily, get out of the way." Mr Russert, slightly irate, responded: "I think that was one of your staff, Mr Secretary. I don't think that's appropriate." After a few seconds the camera returned to Mr Powell and he finished the interview.   Mr Powell said the CIA and other US agencies were sometimes deliberately misled about alleged Iraqi weapons of mass destruction in the run-up to the war. The comments represented the first public admission from a senior US official that Washington had fed unchecked and unreliable information to the international community about Saddam Hussein's suspected arsenal of chemical and biological weapons.   "It turned out that the sourcing was inaccurate and wrong and, in some cases, deliberately misleading," Mr Powell said. "For that I am disappointed, and I regret it."   Mr Powell told the Security Council in Feb 2003 that the US administration had credible evidence that Iraq was making weapons of mass destruction. He insisted that the US government had "first-hand descriptions" of mobile biological weapons factories that he said presented a threat to international security.   Mr Powell disclosed that the information came from an Iraqi defector, a chemical engineer who supervised one of these mobile facilities, and corroborated by "other sources".   The speech, however, failed to persuade Security Council members to authorize the US-led military action against Iraq. But on Sunday, Mr Powell, acknowledged: "Unfortunately, that multiple sourcing over time has turned out to be not accurate. So I'm deeply disappointed."   The Iraqi defector in question has not been publicly identified. Mr Powell said he was "very concerned" about the fact that he was fed misleading information but insisted that this UN speech was based on "the best information that the CIA made available to me".  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        By J.R. Engeriser, Milwaukee Urban Star    Today The New Yorker released information connecting top-level U.S. officials, including Secretary of Defense Donald Rumsfeld, to a secret operation that "encouraged physical coercion and the sexual humiliation of Iraqi prisoners."  Known as Copper Green, among other code words, the Special-Access Program allowed for practices far more severe than Geneva Convention provisions, according to statements from intelligence officials in a report by Pulitzer Prize winning journalist Seymour M. Hersh.   The Special-Access Program was initiated in 2001 in the early stages of the hunt for al-Qaida in Afghanistan, and expanded by Rumsfeld to the Abu Ghraib prison in Baghdad last year. National security adviser, Condoleezza Rice, approved the program and President Bush knew of its existence.  The abuses that occurred under this operation received world attention earlier this month when photographs depicting physical and sexual mistreatment were leaked to the public.  According to the report, photographs were taken as part of the operation to scare prisoners into spying on associates for fear that the embarrassing images would be disseminated.   Similar pictures that were obtained by Rumsfeld and Pentagon officials in January via the Army’s Criminal Investigations Division went unreviewed because “they thought what was in there was permitted under the rules of engagement,” an intelligence source said.  Some more severe methods that were not specifically approved were encouraged and uncontrolled. “The rules are ‘Grab whom you must. Do what you want.’" said the source.  The information comes just six days after an Islamist website posted a video portraying the beheading of American businessman Nicholas Berg in retaliation of the abuses shown in leaked photographs.  Several GI’s face prison abuse charges in connection with the scandal, as the Bush administration has maintained that the incidents were the unapproved criminal actions of a handful of individuals.  The Pentagon has strongly denied the allegations released yesterday on the New Yorker website, labeling them "outlandish, conspiratorial, and filled with error and anonymous conjecture."  Recent statements from the Red Cross and family members of charged GI’s, however, support the implications that sources of abuse practices were further up the chain of command. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   For the love of Jehoshaphat I am so sick of hearing about Google's Gmail and not having an account.  You see, I've visited ZDNet where they have  urlLink Esther Dyson  practically peeing her pants about it every five minutes.  I've seen dozens of news articles, reviews, and  urlLink screenshots . I've checked eBay where you can actually  urlLink buy an invitation , which I considered doing until the bids went up to over 70 freakin' dollars per invite.  I have checked my  urlLink Blogger  dashboard again and again because we who are regular users are supposed to get invited.  I have expressed my interest in an account by filling out the  urlLink form on Google .  Hell, I even joined  urlLink Orkut  and participated in a Gmail survey. Do you think that any of this has gotten me closer to getting an account?  So enough of all of this buildup.  Here is my message to Google: Think of the poor saps who are getting soaked for 70 bucks a pop on eBay.  Think of young Yeroc who has offered up his birthright on  urlLink Gmailswap .  Think of the data clouds that will form and all of the "relevant text ads and links to related web pages of interest" that will be placed.  Most of all, think about how much it will piss off the State of California.  Come out of beta now Gmail!  Otherwise mail an invitation to gmailalready@urbanstar.com.  Thanks.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        By J.R. Engeriser    In times of terror and war, it might be nice to reflect back on the Gospels of Jesus for a little wisdom. He, undeniably, was an extremely bright individual and had great ideas. Non-Zionists, stay with me on this. Over the next little while I will be revisiting the Gospels and throwing out an occasional post that might even shake the hypocrisy out of a Bushite. The current administration here in “God’s country” isn't very  urlLink WWJD .  The Jesus people have stopped listening to their own guy.  As a mood setter, Jesus Flash #1 comes from Mark 2:23-28, where Jesus talks to the Pharisees. Pharisees were the religious leaders of Jesus’ time. They used the people’s respect for scripture to control and swindle.  urlLink Jesus slammed the Pharisees  whenever he had a chance.     [23] One sabbath he was going through the grainfields; and as they made their way his disciples began to pluck heads of grain.  [24] And the Pharisees said to him, "Look, why are they doing what is not lawful on the sabbath?"  [25] And he said to them, "Have you never read what David did, when he was in need and was hungry, he and those who were with him:  [26] how he entered the house of God, when Abi'athar was high priest, and ate the bread of the Presence, which it is not lawful for any but the priests to eat, and also gave it to those who were with him?"  [27] And he said to them, "The sabbath was made for man, not man for the sabbath;  [28] so the Son of man is lord even of the sabbath."    Sometimes you have to break the rules. After all, the rules are made for us, not us for the rules. Notice that David stole bread, not just any bread, but holy bread, because he and his associates were in need. And, it was okay by Jesus. Starving yourself for the sake of following rules did not make sense to Jesus, because at that point the rules would no longer serve, but hinder.   Jesus questioned authority and rules. How else were things going to change? Not by sitting idle. He rebelled and started a revolution.   In the 1930’s, a man named Joseph Rutherford, the leader of the Jehovah’s Witness movement at that time, declared, “Religion is a snare and a racket!” His followers would walk up and down the streets with placards around their necks advertising this slogan. He said "Religion is the worship and service of the Devil and his associate demons .... Religion is the chief means that puts fear into the minds of the people and leads them into the Devil's snare .... Truly then, as stated, 'religion is a snare and a racket,' employed to collect money from them under false representations."   Problem was, Rutherford, while saying these words, was starting a religion. It went downhill from there. But, he set out with the right idea. When religion does bad things to us, like start wars, break up families, or exploit our trust, it’s time to put the people running the show in the same category as the Pharisees. Jesus said  "Woe to you, scribes and Pharisees, hypocrites! for you are like whitewashed tombs, which outwardly appear beautiful, but within they are full of dead men's bones and all uncleanness."  -Matthew 23:27 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK. I don't have anything against Microsoft other than they are way too big. To my mind, they gained their power by building a better mousetrap and then selling it like PT Barnum. Yes, they became big bullies from their sheer size. But this is ridiculous. A patent on the double click????????? Next thing you know, somebody will try to patent flipping the bird. Maybe I should try. Every time some idiot tries to prove how cool they are by sticking their middle finger up, I get 5 cents. It's just a simple hand action for crying out loud. Doesn't the government have better things to worry about than this?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got back from seeing The Day After Tomorrow, so I figured I would post a quick review. A couple of weeks ago I received an e-mail saying the Bush administration didn't want people to see this movie. I see why. One of the first scenes in the movie is of an environmental conference where the Vice-President (a real close likeness of Mr. Cheney) said that global warming was overblown and the economy was the only thing that mattered. Sound familiar? We have all been handed the same line since the Reagan administration. As I'm sure most of you have seen in previews this movie is about a new ice age that comes up overnight (literally). Kind of a scary thought that it could happen like that.   On the whole I thought that the story was really heavy handed, but to make the point that our planet is so very fragile, the story has to be. It definitely scared me to think that everything can change overnight.  As for the usual movie stuff, the story was somewhat slow and not what was promised in previews. But when are they ever? The real draw here (besides the message), is the special effects. The scene of a wall of water 100 feet high descending on New York City was amazing. The acting was passable at best, not much in the way of emotions or depth, but this was not a movie you go to for great acting.   Overall, it was a decent movie with a good message but you could wait for video, that way you can skip the slow spots.  One little thing I did like is a minor character was an atheist like me. It was nice to see that put in there without being a putdown. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You're all invited to come with me to see Fahrenheit 9/11 on its opening day June 25th, unless we can get a sneak preview.     Michael Moore's documentary won the top prize at the Cannes Film Festival. It's the first time in nearly 50 years a documentary has won the Palme d’Or (the Golden Palm).  The film received a nearly 20 minute standing ovation at the festival.  Disney refused to let its subsidiary Mirimax release the film for political reasons, and it was thought that it would not be seen in the United States.  But now Moore has struck a deal with Lions Gate and IFC Films to release it on a record number of screens.  Since the website showing the film's  urlLink trailer  crashed from too much traffic, I have posted some video:   urlLink The Fish Rots From The Head Down   More resources available at  urlLink Michael Moore's Site 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Tim A wrote:  I live in the Riverwest community and am sure I could make some kind of contributions to your paper. Please let me know what direction you are going with this.    Here are a few facts about this project. We are a group of reality journalists stepping into new territory by establishing ourselves via a publicly accessible forum. Whereas most news organizations work behind the scenes, our day-to-day activity is publicly accessible on the World Wide Web.  You will see drafts, works in progress, and conversation amongst the staff. We have a journalist from Washington, three UWM students, a young lady who came from the Shepherd Express, and just some guys who work at Target.  Some of us are liberals and hate the Bush administration. But that is not a prerequisite.  Some of us are artists, mothers, photographers, or poets. The Star is evolving as we find our voice.  The result will be a publication circulated in Milwaukee, Wisconsin in print and worldwide on the Web. Each contributor is starting projects and posting what they wish of their progress for open discussion.  Contributions may be in writing on any subject or can take other media art forms.  Through public discourse we hope to find and speak truth.  At this time you must be asked by a current member of the Star to become a member of our forum.  Interested parties may submit a request to   Please include your name, city, and how you wish to participate.   Jim    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi all, I'm finally here. I see some familiar faces...now where is that loser Jason? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I would like to explore the relationship between the New York Times and the U. S. Central Intelligence Agency.  As I work on this, please contribute any comments regarding this topic.  Jim
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welcome to me! Thank you Jim and Joe for inviting me to participate.  I was the classified advertising manager for the "Metro Express" paper in 1999-2000. I am very excited to be involved with a new publication. Unlike my prior involvement with the "Metro" paper, I am sure that we will not be subject to a merger. The "Metro" paper merged with the "Shepherd". I would like to use this venue to explore my artwork, my commentary on today's political situation and ad sales. Thank you once again.   Mary Collen
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since the topic of Anarchy has been brought up, I have installed a radio station in streaming audio.  It features our archives of Noam Chomsky and Howard Zinn, who are Anarchists.  They are also two influential liberal voices.   urlLink Anarchy Radio    Reading   Here are two works by Anarchist authors from our archives:   urlLink Thomas Paine - The Age of Reason (1795) Part I    urlLink Part II    urlLink Henry David Thoreau - Walden (1854)   External Link:  urlLink Anarchist Archives   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a news story in progress.  -The definition of Acedemic Detail.  -Putting our schools to work saving taxpayers money.  -Health Care in Pennslyvania Example, High blood pressure medication cost savings.  -We need to get today's students involved with government if government is going to have a bright future.  -Why pay some corporation when you could get students to do it for free, we'll just pass it off as part of an education.  -Academic detail needs to persist at the very local level. Every school in this country should have involvement in our government from local, state to federal.  J D Brenny 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "No nation has ever benifited from a prolong war."  Sun Tzu --458 B.C.  -Scripting todays war with the historical context of the much celebrated, Art of War by Sun Tzu.   This is a news story in progress  J D Brenny 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a news story in progress.  -Agreeing with the evangelicals?  -Just when I was giving up hope in the political process  -So Why Bush?  -How many attacks can this country really take, I mean come on.  -How to prepare for anarchy, a lesson from the good old US ARMY SURVIVAL MANUEL.  -A call to fellow anarchists to get out the vote!!! endorse your president.  -Population Numbers and swing states. Do you know how many of us there are in Oregon, Idaho, Wyoming and Montana.  -Long Term Environmental Issues. Over Population effects.  -Rally against Kerry, A classic case of the means justifies the end.  -Finally a candidate that promotes good old fashion Darwinism.  J D Brenny
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jim  I need you to send an invitation to this blog to my brother @ c_brenny@yahoo.com My brother is a virtual wiz at computers and digs harder into the internet than anyone I know. He needs a blog.   Joe Brenny
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For the full report go to  urlLink http://publiclands.tu.org/pdf/TU_Oil_Gas_HI.pdf    FACT SHEET Gas and Oil Development on Western Public Lands  Impacts on Fish, Wildlife, Angling and Hunting  Trout Unlimited – through its Public Lands Initiative - produced this report to document the potential effects to fish and wildlife from energy development on millions of acres of public lands in the Rocky Mountain West. Currently, 32 million acres of public land is under lease for gas and oil development, translating into more than 110,000 permitted natural gas well, with more than 10,000 new wells approved by the Bureau of Land Management in the last three years.   Economic Impacts:   According to the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, there are 47 million hunters and anglers in America. In 2001, wildlife-associated recreation – which includes hunting, fishing, viewing, and other related activities – generated over $100 billion in economic activity, or roughly 1 percent of GDP.   The Rocky Mountain states of Montana, Wyoming, Utah, Colorado and New Mexico attract nearly 9 million people each year for wildlife and fish recreation, generating over $5 billion each year for those states’ economies.   Fisheries Impacts:   More than 15 percent of all trout habitat in Montana, Wyoming, Colorado, Utah and New Mexico falls within areas containing gas and oil reserves where production could occur.   Some 50 percent of Yellowstone cutthroat trout habitat, 40 percent of Bonneville and fine-spotted cutthroat trout habitat and 20 percent of Colorado River cutthroat trout habitat lies in areas targeted for production of gas and oil.  A study on Montana’s Tongue River, located in the Powder River basin, shows a dramatic decline – as high as 70 percent -- in mayflies, caddisflies, dragonflies, and other macroinvertabrates caused by discharges of polluted water from coal bed methane wells. When insects disappear, fish are soon to follow.   Big Game and Upland Bird Impacts:   27,000,000 acres, or 52 percent of Wyoming’s elk habitat falls within areas of potential gas and oil development.  9, 600,000 acres, or 30 percent of Colorado’s pronghorn antelope habitat falls within areas of potential gas and oil development.  3,000,000 acres, or 43.5 percent of Utah’s sage grouse habitat falls within areas of potential gas and oil development.   National Energy Policy: streamlined permitting process and compromised wildlife protections:   On millions of acres of prime fish and wildlife habitat throughout the Rockies, the government is issuing leases to gas and oil drillers before completing required plans to manage wildlife, fisheries and other public resources.  One of President Bush’s top domestic policy objectives is to open more public lands in the Rocky Mountain West to oil and gas development. In the spring of 2001, Vice President Dick Cheney's National Energy Policy Development Group recommended dropping wildlife protections in natural gas reserve areas. In the summer of 2003, the White House set up a special task force to reduce protections for wildlife and fisheries – referred to as “impediments to oil and gas development” in policy documents – to speed up energy extraction in seven wild basins across the West.   Portions of the National Energy Bill could codify the misguided wildlife policy that drastically reduces protections for wildlife, wild streams and fisheries on millions of acres in the seven western basins: the Powder River basin (MT, WY), the Upper Green River basin (WY), the Rocky Mountain Front (MT), the Roan Plateau (CO), the San Juan basin (CO, NM) the Valle Vidal (NM) and Otero Mesa (NM).    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is taken from the Geobacter.org website. There are accompanying publications available on the site. This is a news story of the century mark my words. (Joe Brenny on 6/1/04)  About Geobacter  Geobacter species are of interest because of their novel electron transfer capabilities, impact on the natural environment and their application to the bioremediation of contaminated environments and harvesting electricity from waste organic matter. The first Geobacter species (initially designated strain GS-15) was isolated from the Potomac River, just down stream from Washington D.C. in 1987. This organism, known as Geobacter metallireducens,   G. metallireducens  was the first organism found to oxidize organic compounds to carbon dioxide with iron oxides as the electron acceptor. In other words, Geobacter metallireducens gains its energy by using iron oxides (a rust-like mineral) in the same way that humans use oxygen. As outlined in the publication links, Geobacter metallireducens and other Geobacter species that have subsequently been isolated provide a model for important iron transformations on modern earth and may explain geological phenomena, such as the massive accumulation of magnetite in ancient iron formations.  Geobacter species are also of interest because of their role in environmental restoration. For example, Geobacter species can destroy petroleum contaminants in polluted groundwater by oxidizing these compounds to harmless carbon dioxide. As understanding of the functioning of Geobacter species has improved it has been possible to use this information to modify environmental conditions in order to accelerate the rate of contaminant degradation. As outlined under the Bioremediation link, Geobacter species are also useful for removing radioactive metal contaminants from groundwater.  Geobacter species also have the ability to transfer electrons on to the surface of electrodes. As outlined under the Microbial Fuel Cell link, this has made it possible to design novel microbial fuel cells which can efficiently convert waste organic matter to electricity.  As outlined under the Genomics and Systems Biology link, the genomes of several Geobacter species have been sequenced and are being incorporated into a computer model that can predict Geobacter metabolism under different environmental conditions. This systems biology approach is greatly accelerating the understanding of how Geobacter species function and the optimization of bioremediation and energy harvesting applications.  We have found that dissimilatory metal-reducing microorganisms, such as Geobacter and Rhodoferax species, have the novel ability to directly transfer electrons to the surface of electrodes. This had led to the construction of microbial fuel cells that are superior to previously described microbial fuel cells in that: 1) that are much more efficient; 2) they do not require the addition of the toxic electron shuttling mediator compounds employed in previously described microbial fuel cells; 3) they have remarkable long-term stability; and 4) it is possible to harvest electricity from many types of waste organic matter or renewable biomass. Immediate application of these microbial fuel cells will be for powering electronic monitoring devices in remote locations, such as the bottom of the ocean. However, many other applications are possible. Current research is focusing on elucidating the mechanisms of electron transfer between the microorganisms and the electrode in order to design better electrodes or genetically engineer better microbes for higher rates of electricity production. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      With all the talk this week about Reagan dying, Thursday came the news of someone that really affected my life in a positive way. Ray Charles was one the great musicians of all time.  And, I, for one will miss his voice. I can't think of too many people that have had such an influence on popular music in the last 50 years. In my mind the only thing greater than his music is that he never let his blindness be a factor to slow down his life. It was more of an inconvenience to him rather than a disability. I have never heard of him using an excuse or whining about the bad in his life. If only everyone would face up to their challenges and not blame others for their mistakes this world would be a better place.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      People reading the Knight Ridder report about George W. Bush's visit to Concordia University in Wisconsin were informed that there was "no hint of protest."   By coming to Concordia, a conservative campus and the largest Lutheran university in North America, Bush all but guaranteed a warm reception. There was no hint of protest during the ceremony, and some audience members shouted, "We love you, W," when he took the stage.     Actually, there was a protest during the ceremony.  I attended it.  We must have been missed by the eye of the reporter because we weren't allowed anywhere near Bush's venue.  Looks like my article about free speech zones has some new material.  The New York Times issued this correction:    An article on Saturday about remarks by President Bush at a commencement address at Concordia University in Mequon, Wis., referred imprecisely to protests against his policies. While no protesters were at the actual ceremony, the Secret Service did allow them several blocks away.     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wehhlll.....  One of the first posts I saw on the day of Ronald Reagan's passing seemed, at the least, in poor taste.  It was entitled "Reagan is Dead - Finally!"  The post was by some guy who aspires to be "the most dangerous mind on the Internet", and draws a lot of attention to himself by making  sensational, offensive, thoughtless posts, kind of like the radio jocks that poked fun at Berg after his unfortunate demise.  Now, I see that more sites have put on their dancing shoes for this occasion.  I was very surprised to see that one of my favorites,  urlLink Democracynow.org , has joined the shindig.  If you have ever watched an Internet broadcast that portrays a clearer picture of what is actually happening in this country right now than  urlLink Democracynow.org , I would be surprised.  My neighbor turned me on to it awhile back and I've been addicted ever since.  So, why take the opportunity of someone's death to run stories like " urlLink Reagan Was the Butcher of My People ?"  Perhaps it's to present an alternative view to all of the buzz about how this country is forever in his debt.  It doesn't seem real classy to bash Reagan right now, just as it wasn't en vogue for Michael Moore and the Dixie Chicks to protest the Iraq War when everyone thought Saddam Hussein really had weapons of mass destruction pointed at us. George W. Bush and John Kerry have even suspended the Presidential race for five days to allow the nation to mourn Reagan.  Maybe we can take these five days to remember Reagan for who he really was, whether it be optimist, patriot, or butcher.  Let's just not get so carried away with sentiment that we displace reality.  When I was a kid I thought that Reagan was a pretty cool guy.  I didn't know anything about right wing death squads or "Reaganomics".  I just thought he seemed like a positive person.  Now I believe he was a human being who was part of something much bigger than he ever understood.  I won't be taking this opportunity to slam Ronald Reagan.  But, I cannot be one of the majority you are hearing now who are singing his praises.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After I met with Joe in person to discuss this piece, we've decided to take it down for now.  It is a work of fiction being written by Joe about an over-zealous environmentalist.  Some extreme phraseology didn't really apply to what was actually being said. And, left open to interpretation... well, let's just say someone skimming it over might get the wrong idea (Jim's picturing an elderly woman in Wyoming calling the FBI.)    This is one we'll have to try again.   Jim & Joe peace    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        By J.R. Engeriser, Milwaukee Urban Star     What happens when a bus full of peace protesters takes a wrong turn and gets a little too close to George W. Bush?  I was on that bus and what did happen was, as Bush Sr. would have said, “a little scary”.   You can tell something big is happening. As we drive down the highway I see police staked out for miles at every exit.   urlLink   Roads everywhere are blocked off. And, the Secret Service and local police have established what the Bush administration refers to as a “free speech zone” located several blocks away from where the President will speak.  This is where we, the protesters, may stand.  We are confined to one side of the road in a muddy area behind roadblocks.  Bush will never see us or hear our message to him, and the media will have to go out of their way if our protest is to be covered at all.  With all of these roadblocks, it is hard to tell where you are supposed to go.  A confused bus driver puts us within sight of Concordia University, Bush’s venue for today.   Suddenly, our bus is surrounded.  There are several police cars, motorcycles, and men in riot gear.  A man in a camouflage three wheel vehicle drives out of the nearby woods.  After a short talk with officials, it is determined that we are now  not allowed to leave.      urlLink   On the bus, conversation is buzzing.  “Are we under arrest?”  “Why are we being detained?”  We don’t seem to be getting any answers.  Then a man in a suit pulls up in a car and looks us over.  “He is Secret Service,” I am told by someone on the bus.  The man who is now in charge of our freedom seems somewhat pissed when I take his picture.  With a wave of his hand, we are escorted away from the area with police both in front of us and behind us.  When the police leave us back by the protest area where people like us belong, it is apparent that we are free to go.  Is it because George W. Bush is the most hated man on earth that he needs such an exaggerated perimeter of security?  Moreover, what exactly is a “free speech zone”?  Didn’t the entire United States of America used to be a free speech zone?  These are the questions that Bill Neel was asking when he was arrested in Pittsburgh for holding up a sign that said “The Bush family must surely love the poor, they made so many of us.”  Because his sign was not pro-Bush, he was arrested.  People carrying signs in favor of the President were allowed to stay.  Free speech has a larger perimeter if your message is approved.  These stories seem to be popping up everywhere.  In Italy, during a recent visit by Bush, two radio stations planning full coverage of street protests mysteriously had their power turned off by the local electric company.  When asked about the outage, the company said there was some "strange maintenance work" going on.  Strange indeed.  I guess Americans aren’t the only ones who lose their liberties when Bush comes to town.  John Ashcroft, our Attorney General, had this to say  “To those who scare peace-loving people with phantoms of lost liberty … your tactics only aid terrorists, for they erode our national unity and … give ammunition to America’s enemies.”   urlLink   So we protesters are now the terrorists, it may seem. What Ashcroft and company should be afraid of is the erosion of trust in our government that they have caused.  The current administration has taken that to a whole new level with lies to the U.N., A war started for profit, and the Patriot Act, which strips us all of our rights. Bush has stated that the terrorists attack us because they hate freedom.  The authors of the Patriot Act certainly hate freedom...  Here I went into a rant with some rhetoric.  Wingnut inspired me to put in some facts about the Patriot Act.  More to follow...  Update:  I just found out that Knight Ridder reported a warm reception and "no hint of protest."  Looks like I'll be adding some info.  Jim   More To See    urlLink Plug Pulled on Rome Radio Stations Covering Bush Protests    urlLink Bush in Wisconsin (Protest Pictures)    urlLink Police scolded as Bush protester acquitted   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a lighter note posting here. Jennifer Lopez got married AGAIN on saturday afternoon to singer Marc Anthony. How about we start up an office pool type contest to guess how long this marriage will last. Factor into your guess that Marc Anthony just got divorced himself.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   After a lot of humming I finally got my Google Gmail beta account.  I also have invitations to give away.  So, if you are interested in beta testing Gmail, click on the image to the right.  Please note: If you are a member of our staff, or an anonymous reader who belongs to Blogger, first check your Blogger dashboard.  If this link appears you will get Gmail much faster.  So far, I love Gmail.  It seems to organize your email in such a clear way, giving you many options to categorize and archive your mail.  Don't worry about the element of storage space. You have 1000 megabytes to play with.  This should last you for years before you need to start deleting anything, even spam. This is email without borders.  Whatever you want to do with your mail, you can find a way to do it.  Gmail allows you to place a label on every piece of mail so that you can quickly browse every item in that category.  If you can't find what you are looking for that way, you can do a Google search of any words or phrases in your mail database to locate the message.     Specific emails of vital importance can be affixed with a gold star so that you can find them quickly. You certainly can delete messages at will.  But, Google seems almost offended when you do so saying "Who needs to delete when you have 1000 MB of storage?!"   Start a Data Cloud   Data clouds are sprites of information that users tap into and spread at free will.  It can be text, video, audio, or any media.  You are not limited by low file transfer sizes to participate in this phenomena.  Future generations will reference Gmail as an entity that changed the structure of electronic communication.  Leading email providers, including Yahoo!, are already scrambling to compete, even as Gmail is only in beta.  One element that needs improvement is the address book.  You cannot create email groups, that is, lists of contacts who all need to receive bulletins related to the same subject.  Let's say you have a business staff and would like to send frequent bulletins to a specific department or list of associates.  You would need to cut and paste the email list from earlier bulletins to keep the group in tact.  Outlook Express handles this much better.  I have yet to see how well Gmail provides 'weapons of mail destruction' to handle SPAM.  I'm sure that it will be better than Microsoft, which provides nearly zero protection in its mail clients.  Gmail forces you to think differently about your email.  It gives you all of the power, and then takes it a step further.  The most intriguing step you must take with Gmail is facing that point of pushing the "archive" button, thus releasing your mail from the inbox and from there on relying on the unique interface to find past items.  It's exciting, but a little disorienting.  Some privacy groups are concerned about how Gmail scans your messages to put ads in your email.  So far, this hasn't bothered me. It's really no different than how search engines and web pages place ads, except there are no banners or images, only a table on the right with text links to related subjects.  No person ever views your mail in this process.  It's only a bot doing the work.  It is, as far as I'm concerned, the most non-invasive free email service available.  Jim  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Mankind must put an end to war, or war will put an end to mankind...War will exist until that distant day when the conscientious objector enjoys the same reputation and prestige that the warrior does today." -John F. Kennedy   The outcry I see against Michael Moore so far shows me that we haven't quite reached JFK's vision. If you believe in these words by JFK, you should see Fahrenheit 9/11. If you don't, you have a much greater need to see it.   Aside from those blindly towing a party line, I see Americans wondering why they were lied to and why this administration is the scarriest ever since Nixon. This movie will answer these questions.   urlLink trailer   Peace  Jim 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        "I prefer the most unfair peace to the most righteous war." -Cicero   "The way of peace is the way of love. Love is the greatest power on earth. It conquers all things."  -Peace Pilgrim   "The most disadvantageous peace is better than the most just war." -Desiderius Erasmus   "I object to violence because when it appears to do good, the good is only temporary; the evil it does is permanent."  -Mohandas K. Gandhi   "Mankind must put an end to war, or war will put an end to mankind...War will exist until that distant day when the conscientious objector enjoys the same reputation and prestige that the warrior does today."  -John F. Kennedy   "The past is prophetic in that it asserts loudly that wars are poor chisels for carving out peaceful tomorrows." -Martin Luther King, Jr.   "The arms race can kill, though the weapons themselves may never be used...by their cost alone, armaments kill the poor by causing them to starve." -Vatican statement to the U.N., 1976   "War would end if the dead could return."  -Stanley Baldwin   "In separateness lies the world's great misery; in compassion lies the world's true strength." -Buddha   "It is the job of thinking people, not to be on the side of the executioners." -Albert Camus  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is not actually a story, but I might do a story on each one.  Jim  #10. Milk  Okay, maybe this is unfair of me to mention because I come from the Dairy State and I think the dairy farmers should get paid fairly.  But why did milk suddenly go from $2.09 a gallon (if you know where to shop) to $3.89 a gallon (same store)?!  Are the cows on strike?  If so, give them what they want and let's get those udders flowing again.  #9. Ring Tones  Now you can buy popular song snippets and download them to your cellular phone so they play when it rings.  If you are someone who is doing this, please stop. No one wants to hear your phone ringing to "Err body in da club get tipsy" in video game quality music.  You're music already sucks as it is, and this behavior does not help you to personify that image you're going for. You're wasting your money and annoying people.  #8. Dr. Atkins  There's a reason he's dead. You can't eat only protein and fat and be healthy.  Bread is good for you.  That's why Jesus gave it to people with fish.  Everyone is rushing to sell us low carb crap now.  The other day I saw a sign at the store advertising diet soda as "low carb friendly!"  Diet soda has always been sugar-free.  This is not a scientific breakthrough.  Please eat balanced meals and exercise.  #7. DSL  DSL stands for Digital Subscriber Line.  It is the phone company's answer to broadband Internet access.  Unfortunately, it is usually only about 10% as fast as cable Internet, but costs almost as much.  Since the whole idea of broadband is to give you speed, it hurts my feelings that they even offer this service to people.  If you want a fast Internet connection, install a cable modem and share it via a wireless router with everyone within a block of your house.  Even with everyone surfing at once, it will still be faster than DSL.  #6. Disney  Walt Disney was a great man and had a great thing going.  When he died, greedy corporate executives took over and ruined everything.  Now kids in sweatshops in third world countries are getting ten cents an hour to make Mickey Mouse dolls.  Every few months they shove a new movie down our throats and completely saturate the market with crap based on the movie: shoes, cereal, fruit snacks, t-shirts, Happy Meal toys, hats, dolls, play sets, trading cards, beverages, candy, etc. Don't forget the DVD!  Get it now because soon it will be locked away in the Disney vault for ten years!  By the way, my kids cannot live without these things.  #5. Lawyers  Why should it cost so much to work our way through the legal system and protect ourselves?  If we are going to have laws and a judicial system, legal information and guidance should be provided free to everyone who needs it.  I'm not talking about a public defender who sucks.  I'm talking about a quality service to help us through our day-to-day lives so that we know which end is up. Why should the rich be the only ones who use the loopholes?  The legal playing field needs to be leveled.  #4. Check 'n' Go  These places prey upon those in a bind.  Perhaps someone had some bad luck financially and can't get a loan or even a checking account.  So, places like this charge high fees to cash their paychecks.  Want a $100 loan?  Sure!  That will be one thousand % A.P.R.  It's called predatory lending, A.K.A. loan sharking. What a rip.   #3. Gasoline  A friend of my dad's once said that if gas ever got up to $1.00 per gallon he would stop driving a car.  That was in the 80's. I'm sure he's still driving at $2.39 per gallon.  It's time to stop using this type of energy.  There is a finite supply and once it's gone, it's gone. Why is alternative energy not a top priority?  Remember when people used to drive around in their cars for fun?  When was the last time you heard someone say, "Let's just go for a drive?"  Now, many of us can barely afford to drive to work.  #2. Parking  Charging people money to park their cars is one of the biggest scams ever and should be banned. City parking tickets are a curse and frequently send people into a downward spiral. People who can't pay lose their vehicle registrations and drivers' licenses because of this, wreaking havoc on their lives. Also, their is no reason why anyone should have to pay $20 to park at a concert, an amusement park, or in a parking structure near where they work.  This is usury and needs to be done away with.  #1. The Iraq War  This war has cost us more than anything we have ever bought, not just dollars, but also human lives. Monetarily, we will be paying for it for decades.  What's worse is that the majority of Americans were against it from the beginning.  When you have a president who is told by his people not to go to war, and instead he takes their money, spends it all on the war, and lies about why he's doing it, it's time for a new president.    Jim  You're welcome to add your own rip-offs.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you noticed how Bush's campaign ads lately are really ads for John Kerry?  They mostly point to John Kerry and the Democratic party and say "this is what they want".  When I see these ads I find myself thinking "Yes! Sounds good! So, what's your point?"  It's almost as if he wants you to vote for Kerry.  Now, the latest ad on the official Bush/Cheney website shows angry Democrats speaking out against Bush's actions.  Then, instead of addressing the issues, the ad just tries to make a statement against getting angry. Gee, George, since many Americans ARE angry with you, it looks like you've just spent your money on another ad for Kerry.  The ad also throws in some footage from an amateur video that someone submitted to a contest on moveon.org.  It compares Bush to Hitler!  Well, moveon.org didn't use that spot.  It was voted down.  But Bush was happy to put it in his own ad.  Thanks for the honesty, Mr. Bush. But, if I was the President and the voters started comparing me to Hitler, I probably wouldn't be advertising it!  I don't really think George W. Bush is planning a second term. In fact, if he gets one, I think he'll be pissed. Or, he'll try to get out of it.  It seems to me that his plan from the beginning was to just take as much advantage of the presidency for one term, ignore the will of the people, push his own agenda as far as possible, and make lots of money for himself and his friends.  If you think about it, what else has he really accomplished?  Not expecting a second term would enable him to get away with much more, for instance, killing thousands of innocent people in a war that an overwhelming majority of Americans objected to (not to mention the world community), lying to everyone about it, working with congress to help big companies screw Americans, destroying the environment for profit, spending all of our money and putting us into debt further than we've ever been, then handing the whole big mess over to a Democrat to clean up.  Oh, and uh, good luck with Iraq, Sucker!  If he is serious about a second term, he's either really not too bright about it, or he knows something I don't know. Perhaps I over-estimate the intelligence of the American people.  I think I could do a much better job on his campaign, and I don't even like the guy.  You can make just about anyone look good with the right approach. I just wonder if he's failing at this on purpose. Well, there I go again trying to guess what Bush is up to.  I still can't make any sense out of the guy. It's all just like a horrible nightmare. If we are going to start fixing what he's broken, however, we should probably get the vote out in November.  Remember:  more people voting = Right Wing Conservatives lose.  Works every time!  Well, except in the state of Florida: there they just throw out the votes they don't want.  Jim 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...to see Fahrenheit 9/11.  It's a good thing they had a late showing otherwise I would have had to wait three whole days!  This movie is stunning! Michael Moore can really tell a story. This is his best so far. Amazingly, most of the facts were already in my head before seeing the movie. Fahrenheit puts the facts together so that it all makes sense. It opens with the 2000 presidential election and reminds us of what happened, although it seems we all forgot or just accepted it a long time ago. A good part of the 9/11 reflection is just audio and a black screen. That's where the images in your mind take over.   It is a bit comical at some points.  How can you not laugh at the Bush administration? Otherwise you'd be crying. I had chills during several segments. A movie hasn't done that to me in a very long time.   I hope every American who sees it will be compelled to vote in November.   As it won the Palme d’Or (Best Picture) at the Cannes Film Festival this year, seeing it confirmed the award was well deserved. It wasn't just because the French hate the White House. (Funny how they never realized that French fries aren't really French anyway.)   The audience this evening applauded at the end of the movie. I hope a lot of people see this.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     They actually do this in New Jersey.  It almost sounds so disgusting it has to be tried.  Hardcore hot dog fans probably already know about  urlLink The Hot Dog Page  at hollyeats.com.  This is a trip into the world of hot dogs.  Call it a frankfurter forum.  With reviews around the country, the site also has a section that focuses on  urlLink New Jersey , where they do that deep fried thing "until its skin is mangled and torn."  You can almost clog an artery just by looking at the pictures.  Restaurants are rated by grease stains, not stars.  I am a fan of Chicago style hot dogs.  I'm having a cookout tomorrow and bought all of the ingredients for Chicago style.  I know you aren't supposed to grill them.  They are boiled.  That's why I had to bust open a package of all beef frankfurters tonight and have a couple the right way. Honestly, I just couldn't wait until tomorrow.   urlLink The Hot Dog Page  can keep you occupied for hours.  Follow enough links and you can see amazing things, like a Baldwin enjoying a Guadalajara Dog at  urlLink Pinks Hot Dogs .   urlLink     Which one of those wacky Baldwins is it this time?  Jim 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Most of us have something we want out of this great land that we call America. Some are super-entrepeneurs and want to take over the world with a corporate monopoly. Some are evangelists and want to convince us to embrace a specific religious creed. Others would be happy if multitudes of Americans would buy into their multi-level marketing downline.  My wish is more simple, but still an awesome personal challenge.  It is now possible to walk upon one single man-made trail completely from one coast of the United States clear to the other.  This is called the  urlLink American Discovery Trail .     What an awesome undertaking!  My friend  urlLink JDBrenny  encouraged me to look into trails. And, after a few searches, I came upon the granddaddy of them all. Spanning 6800 miles and 15 states, the American Discovery Trail network seems to be the best excuse in the world to follow the vision of Jules in 'Pulp Fiction': to just walk the Earth. You know, like Kane in 'Kung Fu'.  I believe I could take the entire trail in 40 weeks, or just over ten months. A couple by the name of Joyce and Peter Cottrell have already done it.  They took 18 months, but they are in their 50's and stopped for the winter to take jobs at a Walmart.  I would love to do this before I leave the country for good. If George W. gets another term, I will most likely do so.  Before I go, I want to see more of this great land.  As a bonus, the trail never enters the state of Texas!  Consider me in training for the  urlLink American Discovery Trail .  Jim
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At the request of my non-paying-boss, I give you this treat. A 'backstage' tour, if you will, and you didn't have to donate a goddamn cent to get it, so donate your time/money/estate to your favorite charity/non-prof/community chest if you want a bigger/better/more stimulating benefit.    From: Jim E   To: "Roy G. Biv"   Sent: Saturday, June 19, 2004 12:41 AM Subject: Woody Allen  Like him or hate him?  Jim +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++  From: "Roy G. Biv"   To:  Jim E   Sent: Tuesday, June 22, 2004  4:55  PM Subject: Woody Allen  so- is this whay you were lookin for? have i passed the test? lol Roy  +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++  From: "Jim E"   To: "Roy G. Biv"   Sent: Wednesday, June 23, 2004 7:36 PM Subject: Re: Woody Allen  I love you're writing.  Katie and Jay have also commented favorably. Most everyone's been doing news but it looks like we're going to add a section for your writing.  Out of the Blue, huh? Jim  And what about Woody  +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++  From: "Jim E"   To: "Roy G. Biv"   Sent: Wednesday, June 23, 2004 8:15 PM Subject: Re: Woody Allen  Thanks for the compliment/encouragement/support. ( writing 'hook'...the a/b/c ....). Yes- The 'column' is entitled OutOfTheBlue and will feature whatever is pissing me off/confusing/enlightening ( there it is again.....) me at the moment of my literary birthing. Glad I could add a different angle/direction/feature ( EVERYWHERE!!!! RUN!!!) to Urbanstar.com. BTW- I think its a GREAT idea what you're doing....i find that i am much more perceptive and aware of my environment since being invited to contribute. THANK YOU for reviving me from my 'sheep-to-slaughter' reverie that most americans have fallen into. I am superior to most life forms once again. :) Take care, Jim..... BTW- why arent they commenting publicly (on the site) abt my writing?!?!?!? LOL   P.S. Woody Allen?? dont care for him personally, but strongly admire his artistry.....why do ya ask?? PPS- kd lang with the symphony pops last night was FABULOUS!!!!!! met her at the 'after'. lovely boy, she is....................  +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++  From: "Jim E"   To: "Roy G. Biv"   Sent: Wednesday, June 23, 2004 9:40 PM Subject: Re: Woody Allen  Actually there are two comments on your first post.  One is that snotty one from Cassandra and the other is praise from Katie.  Sometimes you have to hit refresh to see changes. When I first saw K.D. on VH1 in the 80's I really had no idea if she was a man or a woman.  When the song was over and I saw the name in the corner of the screen, well, I still didn't know.  Then I saw her on Pee Wee's playhouse and she wore a skirt and even at that point I don't think I was completely convinced.  It would be fab if you did a little something about her.  I wanted someone to do a bit on Woody. I have mixed feelings about the man as well but  I don't want the arcticle to be a total slam.  I saw Manhattan the other night and it reminded me of how much I love his movies. I might end up doing a story myself.  It would be interesting if you added comments later.  We really should be having this conversation on the blog.  laytah Jim       OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           As I was digesting tonight's sludgefest that is commonly referred to as 'the news' around these parts, I had a thought I felt I must share. In my opinion, I think the worst job/moment/recollection/most-hideous-home-video moment in one's life must be:          The moment when you are publicly named as Ralph Nader's Official Running Mate.        I mean, c'mon- You have to enter life from that moment on with a GREAT sense of humor, otherwise the world will crush you like a bug on the windshield of existence.       Does anyone blessed with this position actually believe that they'll be vice president? Someday? ANY day?? One must stop to wonder that if the person named actually thinks he has any chance to be vice president (again, Someday? ANY day??), then he must immediately be deemed, by a court, of course, Mentally Incompetent To Survive, have M.I.T.S. tattooed in a bold, Georgia font (huh...how appropriate) on their forehead (Pica size to be determined by each individuals receding hairline status at time of ...um....retirement....(Hi Ronnie!! Is it hot down there?? Get out of my yard, you damn kid!!?? Get out of MY yard, you old rotten, whooooo.....(ten deep breaths)...focus....focus.....))), and turned into the streets to live with the other tired, huddled masses yearning to be free in this land that is my land, land that is your land, from California to the ...well, you get the point.  Anyway...I sure hope he kept his day job. Shit....he probably knows a Kennedy or two.......why bother?  Get that tattoo needle ready....and while you're at it, make it two....   Jesus saves!! All others take 3d8 damage and are stunned for three rounds.                                    OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com                                  >  If you send, I may/can/possibly use in a public format, electronically or otherwise, blah blah, blah....names will be kept confidential to protect the innocent- but the stupid are fair game. You have been   >    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Remember where Butch left his father's watch in the movie 'Pulp Fiction'?  It was on the little kangaroo on the bedside table.  The little ceramic boxing kangaroo caddy is actually a collectable piece of Americana made in the 1950's.   As ugly and tasteless as my wife thinks it is (and she is probably right), I have always wanted one. I looked recently and found the same exact 1956 kangaroos available on eBay.  I found one with  free shipping  and won the auction for only $16.05.  What a deal!  Here is the payment request I received from the seller:    Subject: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy  Congratulations on being the winning bidder on the above item. Please make payment for the above item in the amount of $16.05 for the item  plus $7.00 for S&H and $1.30 for insurance for a total of $24.30.  The forms of payment that we accept are check, money order and paypal...  Now, remember I said the auction offered free shipping.  So, thinking I might be losing my mind, I looked back at the auction page and under shipping and handling it says this:   USPS Priority (calculated at checkout)  $0.00 USPS Parcel Post   Call me crazy, but this says to me that if I want priority mail there is a charge and if I want regular mail there is no charge.  So I thought, "oh, they must be assuming that I want PRIORITY mail!"  As it turns out, that was the case. But I don't want priority mail.  I want my free shipping!  My efforts in seeking my free parcel post shipping is where it gets interesting. First, I sent this email to clarify:   Subject: Re: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy  Is that for priority shipment?  I was planning on using your free USPS Parcel Post method.  Once I received the response, I knew I was in for some kind of eBay battle.  He said:   Subject: Re: Re: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy   As i am sure you already know  the parcel post method is not free. I leave the amount blank as i do not know where it will be going so i can not determine how much S&H will be. The amount quoted is for priority shipping.  Now I'm thinking, why in the world would I already know that $0.00 shipping means I have to pay for shipping?  Just last week, $0.00 shipping meant it was free.  I guess zero means different things to different people.  It didn't make any sense to me, so I responded:   Subject: Re: Re: Re: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy  I wasn't trying to imply that the Post Office offers free shipping :)  I was referring to your eBay terms where you offer $0.00 shipping if USPS Parcel Post is selected.  Understand what happened here: Your price on the little kangaroo was not the lowest on eBay.  However, $0.00 shipping made you competitive, hence my bid. Your checkout also offers $0.00 shipping if USPS Parcel Post is used, consistent with your auction terms...  Since you appear to have done this by mistake, I won't be a jerk and hold you to it.  Although, if you are willing to honor your original terms, I am  willing purchase the item.  In either case I look at it as an honest mistake and will leave positive feedback as long as you do so also. Let me know either way.  Peace, Jim  At this point I feel I have definately cleared up any confusion as to where I am coming from regarding this auction.  That is, until I get this response:   Subject: Re: Re: Re: Re: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy  The reason the S&H for parcel is $0.00 is because i dont know how much S&H will be. I could always charge S&H for a 4 pound package to california which is considerably more then it would be to ship to someone in new york state.  While that would prevent any confusion i am sure the bidder in new york would not be happy paying $5.00 more then it really cost. I am sure the S&H of $0.00 had to raise some questions in your mind and in the listing i ask that you contact me with questions before you bid. While i did not do this by mistake i also did not do this to try and scam anyone, i just want to make sure everyone pays the proper S&H and does not get ripped off. The difference in price for shipping this priority and parcel is only about $.50 and i have found that priority packages get to their location in better condition. Please let me know what you want to do.  Now it looks like I am crazy for thinking anyone would offer free shipping.  Actually, it's not that uncommon. Just do an eBay search for 'free shipping' or '$0.00 shipping' and you'll get thousands of results. I really want to solve this dilema without exchanging negative feedback.  After all, mine is so far 100% positive.  So this is the last communication so far from me regarding the little kangaroo:   Subject: Re: Re: Re: Re: Re: EBAY boxing kangaroo dresser caddy  I see your side, too. Hope you can see mine.  Free shipping is a common thing on eBay so when I see it I assume it is for real.  If you see:  USPS Priority (calculated at checkout) $0.00 USPS Parcel Post  ...it says to me if you want priority mail there will be a fee which will be calculated later and if you want regular mail there is no charge.  It didn't really put a question in my mind.  In fact, I just recently purchased something that said Shipping $0.00 which meant no shipping charge.  You should put:  USPS Parcel Post (calculated at checkout) USPS Priority Available (add .50 to above)  I'm not trying to call you a scammer, don't worry. I'm just not willing to pay more than I bid under the terms offered.  If this is unacceptable and you decide to relist the item it will not upset me and no harm done.  You can always just cancel the sale and your eBay charges will be refunded to you.  Jim  If I am being stupid about this, please let me know. After all, it's only an $8.30 discrepancy.  But it's also only a bedside table boxing kangaroo.  Jim   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The situation has progressed to the point that legitimate emails from freinds that I want to hear from may never reach me.  Why?  In a word: SPAM.  I no longer have the time or patience to look through hundreds of advertisements to find that one message that may be from someone I actually know.  So, I filter my email.  Creating an email filter means defining a criteria whereby messages are judged by merit.  First, you take an hour or so to log every single known friendly email address into a data base of allowed contacts.  If you are willing to commit more time to this process, certain subject field phrases and all-inclusive domain originations are also submitted so as to be allowed to pass or fail the screening.  Emails that meet the criteria make it to your inbox and become relevant.  Emails caught in the filter are deposited in your recycle bin and become nothing.  Sometimes important communications fail the test and become nothing. If your operating sytem crashes (as Windows often does), you may need to start your filtering process all over, from scratch.    If you have a website, it's more of a challenge.  There are robots that crawl the web harvesting email addresses to be used for the proliferation of SPAM. So, I have converted my online email address to a photograph of an email address, instead of actual text.  Now, I have discovered that robots using imaging technology can read this, too.  If that's not enough, a spammer can use "spoofing" to send you an email that appears to be from yourself, or someone you trust.  The evil of this is: a message from a long lost friend whom you are dying to hear from will never reach you, even if he or she happens to obtain your email address.  Such a message in a bottle will not make it past the SPAM filters.  If you are in business, just imagine trying to receive communications from potential clients. EBay'ers argue amongst themselves daily because emails caught in SPAM filters never reach their destination.  "The seller never sent a request for payment!",  "Liar! The buyer never responded to request for payment!", etc.  We need 'Weapons of Mail Destruction', or a way to obliterate SPAM once and for all.  Prominent mail client providers, such as AOL, Yahoo!, and Google's beta Gmail,  have invested millions of dollars to create electronic methods to detect mass mailings and otherwise unwanted email. This does not help most users who retrieve their email from their own domains and ISP's.  Microsoft has lagged behind in providing such a service for users of its mail clients, Outlook, and Outlook Express.  Every time I check my email and see hundreds of SPAM messages, I become quite angry with Bill Gates for not protecting me.  The community of online service providers are well overdue to come together so as to provide a standardized email authentication system to protect us.  Call it caller-I.D. for email.  The big barrier is that email is free.  Spammers don't pay a penny more than you or I emailing each other, or the business that sends bulletins to employees and customers.  We need to employ standardized software that intelligently sorts SPAM out of our legitimate email.  Technology already exits to do this.  What's the hold-up?  Jim
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'd like to preface/begin/start my newest missive to Urban*Star by letting y'all know a little something about yours truly.   One of the tenets I use to guide myself down those roads I take to bring me to a future part of my life is the belief that there is no such thing as 'coincidence'.   I don't know the exact origin of the word 'coincidence', but before you start salivating/seizing/putting your nipples to the wind to scroll down and leave a comment, know that I above anyone else know that if I surf long enough on the most blessed miracle to have ever happened to have been bestowed upon us lowly sinners, i could find my answer. But first, may I remind you kittens, I have to care enough.  Anyway, I digress. Back to my original point.    I don't believe in 'coincidence'. Everything in our lives happens for a reason. We are constantly being shown signs/hints/revelations. Sometimes they come all at once, and sometimes they are revealed to us in parts- a series of signs/hints/revelations that come in several parts at different times- like the best Agatha Christie novels. We may not understand exactly what they mean or why we are being given this information at the moment of our shining (Danny's not here, Mrs. Torrence!!). As long as we are open enough to know that we ARE being fed information from the universe, and see what is being revealed, and more importantly, REMEMBER what is being shown, we can piece it all together later, when the time is right for us to know the full story.  So- now that you have that little ort, my gracious readers, maybe you'll be able to feel what I feel right now, a feeling I have been trying to put into words, but for one of the VERY few times in my life, i am rendered speechless.   Let me tell you what happened to me today.  I met a person, who'll I'll call "Rick", just so you can get a visual feel for him, back in 1990 or there abouts. I met him at my workplace downtown. He was a new hire, and when we met, there was just that something you feel when you are eight....oops...I mean 8, and you know that the kid that just moved in next door was going to be your best friend, and was- until one of your families moved away, up to the big time. We were best friends- Rick, myself, and his partner, "Les". We hung out alot, and had alot of fun. Then I got involved in a relationship that lasted sev...7 years and 2 months. It was a mental/physical/sexual/emotional abusive relation for most of that time. I was literally cut off from all of my friends and family. But thats a different story for another time....I just wanted you to understand how I lost contact with them for 7 years.   I reconnected with them about two years ago now, but alas, things are VERY different now. Not between us- we clicked again like no time had passed- like the 'happy' episodes of Classmates.  Upon our reunion, I learned that one of only FOUR.....that's right, FOUR people in my entire life* that I have been able to call a true/best/loyal friend, now has full blown AIDS. His is one of the worst the doctors have seen. His meds kinda/sorta/not really work, but on good days he can get around.  *For those of you that really want to know, you'll have to figure it out for yourself. I'll give you a clue, 'tho. My claim to fame is that I'm an Original Valley Child Born In The Summer Of Love.  He came over to my place because I had gotten him some 420, and as a return favor, he treated the Chillem. After the first intake, he started to cough...a really deep/muscle straining/kind you hear in the nursing home (where grandma is housed) that gives you the creeps AND goosebumps.  I asked, "Are you OK??"  He replied, "No, I'm dying from AIDS."  He said it in such a, pardon the pun, deadpan way- the way I remember Rick from way back when- that I laughed out loud while thinking to myself, "He still has his sense of humor. Mine would have gone LONG before."  After a few seconds, I realized that not only was he joking, but he was, pardon the pun again, dead serious. He still seemed to have trouble recovering, so I now asked, since I am such a good host, "Can I get you anything?" while thinking if he doesn't want water or coffee, I can always run next door to the Citgo and get him something.   He replied, "Yeah....a cure."  Such a simple request.....2 words, 5 letters........  Unfortunately, there isn't a Citgo, or anywhere else in any reaches of the far corners of this world/universe/galaxy for that matter that I could run to to get him what he needed. Or popped in to the closest SuperSizeMe to get a Big Aaaaaack! (Come Back To The Five and Dime, Bill The Cat, Bill The Cat.....), an order of fries, and a side of AIDSnoMO.  But Yahweh/Allah/The Hero With A Thousand Faces knows that I would have. After all, what are best friends for? Remember this, gentle readers- Anything and Everything. That's what you do for a best friend.   And that begs another question- WHY isn't there a cure yet? After all the technological advances we have made in medicine in the past 40 or 50 years, surely we must have a cure. There is a cure you know- but to start using it would cost the drug companies millions of dollars annually, but alas, that too is another story for a future meeting.  After he left, I decided to log on and figure out what I was gonna write/go on about/post this week here on the 'ol Urban*Star, and I saw EdwardA's post, and followed through to read the entire article.(Thanks for the post, ERA.) I know that I am being shown things now. For what purpose I'm not exactly sure yet, but I'll keep you posted.   Who knows- maybe I'll finally be the first one to be told the great secret of life......the Why Are We Here question that everyone has been asking, and Monty Python have been the best to come closest to with an answer, but I know that's not It. God...I HOPE that's not it. It CAN'T be It (My liver?? But I'm USING it!!)....or maybe I was just given the real answer to the title of this piece- which is the sound I felt rather than heard (stay with me, now), when I REALLY understood his very simple, but totally unexpected response to my offer of assistance. I don't think his request was one bit unreasonable, 'tho. If there's one thing in life I've learned, it's that you will never get something you never ask for. No matter how outrageous it seems, if you ask enough people, sooner or later you'll run into someone who says "Yes". (But they STILL won't put it on a credit card, even if they do get a two-for-one ticket voucher for doing so.)  We all know/understand/accept the old adage that Life Goes On.....but it sure is a pisser the day you realize that it doesn't get any easier to bear when it Stops Going On for those we truly care about. But....then again.....Life Goes On. And so we do.   OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday, my son and I were driving and listening to 'All Things Considered' on NPR. The topic was an article in the Rocky Mountain News, Denver, about the first child known to have contracted HIV in Colorado. He name is Jonathan Swain. He is now 21 years old. The paper devoted 16 pages to this story. Later, I was able to read the  urlLink entire story  at the Rocky Mountain News web site. This is something that should be read by all. I found the story inspirational and disturbing. It's amazing how little Americans want to know when they are challenged to look at life differently.  This is a subject that is more personal to me, as I had a friend that died of AIDS last year. Watching his fight and eventual loss with the disease had a profound effect upon my life. I hope you enjoy reading this article as much as I did.   urlLink Story 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Are you sure this isn't just the Landmark bar letting out on Tuesday at bartime?   urlLink     I love this one, too, from Denver:   urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Or is there something strange about this scenario? On Thursday I had to accompany my boss to the Summerfest grounds to pick up his tickets for the Prince concert. The man is a fanatic. Actually, it goes way beyond that, there simply are not words to describe his devotion. I will say this, he has the little "TAFKAP" symbol tattooed on his forearm.  He is almost 58 years old. Right there something is off. To me there is just something that is not right about someone close to my fathers age being such a huge Prince fan. Anyhow, we are in his car and I am telling him how to get to downtown Milwaukee because he has *no idea where he is going (he lives in Madison and is from England) and all the while he is yelling-no make that swearing- "You f---ing bloody fat cow..." at everyone on the road, even though he is the one cutting people off. The icing on the cake is that on top of everything else we are listening to, yep, you guessed it, Prince. I *just started working for this guy and here we are cruising the freeway in his car, him almost killing us and/or other drivers, me reminding myself to stay calm, that I've now spent 28 years riding in a car with my father, AKA- The Worst Driver In The World...and in the background Prince is crooning things ranging from "I knew a girl named Nikki I guess you could say she was a sex fiend, Met her in a hotel lobby masturbating with a magazine." to "Get Off, 23 positions in a one night stand..."  Don't get me wrong, I myself am a big Prince fan, but come on! I keep thinking it was all some sort of strange new employee initiation. So I ask you...is it just me? I love my job, LOL. :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         I do not believe in the immortality of the individual, and I      consider ethics to be an exclusively human concern with no    superhuman authority behind it.                                     -Albert Einstein  There are many names in the realm of human language that are used to hurt. We all know what they are so I won't say them for reasons of decorum. Allow me to add one more for your consideration that I call myself. ATHEIST. Yes, I am an atheist. I have held these beliefs, or some would say lack of, for all of my thinking life, since the age of 12 or 13. I can't think of any moment when a light bulb came on. It was just a gradual change in  thinking that resulted in the feeling that it's all a load of bunk.   I was raised in the Catholic church. My father was and his father before and so on. Isn't that how most people "choose" their religion? Ask a person why they are Lutheran, Baptist, Jewish, Methodist, Muslim or Hindu. It's because that's the religion that their parents were. At least that's the way it was when I grew up. With broken families and blended home being so prominent these days there is more exposure to other sects than in earlier times. From what I've seen, the average person will chose to follow the one that's the easiest to swallow and that is the least restrictive in the doctrine. After all it's no fun to behave yourself.  The one biggest myth that I have encountered from the people who have entered my life (including my second wife) is that there was no way that I can have any morals. That couldn't be further from the truth. I feel that I am as moral as anybody else on Earth. I don't need some fear of eternal retribution to keep me in line.  I have encountered many individuals who feel they can "stretch" the rules because they've been "saved". Or, if they're Catholic, they just take it to confession to get off the hook. I live by the laws and morals of society, and take the hit when I screw up. I must admit I've done my share of it, mostly involving beer before a certain age. I follow my conscience and try to do right by that. It would be nice if our president would do that instead of using religion as an excuse or justification for his actions.  Please don't try to convert me or show me the light. I didn't come to my belief blindly. I have read the bible and have a good idea what's in it. I also know how it gets warped and distorted to justify the means. It's amazing(or should I say amusing) how many people feel if I just hear what they believe, I will just end my "evil" ways. Of course most don't seem to realize that the bible was not written 2000 to 4000 years ago. At least in it's current form. The most popular or well known version is the King James version. Why is it called that? Because King James of England had it rewritten in the 17th century. And something always gets lost or changed in the translation. I'm not an atheist because of ignorance, I am because I looked at what was presented and went from there.  I'll be posting more on the subject of atheism and the control of religion on our government in the near future and would like to have an open and wide ranging discussion...or arguments as the case may be.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I came across the following while reading the site here....  >>BTW- why arent they commenting publicly (on the site) abt my writing?!?!?!? LOL  I just wanted to make it known that I look forward to reading your posts. They are so well written and really, they just crack me up! Keep it up! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      John Kerry didn't seem to get the point of the ad posted on Thursday on the official Bush website featuring Adolph Hitler.  I don't really blame him.  There really isn't much of a point to get.  The ad is very poorly done, and has caused confusion for everyone.  Today, I got another email from the Democratic Party complaining about the ad.  It seems they still don't get what's going on.  What's going on is this:  A while back, right before the Super Bowl, MoveOn.org held a contest called 'Bush-in-thirty-seconds'.  The idea was to submit a video ad about the Bush administration.  The best one would be used as a television commercial.  Someone submitted an ad comparing George W. Bush to Hitler.  The ad got voted down and was never used.  However, in a new commercial by Bush's own people, parts of the Hitler ad appear along with angry comments from Democrats.  I guess the idea is, 'look at how angry they are, they even compare Bush to Hitler'.  Because the Bush ad was not done well, the message is not very clear. So, it appears that Bush is comparing the Democrats to Nazis.  Even John Kerry and the Democratic Party thought that this was the comparison.  They screamed to get the ad removed, not realizing it was actually footage from MoveOn.org, a site by Democrats, that they thought was so offensive.  Whoops!  Now, a man named "A. Hitler" has taken out an ad in the New York Times claiming that the Democrats and Republicans really resemble each other more than they resemble him.  Moreover, Hitler claims that the true face of evil is this man:   urlLink     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay. What is going to happen now is this: we are going to see many scares that have nothing to do with anything other than getting us to be really afraid of WHAT?  If you are afraid enough then you will still vote for the same because then you don't have to think!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Jim,   I like the pic but I'm not a Slayer fan. How about an Iron Maiden t-shirt instead
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's official,  urlLink John Kerry and John Edwards  are the Democratic ticket this year.     John Kerry kept a tight lid on his choice for running mate until this morning, when he announced his decision via email to his supporters.  Amazingly,  urlLink the Bush campaign  began running an ad this morning criticizing the choice of Edwards. Since this ad was produced before they even knew who had been selected, I wonder how much money they wasted on multiple ads for all of the possible choices, just so they wouldn't have to wait a day or two to cast a negative shadow on the final selection. I guess you can't expect them to handle campaign money any better than the national economy. It's too bad that after all the country's money is spent and gone, too many Americans are jobless and have lost their unemployment benefits, are sick and cannot afford health care, are children receiving a substandard education, are young adults who can't afford college, or are seniors who can't get the prescription drugs they need.  Invading Iraq must have been really important.   urlLink See an animation from Ben Cohen of Ben & Jerry's Ice Cream that breaks it down into dollars and cents, or Oreo Cookies.   It will be interesting to see debates between Kerry and Bush, Edwards and Cheney.  Isn't it going to be a little awkward for Bush and Cheney to start showing concern for the American public, since they have been ignoring us for 3 1/2 years? Aren't people going to think "Oh, I see. Now I exist because you need my vote?"  Of course, I keep forgetting these are the same people who took office without winning an election.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So another former president/leader/head of the free world decided to write his memoirs. A hefty 900+ page tome, too, I might add. Slick Willie was paid $12 million to remember his past, and Hillary was paid a hefty sum of $8 million for her remembrances a short time ago. Now, let me get this straight. They were paid, collectively TWENTY MILLION DOLLARS for their books, when for 8 straight years they repeatedly testified under oath THAT THEY COULD NOT REMEMBER   ANYTHING  ?!?!?!?!?! ahhhh....America the Beautiful.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Everything just seems surreal today.  It's like that one day at work when I saw the number '666' appearing everywhere.  Today, I woke up after 8 hours of sleep feeling like I got 2.  Today, I heard the phrase "If there's a problem, yo, I'll solve it" in two unrelated incidents.  My neighbor told me yesterday that he was making some obscure Mexican seafood dish.  This morning, the same dish appeared in my refigerator with a note from my wife to enjoy it. (She hates seafood)  A girl I work with gave me a big hug out of the blue.  She always used to despise me.  My boss gave me a vacation day when the calendar was already full.  That never happens.  I totally sucked at work today, until the last hour, and then I got sent home early.  I was invited to play "spin the bottle" on my lunch break.  If we were playing for real I would have kissed the new girl several times, and my friend Tim.  My boss decided to come say hello to everyone at the lunch table.  The moment she sat down, everyone got up and left. Break was over.  The same exact problem I just had fixed on my car is back.  I told my boss that it is in my nature to take things personally.  She responded: "So what do you think it is that makes you crazy?"  Finally, as I am writing this, I saw two squirrels having sex on the sidewalk in front of my house, and the birds in the trees seem to be singing, 'whoomp there it is!"  Ever have one of those days?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink      urlLink     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In today's politically charged arenas, who knew how prophetic this song could be- way back in 1985? I ask you to take a look at/revisit/reexamine&nbsp; it now..... &nbsp;  Everybody Wants To Rule The World     &nbsp;  Welcome to your life   There's no turning back   Even while we sleep   We will find you   Acting on your best behaviour   Turn your back on mother nature   Everybody wants to rule the world    &nbsp;  It's my own design   It's my own remorse   Help me to decide   Help make the most   Of freedom and of pleasure   Nothing ever lasts forever   Everybody wants to rule the world    &nbsp;  There's a room where the light won't find you   Holding hands while the walls come tumbling down   When they do I'll be right behind you    &nbsp;  So glad we've almost made i  t   So sad they had fade it   Everybody wants to rule the world    &nbsp;  I can't stand this indecision   Married with a lack of vision   Everybody wants to rule the world    &nbsp;  Say that you'll never never never need it   One headline why believe it ?   Everybody wants to rule the world    &nbsp;  All for freedom and for pleasure   Nothing ever lasts forever   Everybody wants to rule the world  &nbsp;  urlLink Tears For Fears  (1985) Roland Orzabal &amp; Curt Smith &nbsp; OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Now Jim.....didn't you read the little disclaimer on the W Ketchup Website?? They say&nbsp;the "W"&nbsp;stands for Washington, NOT Dubya (Dubya....what a STUPID FUCKIN&nbsp;NAME!! )&nbsp;(see....there's him on the label just to the left of the "W" logo.....)=========>I saw this about a week ago and thought about doing a piece on it....i went to my little place (in my mind), meditated .....i had been in Roy's Gas/Fried Chicken/Murder Rides pit stop on route....well, it doesn't matter where it is- the fewer the people that know about it, the better.... But if they just happen upon it- well, then, all the better for us I guess..... and felt a little tingling at my wrist.....i looked down and saw a mosquito and thought about the circle of life- how all species in this universe are connected in a very special way and serve a VERY distinct purpose in the Circle. How, when we tear down another section of rainforest in the Amazon and kill a few hundred species (some which we never knew existed), it affects TENS of THOUSANDS of species??.....global consequences......I looked down at the mosquito- and thought that in this world, it was just as special and important as I was; and could possibly have a much bigger part to play in this universe than i did.....  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  And then I just smashed it.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  I went back to that little place that is mine, and mine alone, and started to see whatever it was that was playing on the late show that night.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't realize this was for real. But, it is.&nbsp; If you are a Republican, better stop using that Heinz (owned by relatives of John Kerry's wife) and be all about the  urlLink Dubya Ketchup .&nbsp; Ronald Reagan would thank you.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sun Tzu said:  "The art of war is of vital importance to the State. It is a matter of life and death, a road to safety or to ruin. Hence it is a subject of inquiry which can on no account be neglected."  Indeed. It seems disappointing that the Bush Administration and much of the public have lacked the courage to properly address all points and issues associated with our war on terror and with the contingents of the Iraqi people. If this war can be anything it must be understood, mistakes identified and lessons remembered.   Sun Tzu continues:  "There is no instance of a country having benefited from prolonged warfare. When you engage in actual fighting, if victory is long in coming, the men's weapons will grow dull and their ardor will be damped. If you lay siege to a town, you will exhaust your strength. In war, then, let your great object be victory, not lengthy campaigns. This may be known that the leader of armies is the arbiter of the people's fate, the man on whom it depends whether the nation shall be in peace or in peril."  The outcome of this war is balanced on the shoulders of the Bush Administration, let us all be clear on that. Our war has already cost us over 700 soldiers and hundreds of billions of dollars. We as a people must ask ourselves has the strain been worth the resources. Such is our system that we can change our leadership every four years with the cast of a ballot. Other peoples have not been so lucky.   Sun Tzu continues:  "In the practical art of war, the best thing of all is to take the enemy's country whole and intact; to shatter and destroy it is not so good. Hence to fight and conquer in all your battles is not supreme excellence; supreme excellence consists in breaking the enemy's resistance without fighting. Therefore the skillful leader subdues the enemy's troops without any fighting; he captures their cities without laying siege to them; he overthrows their kingdom without lengthy operations in the field."  We must decide if the stratagem employed by our administration was up to task. It is entirely fair for the people of our nation to remove a leader for incompetence in the field. Only the very gifted deserve to be the leaders of great nations and it is up to the people of great nations to follow great leaders. Political ideologies aside has our current administration shown true talent in conducting this war of ours. Is the role of leader in our country limited to political ideologies? I should hope not, for this will lead only to ruin.  Sun Tzu continues:  "What the ancients called a clever fighter is one who not only wins, but excels in winning with ease. Hence his victories bring him neither reputation for wisdom nor credit for courage. He wins his battles by making no mistakes. Making no mistakes is what establishes the certainty of victory. The consummate leader cultivates the moral law, and strictly adheres to method and discipline; thus it is in his power to control success."  Sir Robert Grainger Ker Thompson adds:  "There is a very strong temptation...for government forces to act outside the law, the excuses being that the processes of law are too cumbersome, that the normal safeguards in the law for the individual are not designed for an insurgency and that a terrorist deserves to be treated as and outlaw anyway. Not only is this morally wrong, but, over a period, it will create more practical difficulties for a government than it solves. A government which does not act in accordance with the law forfeits the right to be called a government and cannot expect it people to obey the law. Functioning in accordance with the law is a very small price to pay in return for the advantage of being the government."  How often people have cried out at the indignities and atrocities of armies. Particularity sharp in our national conscience are the atrocities committed by Nazi Germany and the continued human rights violations in Africa. How stinging is has been for the American people to hear such charges levied against our troops. Abu Grahib has hurt the moral of our nation more than our administration has admitted. It was said to young German men during World War II that; "Be brave, get to the front, and surrender to the first American you see." Believe it or not this mind set saved thousands of American troops' lives. How I would scold the leader of our free people to allow such a scandal to manifest, it is his duty to maintain the discipline and method of our attacking armies.  To those who shame those that question our war I say the shame belongs to you. Ideologies of leaders must encompass their abilities to wage war, our current leader has certainly lacked the ability of a great leader. It is time for our nation to seek out and find great leaders, but first it is our responsibility to remove bad ones.  JD Brenny
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Urbanstar Radio now features the complete work from the slick one himself.  As a bonus for you, Roy, it is read by the author!  This series will be divided into six parts which will update each week.   urlLink Listen Now !
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In the continuing battle to distract voters from real issues, the House of (Mis)Representatives has a bill that just passed committee to ban states from recognizing gay marriages. This comes on the heels of the Senates failure to pass a proposed constitutional amendment defining marriage as between a man and a woman. This sort of posturing is only meant push the buttons of&nbsp;those who feel that moral(religious) issues are more important than poverty and health care and unnecessary military action. It upsets me that we hear more about this than real problems. I'm tired of all of this smoke being blown. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I look forward to my next journey for it will bring together long separated friends. Loveland, Colorado lies on the frontal edge of the great Rocky Mountains and is home to the Bailey family. John and Dustin are brothers who spend quite a bit of time wandering those mountains. Far more time than I have spent and I can see the wisdom it has brought in their smiles. For all my time spent in the mountains I have a seen things that speak so much clearer than any bible. Truly this earth is god's message to us, it speaks so loudly that most can't hear it. That's the thing with altitude, can't hardly breath so you don't talk too much and pretty soon your brain starts working and your ears start listening and things begin to make so much more sense. But enough of all this.   The trip will be of limited time. Three days in the Rawas, living and breathing in the high alpine meadows. Everything to survive your going to damn blasted carry. With mountain hiking there really are only two directions, up and down. Five extra pounds will dog your existence in the high country, lightness is key. Most people spend their lives trying to fill a home with conveniences to exist and fill space. Backpacking employs the direct opposite of this behavior. Take only what you need to survive. This is never exactly true as long as you prepare properly, there are lots of luxuries that carry quite easily. As to our exact departure point into the wilderness I cannot be sure. I have left these details to the experts. John is lanky but shows that he spends his days working in a trench and his weekends in the mountains. Dustin is mostly quiet and friendly. He is the younger brother and I think probably a little crazy. Crazy only in the sense that does not seem to notice incredible risk. My younger brother and I are going to drive out there in a marathon 990 mile 15 and a half hour car ride past farm field after farm field. The high mountains are such a climax to the plains nary a road or farm implement to catch your eye. No where is this phenomenon more evident than the Grand Tetons for those who have seen. I feel reasonably comfortable with this trip and have some reliability in my gear. It is always good to bring a camera for there is no shortage of post card like visages.&nbsp; 7/14/04   It is customary and right for the inexperienced to pack too heavily, a healthy lesson is needed in such matters. However the inexperienced must take care to bring the necessary provisions and gear or a healthy lesson may turn perilous. The first bit of gear that will become very intiment to you will be your pack. Carried for days at a time it must be light, comfortable,&nbsp; and be able to carry everything you intend to bring.&nbsp;The temptation to get an overly large backpack is commonplace and it seems most&nbsp;backpackers live with this mistake. Perhaps the wisest move is to decide on what you will fill your pack with before you purchase one. Internal frame backpacks are more appropriate than external frame ones for the amount of gear I would recommend carrying. The high counntry retains its snow throughout most of the summer, this&nbsp;is a testiment to cold and unpredictible weather. The thought of laying out under the stars by a warm fire must be abandoned. Not only will you freeze and get wet, but fires are generally prohibited in the now drought stricken west. This means you must pack along your shelter and bed. Your tent must be light and packable and fit only one or two.&nbsp; The&nbsp;same goes for your sleeping bag and sleeping pad. I would certainly take advantage of current technology backpacking equipment. It is somewhat costly but far&nbsp;superior than what&nbsp;has been available historically.&nbsp;&nbsp;7/15/04   JD Brenny   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Home is something that can be truly appreciated only after an extend stay and weary travel. We live in a beautiful country, large and formidable. One that could only fall like the giant sequoias, slowly rotted from the inside by parasites and toppled by a strong wind. But even in the decay of a mighty giant growth sprouts and the dream lives on. Much can be learned in 5311 miles more than I would care to type anyway. Tales and pictures are, however, no substitute for the actual experience. I would suggest undertaking a journey across your native land. See what many have fought and bled for, I am sure that with enough exposure it will become a true friend to you. A relationship will develop that will truly be symbiotic and deep down this relationship is genetically linked to the emotion we call happiness.   To my friend Jim.   The discovery trail seems like an excellent plan. However I believe I could lead you on a more pleasing and wilder adventure that would certainly be more taxing and wondrous. Nebraska, Iowa, Kansas and some of the southern areas would certainly bring about monotonous scenery. And maybe if Bush gets re-elected the destination is all wrong. Certainly the trail misses some of the grandest beauty our country has to offer. If it could be my living to lead people by foot through the last of the wildest vestiges our country has to offer I would gladly embrace it. We must understand that the immigrants and their descendents have waged war on this country's landscape since they have arrived. The mountains are the last bastions of all things still wild. It is here we view and enjoy the last remnants of an exiled world. All exiles everywhere have taken to the mountains in crisis it is here that a unique strength is developed, a strength that rivals the command of fire and the knowledge of machines.  I think the true way to discover this country via the available trail networks is north on Appalachian Trail, west across the North Country Trail, South on the Continental Divide Trail and back north on the Pacific Crest Trail. I think overall it might be some 11,000 miles give take a few. But the experience would shape your life forever and imbue one with great strength and great truth. It might be a hasty thing to tackle in one trip.   JD Brenny 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just read a news report on Yahoo news that the department of Homeland Security has a plan in place to delay the Nov 2 elections in case of a terrorist attack. This raises a lot of disturbing questions. Like would a threat of attack delay things, who decides what is credible and real, and how do You tell who has voted during the day if the attack comes in the middle of the day. Maybe it's just my paranoid mind in action, but I see this as a plan to stop the elections if the polls and trends don't look like our current president will win. Somebody please ease my fears.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This Land Jibjab.com  It is a must see......   urlLink http://jibjab.com/  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Actual employment ad posted on onwisconsin.com.....text color/font size/italics are&nbsp;by my hand.  urlLink   urlLink    urlLink  &nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink  &nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink  &nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink  &nbsp;  urlLink     urlLink     urlLink   urlLink   Job Information Job Title:  ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT: Catapult Lear Source:  Classified Ad       Location:  Milwaukee, WI  Date Posted:  07-18-2004  Job Description Description:  ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT: Catapult Learning (formerly Sylvan Education Solutions), is the country's     leadeing  provider of high quality educational services to schools, school districts and community organizations   . We are currently seeking a detail oriented, energetic ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT to support our programs in the Milwaukee area. RESPONSIBILITIES:Maintains calendars, schedules meetings and interviews, makes travel arrangements, assist with special projects and events, directs and field inquiries for managers. May communicate by phone or email on behalf of managers. Communicates with employees, outside agencies and vendors, and internal Catapult customers by phone or email. Process purchase orders, check requests, invoices, expense reports, and assists with tracking budget expenses. Processes and transmits correspondence, agreements, contracts, and other documents. Provides support in research of files and data as necessary. Works on projects and committees as needed. COMPENSATION: commensurate with skills and experience. Extensive benefit package availableREQUIREMENTS: Minimum of three years adminstrative experience, preferably in a fast paced corporate environment. Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, and Lotus Notes. Strong organizational ability and skill is prioritizing multiple responsibilities. Strong customer service and communication skills in both oral and written communication. Ability to be flexible in terms of managing multiple priorities, and in working overtime as needed for special projects and important deadlines. Fax resumes to  (414)672-1089 or email to  urlLink lori.bares@educate.com  No phone calls, please  OutOfTheBlue@urbanstar.com urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Our government has repeatedly told us that we all should prepare for a likely terrorist attack. But should such an event happen what should we do? How will we survive? The government has the answer. Its all there in the trusty US Army Survival Manual. In the event of a catastrophic attack on the infrastructure of our society we should expect to be able to survive with out any modern convenience and be able to procure water and food from nature. Have you thought about this?   "With training, equipment, and the will to survive, you will find you can overcome any obstacle you may face. You will survive."   Much is said about the will to survive and how to achieve it and rightly so. In such an event we must remain cool, resist panic, and stay safe.&nbsp;You may be isolated, cold, in pain, injured or in shock, thirsty and hungry. All these scenarios are possible and probable according to our government. Do not fear, the manual will take you through each scenario frankly and provide the minimal equipment required to survive in any environment. Even if you should find yourself completely bare and without tools and provisions the manual offers sound advice.   All Americans must understand the potential situations terrorists might impose on us. Become familiar with topics like:   Survival Planning:  "Survival Planning is nothing more than realizing that something could happen that would put you in a survival situation and, with that realization, taking steps to increase your chances of survival. In other words, survival planning is being prepared."   Survival Medicine:  "In a survival situation it is you who must know what to do to stay healthy. In other words, you must know how to avoid illnesses and how to prevent and treat injuries."   Field Expedient Weapons and Tools:  "The main reason why you need a weapon is so you can hunt on the move. A field expedient weapon is not intended to protect you from enemy soldiers, but it can extend your area of defense beyond your fingertips. It can also give you a feeling of security."   Water Procurement:  "Water is one of your most urgent needs in a survival situation. You can't live long without it, especially in hot areas where you lose much through sweating. Even in cold areas, you need a minimum of 2 quarts of water a day to maintain efficiency."   Wild Plants for Food:  "After water, food is your most urgent need. So in a survival situation you should always be on the lookout for wild foods and live off the land whenever possible. Save your rations, if any, for emergencies."   Wildlife for Food:  "Meat is more nourishing than plant food. In fact, it may even be more readily available in some places. But to get meat, you need to know the habits of, and how to capture, the various wildlife."   Shelters:  "A shelter can protect you from the sun, insects, wind, rain, snow, hot or cold temperatures, and enemy observation. It can give you a feeling of well being; it can help you maintain your will to survive."   Firebuilding:  "A fire can fulfill several needs: It can keep you warm; it can keep you dry; you can use it to cook food, to purify water, and to signal."   Water Crossings:  "When you are in a survival situation in any area except the desert, you are likely to encounter a water obstacle."   Field Expedient Direction Finding:  "There are several methods by which you can determine direction by using the sun and the stars. You can come up with a more nearly true direction if you have knowledge of the terrain of the territory or country."   Signaling:  "One of your first concerns when you find yourself in a survival situation is to communicate with your friends/allies."   Desert, Tropical, Arctic and Sea Survival:  "Survival in a desert, or in any area, depends upon your knowledge of the terrain and the basic climatic elements, your ability to cope with them, and your will to live."   Knots:  "In a survival situation, you need to know how to tie different knots and what knot to use to meet a particular need. For instance, making snares, field expedient weapons, and shelters requires the use of knots."   All these topics make for fine bedside reading. The knowledge contained moves beyond the realm of survival and into practical living. If we truly want to ignore the terrorists we must be able to live without and modern convenience and not just survive, but thrive.   JD Brenny    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As a student of UWM I must have walked past Sala da Pranzo hundreds of times. Its located on New Hampshire Avenue just off Downer Avenue. It always seemed to be a bit hobnobby, but respectable and the patrons all seemed to be enjoying wine way to early in the morning. It seemed pricey yet maintaining that 'Eastside Upper Class' sense of casual. For my wife's birthday I decided to finally check this place out. I enjoy a well cooked meal and have found that few restaurants deliver. I make nearly all my diners and practice in self taught culinary art. If I go out to eat I like to find unique and non-chain restaurants. Milwaukee and the surrounding suburbs happen to have a remarkable amount of them, though they are hidden. Sala da Pranzo certainly measured up. They serve mainly Italian dishes and use all fresh ingredients. The menu is surprisingly large and their prices reasonable. 50&nbsp;bucks for an all out dinner for two including soup,&nbsp;salad and&nbsp;drinks. An easy $25&nbsp;lunch for two could be had.&nbsp;I would recommend giving this restaurant a try for some non-occasion. Bring a friend or a lover.&nbsp;The drive there is a scenic and&nbsp;enjoyable cruise up the lake shore and into&nbsp;the old fashionable end of Milwaukee.&nbsp;I would recommend coming into town a little before your meal and take a walk in Veterans&nbsp;park or out on the McKinley Pier. Perhaps&nbsp;just park far enough away to get a nice walk through&nbsp;the neighborhood, but come in ready to relax and eat.&nbsp;   JD Brenny   Sala da Pranzo  2613 E. Hampshire Ave.  Milwaukee, WI 53211  Phone: 414-964-2611    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mary received&nbsp;a call from Mayor Tom Barrett today inviting us to see John Edwards in Milwaukee this Satuday, July 24th.   Free tickets are available&nbsp; through the following link:    urlLink Tickets: Edwards Rally Milwaukee, WI   The event will be held at King Park, 1531 W. Vliet Street .&nbsp; Gates open at 10:00 A.M.&nbsp;   Because of security, no bags, umbrellas, or outside signs will be allowed. Please limit personal items. This event will take place RAIN OR SHINE.   Hope to see you all there.   Jim   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No, not Edwards. &nbsp;   &nbsp; Together with John Lennon&nbsp;at a 1971 anti-war rally in New York. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Let me begin by saying that this article&nbsp;sites&nbsp;no scientific evidence. As a&nbsp;honeymoon idea I thought it might not be&nbsp;a bad idea to drive clear cross the country&nbsp;in a rented car, stopping along&nbsp;the way&nbsp;at a few of our national parks and monuments. Leaving from Hartland, Wisconsin with aim to hit the coast in Washington. The route would have to be a strategic one to hit a good number of these national interests. It came down to the South Dakota Badlands N.P., Mount Rushmore N.M., Jewel Cave N.M., Yellowstone N.P., Grand Teton N.P., Craters of the Moon N.M., Mount Rainier N.P., Olympic N.P., Cascades N.P., Glacier N.P., and Theodore Roosevelt N.P. How much time I wondered, more importantly how much time could I get. Workplaces tend to be slightly lenient to newlyweds so I managed to get 16 consecutive days off. With $1800 in wedding money from my loving relatives and friends Casey and I were off. It should also be noted that Casey is 24 weeks pregnant with our child Kali. Casey and I are reasonably adept travelers, in fact,&nbsp;24 weeks ago Casey and were exploring the Big Sur National Forest in California. I especially live for the traveling, I toil away hours planning and take great pleasure in exploring.  &nbsp;  Our&nbsp;journey together began Saturday 6/26/04 our wedding day. The weather, in a dramatic change became very pleasant, 70 degrees and not a cloud in the sky. We married and had the reception at my parents house in Eagle, WI. Marriage ceremony and reception went excellent. Got a somewhat late start on Sunday because a friend of mine demanded that we bet him to walk over the bonfire coals&nbsp;barefoot. We all&nbsp;knew it was&nbsp;sheer madness and refused to bet him, but he did it anyway and&nbsp;was&nbsp;driven to&nbsp;the&nbsp;hospital&nbsp;$63 richer, but with severe 2nd burns on his feet. &nbsp;The drive to South Dakota is relatively uneventful. Minnesota gives your eyes a wonderful welcome crossing the Mississippi river, but soon glazes them over with endless miles of flat cornfields. Wind mills become tremendously interesting. Made it as far as Souix Falls, SD on our first day of driving. 505 miles.&nbsp;   Day 3. The next morning a Monument to the Native American Cow god was the first thing I ran across. It is interesting that all the cattle that are penned in with it stay on the backsides of hills, careful to keep out of sight of the thing. Local gossip claims that the cows approach the monument at 7:00 am and 7:00 pm and they bow their heads in a strange prayer. Very strange indeed.&nbsp;It appears that human life in SD is wholly dependent on billboards and that without them travelers might get the notion that the state is more or less devoid of motels and amusement. I got suckered into stopping at the worthless Corn Palace, the feature content of about 40 billboards. The Badlands take you by surprise, they appear to be giant sand castles grossly out of scale. All the spires and knife ridges, as far as the eye can see, have exactly the same red and tan color pattern and all the sediment segments line up perfectly over a huge expanse.&nbsp; Entirely logical when you think about it, but the brain stumbles at the sight of it. Up close the first thing you notice is how incredibly fun they are to climb around and or on. At the first pullout kids are crawling all over the ridges. After exploring the nature trails and boardwalks I would recommend getting off the trails and search for fossils. Search the yellow clay areas for the best chance of finding any. I searched&nbsp;but&nbsp;yielded no fossils. Casey and I hiked into the wilderness a bit with a blanket and watched the sun set and the acrobatics of some bats. There was a full moon and more stars than I have ever noticed, we had plenty of light to make it back to our little cabin inside the park. 790 miles.  &nbsp;  Day 4. After 1,247&nbsp;signs, finally we have arrived in Wall Drug. The ultimate&nbsp;setup job. Wall to wall junk, everything for sale. I considered myself lucky to leave only with a free bumper sticker.&nbsp;&nbsp;The first thing you notice coming into Mt. Rushmore is how goddamn pretty the Blackhills are. You don't get a chance to really walk amongst them inside the park. Getting off the lone trail is prohibited and strictly enforced. The monument was quite impressive, but my mind was preoccupied with the question of "Why are the flags still at half mast for Reagan?" and with the disappointment of being unable to really explore the land. Jewel Cave was a little more interesting. We took a tour through the cave. 723 steps that my wife was dreading and an hour and twenty minutes underground. Worth every penny and the pain of traveling with a group and tour guide. We continued west and called it a night in Moorcroft, WY. It was a cheap motel and I haggled the guy down 15 bucks on the room, but it still was not worth it. Casey claims to have come away with flea bites. 1014 miles.  &nbsp;  Day 5. There are&nbsp;vast expanses&nbsp;of our country that are hardly worth opening your eyes for. The stretch between Moorcroft, WY and Yellowstone N.P.&nbsp;happens to be&nbsp;one of them. Right in the middle of this expanse, however, is the first taste of the mountains&nbsp;to come.&nbsp;The&nbsp;Bighorn Mountains rise like an oasis&nbsp;in the high dessert. Chances are you might even&nbsp;see moose or two. The Bighorn's also leave you with the big question, to take highway 14 or alt 14 through&nbsp;different passes. As it was explained to me, both routes are equally long and equally pretty. But, Alt 14 has a steep grade, 10%, and&nbsp;a larger number of&nbsp;switchbacks and one might&nbsp;infer that&nbsp;it&nbsp;would require a bit more road driving skill to negotiate. It seemed to&nbsp;me that alt 14 has a few more towns along it that will slow you down and generally depress you than hwy 14. Getting&nbsp;past Cody, WY is when things begin to look up. The&nbsp;drive into Yellowstone is gorgeous and once your there you might as well hit every big&nbsp;attraction.&nbsp;It is not hard&nbsp;to take hundreds of pictures in Yellowstone, everyone there does. The thermal areas of Yellowstone rival the Badlands in strangeness and are probably unrivaled. However, there is a price to pay for witnessing this spectacle of nature. Lots&nbsp;of people and lots of traffic. 600,000 years ago&nbsp;Yellowstone catastrophically blew up, unfortunately there were not many tourists there to experience it.&nbsp;Casey and I toured the east side of the Grand Loop road and stopped at the mud volcano area and&nbsp;at the upper falls of the Yellowstone river. The bison and elk are numerous along the roadways and care little for&nbsp;traffic&nbsp;or&nbsp;gawkers. We stayed&nbsp;two nights in a&nbsp;cozy little cabin in Mammoth Hot Springs. The hot springs area itself,&nbsp;consists of very unusual terraces, bone white and where the&nbsp;boiling hot,&nbsp;mild sulfuric acid solution runs&nbsp;a weird algae like organism&nbsp;grows. They are called&nbsp;thermophiles and they range in color from&nbsp;shades of orange and red to white. 1447 miles.&nbsp;   Day&nbsp;6. Casey and I drove down the westside of the loop to check out the&nbsp;various geyser basins and, of course, to witness Old&nbsp;Faithful blast off.&nbsp;The Park is beginning to recover from the 1988 fire that&nbsp;burned most of&nbsp;Yellowstone and most of the lodgepole pines are only about 10 ft in height.&nbsp;The forests are littered with old skeletons&nbsp;that tower over the newly emerging forest. But&nbsp;lodgepole&nbsp;pine forests never have compared with the mighty redwood and spruce forests of the western coast or the oak savannahs of the&nbsp;Midwest. Certainly it is not the reason anyone comes to Yellowstone. The whole&nbsp;westside&nbsp;is scattered with geyser basins each with an assortment of unique&nbsp;geysers, pools, mudpots and fumaroles. The air stinks of sulfur and&nbsp;you can not&nbsp;help but&nbsp;think&nbsp;you&nbsp;are on some strange planet or visiting the planet in a much older time.&nbsp; The Old Faithful area&nbsp;has the most&nbsp;abundant and revered&nbsp;&nbsp;of the features and is subsequently the most packed with visitors. The trade off is worth it, but they do not call Yellowstone the Disneyland of national parks for nothing. After spending the day shoulder to shoulder on the boardwalks and bumper to bumper on the roads the most relaxing thing to do is take a one way trail into the wilderness and quickly leave that&nbsp;to go completely free style through the mountains. This is not allowed in the thermal areas and would defy common sense.&nbsp;But I guarantee you that you will not see another soul in the mountains though. Yellowstone encompasses 2 million acres and 2 million visitors spend their time on maybe 200 acres.&nbsp;Really getting away from the roads impresses you with the fact that Yellowstone is more than just geysers,&nbsp;pools, mudpots and&nbsp;fumaroles.   Day 7. The drive south out of Yellowstone pits beauty and frustration in an all out slugfest that continues long past Grand Teton N.P. However, beauty lands a good blow to frustration when the Grand Teton peaks loom off to the west. The Grand Teton view almost puts every other scenic mountain view to shame. With no foothills the peaks climb from a flat plain to nearly two miles into the sky. Pioneers who came into this valley on their way to&nbsp;California must have cursed their luck.&nbsp;This is actually how the town of Jackson was created, tired and smart pioneers who knew damn well they was no way in hell&nbsp;they were gonna make it over them mountains with a wagon. After leaving the park we&nbsp;drove on for Craters of the Moon N.M.&nbsp; The drive through southern Idaho demands the rational mind to question why anyone would like to&nbsp;live there.&nbsp;Very dry and very flat. In the middle of the dryness and flatness the&nbsp;Devil staked his claim and decorated&nbsp;his area with homely lava flows and black craters. All quite recently too, right around the time Christ&nbsp;was born. Coincidence? Anyway, the Devil&nbsp;has a unique eye for&nbsp;landscaping that is worth checking out and spending the night in. Plus for those looking to check out&nbsp;all the wierd lava flow features, Idaho is a lot closer than Hawaii. Despite the illegality of rock collecting it is almost impossible not to take&nbsp;home just a little piece of hell. 1920 miles&nbsp;   Day 8. From Craters of the Moon N.M. to Mount Rainier N.P., this shakes up to be a long drive. Luckily we gain an hour briefly catching up with the sun. Eastern Oregon is the only highlight of this drive Before arriving to the park. A short foray into the mountains&nbsp;with&nbsp;a different type of pine tree growing all over them. Once you finally get inside Washington a bit and Mt. Rainier first comes into sight it is imperative that you stop for fresh cherries, provided that they are in season which is about all summer. The Wenatchee National Forest that borders Mt. Rainier is absolutely beautiful.&nbsp;In fact all of western Washington can be summed up quite nicely in three words; "Pretty damn pretty." Mount Rainier towers over some other rather tall mountains and lush alpine meadows home to hundreds of species of wildflower. We stayed in Paradise, WA&nbsp;in an old&nbsp;chalet. &nbsp;I hiked up 1500 ft from the inn to where a thick fog had developed. The rest of the surrounding mountains were visible, but there was about 7000 ft of Mt. Rainier that was still shrouded. Much of my climb was over snow and I passed a few downhill skiers on my way up. Supposedly&nbsp;at this time of year and especially because it was the Fourth of July weekend the park is supposed to be packed, even impossible to park.&nbsp;Thankfully,&nbsp;this was not the case and the neat old lodge we stayed in was relatively quiet. The crowd that this place gathers consists of mainly foreigners and classy Americans. Casey and I do not fit the mold, but are hardly ones to care. At the 'lounge' I demanded that the bartender stop playing godawful Sting music and I slipped in a Muddy Waters CD of mine. This greatly improved the atmosphere&nbsp;of the place and landed me free beers for the rest of the evening. 2554 miles.   ....To be continued  &nbsp;  JD Brenny                   urlLink Wedding Pic.JPG    urlLink Badlands.JPG    urlLink Jewel Cave.JPG    urlLink Mammoth Hot Springs.JPG     urlLink Morning Glory pool.JPG    G urlLink rand Teton.JPG    urlLink Craters of the Moon.JPG     urlLink Mt Rainier.JPG    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To post extremely bad poetry whenever I feel like it.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Thanks!  &nbsp;  With that said, I'd like to point out our date of July 22 as our&nbsp;originally projected first print date.&nbsp; I'm impressed with the contributions so far, and have been getting positive feedback from those who are already checking us out.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I'm going to take new works in progress up to the 22nd and ask that we complete those by the end of the month.&nbsp; I have been talking to some of you about this and want to get the word out that we are contemplating several ideas as to&nbsp;how our site will take&nbsp;printed&nbsp;form.&nbsp; Ideas are welcome. And, there have been very good ones&nbsp;already.&nbsp; I'll speak to each of you individually about this.&nbsp; One thing I really want to get done is the audio interviews with all writers.&nbsp; If you have already written an article, you have mail waiting from me regarding this.  &nbsp;  Statisic: our site received 52,006 hits in the month of June.&nbsp; 27% of those hits were to old pages on our server relating to flash mobs.&nbsp; The rest are related to our new blog. Pretty impressive.&nbsp; Type a phrase from our writings into the Google search engine and you'll find that many times our site comes up as one of the first few listings.  &nbsp;  So, keep those ideas coming!&nbsp; I know many of us have been extremely pre-occupied with the Bush administration, and understandably so.&nbsp; This will inevitably be a main topic up until the elections, but I'm going to try to expand my one-track-mind to cover other areas as well.&nbsp; We already have a lot to work with.  &nbsp;  Thanks again.  &nbsp;  Jim   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I go for price when I visit the grocery store.  So, price has made organic produce scarce in our home.  The other day, the bananas were looking a little old and brown at Pick 'n' Save.  However, the organic bananas looked fresh. They were only 20 cents per pound more, so I brought them home.  The difference with the kids was amazing.  Usually, I can't get my kids to finish a whole banana, and a lot goes to waste.  With the organic, both kids finished the whole banana, then asked for more.  The taste must be the reason.  I tried one myself, and it does taste much more like a banana.  My pocketbook is already crying out in pain because I know more organic produce is to follow.  But, if we can have less waste, I think the extra cost might be worth it.  More to follow....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        By J.R. Engeriser    How do you stop the Bush hate machine?  Take away the ammunition.  Last night we witnessed the three greatest Democratic speeches of our new 21st century, those of Al Gore, Jimmy Carter, and Bill Clinton at the Democratic National Convention.  In a work of brilliance, the Democrats clearly set the pace for a strong race.  Any perception of a negative campaign has been erased.  I present you with the new Democratic Party, with a positive message pointing ahead of and beyond failed Republican leadership.   "Take it from me -- every vote counts"     Al Gore,  knowing the unhealed wounds of the 2000 election, was not afraid to speak the truth about what happened four years ago.  He allowed us to laugh about it, as we needed to, saying "you know the old saying: You win some, you lose some. And then there's that little-known third category", referring to our last election that was ultimately never resolved, leading to the Supreme Court appointment of George W. Bush.  "And let's make sure that this time every vote is counted. Let's make sure not only that the Supreme Court does not pick the next president, but also that this president is not the one who picks the next Supreme Court," he said.  Addressing the Bush invasion of Iraq that has caused world outrage, Gore continues "Wouldn't we be better off with a new president who hasn't burned his bridges to our allies, and who could rebuild respect for America in the world? Isn't cooperation with other nations crucial to solving our dilemma in Iraq? Isn't it also critical to defeating the terrorists?"   "We have to be crystal clear about the threat we face from terrorism. It is deadly. It is real. It is imminent. But in order to protect our people, shouldn't we focus on the real source of this threat: The group that attacked us and is trying to attack us again -- al-Qaida, headed by Osama Bin Laden? Wouldn't we be safer with a president who didn't insist on confusing al-Qaida with Iraq? Doesn't that divert too much of our attention away from the principal danger?"   "We cannot lead if our leaders mislead"     Jimmy Carter  took the stage next, giving his first speech at a Democratic National Convention since he accepted his nomination in 1980.  Carter's words, spoken softly and eloquently, hit hard with a concise truth not heard in quite a while.   Carter made a significant connection between George W. Bush's sketchy military record and his choices regarding Iraq: "As many of you know, my first chosen career was in the United States Navy, where I served as a submarine officer. At that time, my shipmates and I were ready for combat and prepared to give our lives to defend our nation and its principles."  "At the same time, we always prayed that our readiness would preserve the peace. I served under two presidents, Harry Truman and Dwight Eisenhower, men who represented different political parties. Both of whom had faced their active military responsibilities with honor."  "They knew the horrors of war, and later, as commanders-in-chief, they exercised restraint and judgment and had a clear sense of mission. We had confidence that our leaders, military and civilian, would not put our soldiers and sailors in harm's way by initiating 'wars of choice' unless America's vital interests were endangered."  "We also were sure that these presidents would not mislead us when it came to issues involving our nation's security. Today, our Democratic party is led by another former naval officer - one who volunteered for military service. He showed up when assigned to duty, and he served with honor and distinction."   "John Kerry said, 'Send Me'"    Bill Clinton,  introduced by Senator Hillary Clinton, climaxed the evening with words that invoked a frenzy of tears and enthusiastic support.  He spoke of his new financial status, being in the top 1% of the nation's most wealthy, and how well he is now taken care of by the Republican Party:  "When I was in office, the Republicans were pretty mean to me. When I left and made money, I became part of the most important group in the world to them. At first I thought I should send them a thank you note -- until I realized they were sending you the bill."  "They protected my tax cuts while:  - Withholding promised funding for the Leave No Child Behind Act, leaving over 2 million children behind  - Cutting 140,000 unemployed workers out of job training  - 100,000 working families out of child care assistance  - 300,000 poor children out of after school programs  - Raising out of pocket healthcare costs to veterans  - Weakening or reversing important environmental advances for clean air and the preservation of our forests."  The Democratic platform this year is out to bring America together as a nation, as the Republican agenda is seen as of late to be one of 'divide and conquer'.  Anticipating the negative attacks from the right, Democrats are getting a good head start at taking away some of the ammunition surely set to be soon fired off. Repulicans are seen to falter if the focus is directed mainly at the issues.   You may view the full text of each speech by following these links:   urlLink Text of Al Gore's speech    urlLink Text of Jimmy Carter's Speech    urlLink Text of Bill Clinton's Speech    NEW!   urlLink Text of Barack Obama's Speech 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a picture sent to me by Jon Bailey of the BBB Guide Service. Jon is a long time friend of mine and I plan to meet with&nbsp;him this coming weekend. The itinerary calls for a Leftover Salmon show at the Mishwaka amphitheater in the Poudre&nbsp;river canyon, CO (festival style) and for&nbsp;a couple&nbsp;days spent in&nbsp;God's&nbsp;country.&nbsp;We can be sure that a story will come out of this weekend.  Here's a peek at a few nice mule deer. It'll brighten your day.   JD Brenny    urlLink himountainmuleys.jpg     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is interesting.  Why is it that you feel you are being spied on?  That is to say, it seems that you are connecting this to your involvement with the Urban Star. Let's try to put this into perspective.  First of all, relax!  The pictures below are of paintball equipment.  I only posted them because I wanted everyone else to experience the same feeling I did before I found out what it was. It made me feel something that is uniquely post-9/11, unique to this moment in time when neo-conservatism is well on it's way to completely taking over this country. A time that government agents don't need a reason to invade your home or put you in a prison suit behind barbed wire indefinately.  You are not alone in your fear of this site. One of our first contributors, (an avid supporter of the Patriot Act I might add), was scared away by an ill-worded post here.  I spoke with him in person, explaining that his own admitted fear of free speech in action negated his defense of the Patriot Act.  He did not agree.  I am hoping he will return.  Let it be know that there are no boogie men at the Urban Star.  No terrorists here.  Just some harmless activists and free thinkers.  Perhaps printing the thoughts of normal everyday people is dangerous in some minds.  But, that is only due to the fear mongering of the regime that illegally occupies the United States, the Bush administration.  I would ask all to please ignore the solicited fear, tune in to the Democratic National Convention this week, and remember that this can still be America if we don't make the same mistakes we made in 2000.  I don't wish to make light of your plight, however, Cass.  Please tell us why you feel you are being specifically targeted.  How do you know that the strange men at your door aren't just Jehovah's Witnesses?  Also, please explain the racist links.  I am quite sure your reasons for posting them are noble.  An explanation, however, is  required.  Mostly, I hope you are safe and that you can rest at ease.  Jim 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A neighbor borrowed my digital camera and left these photos on the memory stick. Click to enlarge.   urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink    urlLink      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you saw John Kerry's speech at the Democratic National Convention,  you may very well agree that it was his best speech so far. He deliverered an excited, presidential if you will, address.  He was actually sweating a little. Believe it or not, sweat transfers to sincerity on camera. There are many subtleties that affect the perceptions of a candidate. Sweat can transfer to smarmey, as it did for Tricky Dickey back in the 60's. Kerry's sweat worked in his favor, given his usual stiff presentation. Some say "why focus on such a small thing as appearance?" The answer is that the media picks up on these things. At least one pundit mentioned his perspiration.  A reporter from the Boston Globe (he wears a bow tie and it was on Charlie rose) mentioned "jumpers" at one of Edward's appearances during the primaries. Jumping is an element that the press uses to gauge how excited the crowd is during a candidate's speech. The more "jumpers" the better. Clinton had this affect on crowds. So did JFK. By all means, when attending any future Kerry appearances: JUMP your heart out! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'll be unable to attend.  Hope some of you can....  Tickets to the Milwaukee rally are available.  What:  John Kerry Rally in Milwaukee   When:  Monday, August 2, 2004  Gates open at 4:30 p.m.   Where: Pere Marquette Park  900 North Plankinton Avenue  Milwaukee, WI   urlLink Click here to print a ticket     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Real audio file added to Urbanstar archives 08/11/2004   urlLink Listen Now: Sut Jhally - September 11th and the Use of Fear   Dr. Jhally is Professor of Communications at the University of Massachusetts at Amherst.  This lecture from November 18th of 2003 is a clear and succinct description of how recent U.S. actions and policies have changed the world, and what is at stake in the the upcoming November elections.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      PDF files added to Urbanstar archives 08/11/2004   U.S. Army Survival Manual FM 21-76   Chapter 01 -  urlLink Introduction  (52KB)  Chapter 02 -  urlLink Psychology of Survival  (56KB)  Chapter 03 -  urlLink Survival Planning and Survival Kits  (29KB)  Chapter 04 -  urlLink Basic Survival Medicine  (248KB)  Chapter 05 -  urlLink Shelters  (310KB)  Chapter 06 -  urlLink Water Procurement  (235KB)  Chapter 07 -  urlLink Firecraft  (182KB)  Chapter 08 -  urlLink Food Procurement  (579KB)  Chapter 09 -  urlLink Survival Use of Plants  (172KB)  Chapter 10 -  urlLink Poisonous Plants  (34KB)  Chapter 11 -  urlLink Dangerous Animals  (81KB)  Chapter 12 -  urlLink Field-Expedient Weapons, Tools, and Equipment  (198KB)  Chapter 13 -  urlLink Desert Survival  (99KB)  Chapter 14 -  urlLink Tropical Survival  (100KB)  Chapter 15 -  urlLink Cold Weather Survival  (244KB)  Chapter 16 -  urlLink Sea Survival  (455KB)  Chapter 17 -  urlLink Expedient Water Crossing  (154KB)  Chapter 18 -  urlLink Field-Expedient Direction Finding  (84KB)  Chapter 19 -  urlLink Signaling Techniques  (208KB)  Appendix A -  urlLink Survival Kits  (138KB)  Appendix B -  urlLink Edible and Medicinal Plants  (23,374KB)  Appendix C -  urlLink Poisonous Plants  (2,573KB)  Appendix D -  urlLink Dangerous Insects and Arachnids  (140KB)  Appendix E -  urlLink Poisonous Snakes and Lizards  (15,977KB)  Appendix F -  urlLink Dangerous Fish and Mollusks  (246KB)  Appendix G -  urlLink Clouds - Foretellers of Weather  (761KB)  Appendix H -  urlLink Contingency Plan of Action Format  (35KB)  
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>