<Blog>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, my interview was rather harrowing yesterday. I was totally nervous going in, but I had a few things going in my favour. First, I'd been through the job interview for this position last year, so I kind of knew what to expect; second, I'd already taken the arduous editing test candidates were subject to, so that helped to ease the tension for me a bit. Finally, having applied for the job last year, I'd had all of this year to plan and come up with ideas as to what I wanted to do with the job.  Those, among other things (including what was apparently a very well-done interview by yours truly), earned me the top job at the newspaper for next year, and I'm totally thrilled. But part of winning meant that another candidate—a friend and colleague whose skills are exemplary—had to lose. I consoled her with kind words and beer, and though I know I should have felt elated last night, I felt uneasy: concerned that she was pissed off at me for winning the job.  Of course, my delusions were unfounded as usual. After a long chat with the losing candidate, I convinced her to apply for one of the other positions on the editorial board (being hired next weekend).  So, for now I can relax and focus on more important things: somehow making it so that Bill Murray wins the Oscar for Best Actor.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm bored and nervous, so I decided to occupy myself with some busy work. Thus: comments! I'm still ironing out the kinks, so bear with me.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I didn't sleep a wink last night. I have a job interview to go to this afternoon, at 2:30. It's not that I'm worried about how I'm going to perform. I'm actually quite confident in my abilities and the ideas I'm planning to bring to the table. No, my anxiety is spawned from a concerned raised by my boss, who was essentially trying to prevent me from applying. Lemme lay it all out for you.  You see, I'm applying to be the head honcho at the newspaper I work at, figuring I've been a part of the organization for about four years now, enough time to watch how things work and generate some new ideas to try out. However, as a result of a superior effort between me and a co-worker, we successfully bid to host a conference here in town. Thus, I took a job as conference co-coordinator. My boss then felt the need to point out that I would never be able to do both jobs (strangely enough, his girlfriend is applying for the same job as I am. Can you say politics?). I know he's wrong—I mean, he doesn't usually show up at work until around 11 in the morning, and he used to spend a good deal of his time lazing about playing video games, so what could he possibly know about having enough time to do other things? But you know, after you hear it enough—these words of discouragement—you tend to start to believe them.  But one of my colleagues e-mailed me this morning, and he had this to say:  "Hey Chief,  Good luck. This thing is yours to lose.  I'm sure you'll do sooper.  See you in the winner's circle."  That made me feel better. Now, I'm going to spend the rest of the morning and afternoon before the interviews talking to myself, practicing what I want to say in my interview. Wish me luck, kids. I'll let you know if I get the job.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I can't really believe what I just read. Apparently,  urlLink Asian Mediawatch  is lobbying hard to make sure that  Lost in Translation , Sofia Coppola's most recent masterpiece, doesn't win a single Oscar this Sunday. They claim that the film is  urlLink racist  and that it perpetuates Japanese stereotypes.  Far be it for me to suggest what people think is and is not racist. Sadly, this is often a matter of perception, and it's such a touchy subject that I don't want to suggest what is and isn't racist, necessarily. In short, if a Japanese person found the film racist, then that's their judgment. What I do take issue with, however, is this statement (from the Guardian online):  "The film has no meaningful Japanese roles, nor is there any significant dialogue between the main characters and the Japanese. Such portrayals perpetuate negative stereotypes and attitudes that are harmful to Asian Americans in the US, where a significant minority of Americans already have negative attitudes towards Asians" (a quote from Asian Mediawatch).  And the question I have in response to this is: did any of the people throwing these claims of racism out there watch the same movie as I did? The film has no meaningful Japanese roles nor significant dialogue between the main characters and the Japanese because that isn't what the movie is about. The movie is about two Americans, masterfully portrayed by Bill Murray and Scarlett Johansson, feeling like fish out of a water in a land that is abjectly foreign to them. It isn't meant to be derogatory, but if the Japanese characters acted like English-fluent Japanese-Canadians or something, there wouldn't have even been a movie to make. Murray and Johansson wouldn't have been fish out of water. They would have been two people visiting a foreign country and having no problem coping with the language and cultural differences.  Asian Mediawatch charges that Coppola maliciously mocked Japanese people's accents by changing "r"s in the script to "l"s. But she had this to say for herself: "Even on our daily call sheets, they would mix up the 'rs' and the 'ls'—all that was from experience, it's not made up. I guess someone has misunderstood my intentions."  I hope  Lost in Translation  does well at the Oscars, especially because I think this is Bill Murray's best movie to date, and an apt example of why everyone should keep their eye on Ms Coppola's career. Now  that's  what burgeoning is all about, my friends.   It sounds like the people levelling these allegations of racism got lost watching  Lost in Translation .
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I would imagine that anyone who reads this is wondering about the title: the musings of a burgeoning journalist. It sounds a little arrogant, I know. Burgeoning, according to my pals  urlLink Merriam and Webster , means "blooming." I don't know if that accurately describes me. Herein lies the arrogance:  I have, for the last three or so years, been working as a volunteer and paid staff member at a student newspaper. Since last September, I've done nothing but churn out a whole lot of opinion articles. Sure, I've written a CD review or four for one of the local entertainment weeklies, but most of my output is opinions. Those hardly constitute journalism, if you ask me. I mean, I think it's important for people to understand the opinions of others, certainly as they relate to issues that affect the majority (or even minority) of people.   But journalism, I think, typically refers to investigating, getting all sides of an issue and then allowing your audience to make their own determinations. Or maybe I'm getting "journalism" and "hard news" confused. Either way, the title of the blog is something of a misnomer for the moment. However, once I finish my time at this student newspaper, I'll be comfortable referring to myself as a "burgeoning journalist." For now, you can all call me a big, fat liar.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, this is my first crack at my first blog. I don't really have anything to fill you in on as yet. But I'll let you know the second I do. Ugh.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know, I know. I should be writing my film studies essay, but I just can't bring myself to write down my ideas. It's the last assignment I have to complete before the last round of final exams of my undergraduate university career... and I couldn't care less.  It's odd; I'll be finished school next year, but I'll still be working on campus. I'm actually really looking forward to next year, though. I mean, I still have to take a course per semester, but it's not really as though those courses are worth anything on paper. They aren't going towards earning me a degree. They're just going to be two classes I take because I want to take them (I'm also required to take them as part of my job next year; you need to be enroled in at least one class per semester), so there's not really any pressure to perform—not to say I ever let that pressure bother me anyhow.  But writing this essay, it's like pulling teeth. And it's totally lame of me to be dithering on this because it's a topic I'm intimately familiar with, and something that I really enjoy:  The Sopranos . I enroled in a "Gangster Film" class this semester, and though I rarely go to class (with this prof, you don't need to. You just need to watch all the films and be very familiar with them) I've enjoyed watching all these awesome gangster movies: the 1932  Scarface ,  High Sierra ,  The Asphalt Jungle  (which stars the same actor who played General Jack D Ripper in  Dr Strangelove )... So many more—too many to mention here.  And I'm writing this essay on the brutality and hilarity of  The Sopranos'  subject matter. I know what I want to say, I'm just too lazy to say it.  I want school to be done.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Roulette Dares (The Haunt of) — The Mars Volta
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm still flirting with the so-called hip hop genre of music. I'm not sure why I didn't dig this stuff before. I think it has to do with the difference in the types of hip hop I've been exposed to over the years. When people say "hip hop," the images I used to conjure included scantily-clad ladies, dripping with sweat, mauling some stylish-yet-rough MC who pays the ladies little attention, and makes sweet love to the camera.  My friend Paul, bless his soul (he's still alive, but I've gone ahead and assumed that his soul hasn't been blessed by either an ordained minister or, you know, a random friend recently), turned me on to this music when we started hanging out a lot together about a year and a half ago, or so. It was weird; this changeover in taste happened at a time in my life when I was also becoming interested in electronic music, something I credit my friends Geoff and Biz with to a large degree.   Through all these people, I discovered Amon Tobin, dZihan & Kamien, J5, Common, Deltron 3030... I'm not sure what common themes these groups have. Probably something to do with outstanding sampling and incredibly intelligent-sounding music, both lyrically and sonically.  I know, I know, it probably sounds like total BS. But it's not; every single person for whom I play this music gets this odd gaze in their eyes and invariable asks me why they've never heard this before. "I know," I tell them. "Cool, huh?" Yeah, they say, cool. Hard to even put into words, really. And it isn't as though these people necessarily share the same taste in music with me, generally. To be fair, I have a friend who nearly lost his mind when I played Amon Tobin for him once. "You listen to this shit? Why don't you just slit your wrists, you gloomy fuck?" I think was his response. I have another friend who cannot fathom why I would ever listen to NOFX. I don't know what to tell him. I just like 'em.  But hip hop: this is fine. And I'm not necessarily talking about the mainstream stuff they cram down your throat on MuchMusic. I'm talkin' the stuff that's slightly off the beaten path—lots of people know about this stuff, but not a lot seem to listen to the stuff on a regular basis. I guess they just aren't exposed to it as often through television or radio.  What are you guys listening to these days?  *** iTunes selection of the day: The Extravaganza — Quannum
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There was a song that came out in 1996, or thereabouts; it was called "Banditos," by a mediocre rock 'n roll band called the Refreshments.   I remember Raph, Mark and I loved that song... I'm not sure why anymore.   But I remember us at Raph's house, wearing ties after a drama play, and putting the ties around our heads, declaring ourselves, for some reason, the banditos. That's one memory I glad to have been able to recall.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Banditos — The Refreshments
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm not really sure what got me thinking about this. Something my girlfriend asked me tonight about people I've known who've died. Not an altogether odd topic, I suppose. But, what is especially weird about her line of questioning was that it brought me back to thoughts of a dear friend of mine who passed away about four years ago. His name was Raphael Kloc, and though I didn't realize it then, his life had a fairly significant impact on me. What brought me to the computer tonight is that I'm having a great deal of difficulty recalling memories of him in my mind.  All I can seem to conjure are stills; images, soundbytes, and even brief 10-second scenes of Raph, animated, doing something uniquely "Raph." But the memory stops before I can see it through. It's been cut short. I don't know why—I can only speculate. Maybe it's because old memories of the latter days of high school have been replaced by new memories—of university, of new friends and experiences. But as I was lying in bed tonight, I suddenly experienced a pang of desperation: I don't ever want to forget Raph. And even now, as the memories slip away, I find I need to get some of my memories of him down before they're lost forever in the folds of my cortex.  The most recent memory I have of Raph is his funeral. It wasn't a conventional event, most likely because Raph died when he was only 20 years old. However, while I recall feeling sorrow, I wasn't excessively sad at Raph's loss. You see, Raph lived with cancer just about all of his life. He had it in his brain, and on his shoulder (which was subsequently removed, leaving him with very little mobility in his right arm [I think]). Knowing full well that his chances of surviving for very long were slim, Raph was determined to try everything and to drink life to the lees, as Tennyson once said.  I remember walking to the memorial and hating the shoes I was wearing. When I entered the church, I was amazed at just how many different people Raph's life had had an impact on. There must have been about 200 people there. Many of them were friends from my high school. It was weird to see how this one person brought so many different people together.  I remember Raph's parents' house. It's very near to the University, just a few blocks west of the Students' Union Building. I remember the parties Raph used to throw; his parents didn't give a shit that all these underage kids would come over to party, drink, and smoke pot. I remember when a friend of mine was so drunk, he mistook Raph's brother's (Phil) bed for a toilet and actually took a leak on it. Thank god no one was sleeping in it.  I remember Raph's wild golden retriever, Miller. He used to eat the discarded bottle caps that would always end up covering the floor at these underage drinking parties.  I remember directing Raph in a drama play. He played an inventor who took old wine bottles and turned them into lamps. His character thought he was going crazy because people kept appearing in his hotel room; the hotel, you see, had placed too many people in a room, thinking the room was vacant. Hilarity ensued. I remember long days of rehearsal with Raph. That is to say, I remember that we rehearsed for long stretches, but I can't remember the specifics of those rehearsals, and it's driving me crazy. I wish I could remember all the good times... I  do  remember Raph telling me once that the father of his high school sweetheart once chased him out of his girlfriend's bedroom with a shotgun. I believed every word, only to find out—months later—that Raph had just been pulling my chain.  I remember "scones," a little thing I used to say instead of "how's it going." Scones was a fusion of those three words that came to punctuate sentences, and not just mean "how's it going?" That saying was picked up by the entire cast of characters I was directing (co-directing, actually, as my friend Brendan helped to direct the play).  I remember drinking beer, eating steaks, and watching the hockey game with Raph, Mark Pickersgill, and Tyler Riopel at Tyler's place.   All I have left are these vague snap-shots of this person whom I know had a significant impact on my high school years, but who is now more or less just a blur. I wish I could remember more, and I'm actually terrified at the prospect of forgetting all these details. Not just Raph—everything from high school is a blur, and it sure as hell isn't from drinking. Three years ago, this stuff would have been fresh in my mind. Now, all I have are nuggets—minor vagaries—and they aren't enough to satiate my desire to recall those times.  I have an overwhelming desire to go back to my old high school and stroll down the halls to see what sort of images it would conjure. But would going back just ruin it? I would imagine that the school's changed a lot since I've been back there. I want to remember it as it was. Shitty grilled cheese sandwiches that only cost two bucks; deliciously consistent slurpees; Dramafest, yearplay, drama class; almost throwing up on the light board in the drama room when one of my actors forgot his cue... I don't ever want to forget any of this. I'm desperate, in fact, to not forget it. What can I do to remember?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Since I Left You — The Avalanches
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My dear friend Iva sent me the following link: the  urlLink Exorcist , re-enacted in 30 seconds by cartoon bunnies. The music at the end is high-larious.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Heart Attack Man — The Beastie Boys
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Artful? Hardly. Last night I learned that although it may be really, really fun, I'm not very good at dodgeball. Moreover, I'm really out of shape and I need to start doing something about that.  But, that's an entry for another time. Dodgeball was, in short, totally awesome. Everyone had such a great time, I think it's something we'll be doing over the summer a few more times. And it will be cheap. I think we had about 23 people show up, and for gym rental plus ball purchases, everyone pitched in $4. Now that the balls have been purchased, subsequent matches will cost far less.  Anyhow, we played for about two hours, all told. I'm not sure how many matches that was, but the time just flew right by. And there were decidedly fewer injuries than I thought there would be. Andrew, a newcomer to our group of friends, took one hard in the face; Tim got a ball in the face right away in the very first match; a few of us were nailed in the junk; and my friend Rob was nailed in the jugular, causing him to nearly pass out while his body tried to figure out what the hell was wrong with his bloodflow. Good times? Absolutely. Hell, maybe we'll even start up a Dodgeball league locally, or something.  I would imagine that any injuries that resulted could have been prevented if only we'd have played a little more gently. However, I would assert that playing gently in dodgeball is next to impossible. Once you gain possession of the ball, it feels like your hand is on fire, and the only way to receive sharp, delicious relief is to launch the offending ball—as hard as you possibly can—at someone on the other team. It doesn't matter if this person is a friend, has a massive head wound, or is cowering, begging you to just gently hit them so they can be "out." Nope. That ball must be thrown   hard  .  I also realized that no matter how long it's been since you've played dodgeball, you'll be right back at your original skill level the second you start playing. It's innate, I think. Since the dawn of time, dinosaurs threw giant red spalding balls at each other. I think a giant dodgeball was in fact how they became extinct. After the dinosaurs, Man discovered dodgeball, and with it he built himself empires, kingdoms, and nations.   Present day is no different. We are all, in our own ways, dodging balls all the time. The key to winning is to pass the dodgeball to your ousted teammates and bring your team back up to strength. How is this a metaphor for life? It isn't. This is mutha-fatha dodgeball, y'all.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Watch out now — Beatnuts
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm kinda jittery right now, waiting in anticipation for an event that will no doubt launch me back in time to an era where picking one's nose and eating it was cool. You see, after much discussion, a friend of mine has arranged to host a day of  dodgeball . At 5pm MST, I'll be geared up and launching those delightful, 10" big red Spalding balls at my friends.  This event forced me to do a little research on dodgeball. Did you know that there's actually an officially sanctioned international dodgeball association? They're called the  urlLink International Dodge-Ball Federation (IDBF) . Now this in itself is not really that impressive. What's most impressive is my discovery that a film about Dodgeball, starring Vince Vaughn and Ben Stiller, is slated to come out sometime this summer! It's going to be called  urlLink "Underdogs,"  or something. But that isn't even the best part. If you check the IMDB's site, and scroll down the cast list, you'll note that Rip Torn will be playing a character called  Patches O'Houlihan .  I'm not sure our dodgeball outting this evening will come close to Underdogs. I'll let you know.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Wet Blanket — Metric
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Click this  urlLink link . It will tell you what the number one hit song was on the day you were born.  Mine: UK: Xanadu by Olivia Newton-John And The Electric Light Orchestra; US: Still Rock 'N Roll to Me by Billy Joel  *** iTunes selection of the day: District Sleeps Alone Tonight (DJ Downfall Remix) — Postal Service
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After completing my midterm exam today—an ordeal much more built up in my head than was necessary, as I felt quite confident as I wrote it, having only missed one question on the identification of  urlLink Er  in Greek Mythology—I hoofed it on over to the High Level Diner, where Biz, my partner-in-crime who's helping to plan a national conference with me was eagerly awaiting the arrival of the publisher and president of the  urlLink Edmonton Journal , Linda Hughes.  Biz and I chatted briefly about a strategy to convince Ms Hughes that it was in her and her newspaper's best interests to sponsor this conference, which will bring hundreds of the country's future journalists to Edmonton for six days. When Linda finally arrived, I was actually pretty excited, probably more than I should have been. But I should explain: not only is she a successful business woman at the top of the editorial food chain at one of the big Canadian dailies, but she has a  urlLink colourful history  as a very successful journalist. She left me with a very good impression, and she was very curious about our quaint student newspaper and the national cooperative of student newspapers we belong to.  Essentially, Biz and I proposed to her that the Journal should sponsor our conference, and that she should help us to find people to speak at said conference. She was extremely open to the idea, chatting about perhaps sponsoring a Journal meet-and-greet lunch. We discussed editorial issues around the city: in particular, the story of an  urlLink Edmonton Sun  reporter who wrote a story proclaiming that  urlLink 25% of U of A students have STDs  (ha!). She offered to allow our conference delegates to tour both the Journal's newsroom and printing plant, and she expressed a lot of interest in speaking at the conference herself.  It was weird, because here's this pretty small lady, rather plain looking in the sense that although she was a smart dresser, she had very normal hair and facial features. But at the same time, she had this aura of authority about her, an almost ineffable quality of superiority—but not in the sense that she thought she was better than either Biz or myself. Perhaps it was more of a sense of experience and of outstanding intelligence.  Anyhow, I want to marry her now. But don't tell anyone that, least of all her husband.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Sordid — Amon Tobin
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Lies, yes. Lies, because I promised I'd explain the name of this blog. I'm not going to do that, though. I'm going to keep putting it off. In the meantime, I'm worrying about job-related stresses and a midterm exam for which I've done none of the studying I need to do. Seven long chapters to read and understand by next Tuesday. Sheesh.  Oh well. You know what made me smile and forget my worries?  urlLink This ad . I'm not a big fan of kids; I mean, I enjoy playing with them, but thank god they aren't mine.  So, yeah. I'm in a panic about school and work, but I know I'll be fine. All because I don't have kids.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Resist — Lifesavas
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A new  urlLink Teen Girl Squad  is up at  urlLink HomeStarRunner !  *** iTunes selection of the day: Rock and a Hard Place — The Supreme Beings of Leisure
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, we all know I'm employed for the next year. So, how come I can't sleep? It's weird, I think I was so wound up from the pressure I was putting on myself for this thing that I'm now having trouble winding down. Does anyone have any suggestions for how I can get a good night's sleep?  I figured out a band-aid solution, for the time being: it's a solution I've known about for months, but have neglected to invoke because I just forgot about it. I wish I could say that something impressive happened, and that's why I forgot about this band-aid solution——the solution I will reveal soon. Which isn't really a solution to insomnia. But, goddamn, is it ever entertaining.  The solution, dear friends, is a little show called  Space Ghost Coast 2 Coast . It's something you can get on  urlLink DVD  now.  Space Ghost  was a Hanna-Barbera cartoon from the 1960s. It didn't do very well. Eventually, Ted Turner and his Cartoon Network bought HB out, and acquired the animation cells from all of HB's cartoon shows: the  Flintstones , the  Jetsons ,  Yogi Bear , the  Laugh Olympics ... All those classics. Anyhow, the folks at the Cartoon Network took the  Space Ghost  animation cells and created a talk show wherein Space Ghost is the host and his arch-enemies Moltar (from the ovens of Moltor) and Zorak (a giant praying mantis) serve as director and band leader respectively.  I lied, though, it's not really a sleep-aid so much as it's a totally hilarious romp through the comedic fields of non-sequiturs. Buy the DVD today. I promise you'll love it.  Tomorrow, if you're lucky, I might explain why this blog is named the way it is. So long, y'all.   *** iTunes selection of the day: 12:51 — The Strokes
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      [tangent] Did you ever begin an e-mail like this: "---BEGIN TRANSMISSION--" [/tangent]?   [Editor's note: this entry was written over the course of about 70 minutes]   I'm in the office right now, and it's as silent as a morgue just before zombies start eating the face of the lab tech chewing gum and listening to his walkman over there. I so rarely get to be in the office without there being some sort of cacophony other than my own occasional witty remarks and airy nothings. But right now, it's serene. It feels even more quiet knowing that today was the last day of finals and there's virtually no one on campus right now, except for the drunks in the bars. But even they could not ruin this fine moment of peace.  I just checked to see if any of my marks were posted; I passed the gangster film class without going to class once. One down, one more to go.   I'm not so confident about the Classics exam. I remember myths, but I have trouble matching the names to those myths. So, I can never answer questions like "Who was *GREEK HERO*'s son? I guess I wasn't expecting that level of detail. But I'm hoping the written portion—worth more than half the total marks on the exam—pull me through this one, otherwise the class I take next semester won't be an Open Studies class.   But, I'm being pessimistic. Other than that, the rest of my week went fine; I filled most of the time by meeting each one of the newspaper's other staff members to discuss expectations and such for the following year. It's cool to get everyone on the same page, you know? They're all so excited, and it makes me even more excited about next year seeing that 'lil spark in their eyes. But I'm trying to be real about my job: I know the experience of leading this shit-show will either destroy my psyche beyond repair, or raise me to the status of gleaming god of men in both mind and body.   In truth what will happen, however, is that I will gain the twenty pounds I plan to lose over the summer. O, Life!  I'm excited about summer. I'm excited about work (I just spent the last half hour filling my whiteboard with things to do—and everything's ordered with categories!), Vancouver (nori! other-province newspaper-folk, naked hippies, the colour green), sunshine (oh my. two parenthetical phrases precede this one, so I guess precedent dictates I continue with the theme. The theme is: sunshine), fresh air (Yeah Biz, that's right: fresh air. You keep that stank of yours in your own office, my friend), RT's cabin (Sorry! and other assorted boardgames, Bocce [bocci?], camp fire), frisbee (hmm. S'a disc, is all)... It's going to be so fine.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Chocolate Lovely and Marine Machines— Amon Tobin
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For all those of you concerned about the over-use of  urlLink clichés , I declare: procrastination is, indeed, the thief of time. And if procrastination had a name, I believe it would be something like "My Friend Edward." He would speak French, and while I'm studying, Edward would spend his time on my computer looking up random weblinks that are funny. Yes, it's true: there's a little  urlLink Edward  in all of us.  So, what have I been doing instead of reading about  urlLink Odysseus and his many exploits  following the  urlLink Trojan War ? Well, I've played countless hours of  urlLink Grand Theft Auto: Vice City , the result of which is that, thanks to the completion of all the  urlLink paramedic missions , I can now run without getting tired. That is to say that my character in the game, voiced by one  urlLink Ray Liotta , can now run without getting tired. I, the real  urlLink Thomas , am still a fat baby.  Other tasks include adding a different  urlLink comments script  to this blog, so as I can use the trackback function (though I doubt it'll ever truly matter). I also watched  urlLink episode one, of the fourth season of  The Sopranos  . It looks like it's going to be an interesting season indeed. I really wish I got HBO (or its Canadian equivalent) so that I could keep up with the New Jersey family all the time.  Yep, I'll do anything to avoid studying, especially for a first-year mythology course the contents of which I am already familiar.  What do you guys do to avoid studying?  *** Special Note: The first person who can tell me the  Space Ghost Coast 2 Coast  reference in this post will win the CD  urlLink  Earth N Bass Volume 1   (I'm not even joking). iTunes selection of the day: Searchers — Amon Tobin
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Apparently, the United States is employing  urlLink a variety of innovative methods  in order to grate on the nerves of its enemies.  I thought this was kind of funny, because, if I were a US marine, I wouldn't be laughing at all. It doesn't matter what kind of music it is—if it's being played over a loud speaker over and over again, it's going to get annoying no matter what.  So, now you have twitchy marines who are irritated because they have to listen to AC/DC non-stop, and you have a group of Sunni Muslims trying to decipher the sexuality of AC/DC's lyrics. What a fucked up occupation this is.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Smoke & Mirrors — RJD2
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       [Editor's note: this format of blog post was shamelessly stolen from  urlLink Blorg.org's  Smorgasbord. Thanks for the tip, doll.]   8:01pm: Begin watching "John Voight's Convertible" episode of  Seinfeld   8:07pm: Michael Flatley's  Lord of the Dance , as interpreted by Stampy, the giant beast who lives upstairs, begins. By the sounds of it, Stampy dons wool stocks this eve. My irritation is in control.  8:10pm: Commercial tells me that if I chew the right gum, boys will like me. Later, Hilary Duff tells me that what once was a gas station is now a clothing store carrying her brand of shitty togs.  8:12pm: Stampy stomps five times in one spot. I'm distracted.  8:16pm: Jon Voight, the actor, bites Kramer's arm.  8:22pm: A Woody Wood Pecker float pops because of Jerry Seinfeld's negligence.  8:23pm: Stampy paces around her apartment, stopping every two or three seconds, just to fuck with me.  8:25pm: Sounds like she's pacing around in a circle. She just slammed a door.  8:26pm: Acura demands I must buy once of its cars.  It's actually usually worse than this. Normally, Stampy'd have the dishwasher going as she made her rounds. She'd also have stuffed a running jackhammer down her garbage disposal. It wouldn't be so bad if, between these thuding noises, Stampy busted out some "phat" "rhymes," as the kids say. Sadly, she seems to lack any real flow.  I'm starting to suspect that Stampy's actually just one of those giant tin solider wind-up toys that strange people come by every other day to wind up... you know, the ones that sometimes like to wear high heels.   Huh. It sounds like Stampy, the tin solider has, like me, been won over by wiles of an early  Friends  episode. Farewell, gentle reader.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, you know how I was mildly spazzing in my last post? Yeah, that was dumb.  This afternoon's exam was easy—easy to the point where I was kind of offended. I was expecting to be challenged, verily nailed to the wall for my lack of diligence in attending class. No such justice was meted our, however. Instead I answered three questions (yes, only three LONG answer questions). The first asked me to discuss the American values being deconstructed in Gangster movies. The second and third were similar in topic and just as easy to answer.  Still, I feel uneasy. I  really  didn't have to go to that class. Not once. Is this what $500 gets me? A class where I don't have to worry about studying? Maybe it's just the content of the class and the fact that I really, really enjoy film. Maybe that just makes it easy for me. There's one kid in this class with me, a fellow named Andrew, who studies his ass off. He takes notes in these weird web patterns, basically linking ideas together, and when he gets home, he turns those webs into notes. Me? I just watched a few movies and I was ready. I suppose that makes me either incredibly awesome, or incredibly deluded for even suggesting my awesominity. I'll let you, the reader, decide.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Jazzy Bells — Outkast
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Deep breath. In through the nose, and out through the mouth. Iiiinnnnnn. Ooooouuuutttt.  Ah! Shit, that doesn't really work, does it? It just makes me want to pass out. And passing out, my friends, is not the way to go when you have an exam to write in less than 3.5 hours. Now, I know what you're thinking: "It's just film studies, thomas. You cannot possibly go wrong, especially since you've seen all but one of the films on the syllabus." Indeed. However, I cannot shake the odd feeling that I have no idea what I'm getting myself in to.  Then, I think back to last semester. I was in a film studies course with the exact same instructor. All told, I think I showed up to about four classes last semester. I ended up with a Bno fuss, no muss. This year, however, I've only been to two classes. But I have this sense in the back of my head that I can't possibly fail. I can't. I just can't. I've watched the first two  Godfathers , the 1983  Scarface ,  To Live and Die in L.A. ,  Goodfellas ,  Heat , and, my favourite,  The Sopranos  (we only had to watch one episode of the show, but just to cover all my bases, I decided to watch seasons one to three inclusive).   I'm prepared. I've read up on each film. And yet, I can't help but feel as though, because of my rampant absenteeism this semester, the prof will see me stroll into the classroom this afternoon and say, "Who the fuck are you? You don't get to write my exam." Mind you, I get this sense all the time before exams, especially when I haven't been to class in three months. Still, what if...?  Well, rather than panic, I think some orange juice is in order. As is a shower. Did I mention it's snowing here? I mean absolutely dumping snow. It's horrible. Not because I hate the snow, but because now I don't want to go outside, which makes me all the more anxious about going to school to write this exam.  I promise to stop complaining soon.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Progress  Niceguy
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Smorgasbord, over at  urlLink Blorg.org , posted  urlLink a rather interesting analysis  of the patterns of  urlLink The Apprentice , that reality show where Donald Trump whoops ass to get himself a new junior vice-president or some such. Definitely  urlLink worth the read .
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My lovely girlfriend lives in a lovely little condo complex not far from the U of A campus. It's a delightful little place with its share of charms, not the least of which includes a balcony (on the third floor) that looks down upon the street, in full view of the adjacent McDonalds and Taco Bell. The condo, however, is not without its faults, as most places are. These so-called faults are quite trifling, and number no more than five (most of them having to do with my girlfriend's habit of not placing rinsed-off dished directly in the dishwasher—sorry, love).  No, the biggest fault of this condo has to do with the resident living above my girlfriend. This resident has been lovingly named "Stampy" by Colleen and I. She has hardwood floors and she weighs 500 pounds. She also likes vacuuming and running the water between 11pm and 3am. With her, there lives a herd of no less than seven baby elephants whose sole purpose in life is to walk across the hardwood floors as heavily and languidly as is elephantly possible. Even when the car that we believe belongs to Stampy isn't in its parking stall, the vacuuming, trudging, and running water continues unabated.  There's only one explanation for this parade of noise, and I think it has, mostly, to do with the fact that Stampy is an inconsiderate bitch. Not only does she like to step heavily on her hardwood floors at the most inopportune times of the early morning, she also insists on, apparently, wearing high-heel shoes as she does so. Meanwhile, her brood of African pachyderms make odd noises and dance... with the vacuum cleaner.  I've thought of going up there and either, A) yelling at her until she understands that, quite aside from it being rude to wear shoes in the house, she's a loud, inconsiderate shit-breech who deserves to be tossed off the top of her building, B) asking her to, please, keep it down, or C) beating her over the head repeatedly with my own vacuum cleaner. But, then, I'd have nothing to complain about.  Hell, I'm not even sure Stampy is a woman—it could be a man with a penchant for heels and late-night cleaning. Perhaps she has some sort of odd psycho-pathology that she can't break. Maybe she has OCD and simply MUST clean. All. The. Time.  Oh Stampy! Won't you just let me sleep!?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Ghostwriter — RJD2
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As the world of work settles down for the year, I find myself staring down the barrel of the gun that is my academic life. Two finals isn't too bad. But I'm at the point where caring has gone down the pooper, and all I want to do is play Frisbee and nothing else.  I usually feel like this in April, when school begins to wind down and the big exam push comes. But I'm never sure how to shake the feeling of malaise except to get all worked up about school, and to essentially feel more or less completely stressed out about having neglected my studies for the entire semester. I tend to semi-nullify those feelings with other feelings: self-aggrandizement. "I've never failed a class," "I'm a smart kid, I should have no worries," and "I've got this whole university thing figured out," are common thoughts that pass through my mind.  But what if, this time, I'm totally humped? Maybe I could work for Google as a janitor or something.  How are all you kids out there in webberland feeling about this time of the year?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Something Wicked — The Herbaliser
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As of yesterday, Prime Minister Paul Martin dropped the writ and called for a Monday, 28 June  urlLink election .  I figured I could take this moment to discuss the merits of the leaders of each of Canada's major political parties. But I've decided to leave that up to the pundits. It's not like  urlLink Harper ,  urlLink Duceppe ,  urlLink Martin , or  urlLink Layton  said anything new at their respective press conferences yesterday, anyhow. It was the same electoral politispeak that makes "young people" like me want to move to a deserted island (or, even better, a desserted island) and never participate in another election again. Ever.  Nope, it's not promises I wish to discuss here today; it's language translations on Canadian television that have me using the most vulgar of emoticons on MSN.  I was watching  urlLink CBC , Canada's subsidized national television network, yesterday as each of Canada's potential future leaders waxed political on their visions of Canada under the control of their respective parties. As is customary, the speakers switched between English and French on the fly, prompting the interjection of bewildered-sounding translators. Let me be very clear: I  hate  this.  I've spoken both of Canada's official languages basically since birth, and I'm something of a—oh, what's the word? ... Ah yes: dickhead—when it comes to French and English. In my mind, everyone in this country, as a condition of citizenship, should speak, understand and appreciate our official language. I won't tolerate complaints stating that French is useless, or that it's only good to know if you happen to travel to Québec or Ottawa. That's weak.   So, as someone who speaks, understands, and appreciates both official languages, it chaps my hide when some retard comes on the TV to translate Steven Harper's poor French pronunciation, especially when these translations are taking place on Canada's national network. It's jarring and pointless. For me, anyway.  "But, thomas, why not just switch it to the French CBC if you want to hear the French so much?" Well, that's exactly what I did, thank you very much. Sadly, once Giles Duceppe was on the TV, the French CBC just kept him on. Meanwhile, poor little Jack Layton, speaking some pretty decent French, was being translated on the other channel. Gah!  I know it's not something I should get this upset about, but it strikes me as lame that many Canadians don't speak Canada's second official language.  To you, I say: Être Canadien c'est être bilingue.  Yeah?   *** iTunes selection of the day: Jamming — Bob Marley
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just had to share these with everyone:   urlLink Eple  — Röyksopp  urlLink Star Guitar  — Chemical Brothers  Neat, yes?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Pretty Penny — Stone Temple Pilots
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Colleen (my girlfriend who demands her own screen name and shall henceforth be known as Little Roy) and I were getting into the parkade elevator in Little Roy's (LR) building when a gray, mid-eighties BMW pulls into a parking space. I, carrying my longboard, and LR entered the elevator and were quickly joined by Stampy herself.  Allow me, for a moment, to diverge and describe what was once a mere spectre... And although I once thought that Stampy was a 10 000 pound anthropomorphic paint shaker, I now know that I was wrong. So very wrong.  Stampy, it turns out, is not unlike the character from  urlLink Beetlejuice , who serves as advisor to Adam and Barbara in the Netherworld. You remember her; she had a slice right across her neck, and whenever she'd smoke, the smoke would come out of her neck hole. Wonderfully sick. Well, here's a little equation for you:  Stampy = (the character from  urlLink Beetlejuice , who serves as advisor to Adam and Barbara in the Netherworld. You remember her; she had a slice right across her neck, and whenever she'd smoke, the smoke would come out of her neck hole) - neck hole + longer, poorly dyed blonde hair - cigarette - ominous warnings about contacting Beetlejuice + random inquiry and awkward chit-chat.  Anyhow, there we stood, in the elevator. The follow dialogued ensued:    STAMPY GLANCES DOWN AT THOMAS' LONGBOARD   STAMPY What's that skateboard for (OR SOMETHING EQUALLY ASININE)?  THOMAS It's my longboard. They're not the same as skateboards; they're used as a form of transportation, not doing tricks.  LITTLE ROY (TWITCHES UNCOMFORTABLY WHILE SIMULTANEOUSLY GLARES AT STAMPY FOR BEING SO LOUD ALL THE TIME)  STAMPY Well, you won't see me on one of those things anytime soon.  THOMAS Don't worry. I'll do enough riding for the both of us. (SMILES STUPIDLY)   EXEUNT LITTLE ROY AND THOMAS, STAGE ANYWHERE BUT IN THE ELEVATOR WITH STAMPY.    Stampy was actually behaving like she was kind of stoned. Her eyes were half shut, and her speech was a little bit slurred. She kept lolling her head, too. Maybe she's constantly medicated.  Maybe  she was coming down, and when she gets up to her apartment, she takes another hit or six and starts stamping around until her next hit.  Of course, this is nothing more than libelous conjecture. I know who Stampy is, but I don't know why she stamps. The plot thickens.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Reptilia — The Strokes
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was good. Not only did I finish, and thoroughly enjoy, Yann Martel's  Life of Pi  (and any assertion that the book is slow to start is false), but I hooked up with my friend  urlLink Graham , a young man who designs longboards, and got from him my first  urlLink longboard , a beautiful little number that I haven't named yet, although I'm pretty sure it's a boy. Anyhow, suggestions for potential names would be much appreciated from the viewing audience.  This evening, I spent some time in St Albert with my buddy Pauly. There's something I find troubling about St Albert everytime I'm there: a vague, dull sense of malaise about the place. I couldn't figure out where this emotion was coming from until about an hour ago, as Pauly drove me back home.  My memories of St Albert are limited, although I spent a great deal of time in the small town visiting my mother's parents. We'd be there at least once a week. And as my grandparents grew older and eventually passed on, I associated a numbing sadness with the town. My mind associates the elderly with St Albert, and I find it sad. Now, my aunt lives in St Albert, and she's growing old—starting to look like my grandmother, even.   I don't know... I always feel like I'm going to get broadsided my a slow-moving funeral procession when I go to St Albert. It's the focal point of some of the most poignant and difficult times of my young life.  My sort-of cousin, Kevin, is having his wedding reception there next Saturday. When I saw on the invitation where this reception was to take place, part of me felt... discomfort. St Albert hardly seems like the place to celebrate a marriage—a rite, typically, of joy.  Oh well. I don't hate going to St Albert. It's just that I'm having trouble separating emotions of events that occurred there from the town itself. And it's not like I have this feeling whenever I'm  in  St Albert. I mean, I hung out with Pauly and his friends at one of their houses there, and I felt fine. I only experience this sensation when I'm driving through St Albert streets. I feel as though I move back in time when I go there. Still, I kind of wanna go back there by myself and just explore. It might evoke some other more pleasant emotions I hadn't considered.  One more thing:  urlLink Jennifah  over at First-flight will be coming back to Edmonton at the end of summer to start a new job. I just wanna to throw a shout out your way, Jen. I'm really excited to have you and Tim back here.  Now: bed!  *** iTunes selection of the day: Southernunderground — CunninLynguists
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think the second post I ever made here at half-doubting thomas mentioned that, one day in the near future, I would relate to you the reason this blog is named the way it is. That day has finally come. I give you:   Half-doubting thomas' genesis   It was a quiet afternoon, and we were in the middle of a board meeting. There was some proposal before the board and Gerald, the chair of said board, noted that his comments on the proposal (it doesn't matter what the proposal was) made him sound like a half Negative Nancy, and half Doubting Thomas. I'd never heard the phrase "Doubting Thomas" before, and thought the idea of a "half-doubting" Thomas was even funnier. Thus, after dithering for awhile over what I would name my blog, I took a page from the Gerald quotebook. And while "half-doubting thomas" is something of a bastardization of what Gerald originally said, I must still issue props where they're due.  Thank you, Gerald, for giving my run-on sentences a forum in which to exist.  And who said board meetings were no fun?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Billy Club — Lagwagon
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got a new CD today—from the fine folks at  urlLink Fat Wreck Chords . It's a split CD that features Tony Sly (lead singer of  urlLink No Use For A Name ) and Joey Cape (lead singer of  urlLink Lagwagon  and  urlLink Bad Astronaut ) performing acoustic versions of their respective bands' songs. Now, I've always been a sucker for the bands on Fat's label. It's the sort of punk rock I took a shine to when I was in high school, and I still love this stuff.   But to see these artists demonstrating that they aren't limited to just one genre—that they have ears for different sorts of musical arrangements—is nice, and amazing to hear. And that isn't to suggest that the music they play is particularly difficult. Although I certainly couldn't play what they play, I doubt power chords are all that difficult. It's the arrangement of guitars, pianos and strings that I'm enjoying about this new album (called  Acoustic , by the way).  Which leads me to something I'm not particularly proud to admit, but I feel I must: I love remixes, B-sides, acoustic versions, and—most shamefully—cover songs.  I know, I know. Shameful. And while I eventually got irritated with the Ataris' version of "Boys of Summer," I will admit to enjoying it at first, if only because it provoked memories of my long-dormant punk rock sensibilities.  So yeah, applying a fresh sound to old tunes is something I enjoy hearing (though I'd agree that the Ataris' "Boys of Summer" was hardly fresh). Which brings us to remixes; from Bonobo's version of Amon Tobin's "Four Ton Mantis" to the "Ghostwriter" remix on RJD2's  The Horror  single, I can't get enough of interesting new twists artists apply to songs... One more reason why I want to buy  urlLink GarageBand : so I can make my own remixes.  How do you guys feel about "recycled" music?   *** iTunes selection of the day: Exit — Tony Sly
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's getting harder to do this—update my blog, I mean. On the one hand, I'm a fairly regular person with rather regular thoughts that I don't think would interest you, the reader. On the other hand, this isn't necessarily for you, the reader. So, I struggle with what to compose, taking into account what sort of post would garner the most comments, and what sort of remarkable things occur in my life. Given that my posts of late have been few and far between, I think it's fair to say that I'm just lazy.  I bought a book on Friday: one whose unassuming title nearly caused me to dismiss it as stupid. The subtitle, however, was the kicker; "The Zero Tolerance Approach to Punctuation" is what this books purports itself to be. Being an editor concerned with all things linguistic (or at least punctuational, if such a word exists, which it does not), I figured that this bestseller—whose title, incidentally, is   urlLink Eats, Shoots & Leaves  —would be a worthwhile purchase. It turns out, this book is more of an investment in "capital-Q" Quality more than anything else.  "But, Thomas, was the book any good?" you may be asking. I polished off its 209 pages in less than eight hours (over three days, mind you. But eight hours sounds far more impressive). The author, my newest heroine, is Lynne Truss, and the lessons she's put down in this book are both familiar, apt, and hilarious. For example, consider how punctuation can change the way we read things:   A woman, without her man, is nothing. A woman: without her, man is nothing.   Now I'm not going to argument the validity of either statement, although my opinions may provoke a number of you to post comments. No, no, I'm not interested in all that. But isn't in exquisite how a few marks—verily nothing more than flourishes of the digital pen—can completely change the meaning of a sentence? I think that's what frustrates me so much about netspeak; it's a jumble of run-on sentences and non-words designed to fit into the paradigm of as "much information in as little space as possible." But what good is that sort of thinking if the message ends up becoming completely garbled at the end?  I was never taught grammar properly in grade school. High school saw us gloss over grammar in favour of discovering what Jane Austen thought was romantic (which, it turns out, I could have skipped reading if I'd known  Pride & Prejudice  was nothing more than a long, boring  Taming of the Shrew )(OK, I'm lying here; I loved  Pride and Prejudice ). I didn't take up grammar in earnest until my third year of university, and then only because I was in a non-fiction writing class. Why these rules—for commas, colons, semicolons, periods, brackets and apostrophes—aren't drilled into us on a consistent basis from the moment we step into the classroom is beyond me.  So, yeah. Read it and weep: I haven't posted recently because all I can think about is grammar. And you thought you were sad and pathetic (you are, it's just a matter of degrees).  *** iTunes selection of the day: Slip Slidin' Away — Paul Simon
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I recently chided nori maki over at  urlLink Swiss Fondue  for not updating her blog every ten minutes. For awhile last week, as I attempted to get my bearings at my summer job, I spent a great deal of my time trolling the blogscape for hilarious anecdotes. I am, after all, stuck in an office most of the day. I need someone through whom I can live vicariously during the day.  My scolding of nori's lack of updates was, before long, revealed to be nothing more than a selfish hypocrisy. It has, after all, been over a week since last I updated the goings on here at Half-Doubting Thomas. And let me tell you, fans, I sure as shit haven't been idle. Not a chance.  I've spent a good chunk of time over the last week playing a little game called  urlLink GLTron , a delightful little app for the Apple that simulates fantastically the lighbike races from  Tron . Every day, Biz and I play about 60 games between the two of us. That's nothing on what Biz and Diz did the other day; they played over something like 500 games against each other. Those kids are destined to be Master Control Programs in their own little TronWorlds someday.  Well, the birds are chirping outside, and you can't tell me, nori, that my blog isn't up-to-date. Not that you were the one who opposed my hypocrisy. What does this have to do with chirping birdies? I'm going outside to enjoy the sunshine, that's what.  Happy Saturday, y'all.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Put You In Your Place  Face to Face
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, after owning my longboard (which I've named after Yann Martel's tiger, Richard Parker) for well over a month, it finally happened. On a ride through the river valley with Pauly, I bit off more than I could chew. A slight but distinct downhill, which saw me achieve fairly high speeds, got the better of me. After losing control of Richard Parker, I decided to bail to the right of this asphalt path. I was going a bit too fast for my legs to be able to keep up when I jumped off the board. The end result was me sliding a few metres through the grass, scraping my left hand, and my right shoulder, hip and elbow.  I think I probably bruised a few ribs and definitely bruised my right hip. It kinda hurts to breathe. Thank god Pauly was there, though. He drove me home and made me stay awake when my skin turned grey and I started passing out in his car. Shock's pretty nifty. I just wish it didn't feel like dying.  So, Pauly took me home and I made my mother dress my wounds. She's a hell of a nurse, Moms is. She bandaged me up and I spent the rest of the evening lamenting my sorry state. This morning, however, when I woke up after a fitful sleep, I couldn't help but notice how cool my injuries look. If nothing else, they'll illicit sympathy from both friends and enemies.  I think I'll go drown my sorrows in a bowl of Raisin Bran. Stay safe, friends.   I'll try and post some pictures of my sorry state later on.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Scarlet Begonias — Sublime
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It just dawned on me: the house that I grew up in, a house whose walls contain an immeasurable amount of memory both sweet and bitter, has been sold. My life between the ages of seven years right up to now, at the ripe old age of 23, went to the Lennon family for $315,000 CDN. At first I thought I didn't care. But after lying in bed and thinking about it for a bit, I realized something: this is the end of an era. And while life is supposed to be filled with these sorts of ends (they actually call them new beginnings for you glass-half-full types), it still makes my eyes well up with tears and my stomach do an Olympic-amount of somersaults.  It's around 1am as I write this. And while I finished yet another chapter in the book I'm reading ( 100 Years of Solitude  for those of you keeping score) I started to imagine what my bedroom looked like when we first moved in here. In 1987, after some significant decorative efforts on the part of my father, I was the proud owner of my own bedroomfor the first time in my life. This room, over the last sixteen years, has sported a variety of colours on its walls, and a very flashy wallpaper border near the ceiling that featured Mario of Nintendo fame kicking the shit out of Koopa Troopas and Goombahs. A different time.  My reminiscing wasn't isolated to my bedroom, however. An image tacked to my corkboard shows my little brother delivering a faux-uppercut to my older brother. In the photo, they look to be about six and ten, respectively. This little event took place in the playroom; what once seemed like a cavernous space where me and my brothers would invent violent games involving soccer balls and pillows is now a place for DVD watching. Soon, it will be the room where another family gets to create memories. And yet, I can't help but feel as though they'll be trampling on the memories of my family.  I never minded moving all that much. I've moved out of this house twice already, but I keep coming back. It's home. It's hard to stay away.   As of August 13th, however, I will be homeless. My memories and a few photos will be all I have left of this place. And though it might look like just another house on the outside, inside it's a place of enchantmentit's a place where we celebrated life and mourned the loss of loved ones; a place that has seen no less than four degrees awarded to various family members, myself included. It's a place that I never want to forget.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm sitting here sipping tea and poring over my old high school yearbooks. I got into a conversation with Ash over MSN, and it turns out we went to the same high school. Anyhow, nostalgia and phrases of "did you have XX as a teacher" abounded and the final result was an inescapable urge to go through all of my so-called high school memories. Far from there being so much I've forgotten, as I had expected, there's a great deal that, thanks to this shoddily designed and layed out tomes, I do in fact remember.  I don't think I credit high school enough for getting me to where I am today. Why would I? It's about six years behind me now, and I'm too cynical to admit that perhaps some events there helped to shape who I am today (duh, I know). What struck me most, as I gazed at these old, young faces of friends and acquaintances, is just how far I've come—how far all my friends from high school, many of whom I still hang out with today, have come as well.  We more or less all have degrees now. Some of us are on to our second degrees, some are working jobs they love, others are biding their time before they have enough money to explore the world. Some of us died a little inside when  Survivor: Allstars  came out, while others lament the  Psycho  remake as nothing more than a money grab. But by and large, aside from the years and, thankfully, the abatement of ridiculous drinking habits, we came out ok.  Thanks, high school. I often poke fun at you, but you are the basis for the life I live now, in many ways. The only difference between now and then? I'm older, wiser, and a little bit more sedentary. And I keep a blog.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Wind in your Sails — Joey Cape
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I never considered my own convocation very much. I thought about it in passing, imagining in delusional states that I would get some kind of verbal recognition beyond "Thomas, Bachelor of Arts." No, at my convocation, they would declare me Prince of Awesome and give me my own national holiday.  I've been to three convocations in my lifetime. The first was for my dad. That was pretty special. Dad decided that, while working full time, he was going to also get his MBA. It took two grueling years, and he was ready to quit about 4 months before the end, but my mother scolded him. "You'd  better  finish this degree. Otherwise, what the hell were the last two years for?" His convocation ceremony was small... There were only about 15 graduates, because it was an Executive MBA program. Short and sweet.  The second was of my older brother. He got his Bachelor of Science on a warm June afternoon, and I was the resident photographer because my parents couldn't operate a camera to save their collective lives. The ceremony took two and a half hours. I don't remember any of it.  The next was my older brother's Masters degree convocation. I got to travel all the way to hot and humid Ontario for that one. That one I remember, too. I'm not sure why, but I felt a powerful swell of pride at the Ontario ceremony. Maybe it was the humidity...  Now, on the eve of my convocation, I can't help but feel a powerful swell of pride as well. This degree was six years in the making, and though much of it is a blur, I know I truly earned this piece of parchment. Besides, I get free breakfast tomorrow morning with the Dean.  This weekend: the ceremony itself and what I did to pass the time.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Everything is Everything — Lauryn Hill
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It exists in a game called  urlLink EverQuest .   urlLink The Walrus , a terrific Canadian mag that's only been around for a short time, published this terrific article on  urlLink the economics of EverQuest . It's so interesting, even for those of you out there who don't give a fuck about economics. It's a long piece, but it's brilliant. BRILLIANT!  *** iTunes selection of the day: Otherside — The Red Hot Chili Peppers
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's easy to forget how varied a collection of experiences my life has been. Thanks to six years of post-secondary, I've had the chance to meet hundreds of fascinating, annoying, fragrant, frustrating, and loving friends, enemies, well-wishers, and hangers-on (obviously, not every adjective in the previous sentence applies to every noun in the previous sentence, although, strangely, I have had some very loving enemies in my brief quarter-century on this rock).  Little Roy and I went out for coffee and cheesecake the other night, figuring on a quiet, subdued, and uninterrupted evening of conversation and the reading of whatever newspapers happened to be within reach. It was not to be: instead, I had a run-in with an old, creepy English professor.  Now, this guy, identified as ML, was a terrific prof. In fact, aside from my work at the newspaper, I credit him with helping to make me a better writer. I really enjoyed his classes—in fact, it was one of the few classes I attended in the twilight of my academic career. It was only after the class that I'd started to hear the rumours about ML. Allegations of misconduct with female students notwithstanding, I was willing to give him another chances. So, I enrolled in a fourth-year English class of his two years ago, only to drop the class early because of other commitments. However, before I could drop the class, I received an extensive package of photocopied readings for which I never paid ($7 was the total). I took the copies and ran. I never, ever paid the man...  ... Until today. LR and I ran into him in a café, as I said, and he somewhat accosted us. He demanded his money, and then asked if the newspaper would publish his poetry. I made some vague promise that I'd look at his copy, but I didn't really promise that I'd print his words. Still, that didn't stop him from writing me a note, right there in the café, (complete with different coloured felt marker marks) that reads:    To:    T  homas,  E ditor-in- C hief  (  alleged  )   From:  Tony Soprano, PhD  Re:  The   D  eep   P  oetic   P  ossibilities of   W  riterly   T  ranscendence and $7.00 photocopy fee   (E  nglish   461)     NOTE:  The colours and bolds here are just about precisely how the note looks. Very creepy.  Today, I sent ML his $7 through campus mail, and am hoping to never hear from him again.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Aural Pleasure — Blackalicious
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm in the process of packing up all my stuff (for the fourth time in about three years) and moving it to my new apartment downtown. And by "in the process," I mean "doing nothing even remotely related to packing."  I think the problem is that I don't know where to start. Despite having moved often over the last few years, and though I like actually living in new places, the actually moving part of the process is boring.   When I'm packing things up, I always consider what I'm going to need to use right before I move; my desire, then, is to pack those things last. But this complicates things, because I'm usually completely wrong about what I'm going to need to use. Or does it complicate things? I'm not really sure.  To be fair, I don't own very much stuff. Last week, I went shopping for all the kitchen and bathroom stuff I'll need in this new place of mine (incidentally in downtown Edmonton about a block and a half south of the Milner building on 104 street, which houses such companies as ATCO iTek), and most of those things are in boxes anyway. Now I just have to place them in larger boxes. I could chalk my lack of action in this regard up to laziness, but I'm hoping it's not that simple. Hoping.  Actually, I do feel a general sort of malaise at the entire prospect of moving. Since this is that last house I'll have lived in with all of my family together, it's sort of an emotional time; my mom's a total basket case. As she slowly packs up the house and sorts through things for next weekend's garage sale, new memories come forth, and new sadness in some cases, too.  But I guess we just have to grin and bear it. I suppose I'll start by packing all my CDs and random bedroom knick-knacks—like my inukshuk statues (I own two, for some reason), pictures, and the contents of my desk. Whether or not that will happen this afternoon or tomorrow evening, at the very last minute, remains to be seen. In any case, I'll be sure to keep you updated, oh wise Internet.  Wish me luck.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Magnetizing — Handsome Boy Modelling School feat. Del tha Funkee Homosapien
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As summer tradition dictates, and has dictated since the very early 90s, I am once again in the midst of reading one of my favourite books:  The Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy  by the late Douglas Adams.  As any DNA fan would know, the HHGG  urlLink movie  is currently filming, and stars such luminaries as Sam Rockwell (as Zaphod Beeblebrox), Martin Freeman (as Arthur Dent), and even the Mighty Mos Def (as Ford Prefect). I've been excited for movies before, but this—for me, this is LOTR-scale excitement.  I'm excited, even, by the  urlLink teaser trailer  which, while it doesn't reveal much, is at the very least compelling (Mac users should go to  urlLink download.com  and search for VLC player. That'll play .AVIs for ye).  So, who's with me in the summer of '05?  *** iTunes selection of the day: HHGG — BBC Radio
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went to the Globe nightclub last night for a friend's birthday. I'd never been there before, so I wasn't sure what to expect. When we got to the door, I felt like turning around and going home—they use  urlLink BarWatch  barcode scanning software to scan IDs (the URL I've posted isn't the company's site, unfortunately. That site was taken down when  urlLink this  webpage was created—read the link for the whole story). Not only do they scan the barcode of one's driver's license, but they also snap a photograph of the ID itself, something I'm not altogether comfortable with.  Here's why: I have  no idea  what they're doing with that information. None.   I'm guessing most bar patrons would assume that their information is being stored on a machine so that bar owners can keep track of troublemakers or something. Why, then, was there an ethernet cable running from the computer to a jack in the wall near the entrance? A centralized server somewhere in the sub-etha, perhaps?  I once heard that BarWatch stores information on a centrally-located server so that bars can shares DBs to see if any of their clients have been causing ruckuses at other bars. Why on earth would I want the Globe telling Cowboys what I've been up to?  What's creepiest is that people just hand their shit over without question. There are no terms of use posted. Big brother is truly watching.  I'm going to coordinate a feature on this when school starts. I feel like people need to know, y'know?  Am I overreacting?  *** iTunes selection of the day: Theme from Mission Impossible — Billy May & His Orchestra
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        You are starch. You are rigid, opinionated, hard-willed and not too friendly about it. You keep people out of places, or you keep them in, and without you a lot of things would collapse. hopefully you'll never have the authority to burn people at the stake. Sir. Ma'am.    urlLink   Which Biological Molecule Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    *** iTunes selection of the day: Main Aim — The Dwellas
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         My life is rated NC-17.  What is your life rated?    Now, I'm not sure I agree with this. I mean, for all my bizarre foibles and self-destructive habits, my life  should  be rated R. But, I've never argued with the Internet before. She is, after all, smarter than I am.   Adrift in a sea of sexual innuendo   I went sailing with Bizzak and the Wednesday night heroes (not the band—the boys what sail with Bizzak on Weds nights) last week. It wasn't as windy this time as the last, but we still travelled at about two knots, floating slowly across the lake—and then back the other way—for about five hours. Points of discussion included the amalgamation of Edmonton satellite towns with the city itself (an idea I think is dumb; Edmonton should figure out its own budget before it starts mismanaging the budgets of other small communities), a lament on the poor planning of the LRT line, and, of course, a brief run-down of Mr Jim's many sexual exploits. High-larity.   I was only  Quidam !   Big Marty was kind enough to take me to Calgary this weekend in order to take in one of Canada's greatest exports: the Cirque du Soleil. The show this year is called  Quidam , and it's just as phenomenal—if not more—as when I first saw the Cirque at the tender age of thirteen. I'm not really sure how to describe what CdS is. It's ballet, electronica, feats of strength and incredible amounts of concentration resulting in an amazingly visual display. And the costumes are rad as well.   24 years of strange, strange life   I turned 24 yesterday. I feel lamer, but not older. Is that normal?   Addendum   I've been in the process of completing this post since last Thursday. I'm experiencing blogger's block. Later this week, stay tuned for some Audioblog posts. :D  *** iTunes selection of the day: Break — Jurassic Five
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Bizzak and I have a ton of Ikea office furniture to assemble. Now, doing this sort of thing with the supplied Allen key wrenches is, at best, frustratingly slow. Thus, we stopped by Home Depot on the way to the office on Friday to buy some hex driver bits for Bizzak's power drill. Figuring I would, at some point in my life, really need a power drill of my own, I decided to buy one: a $120 deal with two 14.4 volt batteries, a flashlight, the drill itself, and a nifty battery charger (the device also came with four different driver bits).  I didn't expect that a power drill would bring out in me the industrious-tool-man archetype, a reputation that members of my gender have had to suffer since the inception of power tools. But it has. I love my drill, and I'm just  looking  for excuses to use it—to screw, to drill holes... anything!  So, kids, what are some hilarious and obscure uses you can think of for this drill? I'm dying to use it, and I just can't wait until Monday when we start assembling more furniture.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Uranusexplodes — The Smalls
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's raining outside. I'm not going to work.  I love how I can do that. I think that's one of the reasons that, in some iteration or another, I've stayed for as long as I have at the newspaper. Time. All I need to do is manage time, get my work done when it needs to get done, and I can do whatever the hell I want whenever the hell I want. It's beautiful.  Yesterday, I hung out with some folks and watched the Amazing Race. Aside from shouting at the television, I spoke with my good friend Duong. We spoke of time, in fact. Duong was concerned that the schedule he keeps prevents him from staying sharp and innovative. He wakes up around 10am each day, heads to work, puts in his 8 hours and that's the end of it. Duong feels that a strict routine will result in a sharper mind and better ideas. I said I disagreed, and so he argued that we're in very different lines of work: he, a scientist working on a masters degree, and I an editor working on... editing.  Maybe he's right. One thing I know for sure is that I'm far more creative vis-à-vis writing during the evening time. Maybe it's because I don't like routine. I like to shake things up, I like working on little, different things each day. I cannot abide long-term projects. After a few days, I become bored with them (a note to my employers: this doesn't mean said project will not get completed. heh). And I  hate  scheduling things. I'd rather things just randomly occurred.  Regardless of schedule, time management or whatever, the metaconcept at work here—if there is such a thing—is what Kevin Nealon was talking about in the movie  Happy GIlmore : things are indeed circular. It's mentioned in the  Lion King  as well: the Circle of Life. Filmmakers know this, and now so do I. I enter into the record my jaunt to Nijel's last night (Amazing Racetown, for those of you joining us halfway through this post); I walked in, expecting only to see Duong and a few other people I probably wouldn't know. Turns out, three friends (dear ones, at that) and a few hangers on from high school were there.   These are folks I hung out with on a daily basis about seven years ago. Of course, with university, new experiences, and new groups of friends—for all of us—I saw these people less and less. And now, it's as though we've come full circle. I'm looking forward to spending more time with these folks over the summer months and into the fall. And I can't help but feel as though, somewhere deep down in my soul, someone is doing the bulldance as a result.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Röyksopp's Night Out — Röyksopp
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A blog runs through it   I've taken certain lengths here to preserve my anonymity, figuring I didn't want people I know stumbling upon this blog and being privy to my most sensitive thoughts and feelings, as well as my most brilliant insights. However, since the latter three things happen so rarely around here, I decided to finally do it: I created a profile for myself.  It doesn't reveal all that much about who the real-life me is, but this blogging persona of mine is fairly well catalogued directly to the right, at the top of this nifty little sidebar.  Now you all know what I look likeat least those of you who didn't beforethrough the lens of a camera being turned at a slight angle in the middle of a snapshot. "Woohoo," as they say over in Europe.   The ongoing goings-on   I had a ridiculously busy week, made all the more ridiculous because of the sudden passing of my Uncle Yves.   Monday : An election was held here in Canada resulting in a Liberal minority government. I doubt it'll last much longer than a year, but hopefully within that time, the NDP can work in some election reform stuff so that the seats of the House are properly distributed according to voter percentage.   Tuesday : After a lazy day at work, Bizzak, Dizzak and myself were invited to sail aboard the Edmonton Queen, thanks to the fine folks at the  urlLink NCRA . We were wined, dined, and generally well-looked-after. The three of us later adjourned to Little Roy's place to partake of snacking foods and TeleToon's so-called Powerhour (includes Family Guy and Futurama).   Wednesday : Went sailing on Wabamun lake with Bizzak, his dad, and a fellow by the name of Mr Jim whose heroic consumption of alcohol is indeed a sight to behold. By the end of the night, his speech was slurred as he belted out strange rugby drinking songs. On the ride home, he slumped in his chair and sawed logs. When it came time for him to go inside his house, he fell over on his front lawn. It was good times.   Thursday : My older brother and I made our way down to Lethbridge for Yves' funeral, stopping in Calgary for some Krispy Kreme delights. Any weight-loss I experienced over the past few weeks (and I have, certainly by sight, as my next door neighbour attested last night) was nullified. We also made our way to KK on the way back to Edmonton the following day.   Friday : The funeral. Countless aunts, uncles, cousins, second cousins, and random family friends were there. Many of the older folks spent their time trying to convince me that at one time or another, they'd changed my diapers. I'm grateful, I suppose. The funeral itself was niceor at least as nice as funerals are. I was just glad to come back home (this very same day). I spent the night at Little Roy's watching Batman on Family Channel. I fell asleep on her couch and didn't wake up until 5am the next day.   Saturday : Didn't do much all day. Spent the evening watching some Band of Brothers with Ash, followed, of course, by the Powerhour. I'm realizing more and more that my life revolves around entertaining movies and cartoons. And you know what? That doesn't bother me one bit.   Sunday : Marty came by and enjoyed some treats with me. It was nice to see him after so long (a few weeks, anyway). He's taking me down to Calgary to Cirque du Soleil in a few weeks... as a birthday present. What a swell guy!   Monday : Breakfast at the Highlevel Diner, followed by a brief stint at work, followed by a trip to Ikea to order a great deal of new office furniture for work. That cavernous wasteland of newspapers will at least look like a *nice* cavernous wasteland come school time.   Odds 'n ends   - I have a Google Gmail account, and I don't give a shit about the so-called privacy issues. There's nothing very sensitive in my e-mail, beyond the occasional "chix filled with sweet wite cum" that finds its way into my inbox. - My property manager, Margaret, was kind enough to not charge me rent for July, because I won't be moving into my new apartment until August. She is very quickly becoming one of my favourite people on the planet. You'll probably hear a lot about her here over the next six months. -  urlLink Jennifah  and her lovely Tim are coming home on the 23rd. She doesn't know this, but I'm extremely excited to have her come home. I didn't realize how much I'd miss her, but, it turns out, I missed her a lot. - Need to come up with some kind of story ideas for freelancing, so as to supplement my pathetic income.  That, friends, is all for now.  *** iTunes selection of the day: Between Love & Hate  The Strokes
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, kids, it's 1:20am, I'm loaded with caffeine, and I have a bone to pick with so-called  auteur   urlLink M. Night Shyamalan .  I saw  urlLink  The Village   this evening with Little Roy and Sister Vero. Before the film began, I was convinced of Shyamalan's hubris as a writer/director. In my opinion, he thinks very highly of himself even though his films are heavy-handed nonsense, for the most part. I will concede that  urlLink  The Sixth Sense   was a tense and enjoyable watch. However, certain patterns have emerged in Shyamalan's work that must be stated, deconstructed and openly mocked.  First of all, he ruins every single one of his films with in-your-face, "the-viewer-is-obviously-dumber-than-I-am" commentary. Take  The Sixth Sense ; this movie boasted a great deal of tension and build-up, and even when it was revealed that Malcolm Crowe was dead, the film was still interesting... That is, until Shyamalan appears with his iron fist of obviousness. It felt like, after the first moment we realize Willis' character is dead, Shyamalan felt the need to grab us all by the sides of our heads and shout, "DON'T YOU GET IT? HE WAS DEAD THE WHOLE TIME! I'LL SIGN AN AUTOGRAPH FOR YOU, IF YOU LIKE!"  Fine. The concept was cool, and I could deal with the fact that the director clearly thought I wouldn't "get" his film.  Along came  urlLink  Unbreakable  , by rights also a thoroughly enjoyable film with bizarre twists... That is, until Shyamalan appears once again with an even heavier, more obvious fist. "DON'T YOU GET IT? SAM JACKSON IS THE VILLAIN! HE GAVE BIRTH TO WILLIS AS THE HERO, ONLY IT TURNS OUT HE WAS TOTALLY THE BAD GUY! I WILL SERIOUSLY SIGN ANYTHING—A T-SHIRT, EVEN!"  OK. I enjoyed your first movie, M. Night, and  Unbreakable  was very entertaining. You're bashing my head with the plot, once again assuming I'm not smart enough to figure it out for myself, but whatever. I enjoyed.  Then, the "masterpiece" of garbage  urlLink  Signs   was born. What a horrible slab of dogs' ass (yes, kids; not just one dog. Many). Not only is the viewer supposed to believe that an alien race—one capable of interstellar travel and impervious to everything but water, mind you—is dumb enough to invade a planet composed almost entirely of delicious dihydrogen oxide, but we're also supposed to accept that Shyamalan has taken the Bible and decided to grab the back of our heads and slam our faces repeatedly into it. "DON'T YOU GET IT? HE LOST HIS FAITH, BUT BECAUSE OF THE WATER-HATING ALIENS, HE HAS IT BACK! HIS FAITH! RETURNED!  DEUS EX MACHINA ! CAN I SIGN YOUR BREASTS? SERIOUSLY, I'M AN  AUTEUR ! I SHOULD SIGN SOMETHING!  Jesus Christ, Night (can I call you Night?), I get it. God intervenes—with a fucking supersoaker, no less—and saves what's left of Mel Gibson's soul. Whoopdy do. Was all that religious nonsense really necessary? You bruised my nose slamming my face into the Good Book.  I figured most of this bullshit was just a blip on the radar. I mean, the man's only directed four major films, and really, every director will in his or her career direct a bomb. But something's wrong. Night has finally lost his fuckin' marbles. So,  for those of you who have yet to see  The Village , I'm about to give the entire plot away. Read at your own peril    The  fucking  Village . Sweet zombie Jesus, Night.  What in the hell were you thinking?  First of all, the pacing was all wrong. Moments of tension were suddenly broken by the boring lives of the Amish community of Covington Woods. Those boring moments were shattered by tension. However, tension is far more effective if it's built up and maintained throughout the film—not built up and suddenly demolished by unsympathetic blind characters and retards—and the random goings-on in this village served only to break a rising tension.  Halfway through this film, the entire plot is given away. Boom. Just like that, we're told that the monsters aren't real. They're a concoction of the elders, all of whom used to live in the real world until they were all joined together—in a counseling group—by traumas in their lives. "DON'T YOU GET IT? THEY WANTED A BETTER LIFE! FREE FROM PAIN, BUT STILL FULL OF HOPE! GODDAMMIT, PEOPLE! THE  WALKER  NATURE PRESERVE? DUH! WALKER'S DAD WAS A FREAKIN' BILLIONAIRE! NOW GIMME THAT AUTOGRAPH BOOK SO I CAN GODDAMN SIGN IT. AUTEUR!"  OK, buddy. You should, maybe, take a lesson from Quentin Tarantino when it comes to the chronology of your plot. You revealed details at the most inopportune times, effectively nullifying any of the tension the existence of your monsters created. By the end of the film, all we cared about was figuring out exactly what this fucking town was all about. Was that the point? Maybe. But it was disappointing and heavy-handed all the same. You essentially duped your viewers. In a bad way.  Moreover, your inclusion of Noah, Adrien Brody's character, was insulting. You couldn't explain his behaviour—the stabbing, the dressing up—so you just made him retarded. "THE AUDIENCE WILL WONDER WHY HE DID ALL THOSE THINGS! SO I MADE HIM RETARDED! DON'T YOU GET IT? HUH!?"  Christ. And what really chaps my ass is his insistence in including himself in every single one of his films. I know directors do this. Hell, Stan Lee's been in every single Marvel film, as far as I know. But you couldn't bear it, could you Night? You  needed  your face in this film. How else would people know it's one of your films, aside from the heavy-handed, in-your-face commentary and the fact that your name appears in the credits?  In short, if you've already seen  The Village , I feel your pain. Though moments of this film had me interested (and to be fair how the village itself came to be was a pretty nifty concept), I was mostly bored and insulted.  DON'T YOU GET IT, NIGHT? YOU'RE NOT THAT GOOD! I MEAN, YOUR IDEAS ARE REASONABLE, BUT YOUR EXECUTION IS PISS-POOR! AND NO, YOU MAY NOT SIGN MY AUTOGRAPH BOOK!  *** iTunes selection of the day: The Scoop — The Beastie Boys
     
    
</post>


</Blog>