<Blog>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm getting hooked on The Lord of the Rings. I just started watching the first movie about a week ago, and the second last night. Now I can't wait to see the third. I wish I could have been there during the filming.. it would be cool to see the ringwraiths. I liked how they were so mysterious..
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so I changed my colors back to black. I was getting sick of all that white.. well not really, actually they were quite pretty, and nice.. but nice wouldn't excactly be a word to describe me. So I'm going with the half good half evil thing, which suits me since I'm both.. isn't everyone?   However I'm still going to keep the blogger layout thing. It's nice and dark but not TOO dark.. and I like it.
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been working on this holocaust project for school, and its depressing seeing all those little kids stuck in a trashy camp. I wish it would have never happened, but I guess learning about the         machines is cool...  Which leads me to another thing. People back in the 1800s and earlier were far more interesting than people today. They came upwith all these paranormal machines, etc; things that today's science and technology wouldn't accept or probably try. People believed in magic a whole lot more back then too, since they didn't know much about the world, but the thing they did know about was that not everything has to have a logical answer.   They practiced magic, something that most people don't do, and come up with some tech thing to get the job done. People's imagination today is also lacking since there has been no creative machines invented. Why not try creating something like Nicolas Flamel did (like they'd succeed anyway), etc? I just really wish that I lived back then, or if somehow I could just get stuck in a dream forever.   Check out  urlLink this    site and see how great the paranormal world is.  Technology sucks.
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are Form 3,  Unicorn : The |nocent.   "And The Unicorn knew she wasn't meant to go into the Dark Wood.  Disregarding the advice given to her by the spirits, Unicorn went inside and bled silver      ..  For her misdeed, the world knew evil."   Some examples of the Unicorn Form are Eve (Christian) and Pandora (Greek). The Unicorn is associated with the concept of innocence, the number 3, and the element of water. Her sign is the twilight sun.  As a member of Form 3, you are a curious individual.  You are drawn to new things and become fascinated with ideas you've never come in contact with before.  Some people may say you are too nosey, but it's only because you like getting to the bottom of things and solving them.  Unicorns are the best friends to have because they are inquisitive.    urlLink   Which Mythological Form Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dark magician. You love the dark because of it's beauty and just the life that no-one else sees. Mysterious, calm, quiet... But that doesn't mean you're not friendly!   Please rate ^^    urlLink   What kind of dark person are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stayed home today, had cramps. Watched The Last Unicorn and decided to rid of the black look on Furc, so instead changed to my first colors ever, with a few minor changes. I'm extrememly tired today and hungry. I also feel strangely lonely. ~.~
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today at school we had this traveling play thing, with two people. They were acting out The Hobbit, and it was really funny. I think the play people are called the Traveling Lanterns or something of the sort. Anyway, in the play there were only two people, and one of them, the guy, played Bilbo Baggins, and the other, a lady, played a dwarf, Gandalf, Gollum, and a dragon. When she played as a dwarf it was really funny because it looked like she was actually very short, and she did this little dance and walked all fast, and bent back and forth which a real person wouldn't be able to do. I wish I'd carry a camera around with me everywhere or I would have taken pictures and post them. Or if we were notified earlier about the play I would have videotaped it. I will always remember this day.
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are an earth Dragon! You have a knack for Nature or animals, and are peaceful, careful, chariming, and optimistic. You can throw a tantrum now or then, but who doesnt? You value simple things in life, such as friends, familly, and Nature.    urlLink   What elemental dragon are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have probably watched the lord of the rings at least more than ten times. The first two. I can't wait until the third one comes out. I would see it in the theatre if it wasn't so loud in there. If it takes too long to come out though and I just can't stand waiting anymore then I may just go.  I had a snow day today, which I knew I would. It was snowing pretty hard yesturday and it kept on snowing throughout the night. I also get to stay home tomorrow since we were supposed to go to this play. I'm not going so I figure I'd just stay home, because no other teacher can stay behind. Even if they could I still would stay home. Anything to avoid school.  I have been interested in the harry potter books. To be honest I never really thought I would be but when I started to like magic about a year and a half ago and my mom suggest I read the books and I did, and was just addicted. I kept wanting to read the next after the next ect, until I finished the most resent book, the order of the phoenix, within a week. Now I can't wait for the last two to come out. The next is supposed to come out sometime in June, I think.  Oh yes, and I have already done my survey project. No one has answered it, possibly because I waited the week before, or actually the week the project was due. As a result I have made up the results myself and created the best poster ever. Thank you very much. 
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to do this stupid survey for school, so I'd figure I'd ask you people out there. I need at least 50 responses. The question is:  What is your favorite mythical creature?  The phoenix Dragon Unicorn Hippogriff Gryphon or other ( please specify )?  Whisper me on furc to vote ( I hardly ever check my email ) but if you want to email me instead the address is laurenmay8@hotmail.com. Thanks!
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week I have wanted to stay home so bad (of course that's how it is most times). I am getting SO SICK of school I feel as if I want to just die or something. It's so stupid, you never learn anything that's worth the time.   I just want to be home schooled so my mom can teach me WHAT IS WORTH KNOWING and not just algebra and clouds and cells and crap. I want to be a computer game programmer or concept artist, so she could teach me the math that goes along with that. I will not waste my time learning stuff I don't need to. We have projects, we have reports...   AND WHAT GOOD WILL IT DO?
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got out of school early today and am going to the dentist in two hours as of now. Oh, and also, I, or rather my dad, ordered The One Ring from here: http://www.lotrfanshop.com/  It will be my only birthday present, which is May 8th, but who says I won't get any late presents?
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was.. crap. I fought my parents and refused to go to school, but it didn't excactly work. But now that it is Friday night I am happy. Happier than is usual for me :)))
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, today is really annoying, like any other day. First of all I stayed home today (not annoying) because I have the "poops" (annoying).  Next there is furc, which has always been annoying and always will be if people keep being stupid. Wani. What a moron. Talks about pointless things. Like Kambi and Pyerate or however the hell her name is spelled. And frankly, I don't care if any of you object to this little rant, because it is my oppinion and (also in my oppinion) is very close to truth.  Wani also says that I have this stupid "Elly's" colors. It's not like a stole them, because I don't even freaking know her let alone seen her before. My colors are original; I don't care what anyone says.  Good day.
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went back to school. Not much else going on, not much does anyway, most things go on in my head. Not in my life. I've been very annoyed with people and school, and two of my teachers, for math and spanish.  My math teacher is a dipwad. He easily caves in, gives in, and is just overall very stupid with "kids" (Don't like to call myself a kid.. despise them). He does not know how to handle those idiots who get out of control.  The spanish teacher is just annoying. Her stupid spanish accent, her stupid hair, her stupid homework, everything. I don't even do anything she assigns really. I'm not going to Spain, and I'm not planning to.
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All week I've been tired. Two days I stayed up ALL NIGHT and most of all day. This has really messed me up. Right now I have a tired headache, and to top that off I smell like crap. Also there has been no school all week and it has seemed like such a long time, and now on Monday it's back again. All the more to make me more annoyed.
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have watched the last Lord of the Rings, and not at the theater either. My dad knows someone who works at Borders that could give us a copy of the DVD. It was copied from the computer so there's no special features, but at least we have the movie before everyone else does.  I liked the movie a lot. At some points I was cheering on the evil, some parts cheering on the good. It's hard to descide who's side you want to be on. But at the end the good was too powerful and relaxing, and just gave a feeling of comfort, I guess, which darkness can bring sometimes as well. I can't wait for the extended version to come out, which unfortunately will in August. At least it's something to look forward to when school starts again.
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IT IS NOW 4 THIRTY A.M AND I AM A LITTLE TIRED. I should be going to bed soon eh. Well there is not much to say so I don't even know why I am typing thiso ll0lz eh
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have seen the exdended version of The Two Towers today and I must say it makes far more sense and is much more interesting than the original. I've noticed they cut out a lot of funny scenes such as when Merry and Pippin find a cooked chicken in the water near the end. They also left out pretty important parts, too. But they probably cut out all those extras since you could pretty much get the jist of what is happening without all those scenes.
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LOTR personality test:  You are most like  Aragorn (Strider) Son of Arathorn  Aragorn's decisions often seem against conventional wisdom, but he knows what to do and why it must be done, regardless of the cost. You are good at making contingency plans and come up wiith efficient means to acheive clear-cut ends. You are highly independent, and continue on with your plans even in the face of data that might suggest to others that it's no longer feasible. Time alone is important and solitary activities refresh you. You have a tendency to introspection. In your desire for clarity in life, you may have the tendency of being remote or even "heartless". You try to schedule your life as much as possible. You tend to finish your work before resting.   As the foil to Aragorn, Sauron clearly embodies the evil side of this personality.  Traits: Pragmatic, autonomous, ingenious, resolute. On the dark side you could desire power and       tion.  URL: http://www.hobbitlore.com/personality/index.php    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We just bought the expanded editions of the first two Lord of the Rings, and I loved it. I've only seen the fellowship one, tomorrow I'll watch the two towers. The expanded editions show important things they left out as well as funny, comic things. The special features are cool too, but there's A LOT. And seeing all the digital effects is a heads-up for me when I (hopefully) become a computer game programmer or concept artist.
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever realise that tons of people have really stupid descs? Well sure there is the occasional newbie desc and RP desc but I'm talking about those that always have to do with pain and love and darkness. Ones that I think are lyrics to songs, but still. It's getting very old and tiring clicking people and finding stuff in their descs like "Pain is love and we shall die 'till the end" and other jargon of the sort. It's all the same these days. DARKNESS. PAIN. AGONY. Sure, I do love the dark, well maybe not exactly 'love', but that's only because I'm senseitive to the sun; it gives me a headache and in result it makes me very irritable. I do not favor pain, it makes me feel sick, and agony the same. WHAT IS SO APPEALING TO AGONY AND LOVE AND PAIN AND DARKNESS THAT IT FILLS EVERYONE'S STUPID IDIOTIC DESCS?  On a happier note today's the first of spring break and I'm going to the zoo tomorrow. Oh yes the wonderful zoo. It stresses me out sometimes because people tend to be so dumb about the animals and either no very little or nothing. I should be a tour guide. 
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stayed home today. WHAT BIG NEWS OH YES. But excactly why I stayed home I will keep secret. So I watched tv and stuff all day, mainly the science channel, argueing in my head about the different theories and my own. I would be a good scientist if the math was left out. I'm a good arguer, especially when it comes to theories, etc, and things I know a lot about. I also watched the first of the series in The Lord of the Rings, which was on the Action channel and will be on again later 4 pm my time (U.S area, I'm in Michigan so yeah). It's most often on the WAM channel, though. It comes on tv like every other day or so, which is good, since our version of the DVD is widescreen and I don't really like widescreen much.  I also got this dragon book in the mail yesturday. I got my other two books (dragon & unicorn ones) last week. Well this dragon book I got yesturday, The Discovery of Dragons, wasn't very believable. I know you're suppost to be open-minded when reading about dragons, but this book is full of letters from times as late as the A.D ages, and I think the paper would surly be very hard to read if it was this old. Also, there's letters in there describing dragons written by an ancient chinese woman, and the letter is in english, not chinese, and unless people who knew english traveled over and tought them how to speak it, seems very fake indeed. The letter also seems to be typed and I don't think, correct me if I'm wrong, that they invented the printing press around 1200, did they? And if this book is so real, why not supply more evidence? Like fossils, or something else that could be more believable? From the moment I saw this huge but thin book I thought it was a big humongous joke, and I still do. It's just not very believable at all, and letters that could very well be fake are not evidence enough.   There's really nothing else I did and I don't think you would care anyway. I just have too many thoughts and so this is like a dumpster for my brain. Enjoy digging in the garbage!  ( You will notice that the heading says Tuesday the 6th. It is in fact the 7th, yes? Maybe it really is the 6th but my computer clock got messed up when I changed the year temporarily... )
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So we got new schedules in school today, right? Well as I found out weeks earlier, Spanish is a semester long so I will be taking it untill the end of the year, which really sucks. But the other elective I now have is 'Wetlands'. I'm not too fond of this change. A class devoted to nothing but wetlands and preserving them, etc. Sounds so much fun. Better than P.E any day though, I guess. I wish I could take computer class again.
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your ideal Middle-Earth parents are Celeborn and Galadriel!  You live in the beautiful woods of Lothlorien.  You are an elf!  Your parents are very wise and will always be fair with you. They also give very good presents that seem cheesy until you realize that they are exactly what you need.  Your mother is as beautiful as the dawn, which means that you will be either handsome or beautiful yourself and your guy friends will want to hang out at your flet all the time to look at Galadriel.  Arwen, Elladan and Elrohir are your niece and nephews, and Elrond is your brother-in-law.  Your Middle-Earth mama is a psychic, which means that you can never, ever lie to her.  She is the disciplinarian and will do her best to see that you become a wise and noble elf.  Your Middle-Earth dad will try to be your best friend.  He is the one to ask when you want money for concert tickets or permission to go to a party.  Since he will really want to impress you with his hipness you shall be forced to listen to him butcher teenage jargon. Example: What up, homechild!  Thou art trippin in that tunic, yo?  Try to keep him from doing this in public.  Even with all that, Celeborn will spoil you, which you will enjoy, so live it up!  I hope you liked my quiz.  Please rate it, okay?    urlLink   Which Lord of the Rings couple would be your dream parents? Pictures and longish answers.     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was looking around at sites a bit earlier, the ones with all the neopets crap and graphics, etc, and I realized that most, but not all, were bright and cheery and happy and had names like 'Frosted Mallow' (only an example, not actually name of a site) and it depresses me. Yes, happiness depresses me. Bright colors, sunshine, candy. THEE ingrediants for a major headache, literally. All this is fine and dandy for summer when there's not a care in the world, but even then the word 'happy', for me, means 'depressed' or 'sad'. Some of these other sites though, are nice and calm and relaxing, and not at all too happy or sad, but just right.  Just thought I'd rant a little.
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your a Magical Angel!Out of all the angels, you are the one most afflicted with magic. You can do many enchantments as well as sorcery. You cant do black magic, because even though your not so "pure" your still an angel. A very kind and curious one at that. Magical Angels are always very easy-going with humans, but intrestingly enough, like to expirement with them with their spells.    urlLink   What Kind of ANGEL are you? (For     s only) This Quiz has amazingly Beautiful Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, as you can see I have changed the color scheme a bit. Also, I have taken more personality quizes, which I love enormously. You will notice this Slytherin Sorting icon/coat of arms after every post. Yes indeed I am a Harry Potter addict. See which house you'd be Sorted into by clicking on it.   It's almost spring break :)) Last Friday I had the day off and this following Friday I will too, and then it's spring break. I can't wait untill Thursday.
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are the mystery woman    urlLink   Which Ultimate Beautiful Woman are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Moody Aragorn    urlLink   What Lord of the Rings Male and Mood Do You Desire?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No school tomorrow!! I'm so happy there is none tomorrow. I will spend the whole day watching movies, going on the computer and internet, etc. :))
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink     urlLink Take the World of Darkness Quiz  by  urlLink David J Rust   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink      I am Rapunzel!  urlLink  Find your fairy tale character  at  urlLink kelly.moranweb.com .   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink      I'm exceptionally artistic!   urlLink  Find your soul type  at  urlLink kelly.moranweb.com .   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Take the 100 Acre Personality Quiz!  
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We board a horse named Cal at my mom's friend's house. Someone, both the friend and someone from the high school, were supposed to meet us there to see another horse I like and might be doing Equestrian with, Cheyanne. They didn't show. We got a good view of Cal though, and he is in bad shape. He is usually fat and now he is pretty thin. He limps. Mom says we may have to put him down if the vet can't do anything to make him better or if the arthritis proceeds.   There was a really cute cat over there as well.. a kitten I think, as it is still pretty small. Meowed really loud and purrs really loud. When I scratch him he licks, just like my two cats. Perhaps they are related? My other cat Sam, which ran away from the vet when going to get neutered just like his mother had done.. I think my two cats are just two of his many sons he had. Pie has inherited his fluffyness and white spot in the middle of his back, and Danny the coloring and tabbyish color from Sam's mom. I'm pretty sure I'm correct on this one. Same was my favorite cat, and so was Flower, his mom, and it's good to know I have a little of both.
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have more cramps. DON'T YOU JUST LOVE WHEN THAT HAPPENS? Oh yes I know you do.  People annoy me. Why not hang people/behead them if they did a crime serious enough? Living with your concious in hell is worse than sitting in jail, where at least you get food and water. Pretty descent.  I have much more oppinions on this and of course it's in another post of mine...  I just feel like saying it over and over again, to let the anger out.
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DANNY CAME BACK!!! I am so happy. He was soaking when he came back, but now he's pretty dry. Now my life is [somewhat] complete again. :)
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There was a huge, HUGE storm yesturday afternoon. I was a bit surprised there was no tornado. Anyway, I let my two cats out in the morning, Pie (the fluffball) and Danny, his shorthair brother. Pie came back a few hours later, and he was soaking, SOPPING wet, complete with leaves and a stick stuck in his fur. Danny never showed. Usually they'd come back together or Pie would go back out and bring Danny back, but to no avail. I am really worried about him. Our whole woods is flooded, about a foot deep my dad says, and I am starting to wonder if maybe it was raining so bad and the wind blowing so hard that Danny found it hard to swim, and drowned. I hope this is not true. But every second he is gone I start to get more and more depressed. Cats are like this sometimes, though. Sometimes they go out and don't appear again for up to a week. Hopefully this is just one of Danny's little "outings" and he will return soon.
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow and all the way to Friday I get to stay home, because my whole grade is going to Washington DC and I don't want to go. They get back on Sunday night. So I'm staying home, which is good, because everytime I come home from school I feel like crap, and look it too. All the more reason to have second and even a third shower.
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Animal abuse..  It's awful, and needs to stop.   How can people be so stupid, hurt a helpless animal, when they know they are going to get caught anyway?  People like this should die. On the spot.  http://www.arkonline.com/abuse.html   Please note that the Stephen King mentioned in animal abuse is not the author Stephen King, but a different one, which I find odd.. At least it's not the author, as he is one of my favorites.  Also check out www.meat.org and http://www.hsus.org/ace/11533 for the slaughtering reality.  Animal abuse is worse than slaughter. People who abuse animals are mentally challenged, as butchers are just doing their job. Based on what I'ved read butchers are good-hearted and aren't violent, and take the whole slaughtering thing in a positive point of view, which is good. The world demands meat; we could just not give them any or have them slaughter their own; but it doesn't work that way and why it doesn't change I have no idea. But untill then, don't think of butchers as heartless, cruel people; they're just doing the heartbreaking dirty work so we don't have to (yet).  Also, PLEASE take the time to browse through here:   http://www.animalsvoice.com/PAGES/archive.html
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We got the second DVD of Harry Potter (Chamber of Secrets) and it is SO MUCH better than the first one. We didn't start watching it untill 8 at night or so, so we're going to finnish watching it tonight.   My favorite House? Slytherin of course, and favorite student, Malfoy. Favorite professor, Snape (000oooh yes). Just thought you'd like to know o.o;
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever notice how being bi seems to be a fad? Take these descs as examples (I will still leave the desc owner's name known, mind you):  Taken from Mavix's desc: {14 . bi. holycrap}  As we can see this little portion of desc is quite ridiculous. She is 14 and already bi. This is very gross indeed, and seems more of a kind of stupid fad now. JOIN THE BANDWAGON! BECOME BI! This is just discusting. And what's up with the "holycrap"? Also, you stole Ashait's colors, Mavix, so get rid of them, you wanker.  Note: Peeb is also bi. I have seen this many times in past descs.  Due to the fact that there weren't a whole lot of people on furc at this time, I will have to add to this ever growing list later.   More bi's: Sadina Anabell, Seamyst.  Also note that most of these people who are bi are retards. "omgwtf" "irabouttocry" and "omgwhy" are just a few phrases these idiots have conjured up.  *If you are any of these people and are offended, too bad. It offends and sickens me that you're bi. Everywhere I click, BI, BI, BI. What is up with this? Ahh well, perhaps it means less children in the world, less disgusting,annoying children/people. Now all we need to do is have a d.eath penalty and less freaking houses.   Kudos to you bi's, in a way... :)
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well the math teacher is being a butt. He says he has to be more strict with the homework since (some people) are going to Washington D.C for three days next week (I'm just staying home). Anyway, he isn't very strict, EVER. I only do half of his homework anyway, which is enough since he doesn't check if the answers are correct but if we have them done or not.
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been searching the internet for the TRUE meaning and TRUE history of "goth" and found only that the EARLIEST this term came from was from the design of the buildings some hundreds or thousands of years ago. So how did "gothic" become what it is known as today? Basicaly what you are saying when you are "goth" is that you are a building. That's really all it means. It wasn't really religion either but a group of people, a tribe of people that just dissapeared, and why that is I still want to know. I have seen SO MANY sites on goths as being dark, or evil, etc, when they don't even know WHAT IT REALLY MEANS. It's not about music, not about wearing black, but WAS a new wave in architecture long ago. These buildings have a very medieval look to them, which I like,and they also have this evil sort of look to them, but it had NOTHING to do with religion or how people dressed. And untill there is a SERIOUS site about what "gothic" REALLY MEANT AND WHERE IT CAME FROM, WITH AS MANY DETAILS AS POSSIBLE, anyone who says they are "gothic" is and idiot. Modern things are way off.
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got two other presents on my birthday besides the One Ring: a Gollum action figure and a Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone DVD. This movie was pretty good I admit, but the special effects could have been better. I think a better director would do.. say like.. Peter Jackson, perhaps? Anyway, HP was on TV last night, the same one I have on DVD, with sneak previews of The Prisoner of Azkaban here and there. I noticed some scenes from the Sorcerer's Stone weren't on the DVD I have, which can only mean one thing: they are coming out with an extended version, copying LOTR. The idiots.  About crime in the crap U.S: It is getting worse. People are starting to think that technalogy is the answer to everything, when it only proves worse since the trouble-makers want to see how far they can go without getting caught. Therefore, I believe the       penalty should be brought back. Annual beheadings should take place for a crime such as       , and the heads of the victims on display in the jail and outside of it as a reminder and example. People are getting away with things too much these days and should be        d and scared into confessing what their wrongs were, the ultimate punishment being       in front of thousands of people. To set a better example would be to stick the heads on road signs, but that would be a little to harsh, wouldn't it? .. Nah.
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was no better than any other. In fact it was a little worse, but then got better and better, but only by a bit. First I had cramps this morning ( I stayed home yesturday because of them ), and my mom was being a butt because she kept straining at me to go. My dad said to call him later when I got to school.. so I did, and went home, watched the other half of LOTR the expanded edition, got my Ring in the mail today, but one thing is still ruining my day.. it is sunny out. Not that I am evil, oh no.. My eyes are just very sensitive to the sun.   I cried this morning. Isn't that great news? And ever realise that after you cry you get really tired? Well that tiredness is still with me.
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         What Natural Disaster are you?  urlLink Take the quiz!  
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink  Which HP Kid Are You?   
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ShadowFire Dragon  In the war between good and evil, your inner Dragon self is rotten with the stench of EVIL. When it comes to the powers of Chaos vs. those of Law and Order, your inner dragon tends to do things by the book.  As far as magical tendancies, a ShadowFire Dragon's nature does not lend itself well to the ways of Magic. During combat situations, the ShadowFire Dragon shows a preference for the rending and slashing of Hand to Hand combat.     Find out your inner dragon: http://Dragonhame.Com  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We went to see Cal yesturday, then to Target, then we went out to eat. I wasn't very hungry but my mom got a salad for me anyway. I only ate a little bit and then I started crying. At first I didn't know why but then I realized that lately, meaning for weeks, I had lost my appetite. If I eat something I don't like one day I end up not being hungry for a while. Then I started thinking of Cal, and how he is being put to sleep Thursday, which is tomorrow. Then my dad asked if it was because of Cal and I nodded yes, and that started my mom crying. The waitress must have thought we were phsycos.  So then today we went to see him again and I got to ride my favorite horse (besides Cal) named Cheyanne, a really pretty appaloosa gelding. My dad also took some pictures of me riding him, and of Cal. I know I should be there for him when he gets put to sleep, but it's all just too sad, and I've suffered too much depression in the past months to go into a deep one again.  When I'm sad enough I'll do anything. Even go to the theater, which I think I want to do, to see the third Harry Potter, just to cheer me up. Comedy and the sort cheers me up.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have cried this morning.. actually this evening because I sleep late (4-9 P.M usually), because it is definate now: Cal is going to be put down. He has to be. There is no cure for him. A horse needs all his legs, and arthritis just takes away his life. I have already suggested an idea of a bionic leg. It would cost too much for one thing, and it may not even be possible. My former filly, though, Dream Catcher (Dreamy) rescently gave birth to her second colt, Bingo, who looks JUST like Cal. Call me strange, but I think Cal already reincarnated.  Also, I have this book (Muggles and Magic) and it has this section on censorship and book banning. For those of you who think the books Harry Potter has something to do with the devil, you're idiots. All it is is a book about this stupid PPPOTTER who finds out he's a wizard and he goes to this wizarding school. No where in the books have there been even the smallest clue that Potter is satanic, etc. Stupid religious freaks. Not all magic is evil.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the place where we board Cal, and he still has pretty bad arthritis; bad as in he can barely move or take care of himself. I have wondered why this can't be fixed with surgery, but even if it could he wouldn't make it up the trailer and to do the surgery where he is would prove       as well. We are going to have to put him down.  Dream Catcher though, our former horse (now about 3, 4 years old) had a second colt by which is named Bingo, that looks remarkably like Cal, and is a little fat and everything. I also got the "Impressionistic Page"      , or      s if you will, it being a mare and foal and all, and they look just like Dreamy and Bingo. I was one out of 350 to get drawn. 
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My stomach hurts pretty bad. I took a shower earlier than I usually do, which was about 10:30 AM or so. Thought I'd get it over with. I'm also very cold.. and bored.. why else would I be typing here? Well, other than put some thoughts away..  Oh yes and I slept for 2 days in a row and I'm still tired. Ever notice the more you sleep the more tired you get?
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Second night of 'Salem's Lot and I'm still not very scared. Don't want to be either. Turns out it was about vampires, which was cool. I've got to get the book.. I saw it at Borders.  Nothing else. Don't plan on there being much.  Oh yeah and I hear a loud frog outside if that satisfies you.
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I watched 'Salem's Lot today.. part 1, and it wasn't that scary, though if I was alone it probably would be. Anyway, I like those kind of movies, with a mysterious guy and all..  Not much else.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the ortodontist today. I don't want to get braces at all. I never even told my mom I wanted any. She just says I'll be happy I did it. And I'll be honest, I do feel the same way somewhat, being that I have a rather large overbite, but still, it doesn't bother me much at all. Oh well.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the people I get mad at: it truely is you. I'm sorry that I have a low tolerance for people who spell phoenexes as "feenixes" and for people who act so remotely stupid I find it hard to believe they know how to even push the button that turns the computer on.  I know I sound snobby. I know I sound as if I think I am better than everyone else. But the truth is, smarter people rule the stupid ones. So I AM better.  Not counting the fact that I have stupid days sometimes. Who doesn't?  But I'm talking those who seem to have stupid lives, years, months, etc, rather than just days.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do so many people like anime? So many freaking layouts about freaking anime. It gets me really annoyed. What's so great about a freaking japanese crap cartoon whose lips don't even move right when they talk? Just the look of anime is enough to make me barf, and even the word, and the mention of it. Sorry for this continueous ranting, but I'm tired and besides, I am looking for a real answer here.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I have quite a series of rants here (as usual). First of all, and what most recently got me thinking, is internet cable. I just saw a Comcast truck near our road. What was that about? I know it may just be for the tv, but it's cable all the same. I am getting SICK of dial-up. Once every place has it I think dial-up should go.  Second thing is too many houses going up. People wonder why we don't have money for anything, and look what they wasted their money on. Houses. There's just too much. There's enough houses already. At least we've got those demelition guys.. that's in the big cities though. Burning everywhere else.  Next is people. Annoying people. Enough said.  This was on the news weeks ago, but I just now remembered it: People stealing things from building sites. That just makes me happy. Keep up the good work, theives!  When me and my parents were going to CompUSA/Koals, they were talking how there are more k.illers(ignore the dot;my computer is sensitive)here than in any other place (any other place meaning London and Canada). Here we have thousands. London 1 or 2, and Canada 30. Some person blamed it on the media, saying they just scare us. I don't know how that would bring up the rate..   When I got to CompUSA, there were hardly any good games there. All the good ones were purely online, and I have no cable, and dial-up certainly does not work for that sort of thing (due to my experience, but obviously I had doubt it would really work for more than a second or two anyway), so that rules those out. And all the computer games there viewed the "world" as if you were above everyone, just controling everything, and not actually being IN the game itself like Morrowind does. All the games there seem to be the same. Neverwinter Nights seemed all right so I got that. Looks a lot like everything else though. I never could find any good game after I got Morrowind. If you like a certain game (no cable, no internet), please let me know. I'd like to get addicted to something else other than Morrowind and Black & White.  I am also looking for some good mods for Morrowind (no Tribunal required, as I don't have that yet), particulary races and bug/quest fixes. Please respond with any good mods I should try. I have a lot already, but half either require Tribunal or just won't open (it says it's part of a "multi-disc set" and it has an error opening; stupid). Also I have downloaded something so the Cliffracers and Slaughterfish won't attack unless provoked, but I have NO idea where .RAR files go and I put the thing in every Morrowind file. Looking for advise there   Edit: I downloaded Zip Genius and that was a huge help. Now I have tons more mods, but the only problem is that I have downloaded a rideable horse mod, only to find it freaking requires Tribunal, and there were at least 20 .esp files! What a waste of space. Stupid Tribunal.. I need to buy that just to get half the good mods to work. >:I
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink be sorted  @  urlLink nimbo.net   Hmm well.. just felt like keeping that html code thing up there ^ I left it as an option to have it there all the time. So I will leave it there this time.  I watched the first LOTR on the WAM! channel. Not much else going on. Except I really want to swim now and we're going to Target tomorrow (or today, rather, being it 12 in the morning).
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Origninaly school was supposed to end the 14th of June. But now it's the 11th. They changed it. And now today is my first day of summer vacation. You'd think I'd be more excited, right? Well, I keep it inside. Don't have the heart to show it. And summer vacation goes by fast most of the time. Before I know it school will start once again and I'll go back to ranting like a maniac on how stupid it all is and how I teach myself what I WANT to know.  If you like and take interest in a certain thing, it will most likely become part of your job. Even having an interest in things such as dragons and mythology, there is the option of being a cryptozoologist or medeivalist. If your job would require math, basic, mind you, which most jobs do involve math, you would learn that. And reading and writing, of course. But after that, it's your desition [having trouble spelling today] what you want to do from there: waste your life or teach yourself what interests you. Even miner interests. That's what I do. Of course I still need to go to school, but there is a dream I have that school only includes math and reading. From there, learn what interests you, and you could have a really good job.  I haven't been on furc for a while now because of (1) I have been too buisy with the real world, and (2) I have been playing Morrowind. I have not had the desire to deal with idiots on furc, which, mind you, are all over, and seem to go online daily. Buttwipes.  I have more rants.. but after all this typing I seem to have forgotten them. If ever I think of anything, I will add on to this. 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yes and I'm bored.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cal got put to sleep today, and I am glad I wasn't there while it happened; too sad. My parents said they looked away as the vet put in the shot, but they saw him laying down after and they said he looked so peaceful. I'm sure he's happy now.  I slept all day and my mom brought home a nice little (should I say little?) present: My mom's friend's daughter; around 10 years old I'd say. My mom asked if I would go swimming with them, and of course I said no. But then about 15 minutes later Nicole, as she's named, comes in my room and just keeps BEGGING me to get up and swim. So I did. And man, is she annoying. When she went back home we watched Kingdom Hospital. I wonder why 'Salem's Lot isn't on DVD? I'd like to see it again soon. Oh yes and Harry Potter is going to be on TV July 11th, which is good, 'cause I get to see Snape again ;)
    
</post>


<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First effect listed is one out of 4 possible.  Alit Hide ------- Drain Intelligence, Resist Poison  Ampoule Pod ------ Water Walking, Paralyze  Ash Salts ------- Drain Agility, Resist Magicka  Bittergreen Petals ----- Restore Intelligence, Invisibility  Black Anther ------ Drain Agility, Resist Fire  Black Lichen ------ Drain Strength, Resist Frost  Bloat ------- Drain Magicka, Fortify Intelligence  Bonemeal ------ Restore Agility, Telekenisis  Bungler's Bane ------ Drain Speed, Drain Endurance  Chokeweed ------- Drain Luck, Restore Fatigue  Coda Flower ------ Drain Personality, Levitate  Cornberry ------- Drain Fatigue, Restore Magicka  Corkbulb Root ----- Cure Paralyzation, Restore Health  Corprus Weepings ----- Drain Fatigue, Fortify Luck  Corprusmeat ----- Drain Fatigue, Drain Health  Crab Meat ------- Restore Fatigue, Resist Shock  Daedra Skin ----- Fortify Strength, Cure Common Disease  Daedra's Heart ----- Restore Magicka, Fortify Endurance  Diamond ----- Drain Agility, Invisibility  
    
</post>


<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got spacers today. They don't hurt much now. Also I watched the last episode of Kingdom Hospital. I wonder why no Stephen King movie is ever in the theater. Only on tv. &nbsp; I have downloaded the Sixth House mod and have joined it.. now it is pretty much all finished. I don't know why I'm suddenly typing this, so don't pay attention.. I feel odd today. AND THIS BLOGGER KEEPS THINKING IT'S 7 WHEN IT IS 10. AND WHAT IS UP WITH THESE NEW POST SETTINGS? 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I do feel extra crappy today. I feel as if it is humid or something, and even the smallest task makes me tired. As I was leaving the bathroom from taking a shower, I felt as if I was about to faint just going to hang my towl up. I have also felt more sad lately even though I already take some pills for it, and have been for a while now. I know perfectly well the reason for how I am feeling. I barely have any appetite anymore. I barely eat. I am hungry as I type this but we have nothing good as of now. I start to get more and more sad and wonder what there is to live for besides love..  Anyway, tomorrow morning (yes, morning) I go to the orthodontist or dentist or whatever and get my spacers. I am pondering on putting up a fight when time comes for me to go. For one thing, I'm going to have to wake up around 6 a.m, either that or stay up all night and then just take a shower when I need to, and another thing is that I never asked to get braces, nor do I want any. Either this or trying to reason with my mom to cancel the whole thing, which there is about a 1% chance she'll actually listen.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes this is my new blog. My other one isn't working.  I was wathcing VH1 and I just realized how much I like Switchfoot and Velvet Revolver and that's all that happened today. Oh yes and I slept a day and 2 nights and read a bit in between.
    
</post>


</Blog>