<Blog>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How can you drop a raw egg onto a concrete floor without cracking it?  anyone to answer this little riddle plus the one from theother day gets 5 points added to their last quiz. dont post tothe site... email me at amynichols10@aol.com.  points also given for most unique / so funny it made me snort.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oooh. the morning after. i hope art is gentle. tell rollins i'm sorry, but sofie and i got invited to another keg party just down the road in matunuck. anyway, congrats on a job well done...  now let the REAL work begin.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      T minus 5 hours. you're SO not thinking about mondrian. i realize this, and do not necessarily expect that the majority of you will be able to speak coherently this afternoon. maybe i wil be pleasantly surprised. also, the syllabus is about to go to crap for the sake of fun and interesting projects that have been brought to my attention. i heart n.y.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i signed up
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      good afternoon children! hope all is going well with your portfolios. well, you'll be glad to know we were both down in the mud today... you figuritively and me litterally. the magic of a poorly drained site, but that's for another class and another teacher. have you ever heard the story about the portfolio faerie?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi kids!  me again! figured out (sort of...) how to get evryone involved in this little wedblog thingey. you should all have recieved an invitation to become a "team member" and i hope to see posts from some of you soon. this is just another way for you all to PARTICIPATE in class discussion, since there isn't too much of that going on right now in terms of critiques and such. the input of your fellow classmates can be as valuable as anything an instructor might have to offer. i am one person, and have my own very strong opinions... but that is what they are. second opinions are great... and third, and fourth, and so on.    don't worry, the breathing will resume in about 48 hours. and the sleeping.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      even though i am estimating that only 5% of students enrolled in lar244 are actually going to check this site, i figured i would put a post-class note up here today.  as many of you (which would be 1 of the 5% actually reading this) already know, i have decided that the mondrian models will be handed in / presented on THURSDAY of next week instead of tuesday. however, i will be handing out your next assignment on TUESDAY. this gives you a bit more time to make your models spectacular. you're welcome.  ps: what do you have if there are 6 oranges in your left hand and 7 oranges in your right hand?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for class today:  hope you all have your model building supplies in hand, and your creative thinking caps on. and your king cakes in your bellies.  one thing i was thinking about... when you go to a restaurant, does it matter to you what the menu looks like?  have you ever been to a restaurant whose menu was presented in such a way that it made you much more interested in the food? i have. i think this might apply to your "programs" that are to be handed in today... i'm making an analogy here guys, are you following?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well hello to all who have to chosen to visit! i hope to use my postings here for little reminders about class assignments, due dates, random thoughts, and inspriational and creative sorts of things. inspirational is sort of a stupid word... who do i think i am anyway?  so, i guess this first posting is simply to welcome you all to another point of reference regarding your coursework in lar244.  if you find the information here useful, let me know by emailing me at amynichols10@aol.com.  i will try to update the site every day, or at least the evening before class.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      S O M E T H I N G  P O S I T I V E  this is why i thought it was ok to throw broadway in bloom at you: on all previous projects, most of you exceeded my expectations, and you seemed to do it with ease. so why not expect something more, right? you all know what drawings should look like, you know their purpose. you learned that in 243 (as well as 201)... i saw it in your portfolios too.  i think where we got off track was when i assumed that you would be able to combine your OWN ideas, your own design, with all of your previous  knowledge. that complicated things rather quickly.  more than anything, i want you all to complete this class and be more prepared for 343. i want you to exceed the expectations of your next instructor.  often in the profession you have chosen, you will encounter sink or sail situations.  i guess this is your first one in my class... now it's up to you to determine what happens.  i PROMISE (which is something i rarely do) that your next project will be very different... i will work with you to explain concepts, talk about how landscape architecture and design relates to the world around us, and we'll go back to the beginning to reinforce the idea of SPACES.  re-read your course description (or i could be one of those boring instructors that reads to you like children...).  think seriously about landscape architecture... and why you are here. if you're lost, ask me.  shit that wasn't quite as positive as i thought it would be. forgive me, i am hung over. just kidding.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone...figured I'd attempt to get a forum going. (constructive criticism only.) how can we rectify this renegade project, learn from it, and make the most of the remainder of the semester? I know few of you check this site, but those who do-please verbalize your concerns. bitching and apathy only go so far. Amy is a resource- we should respect that and utilize her knowledge and experience to prepare us... If nothing else we can learn to communicate more effectively. I think that her "before I forget"... e-mail was legitimate, as I have witnessed a decline in class morale and interest. I know my attitude has been poor recently, and I take responsibility for that. I tend to talk a lot so before I continue I urge you to respond- this blog should be a space for all of us to freely voice our opinions. how about it? graham
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here are a few more details about what i am looking to see for next tuesday (some of you didn't think i was actually SERIOUS about what i was expecting for last class...)  -FINAL (unrendered) layout of your design on 24x36 titleblock.  this is to include notes, dimensions, and any pertainent information about layout and materials.  this also means that your black and white graphics should be up to LAR243 quality.  also, if you plan on adding an elevation to this same sheet, you might want to have that completed as well.  -i will meet with individual groups to redline your plans, and review your progress sketches and elevations.  i MIGHT be around saturday afternoon... have a few more mondrian projects to grade.  let me know if you need to see me. or if you just miss me...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! start collecting corrugated cardboard. you'll need a bunch.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok... nothing relevant here at the moment, but for any of you that need something to make you smile:  www.pbjdance.com (you'll need speakers for that one)   for those of you that need something to make you feel completely stupid:  http://www.madblast.com/funflash/swf/map_test.swf (took me 5 times... ok fine, it was 6)  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok... here's what i want for thursday:  a FULL SIZE title block (24x36) refined plan (showing sizes, some dimensions, notes, etc.) evidence of progress on sketches, elevations, detail plans  remember the LECTURE tomorrow.  and remind me that you all need a quiz soon. yes, a quiz.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally! some of you have taken interest in my sense of humor. i get the feeling it's because you think i am handing out points like they're candy or something. anyway... these are for you:  What has six legs, is green and brown, and is lethal?  What do you call a fly with no wings?  What do John The Baptist and Kermit The Frog have in common?  enjoy.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      happy friday. hope all is going well with your group work situations. i put 2 examples of title blocks up on the wall in studio by the door. but i'm sure you can come up with something much better.  so for tuesday each group should have: -title block (for me to redline / make suggestions) -written program (P L E A S E avoid lined paper... it's painful for me) -concept plan (bubble type diagram w/ notes and proposed features)  next week i'll talk to you about form composition studies (how LINES and TYPES OF LINES affect the feeling of a designed space).  also, go back and re-read your semester project... you know, the ORIGINAL group project i assigned.  it was called EVALUATION OF A SPACE or something like that.  think about a space you'd like to evaluate cause you're going to have to do it in the upcoming weeks.  also... a reminder about the lecture next wednesday night.  10 points on your lowest quiz grade if you attend.  most of you need it. ha.  oh yeah, and what did the zero say to the eight? email me your thoughts on this one... and any other dull or dumb jokes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok... just to reiterate what was discussed in class:  due to weather / spring break / computer lab availability, for thursday i expect that you all will have a "rough" site inventory & analysis (one drawing... on trace, or your choice of media).  by rough, i dont mean messy or sloppy, i simply mean that it is not a "presentation" drawing.  since the client typically does not ever see this step in the design process, i feel like it's ok to keep this part of the project on the "sketch" level.  you should have lots of notes on this drawing... remember: note opportunities & restrictions, NOT proposed features.  think about circulation, environmental conditions, limits and boundaries (those that can be pushed and those that cannot).  this step is to help you become familiar with the site.  any research you can do (and make note of on your drawing) will defintely help.  feel free to call / email if you have questions.  one additional note: i was EXTREMELY unhappy with the level of respect i received in class yesterday.  it was definitely not the first occasion that i felt like people were talking over me.  if you want to have productive discussions (which is the point of this studio class) then you must come to class prepared to let me talk, and then respond.  if i need to start dictating the rules, because you are not mature enough to handle a classroom situation the way i have been running things, i am sure we will see some big changes.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have been somewhat inundated with questions about what exactly i am expecting of you all for tomorrow's class.  basically, i expect that you will have THOUGHT ABOUT and taken the time to absorb the necessary information about the task at hand. i am hoping that you have come to the conclusion that there are MANY improvements that can be made to the space.  i am hoping that as designers, you come up with some orginal ideas... and that based on your (somewhat limited)  knowledge of the site, as well as independent research, you have begun to analyze how and where you might incorpoate these improvements.  landscape design is a three dimensional creative process.  i can teach you the process, the presentation, how to convey your ideas... but the ideas NEED to come from you.  this is the thinking part.  this is where you put in your time.  forget about the drawing for now, think about writing stuff down.  think about research... look at back issues of landscape architecture magazine, or other similar publications.  we'll work on basemaps for a bit during class.  if you've completed yours, great. you are ahead of the game. move on to your SITE INVENTORY DRAWING and your SITE ANALYSIS DRAWING (i can give a bit more direction in class).  i would like to have a relaxed class tomorrow to ease back into the old routine. but class is mandatory unless there is inclement weather and the university shuts down.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      many of you are over your quota in your emailboxes. this is probably my fault, because i sent those darn .dxf files. man that sucks... because not only can you not recieve my all-important emails, but you might not be getting other very important messages from other very important people besides me. so... i guess what i am saying is clean out your mailboxes. and blame it on me.  also... the grading of projects continues. and it's not fun. anyway, some people didn't leave all of their modrian stuff on their desks. i'm not naming names, but that's only because i don't have them here in front of me.   moving on... we'll go to woodward computer lab for part of class on tuesday. i went there today, only to find it locked. that was lame. we'll figure this base map stuff out. take it slow...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today. 4:30pm. woodward computer lab. i'm going to attempt to be there. if you have any questions, you should too. then i'll be up in studio handing out A's like it's my job. some B's too i think. maybe a C or 2. scared? 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just spent some time in studio trying to get your projects graded.  got through most of the photoanalysis / unit shape compositions.  if your photoanalysis (w/ original photo) and/or unit shape composition is not in studio, please make an attempt to leave it/them on the front desk. i will be in once or twice next week to complete the grading.  also, i left some cd's on the front desk that contain the .dxf files for broadway in bloom.  one more note about our current project... don't get ahead of yourselves on this one.  the point of this project is to walk through the design process. you can't jump ahead to the schematic design phase without first inventorying and analyzing the site. good luck, and if anyone needs more direction / input let me know.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am tired. you will not be getting handouts on the design process today. i will talk about programming, inventory, and analysis. that should get you through spring break. we will talk about getting base map information... has anyone been successful? i will make an attempt later today.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well alright, since there has been very little interest in my sense of humor, i'm going to reveal the ridiculously humorous answers to my riddles:  first, if you have 6 oranges in one hand, and seven oranges in the other, you have VERY BIG HANDS.  second, it is very difficult to crack a concrete floor, especially with an egg.   as far as class goes though... i know you need direction on this broadway in bloom project. i'm going to make all attempts to have an organized discussion on thursday about where we are going with this. everyone should be in class at 4pm ready to present their mondrian projects, then the business will begin.  since you will all be familiar with the project requirements, please come prepared with any questions, comments, difficulties, or concerns you might have.  i will be LECTURING about the design process, and giving handouts that will help walk you through the process.  i can give you the tools, but you need the inspiration (shit- there i go using that dumb word again - please someone give me a better word if you have one) and the creativity to make this project successful.  not only do you need to have a "smart" design that fulfills the project requirements, you need to bundle it up neatly and sell it to your client. you need to begin thinking about PRESENTATION.  this means drawing size, color palettes, motif, text, bindings, etc.  enough already. feedback. please.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figured out how to post finally...  So, about the orange thing...I think the answer is "you have a lot of oranges" =)  And about the egg, I have no clue...Although I do remember a project I had to do back in middle school concerning a raw egg...We had to design an apparatus to hold an egg so that it wouldn't break if dropped from a first floor window...I don't remember how I made mine, but I know the egg cracked...I'm beginning to think that the question is a trick...Is it? Do I get points for answering? I know it says email you Amy, but I don't know the answer...  Have a wonderful Wednesday everyone...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      are you afraid?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.broadwaymall.org  for any of you that are bored. or looking forward to moving away from mondrian. and looking towards something a bit more fun... that has an actual defined purpose. please make yourselves familiar with all aspects of this design competition.  your clients... your judges... your design parameters.  we're going to spend a good amount of time on this one, focusing on the DESIGN PROCESS. because it is a process. it doesn't just happen. this is serious business folks. serious fun that is. some seriously fun busness. right.  also, i'm leaning towards having you tackle this project on your own... no group work this time around. any thoughts?  ps: if you didn't like my jokes all you had to do was tell me. i'll stop trying to be funny now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry... i haven't been blogging. but then again neither have you. first, another boring update about where you should all be by class next tuesday. you should have your plan all figured out... notes, graphics, layout, etc.  this means your sketches should be ready for me to review so that i can give you suggestions on how to improve them if they need improvement.  basically, the only thing that should be left for you to do after tuesday is minor revisions and copying onto your final sheet for rendering by thursday.  beyond that... there's the business of the after party. i'd like to know who plans on attending so i can give fair warning to the establishment of your choice.  word.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi guys... a few thoughts: be sure to read the next phase of our current project. the next step is NOT to simply add planting to your island. it is to create unique spaces untilizing materials and planting along with a "theme" to create garden display spaces. be sure to take your creativity to the limits... make your spaces as inviting and interesting as possible. though there is to be only one "structure" (meaning building) you can add other constructed elements such as pergolas, arbors, amphitheater type areas, walls, barriers, etc. keep thinking about materials and most importantly SPATIAL SEQUENCING.  also... there is a lecture tongiht in the weaver auditorium. jim urban will be lecturing about something extraordinarily relevant to the world of landscape architecture (though i do not recall what exactly...). you should go. i cannot.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry for the late posting... it's spring and things are getting busy for me. anyway, as far as me being around this weekend for help on your plans and models, please let me know if you need me. we can sort of just proceed on an "on-call" basis. i have commitments tomorrow morning and evening, but can be available between 1 and 4 in the afternoon. i really don't mind coming to campus because my other options would be cleaning house or raking leaves (neither of which appeals to me). however, i do need some beauty sleep in the afternoon before a social gathering tomorrow night.  i am also available sunday... just need a few hours of sun on the veranda late morning / early afternoon to recover from saturday nights events.  please email in advance if you'd like to see me about your project.  I know i'm asking a lot from you in a short amount of time... do your best work for the amount of time you have.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.dr-joe.net/quiz.html  this is not your quiz. it's just a quiz.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow. broadway in bloom is done. that makes me happier than you know. i, like many of you, felt in a rut.  moving on though... a few thoughts on project 5, part one. i know we are going to move fairly quicky (meaning at lightning speed) through this entire project.  this means you are to come up with the best possible solutions given the time permitted. i may not be around or reachable at critical decision making points, which means YOU'LL have to exercise your own judgement abilities. that's part of the deal.  this is another one of those projects with few restraints, which you will be able to take advantage of further on in part two.  however, there are many opportunities in determining the shape of your island, its boundaries and the relationship of your display spaces.  REMEMBER: the intent of this project is to define spaces using the landform, and the USE of the spaces will be for display of sculpture / art.  views and vistas should be considered, but mostly in terms of backdrop or succession of circulation and variety.  re-read the assignment (or read it for the first time... whichever) because chances are you missed something. well, that's more than a few thoughts.  good luck. feedback is always appreciated.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      monday mornings are not fun. especially when your eye appears to have exploded. which is the case with me right now. just a little forewarning for tomorrow... it looks very frightening, but it's completely benign.  as far as tomorrow goes, i'm looking forward to seeing your group presentations on evaluation of a space, even if it is only with my one good eye. they'd better be good. really good.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i'm still alive
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      had a great time... i have a feeling that the 6 individuals who joined me for some foodies and bevies are the ones who'll read this.   makes me want to re-enlist in the LAR program for another tour of duty.  i looked forward to tuesday and thurday afternoons. now they're just two more days on the way to the weekend.  good luck this summer... and please keep in touch.  i'll probably be in studio on sunday doing grades if you want to make it a collaborative effort. or if you just miss me so darn much you can't stand it...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after my third margarita, i am just now realizing i have ruined your cinco de mayo celebrations.  my apologies.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.subservientchicken.com/  random.  type in a command, and the chicken does it... within reason of course.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a little late... but some ideas for sketches might be found at the following websites if you are still struggling:  http://www.nga.gov/feature/sculptgarden/sculpt1.htm  http://hirshhorn.si.edu/collection/garden.html  http://calendar.walkerart.org/canopy.wac?id=1072 (this one takes some looking around... the main site is "walker without walls" and the walker art center, but the section about minneapolis sculpture garden shows some really neat ideas about incorporating art and other activities in the garden)  http://www.broomhillart.co.uk/sculpturegardens/index.html  http://www.noguchi.org/sculpture_gardens.html  take a look if you need some INSPIRATION. especially at the walker art site... some interesting stuff.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi. this could very well be one of my last blog entries. i know, there are probably 3 of you who will actually read this, but regardless i'll try to give some useful advice for completing your final project.  first point... less is more. that is, unless it's one of those rare occasions where less is less. by this i mean don't overdo it, but don't underdo it either. when you render your plans, do it in a way that highlights inmportant features and elements of your design. render quickly and lightly... it's easy to add layers of color, but difficult to take them away. and did i mention rendering quickly? color is a tool that will help convey your design, but it's no more important than the thought that has gone into your design. but bad, dark, too heavy color can obscure a plan and make it hard to read. if you feel like you are not the best at rendering, and don't have the best grasp on representing your design in color... make sure you use restraint.  second point... sketches should be loose. and if that's impossible for you, they should have a similar line quality to that of your plan view of the island. make everything as uniform in it's presentation as possible.   i really like what i've seen so far... i know you've been working hard. looking farward to seeing your presentations on thursday at 4pm.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    in case you forgot what you look like.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    in case you forgot what i look like.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blogging has almost lost it's pizzazz for me already. ask me again tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... let's see if this is fun. tell me if you think it is.  amynichols10@aol.com
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i had to make about seven million decisions, in the span of only a few hours. i felt like if i didn't finish making these decisions, and make the right ones, i would turn into a pumpkin. or a street urchin.  but that was today (2 hours and counting...).  yesterday there was one big decision. i made the wrong one, and will regret it forever and a day. beginning friday, i had a busier than usual weekend. starting with two seperate graduation ceremonies (kindergarten and day care)... then the paper cut, and handing off of the offsprung to that short guy i once had sex with (really we dated for seven years...). well, friday night was spent far, far, away from matunuck, in a land called honalee. i mean providence. i convinced a boy i was a brick inspector. anyway, friday in providence was cool, but not quite matunuck. i'm just not cool enough for providence. i am not edgy. saturday was spent half in bed recovering, and half in the third extreme little rhody has to offer - newport. some people call it "newie" and i hate that. brought the little me to a cookout, so everyone would know where my looks went (she gets cuter by the minute, and i gain pounds and grow billy goat hair on my chin... it's like that law about mass and how it can't be created or destroyed - just moved around - thats what's going on - redistribution of cuteness). spent saturday night in matunuck - finally! taught the kid about improvised snacking at all hours of the night. jiff plus m&m's. hours later shipped her off to celebrate daddy's day with the wet towel.  wunderlich shows up in a lime green tube top. not her style at all. we sit out and get some sun, but are bored quickly. we decide to go see "anchorman" but it's not out yet. we saw dodgeball, we laugh out load at the parts where no one else is laughing, and we are confused at the parts where the other people are laughing. it was entertaining. one of the dorky dudes looks like jen's ex-boyfriend.   we made our requisite journey to the mist to harass our favorite barkeep pete. we had some clamcakes. they weren't that good and felt like medium sized submarines in my belly.   then back to the beach.. where who do we encounter but bocce boy and his cheesebag girlfriend in her patriots sweatshirt and swishy pants. middle aged men wear patriots sweatshirts and swishy pants. it's just not sexy on anyone... and it offended jen and i for some strange reason. like the c.b. was saying, "haha... he's mine and i don't have to wear lime-green tube tops or $150 jeans to keep him". she was mocking us with her sports paraphernalia. for some reason bocce boy was carring 9 bottles of hard liquor.  we smiled, exchanged pleasantries. i'm getting to the decision-making part in a minute by the way. we walked a through a few rows of cottages, to jen's place. we talked about how pissed we are that her parents are selling it. when you have a house at Roy's you don't sell. you pass it on. they're breaking the code of ethics, and it's not cool. so, i spy bocce boy on what i will call the "sea wall" for lack of any other term. we can see him, all alone... no cheesbag. i'm pretty sure he was smoking a joint. so, as he turns, to presumably walk back to his cottage, we spring out of our seats, and co-in-ci-dent-ily bump into him on the street as we're walking from jen's place to mine.  his house is on the way to mine. it's ideal. we're chatting. i think i farted outload as we were walking. it's all a blur. two brilliantly charming ladies are turned into the mental equvalent of rhubarb pie. his name is todd by the way. fuck calling him bocce boy. it's todd.  todd apparently likes rhubarb a whole lot and decides to INVITE US OVER FOR A BEER! this is where the incredibly regrettable decision was made. i said no. i said i couldn't. i said i had to leave. and we left. i have wanted to talk to, hang out with, make out with, touch, manhandle, converse with, enjoy the company of, play backgammon with todd forEVER. and i said no. jen said no. we had to go. that was our excuse. we had to go.   we fucking blew it.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    congratulations to the hippest six year old i know... she's going to kick first grade's ass in the fall!  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know how when you're 13 or 14 years old... and your hormones are raging? yeah. mine must have gotten so worn out they packed their bags and left. it's a sad, sad story. i hade more sex in my teen years than i have had in my twenties (which are nearly over by the way).  thinking about this (since this week i believe it will be 4 years of almost involuntariy abstainence) brings me back to where it all began. at the beach... deflowered on the bottom bunk, mid-afternoon on a drizzly thursday.  it was like sandra dee and danny zucco. shit. it was nothing like that... except that the song "summer lovin'" sometimes makes me think of him, seamus that is, the boy. i was sort of like sandra dee... but with a spiral perm. and really tan. he was a rich boy from long island... summered in matunuck (too cool for the hamptons i guess...). he was (and i presume still is?) about 6'4". i am definitely still 5'2". what i am not is the 95 lb. emaciated twig that i once was. anyway... love at first sight, blah, blah, blah. with him, blow-jobs were second nature. he was my first... i didn't actually realize it was a form of sex. it litterally just happened. he didn't ask for it. and i didn't give any warning. his mom was upstairs cooking dinner... we were on the living room couch. it seemed logical for me to put this boys privates in my mouth. instinct i guess. but really, i thought this was normal. anyway... REAL sex wasn't something i was even remotely thinking about. i wasn't going to do the nasty... my parents would be so disappointed. ha.  so when brian k., who worked at the corner store owned by the crack head gary, told me that seamus had been in the store and had purchased CONDOMS i was completely undone. the news of someone purchasing condoms in a tiny community like matunuck was likey to end up on some bulletin board as an announcement, next to a posting for a free couch. was i pissed. that night, i confronted seamus. privately, on the beach. he thought he was getting some, i had other plans. i cried, i wept... i thought he loved me. why didn't he want to talk about it first? was he just going to sneak it in me (which, by the way, DID happen to a friend of mine, and we have a song about it... she actually thought she was getting a fingerblast. poor kid)? oh was seamus mad at himself... he knew he screwed up. he had to show how much he loved me. he hurled his entire wallet, containing previously purchsed Trojans into the sea... one of the most dramatic monents in my life. crying... a big man crying... it was heartfelt. i think we went to a bonfire and drank purple passion that night. all was back to normal... sex was off the table.  next morning... i park myself on the beach at 8:30, as i did every day. the manager of the beach and several lifeguards approach, asking if seamus mc***** was indeed my boyfriend, and if he was, they had something i should return to him. the manager of the beach, by the way, is my friend emell's dad.  they handed me a wallet, containing n.y. drivers license and a handfull of condoms. awesome.  anyway, we fucked on the bottom bunk a couple of weeks later, after i got back from soccer camp.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wednesday already? guess i'm right smack dab in the middle of reminiscing about last weekend, and looking forward to the next. did you know that it's nearly impossible to combine old friends and new? or take a bunch of people that you love individually, but when you put them together you realize you like some of them more than others... this was last weekend. the cast: me, wundie, emell... then you add in franco (from san diego), emell's finace wendell, the hottest boy on earth (yes, the same bocce playing god from memorial day)and his girlfriend, and my parents.  this is the sort of mishmash of people you can put together with a cooler full of beer at the picnic table in matunuck.  emell was pretty much well into the boozing before she arrived (though i didn't know this at first). she never brings beer. this annoys me. especially since i tend to purchase only enough for myself, and some extra for people that just drop by... you know, so i can offer a beer and a quick visit. anyway... she never brings beer. and the girl can finish off a 12 pack with ease. which she did. except it wasn't so easy. because at about 9:30 pm, she fell off her lawn chair in couldn't get up. and wouldn't get up. and proceeded to attempt to crawl to the ladies room. what's most funny about this, is that she is also referred to on occasion by wunderlich and myself as "bologna-tits".  what this means, is that her breasts are so enormous they look like big slabs of bologna. so... with her ass crack hanging out of her jeans, and her bologna tits dragging on the lawn, she crept ever so slowly in the direction of the ladies room. yes, my mom was still there. yes, my mom is throwing a bridal shower for this girl in a few months. yes, my mom had had more than one southern comfort manhattan. but mom was less than impressed with the display.  do you want to know the worst of it though? bocce boy says to jen and myself, "pretty funny though... that was you guys a couple of weeks ago". ouch.  we still think he's beautiful, with his tan skin and big white teeth. his hair has gotten thinner, but is still shaggy and lovely. even though his girlfriend is really nice, and i like her a lot, she is still sort of a cheesebag. what do i expect though? they're in their thirties.  some other random tidbitties of information: we went to joyces and heard some good live irish crooning. we stopped in at the mist (out of habit, and because it's litterally 10 giant steps away from joyces). it was indeed the annual smoke free event. lots of people were smoking anyway. ha. (sidenote: i quit smoking on monday... just for fun. actually more out of support for a co-worker who has smoked for 18 years and needed a little reinforcement. we'll see how this goes). the girl... amber. the "voice" of the mist. we successfully avoided her. until we were leaving and she sideswiped us. we ingnored her as she apperared to walk us to the car.  and look at this... just as i recount last weekends exploits... an email from jen arrives: "I hope you can come up on Friday so we can drink our faces off...Or at least end the night feeling embarrassed or ashamed in some way."  watch out providence... we're headed north to start the weekend this time.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok... the weekend is quickly approaching. i have secured someone to sit on my daughter on saturday night, so that i might go out and have some fun.   we won't be at the ocean mist, as i looked at the schedule online, and what i see is a note on saturday, june 12th 2004, saying "ANNUAL SMOKE-FREE EVENT". if this is an annual event, they should be calling it the first annual, because never in history has the ocean mist turned away paying customers because they light up a fag with their brew. i estimate that over 60% of the o.m.'s clientele are smokers... if only on weekends or socially. i usually bring a pack, smoke a few, and then end up giving the rest out to "wanna be smokers", or thouse not allowed to purchase, but can bum as many as they like.  anyway... turns out wunderlich and i met the person who is responsible for this when we were at the mist a few weeks back (on memorial day weekend in fact). and i have proof... and through conversations with wunderwoman, we've pieced it together.  her name is amber. she wore a giant skirt, especially for a pixie sized person. she had a squeeky voice, and carried a binder with her "art" in it. first, she cornered wundie in the ladies room... jen was messing with her i think because she was a little bit out of place, and well, jen messes with everyone.  (note: the previous statement makes it sound like jen is some sort of kinky sex-in-the-potty lesbian... this is not what was meant. what i mean is that jen was making fun of this person, but for the dirty boys of the world, think what you like).  so amber decided jen seemed remotely interested in binder... so she shared her "collages". some sort of magazine clippings arranged to resemble nipples or something... memories are a bit fuzzy at this point. well, amber finds me somehow (seperate from jen at this point). i'm so intoxicated that i fake interest in coversation with her a little too well, and she ends up slipping me her phone number.  (again, not in a lesbian type way - i don't think?)  and telling me that my beloved ocean mist has hired her as the new "voice" of the ocean mist. in charge of booking or some shit like that. she was most proud that when you now call the mist, it's her voice you'll hear on the machine. also, she was telling me how psyched she was about the smoke-free event.  i lit up a p-funk, and continued to smile.  after this weekend, you'll learn about joyce's pub. runner up to mist, only because of it's size, and sometimes sketchy clientele. but we do love the joyce.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      back to memorial day weekend, and some correspondences between ms. wunderlich and myself:  amy writes to wunderlich (before the the memorial day festivities): "one year ago this weekend: 1. you were dryhumping mr. nick mobile on the bottom bunk (who incidentally will be married a few short months from now). 2. we went skinnydipping (me and mr. mobile) while you jumped around on the beach necked. 3. i lost my cell phone (which was later found under the bed). 4. i got stuck hauling my drunk ass up onto the top bunk... where i had to listen to all sorts of funny slurping and giggling. interesting factoids for you. who's picking up the 40's, me or you?"   wunderlich responds (only moments ago because she obviously doesn't check her email with any frequency): "Greetings from the hood!  I just read the precious e-mail you sent me regarding Mr. Mobile...and I just wanted to thank you from the bottom of my ass.  All kinds of feelings came rushing back; like a bunch of German homos at a David Hasslehoff concert.   I'm so glad I have friends like you to remind of my better moments.    This year, I had to settle for dry-slapping a fat boy in the face, while dancing like so many ants on a pile of rotten bananas.  At least I had you as an accomplice.  We are warriors of the night.  ps..i just almost sent this to the wrong address...what a hoot that would've been eh?"  a hoot yes, but even better to have published for anyone to read. footnote: all names have not been changed... just one. and only his last name was changed. because one time, nick called my mobile, and when someone calls me from their mobile, it says "nick mobile" or "fat pussy mobile". wunderlich saw the incoming call from nick and said, "his last name is mobile?". thus we changed his last name.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as of right now, i have 2 minutes to get to a party. that party is 1 hour and 25 minutes from where i am. i just got out of the shower... and my total preparation time often exceeds 45 minutes (that's 45 post-shower minutes). i admit to that. i hate to get dressed right out of the shower. i need a good 20 minutes before donning my crisply pressed yellow button down (thanks to my mom candy for the ironing, she's a saint).  i do want to say a few things about football. non-american football, also known as soccer. simply because i was at soccer practice this morning with 130 6 year olds, and one giant man of a football player. i call him a football player because he is from england. i find myself adopting his accent when i speak to him and it bothers me that this happens. anyway, he's a giant and i love it. i asked one of the 6 years olds (who happens to belong to me) if she thought mr. giant football liked me. she said, "why wouldn't he?". like, duh mom.  anyway... i'm nervous. i have a history of being attracted to people who i only see wearing clothing that they are required to wear... fedex guy, firefighter, and now football man. i adored the fedex guy until one day he stopped in the office on his day off (to see me, i presume) and his shirt was fourteen sizes too small, as were his short shorts. his sneakers also utilized zippers for staying on. the fact that he had 4 kids and 3 ex-wives didn't bother me, but the zip-up sneaks ended the whole thing. so... i'll pursue football man (i don't know age either... could be anywhere from 19-30, i'm so bad a gauging). i'll let you know when the first sighting occurs without umbro shorts and copas.  ok... drying time over. time to put my clothes on. i hope no one thinks any differently about me because of them today.  ha.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the beloved. ask me about the whoopie grass though... it doesn't show up in this photo. the five o'clock whistle just rang. i'm gone.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my other desk... says a lot about me and my days.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my one desk. also location of swan sighting out window in background.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just can't seem to get any work done today. rolled into work at 10 past 10 in jeans and thongs (flip flops, not bum floss). it's sunny. ate some pineapple on the deck. we have a deck at our office... looks out on fishers island, ny. not a bad place at all, but not conducive to working. much more conducive to naps in the sun. in about 15 minutes, thats where you'll find me.   i just swatted a fly... decapitated him in fact. there used to be an intern here about 4 years ago. she would shoot elastic bands at the flies and hit them every time. mr. miagi style, chopsticks replaced by rubber band... you get the picture. it amazes me to this day.  well, i sit in front of a big window, looking out on a street that has many "tourists" walking by these days. we're located in a village or sorts... little shops and such. then there's our office, in a converted old house. no sign on the outside, so people constantly look in the window to see what's up. i swear, a few minutes ago, one of the "swans" walked by. the cute little blond with the chipmunk teeth who got a second chance on the second to last episode. she still looks dynamite - as dynamite as someone who you know has been disassembled, rearranged (with some parts excluded and other added), then reassembeled - can look.  it's friday night. i'll be baking the famous brown sugar chocolate chip cookies for a 30th birthday party tomorrow that is most likely going to be postponed due to inclement weather.  if this is the case, i'll have approximately 80 of the yummiest cookies you'll ever sink into your belly available. let me know if you want some, and how i can get them to you. cause i don't want them around. any recipe that calls for 4 sticks of butter should be banned.  maybe the swan girl will want them so she can be eligible for the swan season II. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      8 minutes left at work. although i don't think i did a lick of it today. moving toward friday though, and figuring out how to squeeze in some time on the beach. though the weather might be iffy. what a dumb word.  post memorial day weekend... things at the cottage colony will probably be somewhat quiet. it's that time of year for wedding and baby showers, christenings, communions, birthday parties, etc.  but wunderlich and i will be there for sure, for some amount of time. hopefully continuing our debauchery, and creating some memories (for someone else to relay to me, and for me to embellish here in blog form).  we are the last of the crew that are quickly approaching 30 (not there yet!), and not married or currently attached. that leads to trouble. our friend rico sometimes joins us but is often alseep by 9. emell (M.L.) is engaged to wendy (real name brent... but only referred to as wendy or brenter).   bottom line... i'm up for living like it's 1992 again. and so is wunderlich. i've retrieved my wreckx n effect as well as my kris kross cd's. i'm ready for this.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there is much pressure now... not having something specific to say to anyone specific. i'm feeling self-conscious which isn't something i do. except when showering at the gym... which i avoid because i don't mind (make that - i enjoy) stinking up the joint anyway.   but yes, my introduction to blogging was for the purpose of conveying information about a class to some students at the university... it was for the slackers who drank too much (which is just the right amount in my book anyway) and couldn't stay awake between 4 and 7 pm.  those students never tuned in. it was the conscientious students who could hold their liquor that did.  well, here's my first story that's not for the kids:  this past weekend - memorial day - i went to a little place on the coast of rhode island called matunuck. i've been going there forever. well, living there i guess. for the summer. since i was was born. but since the age of about 14, i've been going to a more specific place in matunuck called the ocean mist. really silly name when i think about other people reading it... what must they think about a place called the "ocean mist" without having all the smells and visuals attached to that name? think of urinal cakes, miller high life and bean burritos... with windows that look out on block island, then the deck overlooking piles of vomit on the beach from weary patrons (note: same deck was location of me and unnamed accomplice reaching 3rd base). it's heaven. i eat most meals there... was there for about 4 out of 5 meals this past weekend alone. before all the erosion, the beach outside the ocean mist was large enough for beach volleyball... which tended to attract sketchy old men with too much chest hair and aquavelva. but at 14, you overlook those things if he is willing to deliver you a sea breeze, or some other silly cocktail you've hear your mom order once or twice (they thought it humorous when i asked for that manhattan that one time... i didn't know). also, having parents that kept boxed wine (franzia) in the fridge at all times was key in order to get ready for the 1/4 mile journey along the beach from the cottage we live at to the o.m. enough background already.   back to the present... me and one of my favorite people in the world - we'll call her wunderlich (pronounced wonderlick)- going to the o-mist for a show. they have shows there. one big reggae show each summer usually. some lame cover bands. but we don't go for that crap. we go for john cafferty and the beaver brown band(and an event we like to call "naked men"). tonight it's j.c. and the triple b. we love to love j.c. and his cutoff shirt and wristbads. before we go... we're hanging out at my cottage in matunuck.   there are about 350 cottages... about 20 feet by 20 feet in size. placed one on top of the other. summers only. everyone knows everyone. we're sitting on the picnic table having a few beers before heading over to the o.m. wunderlich and i are doing fine... our friend emell (pronounced M.L.) is half (3/4?) in the bag. the yummiest boy to ever grace the premises is playing bocce. with some boys who are not as hot as him, and therefore i don't recall exactly who they were. we've loved him since the beginning of time. he doesn't know that we love to love him the same way we love to love johnny c. until emell makes up a new rule in the game of bocce. addendum #1 to the rules of the game of bocce: next time someone throws, aforementioned yummy boy (who will remain nameless) must take his pants off.  laughter all around, then i feel slightly creepy cause it sounds like a really good idea. wunderlich and i head over to the mist... emell doesn't make it cause she's a sloppy drunk. we (wunderlich and i) decide to drink bad boys (gins and tonics). we manage to drop about 120 bucks... which is insane cause we know all the bartenders and tend to get charged only for every other drink. i don't know. we drank. and drank. gin. gin can be the devil. i think wunderlich was so intoxicated she yelled up to mr. cafferty on stage and asked him for a "good fingerblasting". she and emell coined that phrase i think... fingerblast. it's cool, and we tend to use the suffix -blast for almost anything. for example "tongueblast", "cockblast", "elbowblast" ... and so on. back to that night though.  we managed to find our way home. but decided to roam around looking for a party. no, that's not what we were doing. we just didn't want to go home. but as i was sitting at the wunderlich family's picnic table, trying to explain to wunderlich's brother why she's got me programmed in her phone as "fat pussy", i realized i was going to die. so i told everyone present that i was going to die and i left. wunderlich came too, and we made our way to the ladies room. cause there are no bathrooms in these little cottages. there are common bathrooms... outhouse style.  something funny must have happened inside that ladies room... probably talking about the fingerblast request, or the hairy little man that kept trying to rub up againt me. ms. wunderlich and i stumbled out laughing hysterically about something, and ended up in a pile about 10 yards away from the ladies room. and somewhat ironically, about 20 yards away from yummy boy's cottage. we couldn't get up. we didn't get up for a while.  until the yummy boy came, and helped us get up. while his girlfriend looked on. this was the end of memorial day.  note: much of the previous account was compiled from the collective memories of those individuals referred to, and are not one complete recollection from any one person. personally, i don't remember falling down outside the ladies room (nor does wunderlich). the yummy boy and his girlfriend shared that with us the next day. welcome to summer in matunuck.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    little old me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhh... my blogging responsibilities have ended. no more obligatory posts for my students as the semester has ended and they no longer have to pay attention to a darn thing i say or write.  i miss it terribly. a (somewhat) captive audience. gone. poo.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow. more decisions... but somehow deciding to quit my job and move south to the gulf coast, to sell my home, to relocate my daughter... was easier than deciding whether or not to have a drink with todd the other day.  well... turns out having a drink with todd isn't that fun anyway. the question was posed again this past weekend. i accepted... feeling to say no would be rude. todd is rather boring. old too. had ridiculous tan lines from his giant sunglasses. i think deep down he's homosexual too. ha... i say that about all the boys i once liked.  anyway, back to the other big story. me, jobless and moving in the next three weeks. trading the last half of the summer in matunuck for year round access to the sun.  i'll be out of bloggers reach... or blogger will be out of my reach. packed in a box, on a truck... moving. movement feels so good.  note: wunderlich might be putting in for a transfer too! that lucky whore works for one of those giant corporations that is everywhere you want to be (no not visa, i know... i stole their slogan).
     
    
</post>


</Blog>