<Blog>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finished  Traveling Mercies . It was definitely one of the best books I've read in a long time. I have to decide who I should pass it on to now because it's a book to be shared.  It is an absolutely beautiful day outside today. I love it. I find it amazing how much the weather affects my moods. I was in a good mood today and yesterday because it was nice outside. I could easily have thought of 60 things that should have put me in a bad mood though. And I honestly believe if the weather had been different I probably would have been in a bad mood. The more I think about it the more it upsets me that I let things such as the weather affect my disposition so much. It makes sense - but still. (John hates it when I say "but still..." so tell me if you do too and I'll stop. Ok, maybe not, but still)   I want to be able to look for "the good" in rainy days.  Maybe that should be my new motto or life goal or something important like that.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry - I know I haven't written much lately. I didn't feel well and then was busy. (excuses, excuses)  Do you ever have irrational fears? I do. I have on in particular right now that is weighing on my mind. It's actually pretty common too....   The DENTIST.   I haven't been in over a year. (yes, I realize I'm supposed to go every 6 months) When I was little I had the best dentist ever. His name was Dr. Fred and I never minded going to see him. When we moved to PA we started seeing a man who went to our church and was recommended to us. I left every single time in pain. He would claim my jaw was too small and just force my mouth open. Floss so that my mouth bled. You know how it is. So when I got married, I thought I would just go see the same dentist John did. Well this guy was a completely whack. I kid you not. The assistant who cleaned my teeth made my mouth so sore it hurt to eat for days. Then the dentist came in - looked at my wisdom teeth which had just started coming in and said - "Do they bother you?" When I said, "only sometimes" he said "ok, we'll leave them in then - no biggie."  I have since learned that this is not "no biggie."  I have also since learned that he told my sister-in-law, Jill, that she had no cavities and she has since found out she had four that he missed.  Since seeing this dentist my jaw has given me more problems. It tends to lock up and overall just ache a lot. This made me nervous that I might see the same assistant again. So I didn't call to make an appt. Plus I had a bad feeling about my wisdom teeth so I just put it off. I think I'm paying for this now. I have made myself an appt. to see another new dentist next wednesday.   And I'm scared out of my mind.  It's ridiculous. I know it is. It's irrational. I realize this. Yet, I am really frightened! I don't even know what I'm so scared of to be honest.   So in my prayer time I've been praying that God would help me get over this. Or that I would at least be able to place myself in his hands when I go. I realize there are a lot of other things I could and should be praying about. But this has been pretty much my only prayer topic for two days.  I realize how human I am when such minor things take over so much of my life. I need God in so many ways - and he can use the craziest things to help me remember that.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woo. Busy week. Cards, cards, cards. Oh yeah, I'm trying to learn flash as well. Oy.  Still reading  Traveling Mercies.  Still loving it. Here is what I love about Anne's writing (we're on a first name basis now...)  1.  She's vivid.  I can picture exactly what she is talking about as I read. I took a "creative non-fiction" writing class my last year of college and we talked about this exact thing. The descriptions aren't in anyway cliche, in fact they are just the opposite. Every depiction of every event is truly original. She paints pictures with words. And for me, that is what a good writer does.  2.  She doesn't take herself too seriously.  Anne knows she's been to hell and back in her life. She knows that this has happened to a lot of us. But she talks about her experiences in a way that you don't feel too bogged down and depressed after reading about them. She is still able to have wit and humor while describing the most agonizing situation you can ever imagine. You honestly can laugh and cry at the same time.  3.  I can resonate with her.   I just finished reading a chapter about her insecurities in a bathing suit while she was in Mexico. I nodded my head and grinned to myself the entire chapter! Any woman who reads this book will be able to relate to at least part of Anne's story.  There is something extremely powerful about memoir-type writing. (Yes, I know I just made up a descriptive phrase) To reveal that much of your life and make yourself that vulnerable is amazing to me. I love to write this kind of stuff - but I don't like to share it with too many people. And it's for that very reason - you can open up a can of worms doing that!! And even if people don't judge you like you think they will, if you're like me, that doesn't help you to not feel exposed.   I hate to feel exposed.   I can wear a pretty thick coat and a really good mask sometimes - and when someone is able to rip it off, it frightens me! I like to be the person I think other people want me to be and not who I really am. Or who I was created to be. I'm such a work in progress. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Losing touch with hope The vision of you I once held The vision of you is gone Turn the lights off The shadows lurking in the corner Shut them out   My rock of faith is crumbling The foundation once so secure Is shaken What was  solid to me Is simply fluid to you And I wonder where you’ve gone   Where’s the story? The one you wish you’d told me? The curtain is split Your shadows have been revealed The story you told Is the picture I’ll hold  What time is it in your world  Too late for second chances Or too early to care? The make believe land I once thought real Has faded past my dreams  I can pretend you’re here I will pretend you’re here…   In C.S. Lewis' book  The Problem of Pain  he addresses love in chapter 3. It made me think a lot about the difference between the world's view of love and what love really is. In one spot Lewis is using the analogy between God's love for humans and a man's love for a woman. He says this:   "When we fall in love with a woman, do we cease to care whether she is clean or diry, fair or foul? Do we not rather then first begin to care? Does any woman regard it as a sign of love in a man that he neither knows nor care how she is looking? Love may, indeed love the beloved when her beauty is lost: but not because it is lost. Love may forgive all infirmities and love still in spite of the, but Love cannot cease to will their removal. Love is more sensitiv than hatred itself to every blemish in the beloved; his 'feeling is more soft and sensible than are the tender horns of cockled snails'. Of all power he forgives most, but he condones least: he is please with little, but demands all."   I automatically think of the the "PC" things in our society right now - love people, accept them, etc. But Lewis is talking about a love that wants the best we can be. While we are still loved, God wants us to get rid of our "infirmities" and "blemishes". Love is one thing, acceptance of sin or wrong-doing is another I think.   Change of subject...  I watched the movie,   Judas  , on Monday night. (I think it was on ABC) I was quite under-impressed. I was a bit disappointed actually - I had been hoping for more. My biggest disappointment was with the potrayal of Jesus. In one scene he asked Judas to watch the money because "he was terrible with it." excuse me? This IS Jesus we're talking about - right? Not to mention he was fair-skinned, hazel-eyed, and had blondish hair. Judas was shown as such a zealot. Someone who just got frustrated with Jesus not fighting. I need to research more about Judas I think. But I do think that he was portrayed as someone with more depth than simply the "betrayer" we all think of him as.   Jr. races in Atlanta on Sunday. I'm hoping for a better race than last week. Everyone watch, it's on FOX around noon or one PM on Sunday.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ran out of time today. Hopefully I will have time to write something longer tomorrow.  But I have to say...   Marlaena Cochran - YOU RULE!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In reading   Traveling Mercies   by Anne Lamott last night I came across one of the greatest "conversion stories" I've ever read. I'll type it out here for all who are interested - I hope it inspires someone else to read the book (this is found on page 49-50) You should know that she had just had an abortion, was an alcoholic and drug addict.      "I had a cigarette and turned off the light. After a while, as I lay there, I became aware of someone with me, hunkered down in the corner, and I just assumed it was my father, whose present I had felt over the years when I was frightened and alone. The feeling was so strong that I actually turned on the light for a moment to make sure no one was there - of course, there wasn't. But after a while, in the dark again, I knew beyond a doubt that it was Jesus. I felt him as surely as I feel my dog lying nearby as I write this.    And I was appalled. I thought about my life and my brilliant hilarious progressive friends, I thought about what everyone would think of me if I became a Christian, and it seemed an utterly impossible thing that simply could not be allowed to happen. I turned to the wall and said out loud, "I would rather die."     I felt him just sitting there on his haunches in the corner of my sleeping loft, watching me with patience and love, and I squinched my eyes shut, but that didn't help because that's not what I seeing him with.    Finally I fell asleep, and in the morning, he was gone.    This experience spooked me badly, but I thought it was just an apparition, born of fear and self-loathing and booze and loss of blood. But then everywhere I went, I had the feeling that a little cat was following me, wanting me to reach down and pick it up, wanting me to open the door and let it in. But I knew what would happen: you let a cat in one time, give it a little milk, and then it stays forever. So I tried to keep one step ahead of it, slamming my houseboat door when I entered or left.    And one week later, when I went back to church, I was so hungover that I couldn't stand up for the song, and this time I stayed for the sermon, which I just thought was so ridiculous, like someone trying to convinvce me of the existence of extraterrestrials, but the last song was so deep and raw and pure that I could not escape. It was as if the people were singing in between the notes, weeping an djoyful at the same time, and I felt like their voices or something was rocking me in its bosom, holding me like a scared kid, and I opened up to that feeling - and it washed over me.    I began to cry and left before the benediction, and I raced home and felt the little cat running along at my heels, and I walked down dock past dozens of potted flowers, under a sky a blue as one of God's own dreams, and I opened the door to my houseboat, and I stood there a minute, and then I hung my head and said, "Fuck it: I quit." I took a long deep breath and said out loud, "All right. You can come in."    So this was my beautiful moment of conversion."   One of my favorite parts of that story is when she's in the church and she says the last song was so "raw and pure that I could not escape..." That is how our worship gatherings should be! Raw and pure - what a great way to describe true worship. I want my whole life to be raw and pure before God. What a thing to aspire to!  Lately I feel as if I have a little cat following me around. (yes, I do have a cat - but I mean this metaphorically like Anne did) God is really working on me in so many ways. And he's really good at annoying me about things in my life I need to work on and let Him take control of. He doesn't give up until He gets his way. And that's a good thing - because I'm really stubborn, just ask my husband.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to talk about one of my all-time favorite movies,   Notting Hill.   Now before you think I'm completely shallow, and just a "girly-girl" who likes a good romantic comedy - let me explain why I love this movie so much.  I love the sincerity of the characters. I think Julia Roberts and Hugh Grant do a fantastic job at portraying "real" people. Hugh Grant's character owns this travel bookstore that is basically going nowhere and he lives with an unbelievably hopeless roomate who really is little less than normal.(understatement!) Julia Robert's character is supposed to be someone much like herself in real life. Which perhaps, is why she plays the role so well. But she tries to show that even famous people deal with the same problems you and I do. Being famous won't solve your problems or make your life easier. In fact, according to this movie, fame only complicates things.   The comedic moments in this movie are great! I laugh just thinking about them. The wit & dry type of humor is what I love the most. I especially love scenes in the bookstore with a couple different customers, Hugh Grant's attempt to scale a fence, and the interaction with his "less than normal" roomate, Spike.  The movie also gives a great picture of what many of our lives are actually like. No one in the movie is having an easy go of things. Not the famous actress, not the bookstore owner, not the friend in a wheelchair, not the sister who can't find a man who can treat her with respect, no one. And truth be told, none of us ever have an easy go of things easier. Such is life.   When situations like this are portrayed so well it compells me to remember that there is much more to life than the current situation. There is more to live for - and today is not the end to all. Today is not all there is. I'm so glad for that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "What time is it in your world? Is it too late for second chances or too early to care?"   Saw  The Passion of the Christ  last night. Quite a remarkable film. I'll do dislikes first.   Dislikes  1. The figure of "evil" in the film. First off, was it supposed to be Satan? I've heard both ways. I don't much care to be honest - it was evil whatever it was. I just think it was overkill. To me, the presence of evil was very much apparent without that figure being present. I didn't need the woman floating in the background of the crowd to sense the evil that was there.   2. Parts of Mary's character. This shows my protestantism I think. But I don't think Mary "knew" what was happening much more than any of the disciples did.  3. This one is still in my thought-process --> If Jesus was a human (and we know he was in human flesh) could he have actually endured beating THAT severe and still made it to the cross to be crucified. I think it wasn't that I had a problem with the severity of the beatings, so much as I felt it diminished the importance of the cross. I found myself thinking "goodness, just get to the cross and get it over with," which, in reality, may have been how Jesus felt. So maybe I'm way off base here... Like I said, this one is still in process.  4. I wish there had been a longer resurrection scene. I felt like half the story was told. I found myself wanting to yell after the movie "but there's more..." But to Gibson's credit - he was quite clear in what the focus of the movie would be.   Likes  1. The depiction of Mary as a mother. I am not a mother, but I cannot imagine anything more horrific than watching someone you love go through something like that. And whether or not she did know what was happening has no bearing on the fact that she watched her son die the worst death in history.  2. I'm contradicting myself here, but I did enjoy the evil figure in the first scene. The picture of the snake coming up to "tempt" Jesus to not fulfill his Father's plan and then Jesus crushing his head was quite striking.  3. The "extras." By this I mean things that are not in the scriptures, but help to make this film a work of art. The depiction of Claudia & Pilate, the scene with Herod, the way Judas was haunted and tortured himself. I especially loved the scenes from Jesus' life before his ministry.   4. The language. I am thrilled that someone finally did a movie that doesn't take place in America in the language of the land it does take place in. It seemed richer for it.  5. The actors ethnicity. The actor who played Jesus wasn't a blond, blue-eyed caucasian man. Kudos to Gibson for getting actors that made sense for the roles.  I recommend also the review Taylor Haley wrote for the CCO you can find it here (copy and past this address) http://www.ccojubilee.org/alumnifolder/AlumNews04/mar04/HaleyPassion.html  This Side of Eve plays Club Cafe, tonight @ 9PM. (I had to get my plug in...)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, we ARE going to see  The Passion of the Christ  tonight @ 7:30PM. I'll report later.  John is preaching this weekend on Saturday night. I'm really excited to hear him in this kind of service. He preached before at Wexford - but I think folks at CW are going to be challenged by him. His scripture is:  Micah 6:6-8 (NRSV) 6With what shall I come before the LORD,    and bow myself before God on high? Shall I come before him with burnt-offerings,    with calves a year old?  7Will the LORD be pleased with thousands of rams,    with tens of thousands of rivers of oil? Shall I give my firstborn for my transgression,    the fruit of my body for the sin of my soul?  8He has told you, O mortal, what is good;    and what does the LORD require of you but to do justice, and to love kindness,    and to walk humbly with your God?  I think because Memorial Park is so large and the congregation changes so vastly week to week that there often isn't a lot of "depth" or "push" to the messages. But I really think the congregation on Saturday night is ready to be pushed in some of these areas. How dare we, as Christians, ignore the injustice going on in parts of world. God calls us to be aware of these issues and do everything we can to DO justice and LOVE kindness (or mercy depending on your translation) Christianity is not always about your "personal" walk with Christ. A lot of it is yes, but what are you doing beyond that? Are you putting Christ's commands into action (Love the Lord your God & Love you neighbor) There is so much more to Christianity than attending a Sunday (or Saturday!) service and maybe even a Bible study once a week.   Stepping off my soapbox now...  I'm struggling with change. Rather, I'm struggling with waiting for change. There are several things in my life I want to see change or get better. (it's all relative) But I have to wait for God's timing. I am not a patient person - are any of us patient? I might be one of the worst at being patient though and things I want to happen now or in the very near future may not happen for a while or even a long time from now. God is teaching me something through this. And I think it's something more than just "have patience." I think it might even tie directly into what I was talking about on Tuesday and church being more than one gathering a week.  Learning is hard sometimes.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am in a book group that meets on Friday mornings with three other women from work. We are just starting to read  The Problem of Pain  by C.S. Lewis. I am supposed to have the preface, Intro & Chapter one read by Friday. I started the introduction last night and I can already tell this is going to be a heavy book. I should have expected it by the title, but somehow that one flew over me. (this is often the case) We are reading a Lewis book in preparation for April Staff Seminar where Art Lindsley is speaking on "C.S. Lewis and Postmodernity." I'm excited for that seminar already and I'm not always the most excited person for these things.  In the course of buying the Lewis book I, of course, had to get one more. (can you tell I have an addiction to books & reading?) I bought  Traveling Mercies  by Anne Lammott. I heard Anne speak at the Emergent Convention last March in San Diego and really liked her. Karin Berquist of Over the Rhine has mentioned her and several others I work with love her stuff. So last summer I got one of her novels out of the local libary ( Rosie ) and really liked it. So I thought I'd try some of her nonfiction stuff. If I like this one, I might read  Bird by Bird  next. One thing at a time though. (ha - I'm reading three books now!!)  John and I might go see  The Passion of the Christ  tomorrow. If we do, I'll put my thoughts here. I'm nervous to see it, but feel I should. I hope that makes sense.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jubilee is over for another year. I know that next year's weekend has already begun though. Feb. 25-27, 2005. Frightening.  Between the two of us, John and I managed to purchase three books this weekend:  1.   Emerging Worship:  Creating Worship Gatherings for New Generations  by Dan Kimball  2.  Reimaging Spiritual Formation Needs Community:  A Week in the Life of an Experimental Church  by Doug Pagitt  3.    Good News about Injustice:  A Witness of Courage in a Hurting World   by Gary Haugan  I started the first one by Dan Kimball. I already feel convincted. I'm not sure if that was even Dan's goal in the writing of the book - but I know the effect it has had on me is not what I expected when I purchased the book. I was excited to get new ideas about our worship space at CW and ways to enhance and maybe even "entertain" (oh I HATE that I had to use that word... but I'm being honest)   I read the first chapter nodding my head in agreement about the "Emerging Church" feeling very agreeable to what Dan was saying and resonating. Upon entering the 2nd and 3rd chapter I found myself feeling foolish. He pointed out (quite well, I might add) that a church is NOT about the one or two (or more) weekend services. It is, in fact, about much more than that.   Suddenly it hit me that even though it's important to have a "sacred space" and a good, worshipful gathering - I need to be thinking of ways we can all serve our Lord. I need to be fostering real community. My focus is often too narrowed-in on ONE hour every week! That's crazy! That's not a church.  I'm excited to read the rest of the book.  I was discussing some of this with my Dad last night. Saying that I get frustrated when we get so focused in on one service. He said, "You know Alyssa, I am as guilty of doing that as anyone else." I couldn't say anything except, "me too." God is really good at knocking you flat on your ass when he needs to.  John is on a two-day backpacking trip with Rob. He left yesterday morning and is planning on coming back tomorrow sometime. I'm so happy he got time away. He needed it. I think I also needed some time to myself. I'm convinced that having time apart in a marriage is not a bad thing. (this coming from someone who's only been married 3 1/2 years - so take it with a grain of salt) But they (who's "they"?) do say "absence makes the heart grow fonder. Last night was a night spent with my family. Tonight will be a night spent with my cat and reading. Fun times.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a hard time accepting criticism. I think I've finally gotten to a point where I can admit that about myself. It is something I pray about a lot and I think I'm getting better as I mature. I hope I am. I can remember specific instances (especially throught adolescence) where one little criticism would just destroy me. I seem to have two major reactions:  1. I get defensive. I try to make excuses why I messed up something or why what I did is right or correct. I want to make the other person see that I am right.  2. I get extremely hurt. Even though 99% of the time the person giving me the criticism has done nothing wrong, my feelings get hurt. Usually it is because I'm extremely disappointed in myself. I want to do everything exactly right and when someone points that I haven't or that I could have done it better it really hurts me. I feel as if I have let them down and as if I have let myself down.   For a long time I was defensive about being told I couldn't take criticism well. I am finally starting to come to terms with some of this. I am learning that in order to be a better person and to start becoming the woman God wants me be I have to know how to take constructive criticism and use it. Throughout college I got better and better about being able to take the criticism. I could take comments (good and bad) and not have a super strong reaction. But I didn't push myself to do anything with them. That's what I've been working on lately. When I receive constructive criticism I am trying to do something with it.  I think that will help make a better person. It will help to do my work better. And if I can learn that I don't have to do everything perfect the first time I do it and that is really is ok to make mistakes or fall a little short then I can learn how to reach even higher next time.  This is really hard though. Really hard.  This time of year (Lent, Good Friday, Easter) makes me think more about what I need to be working on to be the woman God wants me to be. After what He did for me, how can I not?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        FRIENDS    A friend of mine asked me today, "What do you think of 'Friends'?"  Here was my response:  I think the when the show originally aired (what - in '94?) It became hugely popular for a couple of reasons. One, the writers & actors had a way of very accurately portraying the mindset of people in their 20's. People who were adjusting to the working world and learning what it meant to be independent but still needed a "family" (their 'friends') They knew just when to pull out the jokes but also when to tug at heartstring to catch people's emotions. Two, the producers & writers weren't afraid to hit on big issues from the very beginning. For example, Ross' wife divorcing him because she was lesbian but them having a kid together. Rachel leaving her fiance at the alter. Phoebe being a surrogate mom for her brother and his wife. They managed to touch on these issues while still poking fun at themselves AND the issues. People needed that comedic break.  I think it held up because people fell in love with the characters. A lot of people who started watching it, kept watching because they were, in a way, "growing up" with the friends. They watched Chandler and Monica get married, they watched Phoebe get married, they watched Rachel and Ross have a child - just as they were doing all of this.   In the meantime the show ran reruns and started catching younger audience members. People like me, who began watching it in college, realized that they really did do a good job of capturing a 20 to 30 year old in transition and then in turn that new audience fell in love with the characters. So you now have this massive fan base that has watched the characters develop and change and touch on tough issues and to be honest, there aren't many shows out there right now that do that in the same way. Sure there are great shows out there - but not many that are somewhat realistic at dealing with these tough issues and change but also still keep a good sense of humor so the subject is light enough to enjoy watching on TV. So people feel they'll be missing something next fall when these characters aren't around anymore. I think it's interesting also that a lot of people almost feel as if an "era" in their life is ending with this show. It's crazy a TV show can make people feel that way. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You thought I'd forgot all about my blog didn't you?  I'm reading some fiction right now for my book club. I'm reading  Till We Have Faces  by C.S. Lewis. I read this during my freshman year in college and I remember staying up until 2 and 3 a.m. because I couldn't put the book down. I started reading it again last thursday night and now I remember why that happened. This is such a good story. I'll tell you more about it as I get into it, I'm only five chapters in right now. But I highly recommend it. The story is based on a lot of mythological tales, but even if you don't understand those or have prior knowledge of them, you'll be fine.   By the way, I did indeed finish  The Problem of Pain  by C.S. Lewis. (Can you tell our book group has been reading lots of Lewis lately?) I liked it - but I'm glad to be reading fiction again for now. I'll just say that. It made me think. Which can be good and bad.   I'm realizing that John and I are going to have some big decisions to make soon. I'm so glad I don't have to make decisions like this on my own. I have God, a husband, and a family to help make them. I would be dead if I had to make decisions all on my own. I have a hard time making small ones. For example, I went to the mall on Saturday night with my mom and my roommate from college, Kristi. I was in search of a dress for my brother's wedding which is taking place on Sunday, June 6. As a bridesmaid I have been told the color of dress I should buy (black) and to "keep it modest, not skanky." (Thanks for the vote of confidence Richard!) I went to probably 6 or 7 different stores, but could not decide on a dress. There was on that Kristi and my mom both liked but something about it bugged me so I just couldn't get it. (I'm super picky if you didn't know that about me) So I ended up spending 2 hours at the mall with nothing to show for it. So, on Sunday, I drug my mother-in-law, Ali, back to the mall and spent another hour and half dress searching. I finally found something and it so simple it's absolutely ridiculous it took me three and half hours of shopping to find it. Now I have to find shoes and necklace. Oy.  We spent four hours in the studio last night. I've found that recording runs two extremes. One being excitement over listening to your songs for the first time and hearing what you've created. The other being sheer frustrating when nothing is sounding like you want it to. I experienced both extremes last night. And I get to back Thursday. Again, oy.   Over the Rhine has a song that says:    Changes come Turn my world around Changes come Bring the whole thing down    I think that pretty much sums up what my family and I have been dealing with for the past two years and I see continuing for at least the next couple years. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      john is backpacking in west virginia with our friend rob. he left yesterday afternoon and will be home friday late afternoon/early evening. i tend to do a lot of thinking when john is gone. i suppose it's because when he's home i think out loud through conversation with him. and when he's gone i don't have anyone to have that same type of conversation with. my cat doesn't care to hear my talk, she just wants me to feed her. don't get me wrong - i love her - but she's not the deep philisophical type.  i think about what i do with my spare time and if it's healthy. i think about how dirty my apartment is and how i really should be cleaning it. i think about the fact that (truth be told) i'm a little jealous he's having fun and i'm working. (sidenote: i have no right to be jealous - i went off the nashville to have fune & learn and left him to take his finals!) i think about what i want to do in life and if my life is goin gin the direction it should be. the list goes on and on.  then i usually end up slightly depressed that he's gone. i don't view that as a completely bad thing though. there really is merit to the phrase "absence make the heart grow fonder." i love him dearly and miss him when he's gone. he is my best friend. yep, i'm sappy. i fully admit it.  this will give me time to see gavin (who i adore and have missed the past week) and to spend time with my mom - something else i haven't done enough of lately. maybe, just maybe, i'll even clean up the apartment some. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        shameless plug warning:    urlLink TSE  has a show at  urlLink club cafe  on july 10th. i think anyone who reads this should be there.  we're getting our new computer today. a powerbook G4. i'm very excited. very very excited. so is john. i'm also wondering if blogger will be completely compatible with our new computer - will a switch to typepad be necessary? possibly - but maybe not. we'll see.  tonight we are taking john's parents out to dinner for their birthdays. (this is their gift) i feel bad that it took this long to get them gifts, both their birthdays are over. i realize neither of them care too much - but that's the way i am. we're going to el campesino, a mexican place, fun. i can taste the chips and salsa already. let's hope my not-quite-healed-holes from wisdom teeth hold up.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm tired today. not so much physically as mentally, although i could take a nice long nap about now.   poor gavin got stung by a wasp right under his right eye on friday afternoon. he looked so pitiful friday night all swollen. and apparently, i missed the worst of it. by the time i saw him he was in a fine mood (he was the center of attention and he loves that) i still felt so bad for him though. i think that when i'm a mother some day i'm going to be a horrible worry-wart! but maybe that's part of being a mom.  this weekend was good. very busy but good. saturday night's music was a bit rougher than john and i prefer it to be. but sometimes that just happens. i'm learning there is not much we can do about that sometimes. sunday was good. it was the first time i helped to lead the music portion of worship at the open door and i really enjoyed it. what a receptive, welcoming, warm group of people. wednesday night is the "community dinner." john and i are going. it is an appetizer theme so i think i'll make something vegetarian so i know john will have something to eat. i always tend to do that at "potluck" type events. i have to watch out for him!  on july 31 communion is being served at cw. john and i are thinking (along with some other folks) of having round tables set up for worship and then having the congregation participate in communion at the tables. a sharing of a meal. post your thoughts in the comments section - good idea? sucky idea? why?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm glad it's friday. not for any particular reason, i'm just ready for a weekend. although weekends will be busy this summer. for the past 6 years john and i have been a part of  urlLink community worship  (cw) at  urlLink mpc . but we are in the process of transitioning to the  urlLink open door  where john has accepted a position as the director of worship through art (or worship & art - i need to remember the exact title even though titles reallly aren't important) we love the people at cw but for the past few months have been feeling a calling to move somewhere else. and there is a lot more that goes into that - but that's the short of it.  we're pretty excited about this. one big reason is because the open door is much closer to our home in the east liberty/highland park area of pittsburgh. i am really excited to contribute to a be a part of a community in our neighborhood.   the transition is tough though. there are people at cw that we are close to. we have no desire to leave these people "high & dry" so to speak. for that reason we are at both cw AND the open door through the end of august. which means on saturday nights we worship at cw on sunday nights we worship at the open door. i think this could get tiring - but thankfully john is doing most of the legwork and administration for cw for me this summer. by doing both cw and the open door he has a fulltime job plus some. which is good since he has no classes this summer. i think we'll need a vacation by the time august 29th rolls around! but i'm still very excited.  my brother got married recently to a great girl named priscilla - so here's a "shout out" (so to speak) to them. Congrats to the young couple!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i enabled the comments section. have fun! let me know what you think.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      pencillin stinks and the taste is awful.  that is all.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm trying to drink more water. i'm trying to eat better. and i'm trying to lose a few pounds. so far its going, eh, ok. i have a nalgene water bottle that holds 32 oz. so i figure i should down at least two of those a day. so far i've been really proud of myself for finishing one. one step at a time - right? my problem is that i pee all afternoon. i think my coworkers wonder what is wrong with me.   i really am trying to eat better. having wisdom teeth out helps with that. since they came out i've had to chew everything really well and eat slowly - which in turn helps me eat less and stop eating when i'm full. so at least i'm thinking about these things. i really do believe i should be eating organic yogurt too - i know what they do to dairy that's NOT organic and while most of john and i eat is organic or at least locally produced i'm having a really hard time givine up my yoplait yogurt. i love it. the red kind please. raspberry is my favorite. but i'm not going to stress about it yet. i'm determined that by vacation (end of august) i will have lost SOME weight. i'm not telling a number though - that's for me to know and you to maybe find out.  i found this  urlLink http://emergentconvention.com/planningblog/  pretty exciting stuff, huh?  oh and john took a job here  urlLink http://www.pghopendoor.com  more exciting stuff! i guess i should edit my info on here. we'll be at CW through august though to help with the transition. there are people there that we really care about and we can't leave them hanging. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's really sad when your "big" task for the week has been to put away a few baskets of laundry.  i don't sleep well when john's gone. i wake up 4 or 5 times every night just trying to figure out where i am. it's really strange how disoriented i can become in my own bed in my own apartment.   john and i have this neverending argument about opening the windows at night. it's either about safety or being hot. the safety one is the one that gets the most heated (no pun intended) we live in what could arguably be a "not-so-safe" section of pittsburgh in a ground-floor apartment that has windows to a back alley. so his argument that sleeping with windows open at night isn't safe makes total sense. i'm really good at blocking out common sense though. i love to sleep with windows open. i love fresh air and cool breezes. so sometimes i win this argument. sometimes i don't. on tuesday night i decided i wanted to sleep with the windows open. i was really excited because i didn't have to argue with john about it. so i throw the window open and pull the curtain back slightly so i can feel the breeze. i'm laying in bed loving the breeze and i suddenly hear a strange noise outside. well, that's all it took. john won the argument and he wasn't even there. i freaked myself out being home alone with the window open. i jumped up, closed the window and turned on the air conditioner much to my cat's dismay.   last night i had to run a couple of errands. i got home, put away the rest of my laundry and sat on my bed staring at the tv. i knew i should read or do something less mind-numbing than watching tv but i had no energy. then i wanted to cry. i don't know why. sometimes i just get overwhelmed when i start thinking about a lot of things at once. things like: will i ever have money to buy a house? when will we start a family? what do i really want to do as a career? is john going to finish his m.div on time? it's ridiculous and i really need to stop obsessing. but so far i haven't mastered that. so i finished that episode by going to bed at 10 o'clock. (early for me) did i say i'm really ready for john to come home?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there's all this new fancy stuff to type with on blogger! fun!  interesting article on gluttony:  urlLink http://www.relevantmagazine.com/article.php?sid=4278   i'm getting really tired of people in general assuming christians have to be right-winged conservatives. it's in the media. "oh you're a  christian, " with just  that  tone. then they go on to say how since you're republican, or since you're like g.w. it's tiring.  or those other christians you associate with (i'm not talking close friends here) who think that you are not a good christian because you're not republican. show me in the bible where it tells what my political stance should be! sure, it gives me guidelines and there are obvious things that i have to take into consideration when voting and/or choosing a political party. but nowhere does it say that i have to support big business. and like jim wallis said at the emergent convention "god bless america is not in the bible"  stepping off my soapbox now...  tse cancelled a show on august 20th. we were supposed to play at border's in the north hills, instead i'm going to see over the rhine ( urlLink http://www.overtherhine.com ) at club cafe. yay!  oh and my brother and his new(ish) wife priscilla are coming to visit on august 24th, then i leave for vacation on august 29th. yay again. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>