<Blog>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                                                      Two little wolves                                                                            once upon a time there lived 2 wolves who had moved out of their home to make there own home. the little wolves had a disscusion on how to build their own home. the first one said he would build his out of chocolate. And the secound said he would build his out of gingerbread. And with no more to say than that they parted.  The first wolf finished building his house. It was now a wonderful gingerbread house. He admired the outside for a while until he decided to go inside and admire the house. As he was admiring his house from the inside a knock at the door was heard. It was a pig and he wanted in. “let me in, let me in” said the pig. “Not by the hairs of my big chin chin.”  Replied the wolf. “Then I’ll eat and I’ll eat and ill eat your house down.” replied the pig. And within 2 seconds the house was devoured along with the wolf.    Then without hearing a thing, the second wolf finished building his chocolate house. He also admired his hose for a very long time before going inside, and just like the first wolf there was a knock at the door. And without a doubt it was the pig and he wanted in. “let me in, let me in “said the pig.   “Not by the hairs of my big chin chin.” Replied the second wolf. “Then I’ll eat and I’ll eat and I’ll eat your house down”. And just like before within 2 seconds the house was devoured, along with this wolf to.  About 1 hr later the fat pig was found dead on the ground obviously his appetite didn’t agree with him   The end 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                                                                Red death                                                                              report  Far away in a little country in Jamaica a whole castle of men and women have died from the disease red death. The castle was built far away from civilisation and surrounded by walls and then locked up. The key was thrown away just so red death wouldn’t get in but red death got in anyway and trapped every one else in there. Red death killed 22 actors, 29 chefs, 30 cooks, 100 civilians, 20 rich people, the queen and Prince Prospero. Police discovered this misfortune early yesterday morning when a erldely civilian that lived in the area was walking past, noticed it was quitter than normally. Doctors arrived after the police had got in and noticed that the daises that killed all of these people was a disease called red death. News reporters say that if they weren’t locked up in the castle, and they were able to get out then they probably would of lived or at least saved a few people. Police are saying now that there is know one to blame except prince Prospero. Red death has now killed over 60,000 people. And red death is now one of the most deadly diseases a person is able to get. So if you know any one living near or has red death please warn them about it. And do not lock yourself in a building that is near red death. To tell if you have red death look for red blood pouring out from places like the face, legs, arms, eyes and feet etc. it takes 10 minutes at least to kick in so beware and stay away from red death or you could be or end up like one of the 203 killed in prince Prospero’s castle. End. -reporter Aaron ziino.       
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Schoolyard bully  So there I was on my way to school hoping I wasn’t seen by Bob. Bob was a menace. Every where he went be it, The school yard, the street, the shopping centre or even the park he started a fight. And he was only 12. I think he had a fight with nearly every one in town. For no particular reason either. Mainly it was just because he felt like a fight. But the worst thing about Bob was that he never lost a fight and that was really bad for the people that he decided to pick on twice like me Jon Jones. So any way back to my story.  There I was walking to school at 8:00, Monday morning hoping I didn’t get seen by Bob but as usual there was Bob. Oh no I thought he was coming my way. “Oh Hi Bob” I said. “Give me your lunch money Squirt” replied Bob. “No” I insisted, but it didn’t matter, Within 6 seconds I was flat on my face and I didn’t have any lunch money left either. I thought to my self ever day after my bashings why does Bob always pick on me. I wish I was big and strong like Bob sometimes.  The next day I was walking to school again same time same way and same amount of lunch money in my pocket as yesterday .But for some time Bob didn’t come to day. I wounder why I think to my self I guess I am lucky in a sense. But just as I think I am safe here comes Bob right on time.  For some reason Bob just walked straight past me. I was so confused at this point of time. Then I saw Bobs mum walking with him as well and from that day on I never got bullied again and Bob he never bullied again because now Bobs mum walks with him every were.  The end 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Mr Brackes                                                                20-5-2004   I think the main problems with homeless people are that the institutions are too big, and crowded. They have over 35 odd people in it’s just is not home. I think the way to bring a solution to this problem is to reuse old building and make them in to flats/units for homeless and make each unit with two people in it of their choice. They need to make each unit really homey with stoves to make  there own food, food they are acutely interested in frigs to store there on food in, a phones to call friends and family even there own bathrooms so they don’t have to share and it should cost from $80 a week to $100 a week. In these buildings in two or three units there should be staff, doctors and nurses. Also you should have a suggestion box for the homeless so they can have a say. So they can suggest thing s like couches, TV’s, frigs beds and things like that just to make it a little homier. That way they will feel a lot happier and a lot happier about coming into an institution. That’s all but I think it will make a real difference.   Because at the moment these institutions are really not home and we really need to do something about it.    Yours sincerely       Aaron Ziino Latrobe secondary school  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Insane News  Professionals every were but in my hair  BOB  WANNABIE  Yesterday afternoon Aaron Ziino professional five time world champion made a special appearance yesterday down in torque beach just west of Melbourne in Australia. He was there also with TV star/ sports world surfer, josh young.   He was there for a photo shoot for the magazine “world water sports”. He was posing with his flame board shorts from his main sponsors for clothing billabong and was also there with his six speed lighting bolt Yamaha jet ski.  The set was set up of a beach, the palm tree was on the sand and the jet ski was sitting next to it on the sand. And in the back ground there was the torque beach water and the beautiful bright sun in the back ground.  The expected price for a shoot like this is a round $10,000. but it didn’t matter to the photographers because they just had to get in a photo before Aaron went on his next world tour.  I'm reporter bob wannabie￼    Thank you.   RACING FAST AS YOU CAN  James evenloderberrys   Just the new jet powered 4x4 Holden sedan v6 was brought out as a concept. The car was just yesterday tested out on a run way and reached a top speed of 1092km an hour. This is expected to be a hit with Holden fans. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Letter to mr white  Did you know that even the a.c.e.r is against giving homework. I know that there are many good reasons for giving us homework like parents expectations and getting in to rutin and things like that but what good does it do us if it is not improving our education then it’s a waste of time.&nbsp; It also can cause other problems such as family fights, eating disorders, bullying at school and it can dint your mental health.   Also if you look at the people that are supporting scrap there are some very important people.  Thanks for listening to me Yours sincerely  Aaron 7p 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So there I was having a nice nap in the warm warmth of the sun when suddenly I hear a crowed of voices, screaming yelling and voices laughing. So I open all of my five eyes to see what the hell is going on and what the hell is disturbing my sleep. And what I see is a class of year sevens. There are all jumping up and down, up and down waiting to get in. That’s when I heard one of the worst things a spider like me can hear “let’s get that spider and kill it. Let’s take its legs of 1 by 1 ,  when we get” said one of the many kids. I panic. I don’t what to do or where to go but I have to get out of here some how or I am going to be one dead spider. I’ll be completely pulled a part.  So then I come to my senses and try to think of a way out of the room, I can’t escape through the front door or I be found or even worse squished by all the feet. That’s when I see a back door. “Excellent” I think. Now I just have to get there and I know just how. Ill will go under the door. But just as I star to crawl the door flies open. “Oooohhhh no” I get about half way before some one picks me up “ahhh” there going to kill me. I’ll be mangulated. So I wriggle and wriggle, and squirm and hiss as hard as I can then they drop me on the floor. I quickly crawl away to the back door and crawl out under the door. Thank god I’m out of there I think to my self, and thank god im out alive. And that is the story of my great escape.   The end 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>