<Blog>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      They call it the "Quarter-life Crisis." It is when you stop going along with the crowd and start realizing that there are many things about yourself that you didn't know and may not like. You start feeling insecure and wonder where you will be in a year or two, but then get scared because you barely know where you are now.  You start realizing that people are selfish and that, maybe, those friends that you thought you were so close to aren't exactly the greatest people you have ever met, and the people you have lost touch with are some of the most important ones. What you don't recognize is that they are realizing that too, and aren't really cold, catty, mean or insincere, but that they are as confused as you.  You look at your job...and it is not even close to what you thought you would be doing, or maybe you are looking for a job and realizing that you are going to have to start at the bottom and that scares you.  Your opinions have gotten stronger. You see what others are doing and find yourself judging more than usual because suddenly you realize that you have certain boundaries in your life and are constantly adding things to your list of what is acceptable and what isn't.  One minute, you are insecure and then the next, secure. You laugh and cry with the greatest force of your life. You feel alone and scared and confused. Suddenly, change is the enemy and you try and cling onto the past with dear life, but soon realize that the past is drifting further and further away, and there is nothing to do but stay where you are or move forward.  You get your heart broken and wonder how someone you loved could do such damage to you. Or you lay in bed and wonder why you can't meet anyone decent enough that you want to get to know better. Or maybe you love someone but love someone else too and cannot figure out why you are doing this because you know that you aren't a bad person.  Random hook ups start to look cheap. Getting wasted and acting like an idiot starts to look pathetic.  You go through the same emotions and questions over and over, and talk with your friends about the same topics because you cannot seem to make a decision.  You worry about loans, money, the future and making a life for yourself.....and while winning the race would be great, right now you'd just like to be a contender!  What you may not realize is that everyone reading this relates to it.  We are in our best of times and our worst of times, trying as hard as we can to figure this whole thing out.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friend:     So r u still in a state of recovery or recovered?  Me:          Recovering is to go back to the state you were in prior to the                  affliction...I'm not doing that.... I’m moving to a very arctic                  region...of no love, no worries.  Friend:     Are you reciting a poem or singing a song?  Me:          No...just me.... why?  Friend:     Just don't do that during lovemaking!  Me:          Why lah?  Friend:     You will sound like Shakespeare or Aristotle...the philosopher! Who                 would want to make love to them?  Me:          I've been reading Thoreau on the Duties of Civil Disobedience...not                 exactly Shakespeare.  Friend:     My god! The ordeal that you’ve been thru has had a colossal                 damage to your sensitive brain!  Inner Voice: * Sigh........... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      By Walt Whitman 1819-1892  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Ah poverties, wincings, and sulky retreats,  Ah you foes that in conflict have overcome me,  (For what is my life or any man's life but a conflict with foes, the  old, the incessant war?)  You degradations, you tussle with passions and appetites,  You smarts from dissatisfied friendships, (ah wounds the sharpest of all!)  You toil of painful and choked articulations, you meannesses,  You shallow tongue-talks at tables, (my tongue the shallowest of any;)  You broken resolutions, you racking angers, you smother'd ennuis!  Ah think not you finally triumph, my real self has yet to come forth,  It shall yet march forth o'ermastering, till all lies beneath me,  It shall yet stand up the soldier of ultimate victory.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I took a tumble today when I went over to Sheraton Subang to inspect site for our next management briefing. Tumbang like a big fat pokok jati in the national reserve! If you check the seismic activity reading at 12:32 p.m. in Subang, you'll see at least a 4 on the Richter scale. And I'm sure there's a crack on the floor where I landed. Oooouuuuch!   I've got scrapes on each knee, the left side worse than the right. It was more embarassing than anything else really! And I've ruined my favorite pin-stripe power suit pants coz of the scrape. Time to go a shoppin'!  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In my attempt to look up several Malay words that have no apparent equivalent in the English vocabulary, I came across a  urlLink Glossary of Culture Bound Syndromes .  I found these following strange and perplexing errr .... phenomenons:   amok: (Malaysia) a dissociative episode characterized by a period of brooding followed by an outburst of violent, aggressive, destructive, or homicidal behavior.   koro: (Malaysia) an episode of sudden and intense anxiety that the penis (or in the rare female cases, the vulva and nipples) will recede into the body and possibly cause death.   latah: (Malaysia and Indonesia) hypersensitivity to sudden fright, often with echopraxia, echoLalia, command obedience, and dissociative or trancelike behavior. The Malaysian syndrome is more frequent in middle-aged women.    Being well aware of the terror of  amok  and the wicked hilarity that is  latah  (thanks to grandma), has anyone else heard of  ' koro '? Certainly something my Gynae never discussed!  However, my initial intrigue was focused on  'latah'   as one night while making conversation with  urlLink my friend Fairy's  mum, a psychology professor,  informed me that theoretically it is a syndrome only found in culturally female-suppressive societies such as in Asia and Africa. One should point out in such communities women tend to be more submissive (to different degrees) and hence the expressive animated outburst seemingly more prominent amongst older women. Does the fact that we see fewer women  'melatah'  these days an indication that Malaysian women are getting better at expressing themselves in a more effective and efficient manner?  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Summertime and the livin' is easy Fish are jumpin', and cotton is high. Oh your daddy's rich, and your ma is good lookin' So hush, little baby, don' yo' cry.  One of these mornin's you're goin' to rise up singin', Then you'll spread you're wings an you'll take the sky. But till that mornin, there's a-nothin' can harm you With Daddy and Mammy standin' by.  (From Porgy and Bess by Gershwin)
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You happened to me. I was happened to like an abandond building by a bull- dozer, like the van that missed my skull happened a two-inch gash across my chin. You were as deep down as I've ever been. You were inside me like a pulse. A new- born flailing toward maternal heartbeat through the shock of cold and glare: when you were gone, swaddled in strange air I was that alone again, inventing life after you.  I don't want to remember you as that four o'clock in the morning eight months long after you happened to me like a wrong number at midnight that blew up the phone bill to an astronomical unknown quantity in foreign currency. The U.S. dollar dived since you happened to me. You've grown into your skin since then; you've grown into the space you measure with someone you can love back without a caveat.  While I love somebody I learn to live with through the downpulled winter days' routine wakings and sleepings, half-and-half caffeine- assisted mornings, laundry, stock-pots, dust- balls in the hallway, lists instead of lust sometimes, sometimes, instead of longing, trust that what comes next comes after what came first. She'll never be a story I make up. You were the one I didn't know where to stop. If I had blamed you, now I could forgive you, but what made my cold hand, back in prox- imity to your hair, your mouth, your mind, want where it no way ought to be, defined by where it was, and was and was until the whole globed swelling liquified and spilled through one cheek's nap, a syllable, a tear, was never blame, whatever I wished it were. You were the weather in my neighborhood. You were the epic in the episode. You were the year poised on the equinox.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      a woman should have.....  one old love she can imagine going back to and one who reminds her how far she has come.  enough money within her control to move out and rent a place of her own, even if she never wants to or needs to.  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her dreams should want to see her in an hour.  a youth she is content to leave behind, a past juicy enough for her to look forward to retelling in her old age.  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black lace bra.  one friend who always makes her laugh......and one who lets her cry.  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone else in her family.  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems and a recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored.  and a 'feeling' of control over her destiny.........   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      for my friends who are going through some rough patches........ hang tight...this too will pass..... :-)  you think i'd leave your side baby you know me better than that you think i'd leave you down when you're down on your knees i wouldn't do that i'll tell you you're right when you want and if only you could see into me  oh when you're cold i'll be there hold you tight to me  when you're on the outside baby and you can't get in i will show you you're so much better than you know when you're lost and you're alone and you cant get back again i will find you darling and i will bring you home  and if you want to cry i am here to dry your eyes and in no time you'll be fine  you think i'd leave your side baby you know me better than that you think id leave you down when you're down on your knees i wouldn't do that i'll tell you you're right when you want and if only you could see into me  oh when you're cold i'll be there hold you tight to me when you're low i'll be there by your side baby  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A young boy asks his father...   "Dad, how does politics actually work?"   The father tells his son...   "Well...you see, it's like this, I make the money and bring it home, so therefore I'm the CAPITALIST...your mom manages and administers the money, so she is the GOVERNMENT…your grandfather monitors and oversees things to make sure everything is in order and running smoothly, so therefore he is THE TRADE UNION...our maid does all the manual labour around the house, so she is the WORKING CLASS...we all have the common purpose, namely your well being, consequently you are like the PEOPLE and your little brother in diapers represents the FUTURE...  Do you understand my son?"   The little boy thinks about it and tells his father that he'll sleep on it and think it some more... During the night the little boy wakes up because his little brother has filled his diapers and is crying terribly. Because the little boy isn't sure what to do, he goes to his parents bedroom...he finds his mother lying in bed but because she is sleeping so soundly, he can't seem to wake her up...so the little boy proceeds to the maid's room for assistance, where he finds his father in bed with the maid, while his grandfather is inconspicuously watching the action through a bedroom window...Everyone is so occupied with what they are doing that they don't even notice the little boy standing in front of them...So because no one comes to his aid, the small lad decides to go back to bed again....   The next morning the father asks his son if he'd given more thought to the question of politics and if so, to explain in his own words how it works...   "YES" answer the boy...  "The CAPITALIST screws the WORKING CLASS...  The TRADE UNION stand idly by and watch...  while the GOVERNMENT sleeps...  the PEOPLE are completely ignored...  and the FUTURE lies in shit...  that's how politics works..." 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    With my Z at Strouds Run: Fall 2002.&nbsp; urlLink       
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Looking back to my years at Ohio  urlLink University , I realised that there are so many things that I have done, but forgotten. Not that these memories aren't memorable enough.....Midst my reminisce, I found these following links that remind me of what I used to do....of who I used to be...   urlLink Battling for Parking Spaces    urlLink Promoting Africa Week at OU    urlLink About Non-traditional Students    urlLink Jida's Coverage of Local Reaction to Sept 11    urlLink Jida's Coverage of Cinema Mall opening in town    urlLink Jida - On Cultural Mixes    urlLink Jida for Children of the World Conference    urlLink Jida for the Institute for the African Child    urlLink Jida - for Stephen   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      During my days as a student at Ohio University, our campus was overwhelmed by the presence of millions of cicadas that hatched underground after a 17 year incubation. They were everywhere. While some were really bothered by millions of bugs, I for one didn't mind them. They make the sweetest music, as I make the solitary walk from Alden Library to the Residence Halls. It was sad to know that they are such self sacrificial creatures, as they come to life, mate, reproduce and die even within the period of a few weeks that they are around.    urlLink More on cicadas hitting the East Coast.....   Later on, we were hit by Japanese ladybugs, which were also cute, but smaller and larger in volume....they got into everything!    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      by George Carlin   (corny, yes I know, but even jaded wanderers get to 'feel' sometimes....)   The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but shorter tempers, wider freeways, but narrower viewpoints. We spend more, but have less; we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and smaller families, more conveniences, but less time. We have more degrees but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more problems, more medicine, but less wellness.  We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom. We have multiplied our possessions, but reduced our values. We talk too much, love too seldom, and hate too often. We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to life not life to years.   We've been all the way to the moon and back, but have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor. We conquered outer space but not inner space. We've done larger things, but not better things. We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul.    We've conquered the atom, but not our prejudice. We write more, but learn less. We plan more, but accomplish less.   We've learned to rush, but not to wait. We build more computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we communicate less and less.  These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small character, steep profits and shallow relationships. These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but broken homes.   These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and bills that do everything from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the showroom window and nothing in the stockroom. A time when technology can bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share this insight, or to just hit delete.   Remember; spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not going to be around forever.   Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave your side.   Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.   Remember, to say, "I love you" to your partner and your loved ones, but most of all mean it. A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it come from deep inside of you.   Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person will not be there again. Give time to love, give time to speak, and give time to share the precious thoughts in your mind.    Life is not measured by the number of breaths we take, but by the moments that take our breath away.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wouldn't it be nice if we were older Then we wouldn't have to wait so long And wouldn't it be nice to live together In the kind of world where we belong  You know its gonna make it that much better When we can say goodnight and stay together  Wouldn't it be nice if we could wake up In the morning when the day is new And after having spent the day together Hold each other close the whole night through Happy times together we've been spending  I wish that every kiss was neverending Wouldn't it be nice  Maybe if we think and wish and hope and pray it might come true Baby then there wouldn't be a single thing we couldn't do Wouldn't it be nice  You know it seems the more we talk about it It only makes it worse to live without it But lets talk about it Wouldn't it be niceeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee...........  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       the way we were.......   A friend of mine sent me several  urlLink pictures  of what Malaysia or rather Malaya looked like ages ago that I thought I'd share. Looking at these, one would know just how far we've gone as a nation, and perhaps remind us that despite our grouses about the pace of development in this country, we fare much better than our brother nations such as Sudan (ind. 1956 from Egypt and UK), Morocco (ind. 1956 from France), Tunisia (Ind. 1956 from France) and Guinea (ind. 1958 from France) and  urlLink others  that gained independence just around the same  urlLink time  as we did. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Lake Garden&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Museum Negara&nbsp; urlLink     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Masjid Jamek -- 1909&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jalan Brickfields -- 1870&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Dataran Merdeka&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Pudu Jail -- 1896&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jalan Tun Perak (Jalan Jawa) 1926&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Bangunan Sultan Abdul Samad 1897&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jalan Bukit Bintang -- 1950&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night, after yet another unorthodox toasties meeting, I came  urlLink home  feeling listless and unsettled. I dragged my feet into my room, settled my things down on the floor, and lay on my bed in one semi-fluid movement. My eyes wandered around the room and rested upon the clutter upon my wicker dresser.....and realised that the simple clutter denoted everything in my life at the present  urlLink time ....a clock which was always five minutes too fast but showing a  urlLink time  past midnight, a pretty but lifeless pot of pristine white wild orchids, a bottle of orange flavored supplements that has remained untouched for months now...and a tower of dull light from a fragile paper lantern at a far corner of the dresser....     
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jules: engrossed by chopticks (Cardiff, Spring 2002)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Battle of the chopsticks ensues (Cardiff, Spring 2002)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    from left: Zariff, Zana, me, Linda  urlLink skiing  at Elkins, West Virginia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Fisherman's Village, Peggy's Cove, Halifax&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    blooms past midnight&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    birthday blossoms&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Non-Halal Meat Over Halal Meat, Montreal, Canada&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Little Amish Girl, Wooster County, Ohio&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Pigeon Head, Montreal, Canada&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Peggy's Cove, Halifax, Nova Scotia&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Peggy's Cove, Halifax, Nova Scotia&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Melenggang hai melenggang........      &nbsp;   All morning today, this song has been playing in my head....   I can't explain why....    So why am I posting it up on my blog...? Saja.... (just coz.....)     &nbsp;   *significance level: nil     &nbsp;    &nbsp;     Joget Pahang       &nbsp;   Melenggang hai Melenggang    dengan tari lenggang    Kalau baik hati    Nanti orang pun sayang (2x)     Dari Melaka ke negeri Pahang    Singgah di Johor beli berangan (2x)  Kami ucapkan selamatlah datang    Apa yang kurang dicaci jangan     Melenggang hai Melenggang    d  engan tari lenggang    Kalau baik hati    Nanti orang pun sayang (2x)     Pukullah gendang hai kulit kerbau    Dalam majlis tari menari (2x)     Sayalah ini bang hoi dagang merantau    Mengharap belas orang di sini (2x)     Melenggang hai Melenggang    dengan tari lenggang    Kalau baik hati    Nanti orang pun sayang (2x)     Negeri Pahang aman sentosa    Kaya dengan tumbuh-tumbuhan (2x)  Niat di hati bang oii...Nak buat jasa    Mudah-mudahan Tuhan kabulkan (2x)     Melenggang hai    Melenggang dengan tari lenggang    Kalau baik hati    Nanti orang pun sayang (2x)     &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Plus ca change, plus c'est la meme chose...    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  The more things change, the more things stay the same.....it's funny how you think you've gotten over a chapter in your life, and yet you let it haunt you...but perhaps,&nbsp;some chapters are never meant to end....perhaps they are meant to play on...like a skipping pirated VCD....&nbsp;    &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Recalling one of my most favorite poems of all time......        &nbsp;    "      I Know Why The Caged Bird Sings      "     by Maya Angelou     A&nbsp;free bird leaps  on the back of the wind  and floats downstream  till the current ends  and dips his wings  in the orange sun rays  and dares to claim the sky.   But a bird that stalks  down his narrow cage  can seldom see through  his bars of rage  his wings are clipped and  his feet are tied  so he opens his throat to sing.   The caged bird sings  with fearful thrill  of the things unknown  but longed for still  and is tune is heard  on the distant hill  for the caged bird  sings of freedom   The free bird  thinks of another breeze  and the trade winds soft  through the sighing trees  and the fat worms waiting  on a dawn-bright lawn  and he names the sky his own.   But a caged bird stands  on the grave of dreams  his shadow shouts  on a nightmare scream  his wings are clipped  and his feet are tied  so he opens his throat to sing   The caged bird sings  with a fearful thrill  of things unknown  but longed for still  and his tune is heard  on the distant hill  for the caged bird  sings of freedom.    &nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       things for which i have time...   While I do have a few things in draft at the moment, none are in the express condition to be posted this present time. As friends and family have complained that its been more than a week since I last posted something, so here's something that I've plucked from a fwd that someone sent me, spared some time fill and posted to keep up with you less busy people... :-p  [CURRENT .. ] - Current Favorite Artist: Javier and Alejandro Sanz - Current CD in CD Player: Soundtrack from 50 First Dates - Current Color Of Toenails: color of toenails lah! - Current Worry: WORK, a performance review that's coming up in two weeks, budgetary concerns, deciding between landed property or not.  [ LAST .. ] - You Touched: my editorial synopsis - You Talked to : My mentor, Nel - You Hugged: hmmmm...been a while...can't remember - You Instant messaged: Azrain - friend - You Yelled At: an idiot in a kancil who cut in front of me without giving a signal  [ FAV0URITE .. ] - Foods: chicken wings and grilled salmon - Drink: coffee lah - Album: Ella Fitzgerald's Basin Street Blues - Song: The way you look tonight by Tony Bennett - Shoes: Killa boots - Candy: Nano Nano - Animal: Giraffe - Vegetable: tomatoes and olives - Fruit: mangoes  [ ARE Y0U .. ] - Understanding: Most of the time - Open-minded: Pretty much so - Arrogant: is that another word for confidence overkill? - Insecure: at times - Interesting: think so - Easily Amused: oooh yeah! hehe - Random: Absolutely! Ask my Toastmaster mates! - Friendly: A little too friendly at times and a little too snobbish at times, depending. But I've been told that I look like a snot. - Smart: Sure why not! - Moody: When the time calls for it.  - Childish: When I dont have to 'be' an adult. - Independent: Incredibly so. - Emotionally Stable: debatable. - Shy: when the situation calls for it. - Messy: When i'm not neat. - Sad: not today, no. - Happy: Most of the time - Hyper:after coffee and double shot expresso. - Trusting: Trust is acquired - Talkative: oh depends...  [ WH0 D0 Y0U WANT T0 ... ] - Slap: she who will remain unnamed. - Get High With: my gay boyfriend who's a HOOT! - Tickle: my nephews...sighhh.. miss them! - Look Like: Me when I'm not being too serious... - Talk To Offline: my grandmother, the way she was before... - Talk To Online: my parents, they need to learn how to use IM!  [ HAVE Y0U EVER ... ] - Been kissed? heck yeah! - Done Drugs? Nope - Dumped Someone? Hmmm, I actually don't know...oh wait..yeah. - Gotten in a car accident? Yes, and it wasn't my fault! I'm a safe driver, really I am! Ask anyone! - Been in love? Yup  [ EITHER/0R .. ] -single or taken? single -Vogue or Cosmopolitan? Neither. The Economist or FEER -Jeans or cords? jjjjjeans -Sweater or sweatshirt? Sweater -T-shirt or tank top? Tank -Skirt or dress? Dress -Rose or Lily? Lilies -Oldies or pop? Oldies -Do you have a best friend? uhuuh  [ IN THE LAST 24 H0URS, HAVE Y0U .. ] - Cried? No - Helped someone? Yeah, a colleague who needed help with the MS Excel program. - Bought something? a tall Iced Caramel Macchiato with extra shots of expresso. - Gone to the movies? No - Said I love you? No - Had a serious talk? Yes, about work - Missed someone? yes.... - Hugged someone? No  [ D0 Y0U .. ] - Wear eye shadow? yup - Put on a front? yup - If you got a tattoo, where would you get it? no where, dont like 'em. - Are you lonely? sometimes... - Are you happy? when I wanna be - What is your astrological sign? Aries, the Ram
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday, America!   (please note irony in para below the poem. The tune for Star-Spangled Banner MAY have been originally composed by a Briton in 1750)  The Star-Spangled Banner— poem, as written by Francis Scott Key, 1814  O say, can you see, by the dawn's early light, What so proudly we hail'd at the twilight's last gleaming? Whose broad stripes and bright stars, thro' the perilous fight, O'er the ramparts we watch'd, were so gallantly streaming? And the rockets' red glare, the bombs bursting in air, Gave proof thro' the night that our flag was still there. O say, does that star-spangled banner yet wave O'er the land of the free and the home of the brave?  On the shore dimly seen thro' the mists of the deep, Where the foe's haughty host in dread silence reposes, What is that which the breeze, o'er the towering steep, As it fitfully blows, half conceals, half discloses? Now it catches the gleam of the morning's first beam, In full glory reflected, now shines on the stream: 'Tis the star-spangled banner: O, long may it wave O'er the land of the free and the home of the brave!  And where is that band who so vauntingly swore That the havoc of war and the battle's confusion, A home and a country should leave us no more? Their blood has wash'd out their foul footsteps' pollution. No refuge could save the hireling and slave From the terror of flight or the gloom of the grave: And the star-spangled banner in triumph doth wave O'er the land of the free and the home of the brave.  O thus be it ever when free-men shall stand Between their lov'd home and the war's desolation; Blest with vict'ry and peace, may the heav'n-rescued land Praise the Pow'r that hath made and preserv'd us a nation! Then conquer we must, when our cause it is just, And this be our motto: “In God is our trust!” And the star-spangled banner in triumph shall wave O'er the land of the free and the home of the brave!     On Sept. 13, 1814, Francis Scott Key visited the British fleet in Chesapeake Bay to secure the release of Dr. William Beanes, who had been captured after the burning of Washington, DC. The release was secured, but Key was detained on ship overnight during the shelling of Fort McHenry, one of the forts defending Baltimore. In the morning, he was so delighted to see the American flag still flying over the fort that he began a poem to commemorate the occasion. First published under the title “Defense of Fort M'Henry,” the poem soon attained wide popularity as sung to the tune “To Anacreon in Heaven.” The origin of this tune is obscure, but it may have been written by John Stafford Smith, a British composer born in 1750. “The Star-Spangled Banner” was officially made the national anthem by Congress in 1931, although it already had been adopted as such by the army and the navy.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "mandi hujan", teddy, skipping ropes and more...  while talking to a friend earlier today, we reminisced about things in our childhood that we missed. Since this blog serves as a means to record my past, present and future, I am gonna post up a list of things about my childhood that I miss greatly... "why?" u ask??? Coz I CAN! hahah! :-p  1. main getah 2. main guli 3. laying the blame on your parents for your misgivings 4. mandi hujan in t-shirt and undies 5. kandos chocolates and other contraband that the Mamak Roti brings 6. the Mickey Mouse Club 7. Fat Albert and the gang 8. main masak masak 9. being able to fit into smaller clothes (!!!!!!) 10. climbing trees in my grandfather's dusun 11. being able to cry your eyes out when you've scraped your knees and not feel embarrased 12. Sitting in the back seat of the car, being chauffered around 13. Asking stupid questions and not feel stupid 14. Learning to ride your brand spankin' new BMX bike for the first time 15. Taking ballet lessons and execute moves that would break bones should one try them now 16. my bantal busuk 17. My nanny and confidante, Kak Mah 18. My doting grandparents.....and being spoiled rotten everytime we balik kampung 19. My wild imagination that just about anything in this world is remotely possible......  (I think this is an ongoing list. Will add more later as I recall more....)  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       a reason, a season or a lifetime....   People come into your life for a reason, a season or a lifetime, When you figure out which it is, you know exactly what to do.  When someone is in your life for a reason,  it is usually to meet a need you have experienced outwardly or inwardly.  They have come to assist you through a difficulty,  to provide you with guidance and support,  to aid you physically, emotionally or spiritually.  They may seem godsent, and they are.  They are there for the reason you need them to be.  Then without any wrong doing on your part or an inconvient time, This person will say or do something to bring the relationship to an end.   Sometimes they die. Sometimes they walk away.   Sometimes they just act up and force you to take a stand.    What we must realise is that our need has been met,  our desires fulfilled, their work is done.  The prayer you sent up has been answered and it is now time to move on.   When people come into your life for a season,  it is because your turn has come to share, grow or learn.  They may bring you an experience of peace or make you laugh.  They may teach you something you have never done.  They usually give you an unbelievable amount of joy.  Believe it! It's real! But only for a season.  Lifetime relationships teach you lifetime lessons; those things you must build upon in order to have a solid foundation.   Your job is to accept the lesson, love the person anyway,  and put what you have learnt to use in other relationships and areas in your life.   It is said that love is blind but friendship is clairvoyant....  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       It's Tuesday and Jida's ready to grab the world by the balls! ;-)      Hehe....figuratively speaking lah!       Workload appears somewhat relatively relaxed, however not much time to be spared. I am working on my first year Re-Malaysianisation Capstone Report due out on Sunday, 15 August 2004. So wait for it.........  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Groooooaaaannn....it's freakin' Monday....having a half 'n half caffeine assisted morning...      It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion, It is by the beans of Java that thoughts acquire speed, The hands acquire shaking, the shaking becomes a warning, It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion....  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My mantra for the weekend........  "Be in pursuit of perfection........                        and realise that perfection is a moving target......"  Have a great one all! I know I will..... ;-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        It is Tuesday and I'm still trying to regain working brain functions from the weekend. It's almost uncanny that one's most hectic weekend is followed by the most hectic work week, encompassing work mass of epic proportions!!!!  
</post>


</Blog>