<Blog>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi Folks, Welcome home, this is where i stay , i mean digitally of course. Its a better representation of me for my Blog holds my thoughts which make more of me than my physical self.  You guys can log in soemtime to read some nice stories or find out what I think about anything under the sun.  I'm just beginning my blog. I'll give you guys more dope once I'm through with all this work I have to do.  Happy blogging Venki.............  
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Its a collection of a series of thoughts. That's what all this is. Digital exhibition or should I comprehensively decry this Intellectual flaunt. Little do they realise that all displays run the risks of exposure.Inspite of it I decieve myself with emotions of fortitude and redecorate my binary home with a new post.  This is taking on the mantle of a distinguished display of a motley of thought flows , so profound that often the expresser is at a loss for words himself.Impromptu and distinguished though all blogs might seem , the steel is actually melted by the travails of time. Discipline is a virtue that is seldom embraced and often the carpet has enough room for discarded virtues such as the former.  Under one such dusty carpet rests my unfinished blog.  Time the destroyer is a different actor now, it has upon itself the mantle of a distinguished teacher who has laid emphasis on this difficult task of regularity.Thus the dust is blown off my digital canvas and here I wield this moulded pad of polymerised hydrocarbons to paint my garbles.Sometimes i do not understand my own inscriptions and to protect my dwindling intellect in such weak moments - my last line says " I'm typing on my keyboard". 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My blog works and I love it...This means I will blog a lot more and you will all love it.                   Positive Visualisations   Hey I just realised....I'm gonna be positive. I think negativity is a disease that afflicts most of mankind. Its worse than one of those lethal viruses you could encounter while you take a stroll across the amazonian jungle or say hi to a few pygmies south of Zanzibar.  To me it was the joy of satire and irony that has lent me a critical eye to everything that i stop to admire. Thus the irony is something the others enjoy and negativity is my job.    Coming to the more pressing task of positivity ,I take it too personally,I Visualize. Visualisations , are my bane.Though leading gurus , people of higher learning and achievement than me profess that it is necessary to see in the minds eye instances of victory and experience the feeling before shouldering a task , I have developed this folly of taking the minds eye to different heights.Its without much warning that these images envelope you.  As I tried to close my eyes , I could see the Bowler running in , I had advanced a few steps down the pitch and the Bat moved in a perfect arc, straight backlift and perfect follow through , depositing the first ball of the innings atop something very tall. I couldnt exactly see what. After more such audacious shots I suddenly walk out nonchalantly to be spotted by a club player who has injured himself. Suddenly i am playing club matches and the Indian team is short of an opener. I havent lost my wicket since my match with Gururajdev bhavan;s Vidyalya under-14 match. There hardly seems to be an option for the selectors and I am narrating stories to the press about how I wasnt surprised.  As Gillespie runs in from Vulture street end I run down the pitch at him , swishing my bat like a Samurai in his last battle , soon the toast of the country , it would always be modest interviews for me.  Nopee i turn over, stop all that now , your too old to run and its an underarm tennis ball match with the kids from the next apartment , I tell myself.Shit no run up I tell myself. Turn over and go back to sleep.  Maybe such visualisations are extreme , but if i dont exude such extreme positivity , i fall prey to a darker depressing negativity. You guys have a cure..?  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I thot if this aint a mail i shld treasure nothin else is.......  hi venk  i suggest u "read in between the lines" below:  Hi Each,&nbsp;   how are u doing?&nbsp;  not too fine really. can u believe it ???? i have  fallen sick again. guess i'm "sick" of this place.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  I guess you have not understand the gravity of the&nbsp;  situation or I am sure u&nbsp;  would have acted ,so I'm explaining in detail.&nbsp;  sure have and i'm u know a real good "actor" when it  comes to "work"&nbsp;   I stay in this place which has no access to buses&nbsp;  and autorickshaws dont go&nbsp;  beyond a point. Even with a 1.5 time tariff they do&nbsp;  not agree to ply tht&nbsp;  side.  thought u were from chennai. a madrasi da machch. ever  heard of tambaram????? or for that matter a.m.jain????  "where autos dare"  I invariably get delayed in the office and&nbsp;  after 11 in the night there&nbsp;  is no one to ask for directions too. I got lost on&nbsp;  friday and it was close to&nbsp;  11.00 in the night and I was surrounded by a mob of&nbsp;  mad dogs.  aaaww, cmon venk!!! thought u had already "gone to the  dogs"  It was really&nbsp;  frightening and I have no idea how i escaped.  nice one again!! better luck next time. i meant that  for the dogs, that is!!&nbsp;   I have to stay in tht house cos my mom requested&nbsp;  some relatives and they&nbsp;  agreed to allow me to stay there.  ok, let me be more considerate and wish u better luck  for this one!!!  Now if i back out&nbsp;  it will reflect badly on&nbsp;  my mom.  understandable da machchaan, in fact the only  "understandable" thing in your mail.&nbsp;   I have a fight everyday with the auto wala's.  planning to settle down in chennai eh????? nice  training and for free at that!!!&nbsp;   I know there arent more competent people than you.&nbsp; u &nbsp;sure??? this aint cricket mate!!! the only other  place where u'll find me competent is at home when the  quantity of food cooked is slightly less!!!!&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  If there is a way of&nbsp;  sending it I know you will find it , but time is of&nbsp;  essence and I get  that for me beats socrates and wordsworth put  together!!!!&nbsp;  reimbursed so dont worry about the costs. I will&nbsp;  send you a check today or  or i'll have u "check mate"d&nbsp;  you send it collect so tht I pay and collect the&nbsp;  vehicle.  no thanks machch!! he pays!!!&nbsp;   I am writing this mail so tht by end of today&nbsp;  inspite of your loaded work&nbsp;  schedule  yeah finally u realized i work my backside off  "bending my back" eh? thought i was a batsman!!  you tell me tht you have sent it .Please&nbsp;  handle this on a prioirty&nbsp;  basis and help your friend out...  "friend"?????? who?????  NEEWAYS, I HAVE SENT IT TODAY. "PACKED OFF" so to say&nbsp;   Love&nbsp;  Venki.  lots n lots of the same da machch  each    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Hari Puttar and more boring blogs"    Did i tell you guys about this new book i read. its amazing! ,a mixture of magic ,sorcery and childish excitement. So what if this was an integral part of Chandamama or if you were a hardcore fan of ambulimama (two books that your grandma if she was a tam or similar books if she was Indian would have purchased for 25 paise....with garish art...and some fantasy to boot... ) and those authors just died of penury and hunger last week. This one is fresh. People just love it , never had they thought that human imagination could stretch into realms like black magic or witchery with a school for it, cows that fly - could you have thought about that , a game while you flew on the broom.....  This book is really amazing i tell you.The author has been acclaimed as some one who has redefined reading and its bounds. It has loads of fans in people who swear by it, quizzes where you can make it or break it with one reading.  I also met this guy , who hates the book. I have no idea why or how somebody could despise a work of art such as this. He says the world is dumb, and its probably because there are comprehension levels which are so low that people appreciate anything they can understand. I told him to take a hike , why such negativity ...why cant people just appreciate soemthing......after all it sells so much and somthing that sells so much can't be bad. They also tell me that the lady who wrote it is making a large dollar- one with quite a few zero's after it.  They said that for her next book she has two with quite a few zeros after it.What a book and what a well deserved fortune...... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Don't Ask me to Write a SOP again "   It is like this journey that begins from a certain point. The destination is defined at the beginning and it seems like the goal. We often believe that it is the goal that defines the journey, but soon we realise that it is the other way around.As we motor along we come to forks , where we make decisions , we see things that change us forever and soon we question the goal.Sometime the desire to achieve is reinforced , frequently the goal mutates and adopts different forms.  I sat on this motorcycle of eductaion , the only one my family had and followed the trails my cousins had blazed.i kept thinking of what makes my bike move and how I can move it faster. Suddenly i met this guy who sold his bike and with a little more money bought a car. I realised this is a more comfortable way to travel.Some time , some where along this path I will be a guy who makes and sells things.  I will also be someone who writes funny stories based on all the people I meet and those untold anecdotes that made my journey. I know I will still have to keep riding  , no matter how much my back aches , no matter how many days turn into dark long nights.though i am impatient and anxious and though I often compare others bikes I tell myself though they will reach faster , it is not the goal that is important but the Journey .......... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         "The Restaurant at the end of the Universe" 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Google Gangadhar 
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Dude Where's my Car"      As i read more and more blogs.....i can only sit back and enjoy the awesome strength of people's thoughts and the widely prevalant sense of humor. Tongue in cheek comments i guess that's what makes our lives.....           Ne ways if you thought i was bloggin to tell u all tht u already knew ur wrong.....here's what i think of bloggin....if its going to be a diary then why let others read it........if its ur opinion then why tell me what u had for breakfast....okie cynicism apart....it is a great medium for sure....i'm trying desperately to make a good samaritan out of myself....like say the nice things about people...like how does my Pukie .."yuckie lookin red skirt look.." i swallow my retch and roll my eyes and with all the appropriate emotions bring out an awesome dress.....and go on to say how it is the most desirous of all creations on planet earth...... the good thing now tho is tht Dinesh Kartik is in....and that does deserve more than a few words.......havent seen much of this lad....but after Parthiv's performaces i guess some time away from the middle will do him good......he's got to deliver......cliched but true...... As i age " which surprisingly seems to be happening faster mentally than physically" i can see through cliche's..........that the best thing about them is that they are hardly cliched.....           more time....i have suddenly become this serious human...and i'm petrified at having my sense of humor...i can laugh at you anytime though...but ....its the paranoia......tht's catching up.......okie if you are reading this blog chances are you may not come back....one for i'm not too disciplined in my posts...and i dont write with purpose.....mostly thought streams...and unplanned gushes......but if u catch the mood...i guess it might start making sense.... okie am rushing for a meeting....will come back and blog more...... as i make this a habit...promise u guys...i will fight it out for readership.......but as long as i keep writing thought streams..there'sllbe only two guys who read this..and both of em will be me!!!     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        "Photograph's"     I ve just had this tryst with photo's. One of those moments when you have to face the undeniable truth.To make matters worse , loads of other people also ask for your snap as if they can't just look up at my face. It's as though they tell you..."see that" ..."its what we have to look at day in and day out".    It should be stopped i decry.Neverthless i still get my snap done. Hope is what drives me. Everytime i get the developed copies there's a techie acronom that jumps up at me "WYSIWYG" is such a complete description of it.    To make matters worse there was this cousin of mine who was hell bent on picking up one of my snaps. I was sure she was about to take it to her town and tell her friends..."look at this" ..there are people who look worse than my brother.    Everytime i thot of looking worse than Chintu...i shuddered...that had to be really bad...and then there was the moment of temporary joy...i didnt have to look at myself.......    Oh depravation has solutions and a silver lining too.....that happens...when i get to see other's snaps......its like asking yourself....can technology improve this thing.......    Then there are specifications....and complications that go hand in hand with every request. Nowadays with everyone asking for foto identification i keep getting this horrible dream about all these guys huddling together in a room..and laughing their guts out....    In any case the story is about five years old when my dad asked me to get a snap done for my passport , at the end of the statement he clenched his fists....and bore down upon me..."get the negatives too and do it today " he growled.    Imperatives in the form of impending tv programs and a few games of cricket at soma ate up my time like some grouchy whale. Having had a blast with over three scores of 30 that evening , the thought of the task on hand slipped away like an eel in buttered fingers.    As i sauntered back home .....contemplating the usual sequence of lies that delayed my return , i bumped into my dad on the stairs. Now this was unexpected and threw my thoughts out of sequence. While i had focussed on answering the question " Why are you late" , my dad raised his palms in knowing certainity and like a stress interview at the iim's " Have you taken the foto " he asked doubtfully.         A clenched fist and an angry dad are worse than Gilchrist in flow , so unfailing ly and involuntarily nodded my head.This took him by surprise and that gave me more steam, you thought i wouldnt have done it did'nt ya" i chattered. Maybe is hould have stopped but i taunted him a little more and again another unexpected question."When will you get it ?". The answer had to be the next day , no other answer would convince him , he was too smart. Tomorrow , i smiled and rushed up. Having averted a disaster temporarily i was relieved , but I knew there was work to be done.    The next day was going to be a long one, so i suspended all work for the night and to plan for the next day hit the sack ealry and woke up late , already on the back foot....i told myself.    5.30pm was deadline. I tried not to think about it till noon and spent my time watching the most boring of vijay flicks , like food on a hungry stomach , the movie was rivetting....and suddenly i glanced up at the clock. It was 2.30. No ways ....there was no technology in the year '99 that delivered foto's with a negative within an hour.Not one to accept defeat.....i ran to the nearest studio and got a polaroid snap clicked.The logical step was to tackle the issue of the negative , I hastily scrawled a number on the cover and walked back home, a plan was brewing.    "Here" i held out my hand, four snaps and "here's the number for the negative" i said. "Number" appa looked down quizzically. Yes some new system, he maintains negatives and gives you copies if you quote the number i fibbed. Nice business model i threw in...for good measure. He turned the snaps over...."are these polaroid" he glared.    I froze in my tracks. He knew he always knows."Never give up " i told my self. Nope , i said , What is polaroid? i questioned. If there was an oscar nearby , the academy would have readily parted with it.    A few months the issue crept under the carpet , for i didnt need the fotos.Suddenly one day it was time for them again and as fate would have it , the guy at the passport office remembered he had six sisters and so thought he loved the number six.....and wanted to respect the number. I happened to pass by his counter then , six foto's he snarled.....sir...but i have four....and i have been in the queue for the last six hours i pleaded. Another six...definitely six snaps....he told himself...and mentally wrote himself a reminder ....should check with the astrologer...maybe its my lucky number.    Thus i was back home...and like all of us...i turned to my dad for solace....he wants six snaps i said......he looked at me...and for a minute i thought i saw a small smile cross his face...but u have the number you can go get the copies.    "Number what number" ...i quipped...then it all came rolling back in a wave.........oh that number...ya so simplee......i smiled...and walked out...I think i must have kicked the gate 14 times ........i swore i wouldnt lie........    But never one to give up....i had to wear the same dress and get another polaroid done.......but one small problem.....the spectacles i had worn in the last snap......had decided to give one side of the frame..retirement benefits..........and suddenly....the world was coming to an end.......    Okie to cut an already long story short...i did get the snap done with a broken specs and an angled face......somehting my dad figured out..but what he still cant figure out is how i got copies to a polaroid....snap.........         But if your a lady readin this...all i can say is I'm not Mr.Photogenic....so lets meet up for coffee.....with me pickin up the tab you can make an informed decision...;)                 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>