<Blog>


<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's not supposed to be sad, is it?  I asked a friend this question last night, and he confidently answered, "No, it isn't. You should be happy." Thing is, I am, I am. Those very same words could've come right off my mouth. It was the right answer. Hell, it was  my  answer.  But suddenly, in the middle of everything last night, I lost my purpose again. Or I lost my sense of purpose. Again.  You see in (one, two, three...) four days, I leave for Japan, to study. I have known it for a year, maybe more. Perhaps in my gut I'd always felt I was moving in that direction, heading there. And I spent the better part of that year wringing my fingers, just wishing the months would fly by, and cursing the old anticipation-is-better bullshit. And now, now that it's just days away, I find myself wringing my hands once again. And for different reasons.  You see, even if the knowledge of going was just below the surface this whole time, and (that dreaded word) anticipation like an echo of the heartbeat, it was easy to ignore and forget about it. Or forget about the consequences of it. Like the loneliness ( Hey, it'd be just like one big party! ). The totally different culture ( It's one hell of an adventure, drey! ). The frightening thought of having nobody to turn to who's family ( Oh, I soooo envy you! Good luck! ). The suffocating idea of leaving every thing you know and love behind ( When you leave and I don't cry, would that hurt you? ).  It's funny really. I feel like I am a poster child for the developmental stages, but instead of going through phases, I go through emotions. And it seems inevitable, and impossible to skip one. Like a barnhouse roof swept by a twister, I have no choice but to swirl and whirl and scramble through each and every emotion this ride takes me. Happiness. Appreciation. Anticipation. Boredom. Depression. Regret. Fatigue. Relief. Appreciation. Excitement. Happiness. Fatigue. Loneliness. Anger. Pain. Grief... Fatigue.  Yes, now I am simply tired. I just want it over with. I want that leaving/ grieving/ planning/ packing/ considering/ rejecting/ fake-friends-suddenly-all-over-you stage over and done with. I want to be in Japan, where nobody knows who I am, what I believe in, what food I like, what baseball team I root for, what I think of Sanada Hiroyuki or Ichiro. Where I don't owe anybody any explanations about the answers or non-answers to all these questions, and the ones I can't verbalize but resonate in side my head.  Now, I'd like to apologize. I lied. I find the reasons I'm wringing my fingers now is the same as they've always been: I want time to fly. I want time to fly me to my departure date. Fly me to Japan and to my studies and to my life there. Fly me to my graduation day, or even to life after that, through it all, whereever it may be. Fly me to that time when everything is over, and I am on my deathbed, where it all would flash before my eyes all over again... Because I find that anticipation often causes disappointment and grief and pain. And I feel I don't have the strength to go through all that twisted emotional spinner anymore.  So yeah, tell me the plot of that movie I haven't seen. Sure, reveal the twist in the end of that book. Okay, order for me in my favorite restaurant, and while you're at it, pick any CD and play it--I don't care what it is. Go ahead, read my palm, my tea leaves, the dregs in my coffee cup. Tell me all and spare me the first-hand experience. Do it quickly, I might change my mind soon, and all will be lost again.  It's not supposed to be sad, is it?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sometimes the mind is just in so much turmoil that ideas and questions just refuse to be put together and coagulate into words and phrases. so we brush aside, ignore, escape, until we finally forget. then you come across something, or read something, then wham! the questions come slamming back and there's no breakwater to protect you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have forgotten to write about how I lost my phone to an imagined in-dire-straits pickpocket a little less than a month before coming here.  I suppose my initial irritation was due to the thought of those forever-lost phone numbers, full-of-sentiment-and-never-to-be-read-over-and-over-again messages, the practical my-bank-account-information-was-stored-there! anxiety.  I suppose I failed to make the loss important, as after a while, I recovered some of those numbers. I forgot all about those once-all-too-important messages. I was excited over the prospect of going to Japan and buying a new phone--and I did get to buy a new, more-savvy keitai denwa here in the Land of Technology.  But tonight I came across a poem by Constantine Cavafy called  Morning Sea , and I remembered why I should've mourned the loss of that little thing.  I remember going home from work, speeding down cliff-side roads in 150-percent-capacity jeepneys and seeing how many different faces an ocean can assume, depending on time of day, weather, and yes, even moods.  I remember an opaque sea, almost like a dance floor, where an imagined partner would guide me into a slow slow dance, ending up with me missing a step and being swallowed by cold, thick saltwater, inch by inch, while he calmly looks on, as if I deserved it for stepping on his immaculately-shined shoes.  I remember a furious sea in San Joaquin, battering anybody insolent enough to try and invade his territory--spewling wave after wave of water-wall, that my stupid attempts at a dawn swim ended with me sprawled, defeated on the shore.  I remember a slumbering beach, slowly waking to the rising sun and cheerfully reflecting the sky's mild oranges and romantic lilacs and gleefully echoing wind-song.  I remember smoking along evening shores, keeping lonely driftwood company and watching late-day joggers, stray dogs, and lovers kissing in the shadows.  I have forgotten all that when I lost that phone, that little piece of convenience--or cause of irritation. I have forgotten all these memories, these memories hurriedly input on message-outbox, as more often than not I would find myself in the mood to write, but weaponless. Armed only with that phone.  And in those time, that phone became more than just a convenience, or an irritation. More than just a way for people both loved, liked and hated to search me out of my dark-hole and bother me. It became my best friend, the keeper of my darkest thoughts, privy to my inner-pain, my untold joy, my celebrated or cursed aloneness.  After  Morning Sea , I now remember why I should've mourned that handy sometimes-journal, that ready-for-any-mood confidante, that old and comfortable friend.  So, once again, memory has left me with nothing but sadness, and a half-hearted attempt at rationalizing another loss in my life. And I fervently hope, that my imagined dire-straits pickpocket truly needed my friend for food on the table, or made his daughter happy on her birthday, or even made his own life a little more convenient. For any other reason I lost those memories, and the only friend who shared them with me is unbearable. It would be like losing them all over again.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (copied and maybe edited a little from my journal,  a few minutes before the 21st of April  in my room in Misasagi, Yamashina, Kyoto City)  I don't know how to write anymore. I mean I can still write and I want to write, but I don't know how to put it down on paper. I mean literally put pen on paper and produce paragraphs. (See, I can't even tell you coherently what I want anymore--literally and figuratively.)  I guess I've lost my patience. I've lost it all over again---the patience to sort out thoughts, to look for and choose the right words, to construct sentences and know when to insert significant pauses, and yes, even the patience to skip a line and create a space between paragraphs. I've lost it all. (If you could only see how awful my handwriting is.)  Is this all really true, you wonder? How can somebody who claim not to know how to write, write three consecutive entries in her blog? You don't get it. Sure, I can type it all up in a keyboard, bang on {Enter} and clack up {Tab} and {Backspace} and choose letters from {Aa} to {Zz}, choose the #!.,@="&)* punctuations. I even have the patience for your old {ctrl-alt-delete} routine, should something go awry.  But I've lost my patience for that magical time it takes to form that secret, silent thought to the chosen, hushed, uttered word, and finally to that again-silent, unerasable, written testimony. (If you could see me sweating it out now, only to complete this routine.)  Where did all that go? Did I lose my muse, as Lyra did? Am I less lonely here? (Yeah, could've fooled me. I would jump and stop all this nonsense right now if the phone rang, but that's another story.)  Before this entry, and I guess even after it, my second journal lies blank except for lists of things to do, people's phone numbers back home, tattoo designs and other crap. Am I losing my memories to other people? The things I've written recently are reports, quizzes, emails, text messages and my shitty blog publications.  Am I losing my memories to other people? Are my moments lost to the confusion and vulnerability and virtuality of cyberspace? Will you even remember this entry, this blog, how  you  felt when you read it after you visit this site, or long after I stop writing here, or forget my password, or when all the ads pull out and this blog has to shut down? Will you? Will I?  I will perhaps one day, fill all these blank journal pages, even throw it away or burn it, but I believe that once written, words can never be taken back. You can admit something by saying it, but you can never, and I mean  never  deny something you have written. Your handwriting will stare back at you and force you to acknowledge it as your own. Even the slightest memories will rush up and squeeze your throat, reminding you when and what you were feeling when you wrote that piece. Pen and paper will be ready to answer a subpoena to tell the truth the whole truth and nothing but the truth about what you wrote, god help them.  It could be that all this shit is laughable and untrue and just plain bullshit by next week, two years from now, tomorrow, or even in the next minute, but you and I will know that the minute I finish all this (the minute a click on {Publish your Post}), that this is how I felt, how I was thinking that very moment I was sweating it out to write this. And perhaps I won't remember as clearly how I struggled, or how difficult this was, but I will never be able to deny this experience again. Ever.  There's this song by Jonny Lang that talks about this girl, writing on her journal, pouring out all her secret ambitions and deepest thoughts, when suddenly the piece of paper flies out the window. She feels bad about this ("A part of your heart/All alone in the night" he sings), but suddenly imagines what if, what if, somebody finds it and reads it and it makes him/her smile, or laugh, or cry or even just nod his/her head in agreement. And suddenly she doesn't mind it being lost at all, because she knows it's not, having written it and confirmed it, and knowing somebody will find it and read it and somehow confirm her, too.  (Right here, about right this time, you'll begin to think,  Whew finally, she'll stop all this angst, all this unproductive anger. She's found that crutch, that part of the story, where you can breath easy and be ready to hear the moral.  Well, fuck, you're in for a disappointment. Let me tell you now, in case you want to stop reading this, I am not finished, I will perhaps never be finished with angst.)  But needless to say, all of the above was a fucking song, and what are the chances that somebody who finds what I've written will really care about what I wrote, or will even  read  what I wrote, or even recognize the stuff between the lines (will they even know that there are stuff between the lines?). What are the chances somebody will even  find  that blown away piece of paper? You know that in real life it'll probably get stepped, trampled, spit on and end up wet and dirty and crumpled and unreadable in some corner, waiting for the rain or the wind to take it somewhere where it can die with dignity. If your piece of paper's lucky, this is what will probably happen. Or someone could find it and use it to pick up their dog's shit in the park.  I know that life doesn't offer guarantees. Hell, the six-year-old understands that right after you tell her there's no Santa.  And I know that that's one of the more beautiful and brilliant things about it sometimes. But tonight it's fucking cold and I've got the cough and I can't finish one cigarette for the burning in my throat.  Yeah, life takes your money and sometimes screws you over. Like that doctor telling me I'm fine and don't need medicine.  I could use some sleep inducers tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i get to be sick in another country.   took my bike home monday last week. three quarters of the way was a fuckin uphill climb that got steeper and steeper. just when my legs couldn't take anymore punishment, it sloped down to one hell of a rollercoaster drop. sure enough the wind slapped at my face, dried my lips, nearly peeled the contact lenses from　my　eyes, and froze my lungs.  so now i have the cold. or kaze, as the japanese call it. i spend my days coughing and sneezing and generally just feeling miserable. i think there's nothing worse than being sick where there's no one to really care if you get well soon or not. nobody to visit you if you stay home to recover. nobody to offer to make you soup or hot tea. no mommy to check for fever. it's sad.  but it's interesting too. i went to the doctor today, daring the language barrier and millions of japanese lining up for their annual medical checkup. i fill up a form, write my name in katakana, indicate that i'm a "firipinjin." the nurse shows me the way to the doctor's office with a polite "douzo," and before i could even start on my "nihongo ga sukoshi wakarimasu" routine, the doctor asks "can you speak english?"  whew. all my troubles over. he checks me up, tells me all i have is a swollen and irritated throat. my lungs sound good, so there's no pneumonia. double whew. in the end he sends me home (no need for medicine) and doesn't even make me pay a single yen. i told you it was interesting.  so, mom, don't worry about a thing. your precious daughter is surviving her first month in japan. i just wish i had somebody to ask me how i am and really want to know the answer.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I was supposed to go to a friend's apartment last week. Thing is, I took the wrong train over. So I'm walking, walking, walking, walking.... and nothing looks familiar at all!!! I've been to his place maybe two times, but I'm so awful with directions, so.  I thought of taking a cab, but what would I tell the driver? `My friend's apartment, please?` Sheesh. I decide to go to Kyoto University instead and call my friend from a payphone there. He lives nearby and we were really supposed to go there anyway... Then at least when I ask for directions, people will know where I want to go...  Okay. Time to paractice my Japanese. I go around stopping friendly-looking, not-too-much-in-a-hurry Japanese. `Um... Sumimasen, Kyodai wa doko desu ka?` They smile, say, `Massugu (straight ahead)` then `migi ni magatte (turn right).` Right. Massugu then migi, massugu then migi, massugu then migi. Sounds simple enough. Right.  Right. Right. Right. Yeah, right. Where to turn right? I tried to ask how many blocks (or stoplights, as Japaanese tend to use shingou as landmarks) before I turn, but the old man started speaking very fast, I couldn`t understand anything! So I just bowed my head as if I understood, `sumimasened` him for his trouble, and walked on, waiting for something to look familiar and tell me I was near Kyodai.  After about 20 minutes, I give up. I ask a nice Japanese lady who can speak a little English. She asks, `Are you just walking to get there? ` That should've been my clue! I was so far away people were wondering how I could just walk it to Kyodai! (And believe me, the Japanese  like  to walk!  It's time to face facts: I am hopelessly lost. In true xx chromosome fashion, I don't hesitate to ask for directions. I enter a shop and ask to see a map. The proprietor tells me I have to take a bus and get off at Hyakumanben. All this was a jumble to me, and all I heard was bus and hyaku man en (one million yen).  I thought the bus fare cost hyaku man en! No way can I afford a bus! I mean, I know prices here are ridiculously high compared to the Philippines, but, c'mon! A million for a bus ride? Do I get to sit on Hiroyuki Sanada's lap or something?  Finally I give up and take a cab. (Which upon later examination, is increadibly stupid, given the assumption that buses cost one million yen). Fifteen minutes and around 1,200 yen later, I got to Kyodai safely and sanely, met my friend, and lived on to survive two weeks in Japan.  And yeah, I've taken the bus to school once or twice. They cost 220 yen. And nope, no Hiroyuki Sanada.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I wake up around dawn, and I have the same feeling I had the other night: that I've got no ballast, nothing to weigh me down, and if I don't hang on I'll just float away. I like Marie a lot, she's funny and smart and pretty and talented, but who the hell is she? I don't mean that philosophically. I just mean I don't know her from Eve, so what am I doing in her bed? Surely there's a better, safer, more friendly place for me than this? But I know there isn't, not at the moment, and that scares me rigid.      You said to me that night: "No, don't change. Don't change anything about yourself."  But you know nothing about me: You don't know that I suffer from vertigo and shouldn't have too much chocolate, cheese, strawberries, and beer. You don't know that I smoke roughly a pack a day and perhaps need to quit. You don't know that I'm thinking of growing my hair long, so I can have cornrows or dreadlocks, or both. You don't know that I'm thinking of getting another tattoo, this time at the small of my back.  You don't know--as I know nothing about you.  You, who took my hand and lead me into a slow dance. You, who drank orange juice with me from one bottle. You, who fed me honey off the blunt edge of a knife. You: who smoked your last cigarette with me, shared your towel, your soap, your toothbrush. You, who ran your hands up and down my back as I lay on my stomach, my head against your shoulder. You, who pulled me into a spoon while you slept, and I couldn't for trying to match my breathing with yours.  We know nothing about each other. Nothing to warrant your odd request. Not our last names, birthdays, the kind of peope we don't like. We don't know how the other feels about pop music, wasabi, baseball, or karaoke. Or how we feel about being away from our homes, our families. About how the other can be lonely, and what we do to cope.  All we know is that when morning came, I had to leave, dressed in yesterday's clothes--with no regrests, but perhaps a bit of sadness. And shame. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In a corny self-discovery essay, I read that to write effectively, one must write about what one knows. But what do I know? I know that I do not know. I even know  what  I do not know:  1. I do not comprehend the ways of mornings-after.  2. I am not familiar with another meaning of casual where rules are set beforehand; and reiterated (numerically) after-fact.  3. I do not know what I did wrong, or if I did  anything  wrong in the first place. (And "I don't mean that philosophically.")  4. I am unsure what to feel about the whole thing, how I should feel about it.  5. I do not know his last name.  Writing all that, I realize, these are what I know:  1. That I felt awkward, at the very least, the next day. And the reasons for it are light years away from the obvious ones.  2. That I worried my friends unnecessarily.  3. That sitting here now, writing (instead of being in a boring class), is running away, whatever excuses I come up with.  4. That somewhere inside me, lies a part of mself I have largely ignored in the last year, who shares this depression with me, though perhaps more profoundly.  5. That I will most probably do it again.  So in an attempt at a half-assed analysis, I am now sitting near the river, drinking coffee and trying to write. However, the atmosphere is much too light and friendly: The tourists in their shorts and tanks and slippers, moms with their strollers, and old couples leaning on their canes--or each other. No dark clouds threaten to hurry me home. The river runs along smoothly, almost... cheerfully. And on the bank are pigeons, and ducks and cranes. There are no crows in sight.   And I am wearing black today--head to foot and inside-out. I am mourning something, yet I cannot seem to apprehend it, much less comprehend its emptiness. Or perhaps this nothingness is all that I can understand of that loss--a presence now-acknowledged, now-recognized for its absence.   Across the river, a little boy is crouched, stretching his arms wide, and going low, ready to pounce. He takes three tentative steps, before breaking into a run, his arms flying like windmills. Suddenly, from behind the weeds, a flock of crows burst out---the sound of wings flapping and low-throated cries echo in the air long after they are gone.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. "It's brilliant, being depressed; you can behave as badly as you like." --Rob Gordon  2. I stayed up half the night making lists of Things-to-Dos. I did 2 out of 7 of today's list, but I feel pretty good about it.  3. I was bored in Japanese class, not because I couldn't understand anything, but because I could, and others couldn't and the teacher spent 45 minutes on the same topic.  4. I saved a turtle's life today.  5. The day isn't over yet: I'm going dancing tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My first serious biking accident (in Japan, anyway) was at a time I as going home to Misasagi, around a month or so ago. It was around 3:00 in the afternoon, and I hadn't had any sleep since the day before. (Hey, I'm setting the scene here).  My old and awfully inconvenient route went something like this: From Kyodai, I take Higashioji-dori (Higashioji Street) straight up to Sanjo-dori, then turn left and follow Sanjo all the way up(hill) to Misasagi. Nearing the Sanjo intersection, Higashioji-dori's sidewalks begin to narrow. Narrow sidewalks in Japan, by the way, mean that two bikers and a lamppost are a tight squeeze. Anyway, since the aforementioned lack of sleep led me to doubt the speed of my reaction time, I decided to take my bike out into the much wider street. (Another stupid-thing-to-do-in-retrospect.)  After three blocks (and three million cars zipping by), and spotting a clear (albeit still narrow) sidewalk, I decide to take my bike back into the pavement. Now, Japan sidewalks are usually biker-friendly, meaning there are no humps to make you bounce on your bike like a rodeo star bent on reaching the 8-second buzzer. In true fashion, I had to choose the one exception... And as my front wheel hit the hump, and my bike jerked in reaction, my brain lost no time in shutting down and my hands immediately assumed no responsibility by letting go of the handlebars, while my eyes widened in quicksilver-stages and 3 million uh-ohs rang in my head.  I landed hard, and so did my bike. Luckily, save for scraped palms, torn jeans and a bruised ego, I was okay. I heaved my bike up and got on it, bent on biking all the way home. (Bruised ego cursing and Eye of the Tiger playing in the background.) I put my foot on the pedal, ready to go... But nothing happened! The chain had come off the grears!!! (Note to self: Buy Cycling for Dummies.) Like any independent 90s woman, I try to fix the problem by myself while surreptitiously looking out for a cute guy to offer help.  Alas, scraped palms, grimy hands and a broken fingernail later, and still thrown hopelessly out of gear, I give up. I  walk  my bike back to the university, to the shop where I bought it. The only place I knew I could get help.  I walk for thirty minutes (all the while shamefully hiding my grimy hands, curling the greasy fingernails into my palms), back up the street I (and three million cars) had just zipped by, suffering what-the-fuck looks from other bikers. (If you see my very "kakkoii," very "nice" badass-bike, you'll understand.) I finally reach the shop, and with a grave "Tasukete kudasai," asked the owner to fix my bike. He was very kind nice about it, and even gave me a stern lecture on safety. (Actually, the only words of the lecture I understood was "dangerous" and "cars"; stern was deduced from his expression, but nevermind that.) Anyway, after all this, I took a deep breath, gave thanks that I was not seriously injured, and got myself ready to... Park my bike at school and take the bus and subway home. And that's exactly what I did.       Note to reader:    All of the above was actually meant as an introduction to my second though not-so-serious accident, which happened yesterday, and was somewhat similar to the first. Somewhat similar because the second one also happened as I was on my way home, suffering from lack of sleep, and the chain had also come off the gears. However, this time, I did not get thrown off (I jumped off gracefully, there's a difference), and suffered no scraped palm or what not (although ego was slightly bruised).  Anyway, since the introduction became the entire story, let me get to my point quickly and painlessly: I fixed the chain-had-come-off problem all by myself!!!!!! And save for grimy and greasy hands, which are totally unavoidable, really, I was no worse for wear!  And so, this time around, with my grimy hands like a proud banner, I get on my bike, grip the handlebars with new-found confidence, and position my foot onto the pedal: I was ready. I was ready to take on anything, set to finish the course. And with head held high, I went home.  (In the background, playing: Chariots of Fire, ego humming along.)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if the ear holds the key to one's sense of balance, will cutting your ear off at moments of unbearable dizziness restore your balance or will it make you dizzy for the rest of your life?  ps. vertiginous, defined as "affected by vertigo, dizzy, or causing vertigo" by Dictionary.com is the adjective for vertigo. Not "vertiguous" as I had previously thought, and unknowingly invented. haha. i stand corrected mr. webster.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for some odd reason, i don't like my camel lights today.  camels, here in japan, are a treat for me. they cost 30yen more than  mild sevens, (and though thirty yen isn't much) i like to pretend they're  my "special days"  brand. like when i'm doing laundry and looking forward  to wearing those detergent-fresh, static-clingy clothes.  but today, they taste bitter, and the paper doesnt make that crackling  sound when i take a drag.   as i ponder possible reasons, i latch onto one i really like: have i  gotten used to my ordinary-days, nothing-special-about-it mild seven  extra lights with 3mg of tar and 0.3mg of nicotine?  in a land i love, but have yet to fit in (where cigarettes are "tabako,"  fish fillets have wasabi sauce, a socket is called a "consent," and PC  keyboards confuse the hell out of me) finding something to call my own  is most comforting. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i'm spending a rainy friday afternoon in bed, when i should be in my laboratory. i'm fighting off (or falling into, i don't know which yet) a nasty dizziness caused by vertigo because i just had to have a ham-and-cheese omelette.  good thing im not allergic to eggs, or i'd probably be dead now.  then again, the way i feel, dead probably wouldn't be so bad.  so i do the next best thing:  i close my eyes. imagine i'm in an open field somewhere, lying naked on the wet grass, all alone for miles and miles. letting the rain wash away all the traces of toxins in my body, the mascarra and dark circles around my eyes, the smell of sweat and cigarette smoke from my hair, the tattoo on my back and other people's marks on my skin.  and just before my own fingerprints dissolve into nothingness, into the oblivion which my body has for so long sought, my soul rises up like a white flag from among the green, conspicuous in its surrender.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (this is an old one, but hey, this is my blog isnt it?)   i spent a nice friday night at home alone, sleeping or eating or smoking, drinking tea i don't like... you get the drift.  and it really was a nice night too: pre summer when there's a slight breeze but not too cool and not too hot, like you can wear a tank top and shorts and not worry about freezing your ass off or sweating like a pig.  i read a book i've read a thousand times since coming to japan, one of the better ones off my shamefully small, entertainment-in-english-and-i-don't-mean-easy-living-in-kyoto collection. the rest are japanese language textbooks...  (oh god, where did my floor-to-almost-ceiling books go? packed hurriedly in a box at my sisters apartment in makati, gathering dust. will the words still be there when i return? or will the pages dissolve at a touch?)  so yeah it's safe to say im depressed. and to make matters worse, i chose to stop rereading that book at its most depressing part when, having read it over and over i could have chosen to edit those out and jump to the funny parts or rewind to the profound ones or hell, even skip to the very satisfying i've-just-started-a-new-phase-in-my-life-and-its-starting-to-make-sense-again-and-none-of-that-corny-self-righteous-cliches-thank-you-very-much ending. but i don't. so what does that say about me?  hell. somebody get a thesaurus and give me the common every-day word for masochist. loser seems too mundane and covers a lot of ground. depressed is... well, over-used. while what just happened and this entry is too long, painful and fucking draining. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wednesdays, I have Japanese class until 6:00pm. Usually, by 5:00, I would be so bored I would spend time cursing my wristwatch for being 5 minutes advanced. I would shuffle my feet under the desk, itching to check my phone for messages or missed phone calls since it usually vibrates anywhere from 2 to 5 times during that three-hour class. Invitations from friends for dinner, or a movie, or just to ask me to tell the teacher why they'd be missing class.  This Wednesday was different. No phone calls. Not a single message. Not even a stupid phone company ad. To make matters worse, I had forgotten to put it on silent mode, which, by virtue of Murphy's Law, should have had increased the chances of it ringing at inappropriate times (e.g., class time) by 500%.  After class, I eagerly check my phone, hoping I had somehow missed something. Nope. So I initiate contact and email my two closest friends inviting them to dinner. No response. I call one of them. He shuts it off mid-ring.  I go to dinner in the cafeteria, hoping to spot somebody I know. No one. I sit along side two Japanese guys, and I cannot even eavesdrop to their conversation. Two minutes pass and they leave the table. I find myself sitting alone in one of the longest table in a canteen that's packed.  I go home. The streets are dark, and my bike light is losing power. I meet no one on the road, not even a rock that would make me take spill on my bicycle, hurt myself and remind me I'm there. I reach my dorm, climb four flights of stairs (I met no one, by the way) to my room. I take off my clothes, lie on the bed, chug on lousy orange juice and take one of the best escape routes known to me: I sleep for 15 straight hours.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I miss my old journal. And my En 21 essays. And my Mcdonalds table napkin scribblings. Those proofs of a time long gone when I can write and not just pretend to know how.  I went home today by bicycle, and it tired me out (That's my excuse. What's yours?). Was lying in bed reading The Best American Essays of 2003, and now I'm tired and envious. Not a good feeling. So, in a spur-of-the-moment decision, I decided to go down to the PC room and churn out whatever I can. This is my excuse. Go figure.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>