<Blog>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "Wrestlemania 20 in one hand. Cock in the other. Lube on standby and a goldfish on ice"  Quote Via Text Message from Gavin Evans  Could it be said any other way? Possibly. But after watching Wrestlemania XX the other day over at his house, I couldn't have put it better myself!  Thanks for the giggle Gav. BANG! BANG! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This past weekend saw the union of two former residents of the Haven (that's our house in Lochaber street), tie the knot. The following has been quite difficult for me to recall as I don't remember much of what happened, it just comes back to me in dribs and drabs but here goes...  Whiteway came up to stay at our house on the friday night before the wedding day. It was a good time to just catch up so we went to Royworld for a few beers. Aside from the DJ being absolute shit and the clientele looking like they had just learned motor-neurone skills, it was a good laugh. We decided to leave early and get some good sleep as we had an early start. A little later Zoe had returned a little drunker than usual armed with a Jumbo Sausage from the chip shop round the corner - I came the closest a man can be to being raped by a woman - suffice to say, it was a traumatising experience and Zoe - when I go to Thailand, I'll let you know what the going rate is for a simple op if you really want one!?  I awoke in a mischievous mood and no sooner had Steve gotten up and made himself a cup of tea, I had slammed a handful of squirty cream in his face (nothing rude here, honest!). It seemed like such a funny prank at the time except for the fact that my brother has a bushy beard (Castaway Styley) and all he could smell all day was a faint smell of off cream, no matter how much he tried to wash it out. That wasn't so bad for me, but listening to him moan about it all day was.  We travelled to Carmarthenshire in Whiteway's mighty Bora with its big paws and more gadgets than Jack Bauer, and we got to our respective B&Bs. Now, at the best of times, i think that Wales has some pretty funny looking names for places but I thought it was hilarious that my Brother and Zoe's B&B was called The Cottage Inn and Me and Whiteway were were staying next door at Pant-Y-Bas. George Michael and Kylie must be regular customers.  Anyway, the wedding, yes.... i was getting round to that bit. The ceremony was very natural and relaxed despite me and Steve thinking that Dom Joly was the Vicar and we thought that two blokes dressed as labradors would start fighting at the back of the church at any time. Rich and El looked like they really enjoyed it all despite not getting the weather they wanted - the wind could have blown the spots off a leopard!  The reception followed and after a tear jerking speech by El's Dad, Caunter did his best mans speech despite our efforts to put him off by our table wearing our Ray Gravell (of BBC Radio Cymru) face masks that we found in the pub. He found it so hard to tell a story about Rich that didn't involve the Stag Week in Prague or dead prostitutes.   After the main meal, many people went to get changed into more comfortable attire for the evenings drinking and dancing, however, there was a hardcore element who stayed on to smoke cigars and drink JD until the evening reception started. It'a hard life I know but in truth, I couldn't move because I had been eaten everything I could get my hands on, including some fake fruit and a bowl of pot pourri.  In the evening, everyone got very drunk and danced wildly into the night thanks to Pat Mustard and his Wheels of Steel (An old timer at the bar stated "The Disco's good -  it's not too loud and there are tunes you can really hum to!"). The bride and groom left for Mexico, Helen Cornish couldn't stop speaking french and I can't remember much else.  Sorry it's a bit long winded and probably a load of nonsense but I'm not gifted like Paul Carr, Shakespeare or Jilly Cooper.  As a final note, I want to thank Rich and El for a fantastic and enjoyable day. I was humbled to have been invited and I wish you all the happiness in the world.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, Rich and Els wedding wasn't soon enough for another "incident" to occur in my life, so, here goes- A friend (Matt James) from work was having a house party on Saturday night and we were informed that there was a fancy dress theme of "Bad Taste" of which myself and Owzy-O took too literally.  O arrived looking like a moroccan waiter (fake tan/ tweed jacket/ Big Ol' Glasses/ tasteless shirt) and I arrived in attire that cannot be expressed without the words "clashing" and "wrong size". Needless to say, we lived up to our part of the bargain. However, no-one else did. We were the only ones to actually believe Matts dress code and, in my opinion, we were glad because we would have put everyone else to shame....so there.  Anyway, the evening was enjoyable. We drank copious amounts of alcohol and didn't spend a penny (well maybe a couple). Big up to the attendees.....Matt, Perry, Katy, Richie Hanner, Dolph, Kev Crowley, even Andros (who, i was told, wanted a bit more of me than I'd like to know. Thanks for the info Matt but I'm strictly asexual).   The evening was going swimmingly (sorry!) and then even more so as Owzy-O and I were willing to take the theme of "bad taste" that next step. Danny Nuts (who was sadly not in attendance-For shame!) had planted the seed in O's mind to buy two goldfish from a pet shop in order to emulate a scene from a popular movie that encapsulated the comic genius of Kevin Kline. Needless to say, the goldfish were our guests of honour at the party and people were shocked to see us commit, what some called, an act of premeditated murder. In our defence, we still find the act to be not that barbaric as it happens in nature all the time, just not by two hairy drunken buffoons. My Dad wasn't proud but I convinced him it was just like sushi for the impatient.  Anyway, next blog- Rich and Els Wedding - I promise no more shenanigans until the weekend.  P.S. I forgot to mention in my last entry that I saw Pierluigi Collina officiate the Arsenal game. Not only does he have the shiniest Head in the football referees' Hall of Fame, but it was a pleasure to see that not all referees are Blankers in Wack. Mr Collina - We salute You!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wednesday 10th of March saw Arsenal face Celta Vigo in the Champions League at Highbury. Guess who had a ticket to see them? Thats right baby - Me! Me,Owzy-O and 4 others won the tickets and a hotel stay in the Hyde Park Hilton through a work incentive and we had ourselves a little adventure. The match itself was impressive with Thierry Henry showing why he is in fact the modern day Jesus Christ complete with black gloves. He danced around the pitch, flamenco style, scoring 2 superbly worked goals which was enough to make any grown Spaniard cry. On reflection, the atmosphere was eerily quiet as even the Vigo fans thought it was a foregone conclusion that Arsenal would win. Also, Highbury was tiny! Whats up with that? The highlight of the night for me though, was that Ainsley Harriott (one of the Calypso Twins and a TV Chef like no other), was sat right behind us. I couldn't help myself and had to have a photo taken with him. After his token catchphrase "What are you like, eh?", the shaking of hands and me exclaiming that he was "my Boy", it was all over and I was left with that tingly feeling inside that you just don't get from reading Heat Magazine.  My mum was proud. His cous cous is good too! Next step was the post match drinks in Hyde Park. I've never felt so much like I was abroad without leaving the Country! I was the only Englishman left in the club which was full of Danes(20%), Mexicans (15%), Yanks(5%), South Africans(5%), and the Welsh(8%)! Still it was a good night and I took as many freebies from the Hotel the next morning to satisfy the Gypsy blood in me.  My tickets to Hong Kong arrived today and aside from feeling the sting in my bank account, I'm more excited than a Blue Peter presenter who just found 10,000 milk bottle tops.  Next time will probably be about Rich and El's Wedding. Stay tuned.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, here it is. I thought to myself, if Paul Carr can do it, I'm sure I can do something to mimic and undermine his efforts and pass it off as my own ideas.  This is a strange and exciting experience for me and I hope that you will all share and enjoy my stories and experiences - Whether you all believe me or not is a different matter, But hey. So without further ado, i declare this blogspot officially open and, if you're all sitting comfortably, my journey will begin thus......................
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Testing, Testing one two..............one, two, two....is this thing on? Hey man step away from the mike!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's French you know! C'est Bon, Eh? Danny Nuts would appreciate it.  Well, my final weekend in Cardiff was a perfect one in my eyes. I had most of Friday off so I just sunbathed and went to Mermaid Quay and wandered around aimlessly in the sun.   The Princess made a surprise visit on Friday Night, which was nice - and as she had work the next day, Owzy-O and I got up at 5.30am to see her off on Saturday morning. As we were awake, we decided to start the day as we meant to go on and cranked the system up in the kitchen and sat in the garden from 6am, much to the annoyance of the neighbours who didn't appreciate pre-dawn karaoke - what's wrong with them?!  From then on we pretty much didn't leave the garden - Not even the glitz and glamour of Saturday Morning Wrestling programmes were enough to prize us from our patio furniture as we were adamant on topping up our tans and drinking ourselves into a stupor.  Nicci came over mid morning and joined in the fun - When Steve got up, even he couldn't resist the lure of the Haven garden and was soon singing along to the TV Themes we downloaded and was drinking Dr. Peppers (thats a cocktail by the way - Half coke/ half beer and drop in a shot of Amaretto - It's lovely!).  We had a BBQ and drank snakebite and then I had some great news - Plymouth Argyle beat QPR 2-0 and so became champions of Division 2. I was so happy I could have wet myself (it was a close call).  So, in order to celebrate the success of my local team and just for the hell of it, Owzy and I decided to venture into town. We went to Slug and Lettuce and terrorised Jimmy Love and Woody for a bit. They soon convinced us there was a better time to be had elsewhere as we were cramping their style so we mosied on over to Cuba. The phrase "Scene Missing" applies here as the next thing I knew it was sunday morning, I was still fully clothed with curry sauce on my shoes, a knitted hat in my back pocket and an inflatable parrot on my shoulder. Methinks I drank too much!  Sunday was basically the same as saturday except Owain was a deeper shade of pink, we had hangovers to deal with and we didn't go out in the evening and ........OK it was completely different but we were in the Garden again and had another BBQ. Suffice to say, we were living the good life and I will miss the summers in Cardiff.  Coming into my last week in work and ultimately Cardiff, I'm really happy to be starting a new chapter in my life, but I have a sneaky feeling that on my leaving Do on friday I'll be blubbing like a schoolboy with scuffed knees.  Keep 'em peeled as my next editions I will set the world to rights and there will be a tribute to  Owzy-O.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am at a point where I am saying goodbye to people that I am not going to see in a long, long time and it makes me feel sad. Not only because I will miss them but also because I have been in this situation before and it is easy to forget them as it is an "out of sight, out of mind" scenario.  However, I hope in this case it is different as this person helped lift me up out of the Great Winter Depression of 2003/4 and she is also one of the most generous people I know.  Clare moved into "The Haven" last August and we didn't know her from Adam (or Eve for that matter). We soon realised that she is Birmingham's Best Kept Secret.   She works for Arcadia Group and she was an Interior Development Consultant or something (never could remember her proper job title but she had a lot on conceptual drawings!). She was on the road a lot which is a tough life to lead, but she has just relocated back home to Birmingham to be a Store Manager.   In all truth she wasn't here much as she went home nearly every weekend and went on a lot of holidays (Easy life, eh) but when she was here she was always the life and soul.  My favourite memories are:  - Karaoke at 6.30am every morning in the kitchen (mainly Bonnie Tyler, Queen and The Jackson 5). - Going to Tescos with her and her sister (Beany) on Mondays nights when I had a broken leg and telling her what to put in the trolley. - Staying up til 2am waiting for the Hey Ya! video to come on Q. - Sitting in the Garden at the end of last summer after work and just chillin'. - And basically for having as corrupt a mind as me, Steve and Owain.  So Princess - Babar, Nowain and Baby wish you the best of luck in your new job and it was a pleasure to serve you, your highness.   Have fun bombing around the mean streets of Sutton Coldfield with the windows down and the system up! And don't forget to keep in touch.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I only briefly mentioned him in the previous update, but I feel he deserves a special mention as he started this whole blogspot thing off. I am, of course, referring to Paul Carr.  Carr has been a divine inspiration over the years. We've had good times and we've had awesome times. We both caught the travelling bug when we went to Spain, Portugal and Morocco around Easter in 2002. We made friends, got laughed at by whores, beat up pick-pockets, played a lot of frisbee and nearly got stabbed by a hobo. That was the life, eh?  Then 8 months ago he decided to go to Oz and New Zealand without me - well that's fine, old buddy, old pal - break promises - see if I care! Thankfully, he thought ahead enough to keep us updated of his exploits with the Original and Inspirational blogspot:  liningoflove.blogspot.com . (I would recommend people take a look if they want an insight into an englishman's perspective on varied antipodean delights or if you just want a giggle.)  Anyway, he had to come back possibly because he ran out of money, but I reckon it's because he missed me and Fred. He arrived back just before the Easter weekend and we had a bit of a catch-up and a chin wag, we slated Oram, witnessed Swiggs being drunk and gay, stared death in the face by taunting Fred.............just like the old days, really.  It was really good to see you back mate. I'll be back in Plymouth in 3 weeks to see your dole-scum antics before I set off for my very own adventures.  Viva La Revolucion! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Easter Weekend is always somewhat a double-edged sword - You do get a chance to have a long weekend and catch up with the things that you've just not had enough time for. However, you end up more knackered and out of synch than if you were to have a two day weekend -  What's up with that!   The events of the weekend were as follows:   Thursday Night  - There was a Works Do at the Glee Club - It was OK I suppose - the acts were funny enough, the food was bland, the beer tasted of piss, I got paralytic etc, etc.... However, I spent no money at all, and I managed to spike Owain's drink with absinthe. Ladies and Gentlemen, I present to you.............. the Whoa-Bomb! (2 shots of Port, 2 shots of Vodka, Blue WKD and lashings of Absinthe served in a pint glass) - Don't try this at home kids!   Friday  - Travelled down to Plymouth to see the family on the Farm (or Potterfork as it has been called in some circles). There are new additions to the family with Lilo & Stitch - the two orphaned lambs - and Runny & Squidgy - the new baby ducklings. Also, my sister has bought a horse called Irish who is in fact bigger than the Wooden horse of Troy.    Saturday  - The morning was spent ripping up fencesposts on the Farm and then wrapping barbed wire onto the forementioned fenceposts and pretending to be Cactus Jack (Have a nice Day! BANG BANG!!). I then went to see Plymouth Argyle play Wycombe Wanderers - It was quite a good match, especially since Argyle won but they'll have to play a lot better against Bristol City if they're going to want to wrap up the Div 2 title on Tuesday.   In the evening, I went to see Paul Carr at his house and we drank gallons of red wine with Mark Oram aka Gunther Organ (his German persona) aka Kram Maro (his evil persona). We proceeded to venture into Plymouth City Centre to meet up with our other friends only to find that they were all trolleyed and that the nightlife in Plymouth has gotten worse (which I never actually thought was possible!).    Sunday  - We went to Treyarnon Bay to open up/ clean up the caravan we have down there in preparation for the new season. Our first stop was to have pasties in Padstow and wander around aimlessly. However, whilst waiting for my brother, his girlfriend and my mother to get their acts together, I saw Holly from the TV series Red Dwarf (thats the original Holly - Norman Lovett) riding his bike on the Camel Trail with his lovely (young) wife.  Lucky swine! We arrived in Treyarnon, where the sun is always shining and, after catching up with friends of the family (the Davises and the Elsons), I went down to the beach with my sisters kids, Jack and Jasmine. The kids kept running towards the sea and, being the super-uncle that I am, I sprinted to retrieve them whilst doing my best impression of David Hasselhoff. However, on the way back, Jack said that he needed to do a No.2 and he couldnt wait any longer as it was "coming out". We were a long way from any toilets and even further from my sister so I let him drop his trunks and do his thang. When people came near I had to pretend that It was dog-doo and that I was disgusted that no-one had picked it up and that my kids nearly fell in it!   Monday  - Back in Plymouth, I picked up the Fred, Carr and Oram and we went to Cap'n Jaspers for a Half-Yarder on the Barbican. If anyone ever visits Plymouth, you have to go to Cap'n Jaspers for Half A Yard of Hotdog - Its like seeing the Eiffel Tower if you go to Paris. We then went to the park for a kick around and a game of frisbee. I almost put Jack to shame but thankfully I was able to get to home in time. When I got back to the Farm, no-one was there so I got my wellies on and started to do what farmers do - Survey the land, get your hands dirty and start a bonfire. Yup - I could get used to the country life.  That's it so get back to work or whatever it is that you do. Ciao for now!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I would like to say farewell/ good luck/ best wishes/ good riddance to all who left the Concentration Camp that is HBOS over the last week or so.    Aarti  - You are a sweet little thing despite your cheeky side. Being a housewife isn't easy you know - those dishes don't clean themselves. Married to an anaestesiologist eh? Don't let him take his work home with him, that's all that I can say. You'll be missed - The Vipers Pit has lost it's ray of sunshine.    Donna  - Working for the National Farmers Union - I promise I won't mention anything about welly tops. I suppose I'll have to start flirting with Lisa Gale now you've gone. I tell you what though - you scrub up well for a Merthyr girl. Best of luck being a milk maid.   Rob Evans  - You are my number one.............Guy. Going off to be a runner a production company. Wanna be a big shot in that business? Then you've gotta take one for the team my boy. Thanks for the laughs and especially for the Indiana Jones Grail Book - a stroke of Genius. Don't get lost in the dirty world of Porn that you download night after night..... and hands off my dream woman! You ever danced with the Devil by the pale moonlight?   Paulo  - Why is it always the people with the least amount of respect for the law become coppers? You can take the boy out of Llanelli but you can't take Llanelli out of the boy! It's a shame to see you leave especially since you were just getting good at your job. Best of luck mate - we'll always have Las Vegas.  And Finally  Owzy-O  - I'm glad you've gone - you were cramping my style. But on a serious note, the place won't be the same without you - definitely quieter anyway. It was sad to see you being so repressed towards the end by the violence inherent in the system (i.e. da management), but they were just jealous of your mullet. Your spirit will live on though as, I'm sure that any practical joke that happens in the future, Paul gray will say "How did Owain do that?".  Nice to see you have moved onwards to the undiscovered country that is the Woman's Royal Voluntary Service - This a perfect opportunity for you to get in touch with your feminine side. I think it's great that the Fat chicks have already been banned from making you coffee - Remember, fat chicks need love too - they've just gotta pay for it. I'm sure that it'll be a great stepping stone for you in your adventures in the wonderful world of Finance while you skirt the shores of Accountancy. I can't wait for the nude calendar shots - Naughty!  Best of luck to you all and keep in touch.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm a week into my trip and there are no signs of nerves - in fact I am so relaxed I'm horizontal (hee hee!)  After my last update, I went to the cinema (I even paid for it on my octopus card - Thanks for the advice - Princess they rock!) and I went to see Van Helsing - It wasn't bad. Good bubble gum for the mind. It was funny because I had a load of teenage girls sitting next to me and they were jumping at all the scary bits - Bless those little people!  On wednesday, it was a national holiday as it was Buddha's Birthday so Lisa took me to see what the Chinese call "Fat Dan" (Quite a good likeness to Woody too!) which is the Giant Buddha Statue on Lantau Island - It was so nice to be there on a day of significance. They were all burning incense everywhere - some incense sticks were like trees!  Another thing that I noticed is that Hong Kong has loads of little areas of, I wouldn't say tranquility, but more imagination and creativity. It really is a wondrous place.  Later today I am going to go to Victoria Peak and take in the views. After that it will be a few more drinks and tearing the ass out of the Nightlife scene again (If I can stay awake that long!).  A freaky thing happened on the way out today, I asked Lisa if she has ever been hit by a car before, but before I finished the sentence, she tripped in a crack in the road and headbutted a moving bus! I shit myself to be fair but she took it all in her stride. Thankfully, she wasn't hurt that bad and my brain is already starting to scab over that particular memory and I can breathe easy again!  I'm off to Bangkok on Sunday so I will update y'all when I get there. I've also decided to do a diving course in Ko Chang as it will be good to be prepared for the Great Barrier Reef and Fiji (should be a damn sight cheaper too!).  Stay safe everyone and I'll be in touch real soon. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey there everybody peeps! That's right - I'm still alive!  At the moment I'm sitting in a Pacific Coffee House on t'internet located right next to a huge building with hundreds of airplane/ porthole style windows which is affectionately called "The Building of a Thousand Arseholes" - The reason being is that it is full of bankers.  Since I last updated y'all a lot has happened. Allow me to retort -   The Journey  - After my parents waved me goodbye at the Bus Station in Plymouth (a tearful moment), I arrived at Heathrow and rang my nearest and dearest to remind them that I do care. In the meantime, I just sat in the bar and got tipsy in the hope that I might get some sleep on the plane - sadly, my plan failed - however, I did have the best seat on the plan with about 8 foot leg room, I was next to the drinks counter and not too far from the loo. Also, Virgin Atlantic has the best in flight facilities ever - You can stop, start, rewind and fast forward any of the films that were on offer (there were about 60 films to choose from). So, due to the insomnia, I managed to watch 6 films!    My arrival  - When I got to HK it was about 5pm. I dawdled for a while and made my way to the recommended hostel called the Jockey Club Mount Davis Youth Hostel. A place situated at the top of a mountain with breath taking views.   On my way to the hostel, I met a very kind woman at the MTR station called Lisa, who pointed me in the right direction and asked me out for a few drinks on the next night to get an insider's view of Hong Kong.   She certainly lived up to her end of the bargain, as we must have visited at least 10 bars and clubs all over HK and we didn't finish drinking until 5am on Sunday Morning! Lisa was generous enough to let me stay at her flat (which is, as she puts it, in the "Knightsbridge" of Hong Kong). Suffice to say, I slept for most of Sunday and had not returned to the hostel (where my rucksack was) for nearly two days! To my pleasant surprise, my bag hadn't even been touched and just sums up that HK is a very safe place to be.   General observations and experiences (so far)  -  - The chinese have an amazing ability - they can remember who you are even if it was only a brief encounter (This could also be because I have been wearing the same clothes for the last 3 days!) - Jackie Chan is adored here! - It is easy to get lost here but it is not intimidating at all. Probably because I tower above nearly everyone. - I have discovered the appeal of travelling solo - When you get lost you can only blame yourself. - I met 4 lads from Bristol at the hostel (Ed, Sheldon, Mark and Josh)and spent Monday afternoon just chilling with them and listening to music. If, you encounter this quartet on your travels, don't let their age fool you - their a bloody good laugh and when it comes to music, they know their shit! - Boys - I hope to meet up with you in Ko Chang at the Treehouse and catch up some more - you never know - you may have something to celebrate if Bristol City win the play-offs (But don't count your chickens!).    At the moment I am staying with Lisa at her flat and I am gobsmacked by her generosity. So, I would like to describe Lisa as best I can:  - She is a clairvoyant mechanic from Essex - Her Dad  IS  Sean Connery! (well a damn good looky-likey anyway!) - She's big on Buddhism and I have to admit, I have become very interested myself since meeting her. - Her mate, Dennis (A Pompey fan), owns his own night club (which was part of our itenerary on Saturday night) and, he is an effing loon, but such a fantastic bloke to meet. - She is a woman of the world - and she's got the scars to prove it - I have met a titanium twin! - She has been so generous since I landed in this mad city - so thank you for everything.  Well, I have to go now as someone is waiting to use the computer. But, I will be in touch soon.  P.S. Thanks to Carr for the Baboon..... Compilation - it is an anthem already to my travels. And, also to the Shaolin Funk (Jimmy and Dan) those mixes have got me seriously strutting on the subway here! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I've done as many goodbye E-mails as I can and now it is time for my final update as I leave for Hong Kong tomorrow.  All there is to say is thanks to everyone for the memories. I'll see y'all next year and some of you I'll see on my travels, I hope.  I would like to specially mention a few people though before I leave:   Everyone at HBOS  - Thanks for the laughs and making it all bearable - I could mention names but it would take forever.   Everyone at Lang & Potter  - Some of you may never read this (My mother says thats probably because most of you can't read!) but I will keep in touch and get ready for my return - if you thought my Dad was insane, wait til you get a load of me. (Donna - I was hoping for a Spring wedding, what do you think?)   My Friends in Cardiff  - Thats the old school crew which includes all previous residents of The Haven (Colin, Bob, Rich and El) and of course the Shaolin Funk (Jimmy Love and Burma Dan) of which I was proud to be a guest member of. You all rock my world and I will be back to visit next year.   My Friends in Plymouth  - Thanks for all turning up at the pub last night - I'll be there for the meal on Christmas Eve as per usual and hopefully without any broken bones this time! And to the Plymouth Volleyball Team, I'll be back in training and kicking bottom next season in time for the summer tournaments next year.   Webby  - You've always been a dissapointment to me but I love you all the same - I've known you since we were both twinkles and even though I haven't seen you that often recently, I'll be back with a vengeance next year. We may have to recreate those Epic squash matches we used to have - I reckon I can still kick your ass!   My Family  -  Mum, Rach, Johnny, Jack and Jasmine  - Thank you for letting me stay at the Farm - it's been lush and I can't wait to stay there when I get back.   Dad  - enjoy the first half of the season, let's hope Argyle are at the top for when I get back as secretly, I'm just a glory hound!  Steve  - Good luck with the new house and see a doctor and get rid of it.   Princess  - I will miss you loads when I go but I'll always have that good luck charm to remind me of you - you're a sweetie and I will be up to visit you loads next year. M'Goi, Princess!   Owain  - He was a bit upset that he was not mentioned as a  best friend in one of my previous posts - well, I would like to amend that statement and say that you are like a soulmate to me and no-one will ever be able to recreate the havoc we caused over the last year! Good luck in Manchester and I will see you soon (If you and Princess want to visit me in Oz I would be absolutely chuffed to bits!).   Carr  - It is going to be so hard to live up to your travel journal but I will try goddamn hard - It's just a pity that I wasn't able to travel with you this time around. But don't worry - There'll be other adventures to be had when I get back. You are a Legend and I will miss you more than I will miss Marmite.   Fred  - I've known you since we were very small (well when I was - you've always been a giant!) and we've always been best friends. If I'm ever blue, I'll just have to look at the picture of you cutting cheese and I'll be able to smile again. Try not to gamble your life away while I'm gone and look after Carr - Don't let him spiral into a world full of internet filth or at least get him to keep some for me when I get back.  I will miss you all and please, please, please, try and keep in touch and I'll do the same.   Goodbye, Cloudy Britain - Hello, Tropical Travels!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As I am off on my travels this week, I thought it would be quite nice to spend a bit of time in Cornwall at the caravan with my two best friends, Fred and Carr.   I originally intended to go on Thursday evening but I made the mistake of only mentioning this plan to F&C when they were absolutely hammered the weekend before! So, obviously we had to delay it.   First things first, I played Carr at squash on Thursday night and my leg felt good - also it was a bloody good match (which I won, of course) but, as it was the first strenuous exercise I've done since I broke my leg, I was pooped for the entire weekend.  Anyway, we left on Friday afternoon to go to Treyarnon and we were blessed with good weather all weekend. When we got down there we had a BBQ and made enemies with a neighbouring caravan as the stupid cow was under the impression that her opinion counted for a goddamn thing  (It's a shame because when you make enemies with the Potters, we'll not just make your life a misery but we'll ruin your children's lives too).   Anyway we had a lot to drink and we had a good laugh (even though Carr didn't piss in his pants like last time).  On Saturday, we went to the beach and played cricket and football and then we waited for Steve & Zoe to arrive so we could go and get drunk. They were of course fashionably late but when they arrived we got a move on and went to Newquay to meet Cornish, Caunter, Rich, El and Whiteway on their Surfari adventure.  We went straight to the pub and they met us a little bit later as they were all a little bit fatigued, so we settled down and watch the end of the football and played a few games of pool. Little did we know we were in the presence of the King and Queen of Hobo antics as a mad pissed-up old woman challenged Zoe to a game of pool (but she kept laughing her head off because she couldn't see the balls) and her mate (who looked like an unclean Uncle Albert) was asleep behind us and was snoring his head off - Newquay really does attract the cream of society.  It was really good to see everyone one last time before I go away - even you Whiteway!  It all got decidedly messy in the end and I don't think the taxi driver was impressed with myself and my brother's malicious scheming and lewd behaviour on the way back - he must have added on a nobhead fee to the fare as we paid through the nose to get home.   Sunday was another lovely day as got back to Plymouth by midday and, after nipping in to see my old volleyball team at the Southwest Championships, we had another BBQ at the Farm. We ate a lot of meat and it was good to see Dad drunk again as it serves as a painful reminder of how not to act when I'm away. Awwww....Bless!  I now have 3 days to go and I am in a word "nervous" to say the least.  That was my last weekend in Britain for a while but I would like to add a few extra bulletins:   HBOS Implodes  - I have been informed that the mass exodus from HBOS has begun - people being fired, shit kicking up and people resigning etc... What the hell is going on!? I hold some people directly responsible for being thoroughly rotten eggs and I hope you all get your come uppance. I would say that those people know who they are but, let's face it - they probably don't!   Crimson Masks all round  - I caught the end of Judgment Day this morning (wrestling - sorry!) - all I can say is: that's how you take a chair shot to the face!   Happy Birthday!  - Last Friday, Laura May, the M.I.L.F. of HBOS, was celebrating her 21st birthday for the 14th year in a row. Hope you a good one and let me know when you next have one of your "car-keys parties" in Plymouth.  I have to go now but I will have one more update before I leave.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok here goes this is my designated itinerary of where I intend to be over the next 7/8 months:   Hong Kong  -  21st to 30th May  - I fly out on the 20th May - 1st stop - should be there for about a week.   Thailand  -  30th May to 28th June  - Going to Ko Chang and considering Chang Mai if I have time - Should be there for about a month.   Malaysia  -  28th May to 9th July  - doing a trek I bought from STA Travel and should be going through KL and Singapore and hopefully to Tioman Island - There for about 2 weeks.   Indonesia  -  9th July to 6th August  - Mainly in Bali but will do island-hopping over to Komodo Island and Lombok - There for about 1 month.   Australia  -  6th August to 18th September  - I fly into Brisbane and will endeavour to visit (in no particular order)Melbourne, Sydney, Cairns, Fraser Island, Uluru (AKA Ayers Rock) and, of course, Brisbane. There for about 6 weeks.   New Zealand  -  16th September to 18th November  - I plan to visit as much as I can. I'm going to be here for as long as I can - possibly 2 and a half months but we'll see.   Fiji  -  16th November to 30th November  - Should be chilling on the beaches here for about 2 weeks.   USA  -  30th November to 22nd December  - I definately plan to see San Francisco, San Diego, LA, possibly Tijuana, and depending on money left over and time to do it, I may attempt some kind of road trip. I will be here for about 3 weeks.   Plymouth  - I will be back home on the 23rd December, Just in time for Christmas on the Farm.  (Dates given above in italics may be liable to change if I either can't stand a place or, love a place to bits!)  I hope to see some friends on the way and let's just hope I don't run out of money and need to come home early - That would suck big-time! Luckily, I'm as tight as a gnat's pee-hole so I should be fine.  My next update will be my recollection of a trip to Cornwall with my two bestest friends - Chas & Dave - no sorry...... Siegfried and Roy. No, wrong again........it's Fred & Carr.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I went to Birmingham to see The Princess and Owzy-O.   I arrived around 11am and when I knocked on the door Clare's Grandma answered and was confused so she said that Clare didn't live there and shut the door in my face! It turns out Clare had popped out to get a few things and when she arrived back, she found me wandering around in her street not knowing if I'd got the wrong address - she had to let me in and her Grandma said sorry and then she hid upstairs. Old people, eh?!  Anyway, we went for lunch at Zizzi's and it was delish'! Good choice C! After that we went to the cinema to see Kill Bill 2 and we decided to spoil ourselves and go "Gold Class". This basically means free popcorn, huge reclining leather armchairs that you can curl up in and being able to take beer in to the cinema with you. It was lovely and what a corker of a film.  When the film finished we went into the arcade for a while and played on the Dancemat Euromix (or whatever it's called) - Well, I am going to Hong Kong and I hear that the streets are paved with flashing tiles and I'll want to blend in - I don't want to look like a tourist now, do I?!  After that we played a bit of Air Hockey (suffice to say, I rock at Air Hockey!) and then made our way back to Clare's house and met her folks - I now know where she get's it from.  That was it really - It was nice to see you both again. I just hope you've stocked up on enough monkey hugs to see you through to next year.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a fab weekend which starts, as in most cases, on Friday evening.  I got back to the Farm and before I had even put my bag down, my niece and nephew (Jack and Jasmine) had me under their control. After a run around with the sheep in the paddock, they had fun with water baloons at bath-time, I read them their bedtime stories and then put them to bed. Little did I know but that took 4 hours and I was knackered!  I invited Fred and Carr to come over to the Farm as we had planned to burn things in proper Caveman fashion. We stacked the bonfire at least 8ft high and threw some petrol on top for good measure. It was lots of primitive fun and suffice to say - It's still burning now - 4 days later!  Anyway, when it got to about midnight we were all pretty smashed and we all had a spiffing time! (Paul Carr - You needs to redeem yourself or your mother will never forgive you.)  Saturday was special for two reasons: 1. It was Fred's Birthday and 2. It was the last day of the Football Season and as Plymouth Argyle were already declared as champions, they were due to have the Cup presentation after their home match.  It was all good fun too and I pretty much stayed out after the football to meet Fred and everyone else in town.  Everyone was wasted by the time I met them and I was glad that I was able be the most coherent of the group for a change!  Sunday was over before I knew it as I was helping out on the farm all day and then ended up burning more things.  Sorry the update is a bit wishy-washy. I will try and be more focussed for the next update which should include: a trip to Brum/ a trip to Cornwall and my Itinerary for the Big Trip.  P.S. I am bricking it at the moment - Not mentally prepared at all yet - Aaaaaarrrrghh!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm desperately sorry to everyone who is expecting some sort of wondrous update full of interesting stories of my past week but time is limited so I will have to keep it brief.  First of all, by the power of osmosis and thanks to some people jogging my memory, I can fill in some of the blanks from last friday night - Apparently, I was intent on power-bombing Matt Ford through the Pool table (sorry)/ My brother put his fingers down my throat to make me sick as I didn't want the Almighty White Russian in my system (oo-er!), and when I started, I couldn't stop - It was everywhere but in the toilet bowl(sorry Royworld)/ and finally, Dave Pin-Up kindly offered me a lift home (at 10.30pm!) and when I was undressed in my room (with only my party-boy thong on) I declared "Let's Go Streaking!!!" or words to that effect.  At present, I am in work (Gasp!) at Lang and Potter - I haven't actually had a day away from work yet. I am fitting curtains N' Stuff at The Whitsand Bay Hotel - Things could be worse I suppose. I'm also nearly ready for my travels - I've got my bag packed and all I have to do is get my money changed into Hong Kong Dollars!  Gotta go, Grannybags (My Mum) needs to use her PC - Tonight should be fun - I'm going to set up a bonfire and burn lots of things!  I'll update y'all early next week - I promise!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As some of you know, there are some people that I will be glad to see the back of, and Owain is no exception.  I have promised him that I won’t get soppy in this tribute but rest assured, I am typing this with a tear in my eye.  To give Owain justice in such a short blurb would not be possible – He is a unique individual as many people will back me up on (Unique is not latin for asshole). However I will do my best to summarise:  I’ve known Him for a long time and when he moved into “The Haven” in November last year, we were a force to be reckoned with, as he’s just as sick in the head as me.   My sanity took a downward spiral when the heavy drinking began, but that also coincided with the 14 hour days we were committing ourselves to at work. We would go out quite often and terrorise work colleagues, acquaintances and anyone who got caught in the cross-fire really. Matt Ford is still a shadow of his former self.  If I could list his major achievements over the last year they would be –  - Inventing the O-Bomb  – Not so much a drink but more of an initiation – he wowed the crowds when he had an ultimate-Bomb comprising of over 14 shots of vodka and 2 blue WKD – Bravo! - Ditching the wife  – it was for the best.  - Coming up with some of the best hair brained schemes  – Dressing gown day – Antiquing Paul Gray – The Meatshake – The Superman Impressions with the office chairs – and the Pirate costume for the January Ball to name but a few. - For being such great support when I broke my leg  –Dressed up as Santa Claus, totally pissed wandering around the hospital - Dropping his beard in the toilet – and the cherry on top was that he had a morning glory that was such a distraction, a nurse had to put a blanket over it! -And finally for generally being a damn good partner in crime.  Fell free to put these in your CV, Owzy-O.  Some people can find his foot-tapping, whistling, singing and general existence to be a bit annoying, especially in work, but you learn to love the crazy fruitloop. However, his culinary skills still need fine tweaking as, although he can rustle up some mighty fine meals, his resourceful can run wild at times and he has a habit of liquidising failed projects and then eating them.  I’m sure there are 101 more stories but my hangover has just kicked in so all I can say is – I will miss you my dear friend and you can come and visit me anytime.   If you want to keep on top of Owain’s progress he has, what he calls, his “staying put notes” journal – it’s  owainglanaman.blogspot.com  – It’s got some welsh in it but don’t let that put you off.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My last day was an emotional one for me - I promised myself I wouldn't cry so I didn't.  The only thing I remember from work is Antiquing the Boss during my leaving speech (i.e. dousing in flour). Paul Gray - you fuckin' rule! - you took it like a man. However, you're reputation will be tarnished forever.  Then came the Leaving Do at Spin/ Royworld..............  What the fuck happened there then!??! Getting me to down a jug of White Russian with 14 vodkas in it! All I can say is - Paul Gray - you got me back - it's 1-1 but this game isn't over!  Thank you, thank you, thank you to everyone who came out (including you Perry - Hee hee!). I was touched that so many people turned up - I would have been crying my eyes out if I wasn't being sick all over myself!  Best of luck in the future to everyone I've known in Cardiff and I will return - you ain't seen the last of me (unless I die which is possible but not worth thinking about).  Keep reading and keep in touch if you can.   The Man has gone but the Legend remains............
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As I'm up early, I thought I'd add to yesterdays update:  On our large walk around the metropolis that is KL, we were accosted by some news reporters who were getting a photo for the paper warning tourists of general dangers to tourists and of the proper way of wearing your bags so as not to get them pilfered. Malaysian celebrity status awaits.  I didn't fancy doing the meal thing with the group last night (even though it was delicious, cheap and there was a film crew there, apparently!) so myself and Kim, went to have some foot reflexology enacted on ourselves - man, was it painful! But, I am now the proud owner of two new feet - I wonder if they were able to sort out the smell? It was well worth it.  I basically chilled out after that with another Bombay Sapphire and went to sleep soon after as I am struggling to stay conscious in this immense heat!  For the second night running, Tom has been courtious enough to harass me when he gets back in at "what the f_____" o'clock. The previous night, he attempted to set fire to my feet, and last night, he was pushed into the room by Vicki and Stuart who both looked ecstatic to be giving drunksitting duties back to me, as they sprinted down the corridor in glee. Tom then dissapeared for 10 minutes and came back completely naked! What's that about?! I did pretend to be asleep though as he attempted to get into his bed and failed miserably and landed on his face! I wonder if he'll be missing a few teeth today?  I woke up early again and had lunch with a camp filipino fella called Elmer. He lives in Dubai and he's super.....thanks for asking!  I go to Melaka today where it is supposed to be even hotter........I can't wait!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I arrived In Kuala Lumpur yesterday and, to be honest, I've been a bit of a nonce as I'm still aching from the jungle trek - another early night for me then!  Before I did flake out on the reliably piss proof bed, we went to the Chinatown for a meal (which was lush!) and then on to the famous night market. It was bigger than any market I've been to, including the one in the carpark of Tesco's at Lee Mill.....on a sunday!  Cue the heckling and me being terribly British, looking at something and then saying "No thank-you, it's a piece of tacky shit".  I woke up this morning to find that KL is an amazingly hot city and it has beautiful, modern architecture, including the KL tower which is the 4th largest communications tower in the world, and the Petronas tower which are rather large and pant-wettingly spectacular.  We stopped off for a bit of lunch and then made our way to the newly constructed shopping mall of Times Square. The main feature of this mall/hotel is that it has a theme park inside of which I went on all the rides and screamed and whooped like I was 5 years old - the only thing that made me come to terms with reality after that, was the ticket/tag on my wrist that told me I was an adult!  Tonight, I will mostly be drinking Gin and we have all been invited to May's (from Cameron Highlands) house for a pool party. Should be fun!  P.S. Carr-magedden sounds scary! So, please people, take it seriously. I hear his "Furry" is quite formidable!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I awoke after only a few hours sleep and, being the control freak that I am, I made sandwiches and bought rations for everyone going on the jungle trek, which meant I had to sacrifice the prospect of breakfast - A minor setback.  Our guide, Kali, arrived at 8.30am and we basically just started walking behind our guesthouse and we were in the wilderness in no time!  Kali is 61 years old but he would put everyone I know to shame as he walks over 25km of rainforest every day and he can chop a tree down with his bare hands! (well, with a great big knife/machete but it still puts Norman Ballantyne's mum to shame!).  The trek was very hard going but so enjoyable - I realised just how unfit I am and I now fully appreciate what hiking boots are for.   The first leg of our trip was dense rainforest that is thousands of years old. I was walking behind Kim who had a severe problem with her cheap-ass sandals that she bought to do the trek, as they got muddy and her feet just went straight out the toe when we were going downhill! This made us a bit of a liability but, we got to the Boh tea plantation within a few hours.  On the way there were all sorts of interestings sights such as rattan trees (if thats what they're called!), bamboo forests and pitcher plants, which are known sometimes as monkey cups - I much prefer monkey cups personally.  The tea plantation was good as we drank several gallons of tea before we went out into the wilderness again! Oh, how I've missed tea!   The next leg was a little bit toasty as we were walking through the plantation at the hottest time of the day. I picked some tea and got a bit carried away and we then came across one of the local villages within the plantation. I was prepared and I brought some toys to give to the local children - I was like santa (but just a little bit more perverted than him - thank god I wasn't Mrs Santa again!). The kids were all a bit crazy but it was interesting to see that there are villages that live so basically and yet so close to civilised/ modern society.  After the village we set off into the jungle again and spirits were low as we all hadn't eaten for a while. Thankfully we stopped but if I went any further, I don't think  would have had a choice in the matter as my legs nearly fell off!  We made our way to the waterfall nearby after lunch and boy, was that a relief - I was baking hot so I just jumped right in. As it was very cold, my body reacted in the only way it knows how. I haven't been able to find "Junior" since that moment but I'm sure he'll find his way home!  The last part of the trip was on the road. which was nice as my limbs had wasted away to just stumps. After asking our guide how many kilometres we had covered during our trek, he said that it was at least 20km! (We told everyone it was 30km, because exaggeration is acceptable in these circumstances).  I had nothing to say to anyone that evening after showering and sewing my feet back on as I had lost the ability to communicate. I slept for a long time after that and dreamt of Indiana Jones getting his ass whupped by Kali, our guide. It seemed so real!?  That was that really - Rob - If you dont called that Indy style adventure, then tough ball bags to you, mate! However, I don't remember him picking tea in Malaysia. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The last thing I remember about Penang is an old man crushing coke cans on the pavement for over 3 hours (I passed him 3 times on that last day and I was beginning to feel like I was in a time warp!) - In a funny kind of way, that's how I'll always remember Penang - A little strange.  I slept through my alarm, as per usual, and myself and Tom (who reminds me more and more of Gareth from The Office - it's very difficult to talk to him now!) scurried our way downstairs to liase with the others and catch the coach to the Cameron Highlands.  It was a 6 hour journey. Some dreaded the thought of trying to sleep on a bumpy old journey like that one, so, instead, I played all of the cheesiest songs on my I-Pod and sung my heart out with, my tune-killing-partner-in-crime, Kim. Allsorts was played including Backstreet Boys, N*Sync, songs from Musicals (Annie, Grease), Bonnie Tyler, and of course, Jordan Knight to name just a few. Most people just shook their heads in disbelief and pretented to be asleep, but I'm sure I saw a couple of feet tapping!  Thanks to Kim and the I-Pod the journey only felt like 30 minutes and we were glad to be in the village of Tanah Rata, where it is beatiful and so much less bustling than Penang.  We arrived at our lodgings (the Hillview) and it is a really nice place to stay - despite the walls being very thin, its a lot easier to socialise because of their lounge rooms on each floor.  The first thing I heard when we arrived at the Hillview was "Puppies!", at which I thought I'd stumbled upon Jerry "the King" Lawler on holiday in Malaysia, appreciating a woman's finer points! However, it was actually because the guesthouse had two puppies here that are so cute, I was tempted to eat one of them. If I ate both, that would just be greedy! They were adorable though and I have a picture of me holding them which could be on every 14 year old girls bedroom wall next year.  Our first port of call was to have a nice cup o' tea as the area we are in is one of the main tea plantations in Malaysia. Oh how I've missed a good cup of tea and, even better, I had a slice of lemon cheescake that possibly made me wet! As it's my last day here today I may go and ask for a whole cake for my impending journey.  After showering up and getting myself all beautiful looking, we went for a meal in the village and we all had something called a Steamboat - What is that I hear you cry? Well, it's basically a big pot of stock put in the middle of the table and we throw everything we want in it (squid, prawns, chicken, beef, jellyfish, eggs, mushrooms, noodles and much more). It was great fun as it was virtually a food fight but what was better was watching the other table not really getting the concept of it, as if an alien spaceship was on the table, or a copy of the Koran.  We all got quite tipsy that night and we all met a couple, Phil and May, from our guesthouse and drank for a long while. At one point we had 70's Disco Duel where we would compete with songs we had on my I-Pod and her CD player and would halt the other by shouting "Cut the Music!". Subsequently there were complaints the next morning and there is now an 11pm curfew. Whoops!  On my next update, will be my account of Trekking through the rainforest and more tea.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally left Thailand yesterday morning on the night train from Surat Thani (wasnt that a Bryan Adams song?). I was glad to be leaving Thailand really as, although it is an interesting and friendly country, it is a bit stinky and there are some unsavoury/freaky characters about (not just ladyboys but on the ferry back from Kho Pha Ngan there were a few people just shadowing you as you walked about on deck and they would just smile and laugh when you look at them!). Im glad that I have seen the things I have seen though.  Arriving in Penang is the first sniff of adventure I've had for a week or so as I have had no expectations or ideas about what Malaysia would be like. I've come to realise that it is, so far, very colonial. There is a lot of westernisation here but they embrace many cultures which makes it a very interesting destination. There is a mix of Indian, chinese and Indonesian cuisine which is great (this means a lot to me, obviously) and the people are all so friendly - They know a lot of our slang words and it's a little un-nerving when the receptionist calls me luv!  Penang reminds me very much of certain areas of Hong Kong. It's not as clean but it's got it's own charm. As Malaysia is a muslim country there is a requirement to dress less slutty for women and to not show so much skin. In respect of this culture I have decided to wear ALL of my clothes so as not to offend anyone however, this means that I'm sweating like a blind lesbian in a fish market.  I have spent a lot of my time in Penang in the Main shopping centre as I can't be bothered with that walking malarkey in the tropical sun.  Last night was my first night in Malaysia and I thought I'd get a bit of sleep before meeting the rest of the group for dinner at 8.30. However, I slept for too long in the hotel room despite Tom shaking me and Wesley trying to ring me to wake me up. When I did surface it was 10pm and I was little confused at to where everyone was and why they didnt wake me up!  By chance I found out where they were eating and I went to catch up with them. Sadly, I was unable to eat all of the leftovers from my fellow group members (as is expected as I am a human dustbin) as they had eaten long before I arrived so I had to actually pay for a meal - How selfish of them!  After the meal we went to a bar called Slippery Senoritas over the road and there was a band playing covers of virtually every genre of music ever.....and they were pretty good too. The female singer was hot to trot and one of the singers was persistent with his air guitar solos that at one point I thought he had an invisible guitar!  As England were playing Portugal in the Quarter finals of Euro 2004, I decided to throw caution to the wind and get a little tipsy. Subsequently I cut some hefty slices into that dancefloor and some of the girls on the tour will be changed forever as they have now been "Egged" - Potter Style (It's a dancemove that is somewhat of an icebreaker, especially if it's on an ice rink)!   Myself and Tom stayed in the bar to watch the game (which almost made we ashamed to be up at 5am watching my nations football team pull a "dominici style" Faux Pas ....again!) and the tipple of choice was JD followed by a whole bottle of Hennesseys Cognac. Tom was being sick down himself (and the bouncer) in no time which allowed me to rib him for being an absolute sissy.  In a bizarre twist he paid me to wear his slightly stained T-Shirt as he wanted to chat up the malaysian girls accross the bar - I thought that was easy money but the downside was that people thought that I was english yob puke covered scum.  We didn't get to sleep until 6am, so I am a little fragile today and a bath and a curry await me back at the hotel.  Tomorrow, I leave for the Cameron Highlands and will partake in some jungle trekking. So, I may be wrestling tigers and getting monkeys pissed before you know it.  As a final note, I would like to thank Dave (The Torr Farm Guinea Fowl Assassin) as my mother tells me you're an avid reader, and to Dawn for printing it out for Webby as he can't get his thumb out of his bum and get to a computer.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My tour started last thursday and we all went out to watch the England v Switzerland game. It was good to see that sort of result but I also learnt a few things: Tom is a raging alcoholic and I'm going to have my hands full for the next few weeks, and, after speaking to Rebecca, I have learnt that embryo porn and skullfucking are not suitable subjects for conversation (Thanks, Fred - You've left your mark).  The next day I was up at 6am to leave Bangkok to go to the Bridge over the River Kwai and see the Death Railway - cheery stuff eh? Sadly, I never had enough time to see Pussy Ping Pong at Pat Pong.  Our guide for the tour was called Rudy and was the campest man I've met since Big A (Adam Taylor). He was good fun and kept me on my toes.  Our first stop was the floating market which was interesting but not quite what I expected. After that we saw some woodcarving at a workshop in which, I think, I was the only person interested.  Next stop was the Death Railway which everyone thought was the Bridge over the River Kwai - I kept on saying that it was a rehearsal for the real thing but everyone already thinks that I'm just a smartarse anyway. Then we actually visited the bridge in question so I took a photo.  The cemetery and the Jeath Museum was morbid stuff which halted any renditions of "The sun'll come out tomorrow" or "Little Spanish Flea" on the return trip on the minibus.  That evening we caught the night train to Surat Thani and then, in the morning, the ferry to Kho Pha Ngan. Thankfully, there have been no tropical storms but only blissful sunshine since we've been here.  Our first night was spent getting hammered and after drinking a bottle of room temperature red wine (and the rooms are pretty hot here!) I was reluctantly coerced into going for a midnight swim. There was phosphorescence in the water though which is like having little fairy lights in the water (you've all seen the Beach, so you must know what I mean).  The next day we all went on a snorkelling trip but it was second best to a good dive. We all crisped up nicely though and I'm just one shade off being the sexiest British black man ever (After Ryan Giggs, of course).  Yesterday I went for Dive 5 and 6 at Sail Rock which is 18km out at sea from Kho Pha Ngan. It was good diving, despite the visibility being only 5-10m as we descended through a chimney in the coral which was amazing stuff.  For the last 2 mornings, I have been up to watch the sunrise at 5.30am and I think there may be something wrong with me. It is however, becoming my favourite part of the day as I have the entire beach to myself and it is so peaceful.   Anyway, next stop is Penang in Malaysia. Culture awaits.  In response to the messages left recently:   my oneness has not yet been found as I'm still too fat - I'm down to twoness.  Also, Aural sex is entirely under-rated. Go for it Paul.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Tour from Bangkok to Singapore has now officially started, but before I update you on my adventures, I want to describe my first impressions of the other 15 people on the tour:   Wesley  (American) - The tour leader - Has an uncontrollable addiction to coffee.   Rebecca  (Lincolnshire, UK) - The baby of the group and has scuffed knees and a boyfriend she doesnt care about.   Tom  - (Ipswich, UK) - As previously stated - a liability is an understatement - the sacrificial lamb of the group and sharing a room with him is interesting. Yesterday he locked the key in the room twice and he has a habit of sleeping at the end of the bed like a dog.   Kim, Joanne, Jennifer and Iona  (Scotland) - All very quiet so far - something to hide perhaps?   Vicky and Stuart  (Northern Ireland) - funny people who like to unwind after a few drinks with a few more drinks.   Miles  (Swindon, UK) - The self proclaimed early riser but I've been up at 5.30am for the last two mornings and I haven't seen him around?!   Dave  (Essex, UK) - Say no more - a veritable dog on heat and otherwise a very funny bloke.   Natalie and Francisco  (Melbourne, Australia) - Opposites attract as Frank is quiet and introvert and Nat is chatty and extrovert (filthy mind as well).   Cena  (Lucerne, Switzerland) - she's finding it difficult to understand the many different english accents, but then again - so am I.    Chris  (Scotland) - He has the driest humour ever and I find myself close to wetting myself on occasions. Red as a beetroot in this sunshine which proves that scottish people should leave their homeland at their own peril.  The group has already split into two definite groups: The quiet types who keep themselves to themselves generally, and the other half is extroverted and portraying defensive behaviour at times (I.e. Toms talks bullshit as defense, Dave starts humping anything that moves and Rebecca pulls the sympathy card by falling down some steps and scarring herself for life).  Myself? I'm auditioning for the role of, possibly bi-sexual, loner - I'll keep 'em guessing for now as probably most of the people who read this website (all 3 of you) have your suspicions too. I've already rebelled against one outing but boredom ensured that I slept for many hours while they were gone.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The day of the Euro 2004 clash between England and France came and it was stormy on Ko Chang. Subsequently, I played cards all day and Roy (from Israel) was duped into a game of "Skinhead", which is like shithead but the loser get's his head shaved. Of course, he lost and I shaved him silly! To prove I would do it in good will I also offered to cut Stacey's fringe but made a bit of a mess of it! Because of that, Roy didn't trust me throughout the entire ordeal.  The game happened......and, boy was I dissapointed! The good thing was that the locals and the owners of Nature Beach were throwing plenty of whiskey and rum around so I was able to drown my sorrows.   The locals (Dar, Tos, Joe and San) have been so friendly here other than just free drinks - There's a guy called Keith from Newcastle who lives behind the huts and I mistakedly gate-crashed his house when I saw that he had a pool table - I thought it was a pub! So nice though and it cost him next to nuppence to build the house and buy everything in it.  San and Joe run the bar and they do a brilliant cockney accent! San is also the spitting image of Pharrell Williams from N*E*R*D!  I met a canadian girl called Terri who was very nice but was quite anti-english when the football came on.   The day after the game, most people had left the Island and I had to fend for myself.  I had my last 2 dives and completed my Open Water Course which was good to have under my belt. However, that morning, they were exploding bombs underwater (for safety reasons) that had been left dormant for years. That would explain the ground shaking at 8am then! It also brought up lots of silt and mud from the seabed and visibility was poor. My instructor said afterwards though that I was the only person on Ko Chang diving that day and if I can dive in those conditions, I can pretty much dive anywhere!  After my diving I basically read my book in the restaurant and some Thai girls (Hada and Jula) were on holiday and I spent the afternoon with them. It turns out that they work on the island and do massage a few beaches up so I got all sorts of massage freebies! Nice!  My last day on Ko Chang, was on Tuesday and it rained all day so I slept in the hammock until the evening. My bag packing was rudely interrupted by a typhoon hitting the island and all the power went so I was sat in the dark in my room with coconuts hitting the roof!  Eventually the power did come back on and I watched the Football and was chatting to a girl called Cassandra from Singapore. I had recollections of Wayne's World and I couldn't work out if I was Garth or Wayne!? She is very nice though and I will try and meet her when I get to Singapore.  As I didn't want to be stranded on Ko Chang when my trek from Bangkok to Singapore starts (on the 17th June - Today!), I left for Bangkok a day early.  Places aren't nearly as bad the second time around and I ended up having a really good night in Bangkok. I found the hotel where the trek starts and stopped for a coffee in a cafe just outside. There I met Fran, Vicky and Laurelle who are all from Reading and are in Thailand for a month. I ended up being their guide for Banglahmpu and around Khao Sarn Road as they had just arrived. We all had a nice meal and ended up getting drunk in Silk's Bar which was playing some "Proper Bo" music - All old school hip hop and house stuff - and the Spain v Greece game. I stumbled home after the game but not before a Thai bloke bought me a drink and we chatted about the football - turns out he was a policeman!  I've checked into my hotel now and it's the most luxury I've experienced since The Farm! There's even hot water - Hurrah!  I'm sharing a room with a guy called Tom from Ipswich who is, as he puts it, a liability - but other than that, I think he just knows how to have a good time!  I have to get back to the hotel now for the briefing but there will be an update soon as I arrive in Kho Phan Ngan in a few days.  (Oh, by the way, Dorian is a spiky (not Pikey!) fruit which loads of people eat here but is smells like vomit and doesn't taste much better - Subsequently, most hotels have a ban on them as it stinks the place out!)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've started a diving course at Bang Bao and after breezing the test and final exam and then doing the basics in the pool, I've now got 2  sea dives under my belt too.  I found it hard to equalize the pressure in my ears at first but I got the hang of it in the end and did one dive that was 14m down for 61 minutes and then the 2nd dive was 12m for 41 minutes. However, the thing to write home about is on my first dive, I was lucky enough to have about 12m visibility and I was swimming with and even touched a turtle! No sign of empty pizza boxes or a rat in a kimono but it was definitely an amazing sight.  I have felt an urgent need to urinate when surfacing too - must be a serious case of compressed bladder syndrome!  The last 2 dives today has been postponed because of storms at sea and, apparently, being struck by lighting with an aluminium tank on your back is not good!  As hoped, I have met quite a few new people at the Nature Beach Resort where I am staying:   Francesca and Stef  - A swiss couple who went diving with me on my 3rd day.   Adam, Hannah and Laura  - They are all from England but Adam has been living just outside Amsterdam for the last few years and has come out for a holiday and to give advice to his sister, Laura.   Yol, Bob and Simon  - The Welshies (Sorry Owzy but there there from the North so please forgive me!) Boys who definitely like their booze.   Paul  - The biggest "Shithead" I've met out here! But only because that's the card we've been playing while it's been raining! He's from Belfast and I hope to meet up with him in Sydney as he's living there at the moment and he's a cracking good laugh.   Roy  - From Israel and he's a scream! He says things that not even Oram would dare to say at the risk of sounding insane. He's been affectionately called "my little Roy Toy".   Toni and Nicolas  - Nicolas is from Thailand and has been living in England - Toni is Greek and a plenty nice guy - He's also been living in England (Luton) for a good few years and he was very pleased when Greece beat Portugal last night! What a shocker!  And Finally,  Stacey and Kate  - Both from Kent and are away for a year. They were in India before Thailand and they have been a Godsend in terms of being able to just really chill out - I've even tried to teach them Shitty Liz/ Black Maria but it proved a bit too much. Kate will never forgive me for bringing it up but she's also related to the Chuckle Brothers! To me - to you - to me - to you! (Sorry!)  On top of meeting all these people I have also been playing a little bit of volleyball and football with a group of 28 Thai kids (age 15-17) and they were really friendly, even though I kicked their arses (shades of the oppression of the good old days of the English Empire - I did what Queen Vic could never do!).  Basically everything is still great here despite the weather being a bit pants. There are wild dogs on the beach that act as a protection agency for the beach huts, but one dog stands out mainly because it is as big as a house! "Sausage" is heavily pregnant and a royal pain in the ass at night as it becomes quite erratic and it often sits in a Buddha pose and attepts to bite her ears, Joey Deacon style.  Anyway, going to be watching England v France tonight so looking forward to a bit of a tense game and many, many beers!  P.S. Forgot to mention before that my last day in Hong Kong I had a Facial and fell asleep but I felt like a new man (and possibly more like a woman) after my massage and face pack - Thanks for paying the bill, Lisa - I'll make sure I repay the favour and buy you a Half Yarder if you ever go to Plymouth!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whew! What a day! I woke up really early because I thought it was midday already but it only turned out to be 7.30am! So, I had some breakfast and sat with Mike and Andy (From Arizona) as we contemplated the day ahead.   We decided it would be a good idea to get some scooters and cruise round the island as we all didnt want to go solo (i.e. crash with no-one to pick up the pieces) - however, I have never been behind the wheel of a motorcycle so I was a little nervous. It only costs 3 quid for the day - Cool, huh?  So our first destination was Ban Bang Bao at the southernmost tip of the Island which has a huge pier with loads of fish stalls and bars - very rustic - it was also better to go south as there was less traffic down there so I could get my practice on the 2-wheeled beast!  I found a place that will do an Open Water Diving Course for about 120 quid and I start tomorrow morning - It's a 4 day course and the instructor is Belgian - should be very...........interesting.  After that we went straight to the northern tip of the island and as we went up we diverted to the waterfall that isnt far from the coast. We had to pay 200 baht each to see it but its only a small price to pay. When we got there it was very beautiful and I even got to have a swim in the river (There's a great picture I now have of me showing how a belly flop dive should be done).   After that we carried on going north and then followed the signs for the Elephant Camp. The road soon turned into a dirt track as we went inland and it was pretty messy as muddy puddles made me look like I had shit all over my trousers!  When we got there the Elephant camp was open and all 3 of us got to ride these mighty beasts on a trek through the woods. Mike and Andy had a guide on their elephant but my guide got off after about a minute and showed me how to get it to obey my orders - it was great! I was like Indiana Jones on his way to Delhi (No sign of the Holy Grail yet though, Rob - I think I took a wrong turn in Tangiers!).  On the way back we stopped off in a restaurant and had red snapper and it was absolutely delicious. Mike and Andy - Thanks for a great day in Ko Chang - It's been the best day here so far!  I Have to go now as my scooter needs to be taken back to Hostel and it's getting dark - see y'all soon, y'hear!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am currently sitting at the computer overlooking Lonely Beach on Ko Chang. It is absolutely lush here despite the fact that it's raining today. However, please allow me to continue where I left off last time:  After a tearful goodbye to Lisa and Hong Kong, I legged it to get my connecting flight to Bangkok via Singapore as I was sat in a Hotel bar about an hour before take off!  I flew with Singapore airlines who are, apparently, one of the better airlines in the world. However, I've become quite a snob since flying with Virgin but it it was good none-the-less. I have also decided to boycott airplane food as it is surely just bicarbonate of soda painted in different colours and makes your stomach balloon like Andrew Best's head!  When I arrived in Bangkok it was gone midnight and I shared a Taxi into Banglamhpu to find a hostel with a girl called Julia but she was quite clearly pissed out of her face and a bit freaky to boot - after finding a place (only 50p a night!) we went to get a couple of beers and chill. However, when we went up Khao Sarn Road all the bars weren't allowed to sell alcohol anymore and the hookers kept pinching my visibly erect nipples through my T-shirt - Whoa nelly!  The next morning, I decided that Bangkok was a bit too much of a stinky shithole of a place and I didn't want to be watching out for pickpockets and adam's apples all the time so I got on the first bus to Trat and then got the ferry over to Ko Chang Island. It was about 9 hours by the time we checked into the Treehouse lodge but I had met some interesting people along the way:  There was a french couple called Arianne and Fabrice who have travelled through Russia, China, Vietnam and Cambodia to get here - Sadly my french speaking of the week before has gone awry this time as I'm too damn tired to concentrate!  There is also a German called Maria and a Dutch girl called Daniella - They are really nice and friendly but sadly, Daniella got robbed last night and now has very little money left! That sucks big time!  Finally, on the bus, I met Mike and his 11 year old son, Andy, from Arizona. They are really friendly and I've had a good time over the last 2 days just hanging around with them. Mike has got a lot of travelling under his belt already but it's such a nice sentiment to take your child with you on a 3 month trip of South-East Asia.  Ko Chang is wonderful and I've already played a lot of frisbee and got a sooooper tan. I've moved up the beach a little bit and I'm paying a bit extra for a room (4 quid - big wow!) as it has more luxuries like lights, a fan, shower, toilet and a safety deposit box. It also opens straight onto the sandy part of the beach.  It's very cheap here and it's doing wonders for my budget - The food is really good and (fingers and legs crossed) I havent had that much spicy bowel action yet - The seafood is good as well as it's mostly freshly caught. there are many fit ladies here too but I stink of prawns and none of them will talk to me! There is also a ladyboy behind the bar which sparks up all sorts of "is s/he or isn't s/he?" conversations.  That's all for now but I'll keep you all posted of any major developments in my adventures soon.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have just checked my bag into the airport and I am waiting for my flight which is at 1830 hours. So, as I have a moment, I would like to reflect on my time here: It's been great! I could easily live here if circumstances were different but, my adventure must resume - who knows whats around the corner (most probably extreme tummy trouble and a ladyboy with a hand-stitched leather dildo!).   I have recently finished another book called  Way of the Peaceful Warrior  by Dan Millman and it has mentally prepared me for anything that the future may bring. It has made me realise that the place is  here  and the time is  now . The past and the future are not worth worrying about - it's being happy in the present that matters. If anyone gets a chance to read this book - do it! Your outlook on life  will  change.  OK, I realise that I sound like a hippy right now, but reading philosophy and reflective literature has given me insight and confidence in myself and my life.  Anyway, enough of that - when you next hear from me I'll be in Thailand with a stinking hangover, Dengue fever and I will possibly be the victim of an amourous thieving prostitute (Let's keep our fingers crossed shall we?!).  In response to the many comments: -  Fred  is God and  everyone else  (especially me) is scum. -  Sorry Whiteway!  Only Taxis and trams here - I've gone Cold Turkey (Bora Stylee) - Postcards will be sent -  Owzy-O  - The comment I made on your Blog was only acidic because you should only kick a man when he's trying to get back up - It's the rules!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I thought I would write just a few phrases I've learned since I've been out here (Forgive my spelling but I'm writing them as you would say them!):   Dong Suk Lo  - I am Lost  Am See Doe  - Do you think I dont Know? (useful with taxi drivers/con artists!)  Lung Lui  - Lovely Lady (Believe me - you'll use this one a lot!)  Suck My Tung  - Sweetcorn Soup (this one sticks in my mind though!)  Lido  - Here  Nam Chi  - Mens Toilets (Lui Chi for the Ladies!)  Fatty  - Faster  Gong sarm, gong say  - You're Talking Sh*t!  Do lay lo mo  - F**k you're mother's c**t! (Do not say this - seriously!)  I also have some chinese symbols for my name and other key words, and "Po" means "woman" in Cantonese! (It can be a bit confusing sometimes with all my hair, I know!)  Also please note that you can all add your own comments on my updates by clicking the comments button below. It'd be nice to know you're thoughts on my useless ramblings. (or you could e-mail me you lazy sods! Only Kidding!)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      .............and came down a sweaty and tired englishman!  Well, for those of you who don't know, I'm still in Hong Kong. The reason? - I like it here and Lisa has kindly asked me to stay another week. It's no biggie though as Thailand can wait and I'll be there for a good month besides.  As I've been able to chill out over the last week and take things easy - I've watched a lot of DVD's and I've read a couple of books -   As far as the DVD's go - I watched  O Brother, Where Art Thou?  (I'm a Dapper Dan Man too) which I loved -  As far as my Feet will Carry me  - A german film that I also thought was amazing -  The Heist  - Gen hackman doing what he always does and the female lead looked too much like Julian "Scary" Clary! - and I've also watched some chinese porn but I didn't know the name - it was more funny than erotic - great hair dos! (Hmmm?)  The books? well I have read  Stupid White Men  by Michael Moore - Very interesting, a little scary and a typical bloke - thinking he can fix anything - even something as complex as the IRA /Northern Island situation by simply converting the protestants to catholics! - What a nob! - The other book was  The Alchemist  by Paulo Coelho - Stunning read - simple plot and so enlightening for anyone who dares to travel and realise their dreams - (And it's only a short book too).  Since my last update I have been busy -   - I went up to Victoria Peak which had stunning views of Hong Kong Island and whilst at the summit, sipping my beer and writing postcards, I noticed the 3 gentlemen behind me speaking french so I said hello to them in their native tongue. It seems it was fully appreciated as they invited me to their table and force fed me loads of red wine. It turns out they were Swiss and I was able to continue the whole afternoon speaking french to them - C'est Incredible! Non? - That evening I met up with Lisa after work in the Peak Cafe and went to a vegetarian restaurant afterwards which is possibly one of the nicest meals I've had since I've been here! Don't worry - I couldn't possibly "turn" if I'm going to be back on the farm - I wouldn't dare! - I found a chinese Elvis! (I promised myself that I would find one in Las Vegas but it turns out I was on the wrong side of the Pacific! I've even got the photo to prove it!) The King Lives! - I have visited Lamma Island - It's sort of a hippy commune but there are no vehicles and I basically vegged on the beach and swam in the clear tropical waters - there was hardly anyone there - Bliss! However, I got quite sunburnt on the bits I couldn't reach so was a bit tender the next day! - And Finally, today I have been exploring the the New Territories around Hong Kong, which are very close to Mainland China - I starting walking on a hiking trail (Hence the Title of this update) and found amazing views and people doing Tai Chi everywhere. However, it was a bit of a weird day all in all:  - I was speaking to an elderly chinese gentleman who was very nice but he had quite extreme views - he stated that I should never trust a Jew as they would stab me in the back when I wasn't looking and that Hitler was "Forgiveable"! (However, he was comparing him to the previous Emperor of Japan who was like a "crazy dog", so I'm told)  - I was eating a meal with salted egg and I thought it tasted a bit peculiar and that maybe they'd salted it too much - then I realised I was eating the shell as well! D'oh! - and I was chatted up by......a giant, camp policeman! I was having a coffee waiting for my train when he started talking to me quite enthusiastically - he then revisited me 10 minutes later and gave me his address, his phone number and he begged for me to send him a postcard soon! What can I say!? I don't swing that way, baby!  Thats all for the moment - I promise you I will be leaving for Bangkok on Saturday even though I'd love to stay, but, my adventures await and I must punish my bowels in a new and interesting country. Ta-Ta!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We jumped in the jeep the next morning and tried to navigate our way to Timbis Beach for the paragliding course. Sadly, I had no idea where we were going!  After, finding my bearings a little bit, I did an illegal U-Turn and was caught out by a dodgy Indo copper. He fined me on the spot for 200,000 rupiah (15 pounds) and made his excuses to get us to pay him there and then! Dodgy or what!?  Thankfully, I've avoided the law since and done everything by the book (if there is one!).  We got to Geger beach to meet Bernard (we were only 1 hour late) and he asked if we wanted to go via the shortcut to the glide site, but its a bit bumpy&nbsp;- as it was a beat up Jimny I was driving, we thought hell yeah!  He wasn't joking when he said it was bumpy! It was great fun to drive but it was very off-road and I now have no testicles left. I was a bit worried that we did the car some damage but then again - who cares!  As the dive site was at a place called Timbis Beach, I thought to bring a towel and I could sunbake a little while Lisa did her ground controls. However, there is no real beach to speak of - it's just arid land! But, the views are spectacular and I get a chance to do some reading and laugh at Lisa falling on her ass on regular occasions.  on a tangent - my favourite mis spelling I have seen in Bali is a shop claiming it was a monkey changer(Carr-maggeden perhaps?). 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The&nbsp;day after Lisa arrived, we chilled by the pool and sunbaked for a while until we felt the burn. I, of course, am quite used to the heat but Lisa was a little bit rouged from it all so we rested in the shade chatting to Glen and Trig until evening time.  We went back down to the pagoda bar at Kuta Puri Bungalows to meet the other Aussies and the Welshies. It was a generally nice evening which was spent getting drunk and losing people along the way.  Sadly, two things marred the night. One was that Lisa walked passed a parked motorbike and burnt her leg badly on the exhaust pipe, and two was that Trig took us to Paddy's which was wall-to-wall prostitutes and an overall meat-market, which isn't quite what I came away for (just like Jesters on Union Street! Ugh!).  Trig also showed himself to be very reminiscent of Dan Wood (of the Shaolin-Funk) in that he has a party trick called the drum which involves his bal bag and a tube of pringles (I'll never eat them again!) and he has an uncanny knack to insult people without even trying. Bless!  Lisa's&nbsp;paragliding course was due to start the next day so we went and found out where it was all supposed to take place and&nbsp;got a taxi to&nbsp;Geger Beach by Nusa Dua to meet Bernard, the Instructor (say his name in a french accent).  After meeting him and going through the course details, he said that he had to dash to do some tandem dives and that we should get a taxi to Agun Payung. So we hired a taxi and he got terribly lost and refused to go all the way to the paragliding site because it was too bumpy! What a cheek!  Anyway, we got there eventually as some guys gave us a lift n their bikes in which I nearly lost a testicle as it  was  very bumpy! Lisa spent a&nbsp;while shitting herself, looking a all the people paragliding but then Bernard did a tandem flight with her to get her into the swing of things. She had to borrow my shoes though! Talk about unprepared! She did love it, but for me,&nbsp;jumping off cliffs is sooo 8 years ago&nbsp;(Treyarnon days). I will have a go sometime soon though (maybe today?!).  On the way back we managed to grab a lift with a guy who sorts out transport hire and has investment in a restaurant on Jimbaran Bay. So, he took us to the restaurant and for the second time that week, I watched the sunset. Again, it would have been a romantic evening if I wasn't with an mechanic Essex girl with a lemming-like tendency to jump off cliffs with a sheet above her head!  After eating, our driver took us to the airport to sort out hiring a jeep to get to and from the paragliding site. We managed to sort out a Suzuki Jimny for 9 quid a day - not bad? I drove his car back to the hotel as he needed to check the car over and change the oil. His car was great to drive but driving in Kuta isn't! Basically, there is no highway codes  especially  for motorbikes! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      (Owzy-O - I hope I spelt the title correctly.)  Well, on Monday, I spent most of my time by the pool as far as I can remember, but Glen had invited myself and Trigger to the Kuta Puri Bungalows down the road for a few drinks with some ...........more australians!  The nice thing was that they are possible some of the nicest, people I have met in the last few weeks - There was Dave (Vegetarian horse lover who looks like Willem Defoe), Dwayne (chisel jawed hollywood hardman type), Jeff (such a nice guy, but ashmatic) and there were others but I forget their names!  The shocking part was meeting two girls from Wales who, believe it or not, lived in Cyn-Coed - just 5 mins from where I used to live in Cardiff!  It was nice to catch up and talk about how bad the Philly is and having to avoid friday nights because of the Valleys descending on the Diff. They were impressed with my welsh swearing too - Thanks Owain!  We all went for a nice meal round the corner from the hotel and it was superb tucker! I had to leave early though as Lisa was arriving at the airport just before midnight.  I rushed back to the hotel and made a sign saying "Black-Belt Jones" on it in felt tip as I thought that there would be loads of people doing the same and she may not be able to see me. I was wrong! I was the only one there and I looked like a bit of a lemon but the moment was sheer comedy when she turned up to see me with the sign.  Now............the fun begins! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After my rant yesterday, I received a breath of fresh air by meeting a brummy fella called Trigger (he wouldn't tell me his real name because it's Luik Matthew Leo - he must be frightened of giving his real name but&nbsp;I stole a look at his drivers licence!).  &nbsp; I sat talking to him by the pool&nbsp;where I'm staying and it was nice to speak to someone who didn't mind me calling his mother a whore as a joke (Come on Aussies - chill out, yeah!?).  &nbsp; As I was feeling a little bit better, I took a risk and went for some seafood at Junbyren Bay (I have no idea how it's properly spelt) and we walked along the beach looking for a nice restaurant. We found a place where we managed to get a 20% discount which was good enough for me! I had the King Prawns which were immense and delicious.  &nbsp; The wierd thing was that the airport runway is at the end of the horizon on the beach so you can see people arriving and leaving on their jumbo steeds. &nbsp; We watched the sunset, I drank guinness by&nbsp;candlelight and a 5 piece band played Hey Jude for us in which we sang along like absolute losers -&nbsp;It would have been a really romantic&nbsp;evening if I wasn't with a 6'3" brummy with unmanagable hair! &nbsp; This morning I have been trying to sort out sending a package home&nbsp;(Christmas presents believe it or not!) and after phoning DHL who wanted to charge me 150 quid(!!!), I went to the post-office and sent the lot for&nbsp;15 quid instead. Whether it gets there or not is a different story though as they bundled it all up in a potato sack and threw it in the back room! &nbsp; Hopefully I'm going to be feeling well enough to do some Scuba diving soon and...............I'm just sending my photos out to the people that I have e-mail addresses of so .......enjoy and let me know what you think. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's the first time in 10 days that I've had an uninterupted night's sleep. &nbsp; It's the first time in 5 days that I've farted. &nbsp; It's the first time in 4 days that I've been able to have a piss standing up. &nbsp; And, it's the first time I've missed home (i.e. Britain) since I left, 2 months ago. &nbsp; The reason? Well, it's that time of year when I normally go to Bath to play volleyball in the sun. It's also because I'm a bit sick of&nbsp;Kuta Bay.&nbsp; &nbsp; If it was interesting I would be fine - but, it's full of arsehole surfers and people hawking after your money. The Balinese are nice enough but they all look like marmosets. The Australians are&nbsp;a mixed bag, but&nbsp;they can't help being a nation of steaming pissheads. The Americans haven't&nbsp;moved their fat asses out of&nbsp;McDonalds yet. And the English people here should know better and just stay at home and sleep with their sister. &nbsp; Kuta is now 2nd on my top 5 of worst places I've ever been (Don't worry Carr - Tangiers is No.1 by a long shot!). However, what I do know is that the rest of&nbsp;Bali is yet to be explored and I'm eager to go to Flores too as I've heard it's beautiful. &nbsp; This is hopefully my one whinging pohm moment and I hope to get over that when I have some worthwhile company (No offence to Ben, Purdey and Kim). Hell, anyone with a brain who doesn't think everything is gnarly will do! &nbsp; I watched an AFL (Aussie Rules Football) game today and I think I understood the rules! It was even partially enjoyable. Other than that, I'm just biding my time and saving some money (and my breath) until Lisa arrives tomorrow and we can get outta the hellmouth that is Kuta. &nbsp; I may apply for a job with the Tourist Office here but they may not like my attitude towards the place. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I watched Spiderman 2 and I think that Peter Parker is as gay a street full of lampposts - what a nob - I shouted at one time "just bone her you poof!" but it didn't go down that well. &nbsp; I had a few beers after that and played pool with Ben, Kim and Glen and I rock once more and pulled off some awesome shots. Those Aussies didn't know what hit 'em! &nbsp; Still feeling a bit ropey, I wandered back to the hotel, but as it had been raining quite hard for about 30 mins, all the streets were flooded so I had to walk the long way round and avoid malicious taxis trying to moisten my legs (that's a strange expression Bruce - I heard the Prime Minister say it, Bruce......). &nbsp; I tried to get to sleep but I was awoken in the night by Ben who had had his wallet pinched in the Bounty Bar by some Javanese tykes - he was shitting himself as it had his Visa Card in it and when he phoned up to cancel the card, they had tried to use it 3 times already! Luckily, they were unsuccessful every time. Ben was furious with himself though. &nbsp; This morning, Ben and Purdey went back home to Adelaide, so I sat by the pool with my bags, waiting to check into another room. It's a hard life you know! &nbsp; Scotty turned up after not sleeping in his bed - what a dirty stop-out! He brought back with him some Balinese surfing kids who terrorised the pool and ,not for the first time on this trip, I thought&nbsp;" this boy's a liability!". I'm glad that I'm going solo now so it's a good chance to chill out and avoid the streets. &nbsp; This afternoon, I ventured out and managed to watch the Wallabies get trounced by the All Blacks in the Tri-Nations. So funny to see, especially as a Brit who knows that it's just a mickey mouse tournament anyway next to the Six Nations. &nbsp; After that, I wandered with Kim to the beach and we just chilled out and watched the sunset. We then&nbsp;went to his Hotel and watched a bit of the Pool Championships n the telly so I'm fired up for a bit of pool action tonight as I'm sure I can do half of those shots! &nbsp; Don't worry - pretty soon these updates may become interesting as I can go as far as 1 hour away from a toilet. Things are going to start happening to me now........... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      .............mainly because the follow-through isn't far behind! &nbsp; Well after the "japanese meal" type updates from yesterday, I went with Benno and Scotty to play some serious air-hockey. However, it just seemed such a good idea for some vodka redbulls to get the games to be that bit more competitive. So, in true Owzy-O fashion, I fell off the wagon temporarily!&nbsp;(Owz - yes I am taking the piss but only because you're a true friend) &nbsp; The air hockey was ferocious and Scotty was deemed the champion but only by a whisker and I know deep in my heart that I won and one of my goals didn't tally on the scoreboard so...............I was robbed, goddamit!  &nbsp; We all had a bit off a sweat on so we stood back to watch authentic Balinese dancing being taught to some children.............outside McDonalds of all places! We went to Tubes to try and re-unite ourselves with the others but they weren't there. We started to watch King Arthur and after nearly falling asleep we decided to just go back to the hotel. &nbsp; It was eerily quiet there as it's away from the tourist trap of Kuta but that was a welcoming thought in the back of my mind. Ben was so tired he fell asleep early, but myself, Purdey and Scotty opted for a drop of JD and listen to a bit of music. &nbsp; After we polished off the bottle, the other two were all up for going out but I was hit with a serious bout of Bali Belly&nbsp;so I&nbsp;let them&nbsp;go on their own  without  parental supervision. &nbsp; I spent the night getting up every 30 mins to evacuate my bowels&nbsp;which isn't as good as sleeping, I can tell you! I'm still feeling terrible today so I've only ventured to the pub for a bit more food and a few games of pool with the locals. &nbsp; To my absolute surprise, Mike and his son, Andy, from Arizona, showed up at the bar looking for me and we caught up briefly on some travelling news from where we&nbsp;have been. I will be meeting them later on as well so there's more of that to come but&nbsp;it was so good to see some familiar faces instead of just more bloody&nbsp;Australians! &nbsp; I'm going to watch Spiderman 2 tonight inbetween my toilet trips so that should hopefully take my mind off things, but then again who knows! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Day 4 was an early start - we were up at 6.30am to get the ferry to Nusa Lembongen - an Island that isn't even on most maps! After shaking the Aussies into action we left and I had to quickly pack my overflowing backpack. I thought that wearing my boots would be a good idea to save space and the ferry must be from the pier so it'd be OK - I was wrong! I had to jump in the water to get on the ferry and everything got suitably soaked! Oh, well - worse things happen at sea you know!  The crossing was surprisingly calm and we (i.e. Me, Ben, Purdey, Scotty, Kim and Travis (an emotionally fragile oz-e who was trailing Purdey)) arrived at Lombongen and it is so different from the Kuta Vortex that I had just been spat out of - so chilled and a good chance for me to recover.  That evening, we went to see Danny, who owns the Lembongan Bumgalows further up the beach from where we were staying, and it was his 50th birthday. His indonesian girlfriend ha set up a BBQ which was quite frankle the nicest food I've had all year! It was such a chilled atmosphere and it was just what I needed.  The next two days I spent sat back and tried to recover from my cracked heels, lost voice and pounding headache - however I also managed to pick up a bad case of Bali-Belly and I burnt the roof of my mouth so badly that it's been bleeding for the last 2 days - What a whinging Pohm I am!  Yesterday was my last day on Lembongan and I was still felling absolutely rotten so I did nothing but sit in the Sukanusa Bar eating Prawns and we watched Dead Man starring Johnny Depp and I thought it was the most freaky, funny, trippy film I've seen in ages - definitely one I recommend and it's quite an old film too I think.  Today, I feel a lot better but I'm still doing an Owzy special and I'm "on the wagon". We came back to kuta and were staying in a luxury hotel called the Masa Inn with lush swimming pools and Air con - the works - it's only 5 quid each - Haha!   My next few days will be spent watching films, shopping and lounging by the pool until Lisa arrives on monday night. The search for sanity continues...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Day 1   Our first port of call is a pub called Tubes - it's really nice there where there are films played through the day, pool tables and good food and cheap beer.   We first met Kim, an Aussie Paul Hogan lookie-likey, who we played pool with and drank copious amounts of Bintang Beer. My pool playing seems to be great between my 2nd and 7th pint but after that, it all goes downhill.  Our next venue was the mushroom bar for some mushroom shakes - I didn't go too far on that one but it still messed my head up - couple that with the fact that Ephedrin is over the chemist's counter here and that's when you start to worry!  We went back to Tubes for some food but we were all a little drunk and were pissing ourselves watching Seabiscuit (which is shit by the way) as the subtitles descibed one of the horses actions as nickering! Well - you live and learn, eh? Everyone else watching it didn't appreciate our raucous behaviour anyway, so we went to the Bounty Bar.  At this bar they had an Open Mic night where I decided to sit it out and scope out the competition. We drank drinks called Jam Jar's and Illusion Shakers which are full of Arak - a Balinese rice wine - and it is potent stuff!  I basically spent the next 6 hours dancing until my feet bled and watching Scotty pissing on the dancefloor - damn Aussies! They've got no manners - at least do it at the bar where no-one can tell!   Day 2   I Woke up at noon and went straight to Tubes where I skulled/downed my first beer - what a mistake! - I can't remember what happened in the next 9 hours but I'm sure some nickering was going on!  I've been reliably informed that I watched an Aussie Rules football game and didn't know what the hell was going on and I thought about getting a tattoo on my back! Don't worry Mum - I didn't get one.  In the evening I watched The Punisher and it just proves that John Travolta will never relive the days of Staying Alive and "just strutting". We went back to the Bounty Bar and I plucked up the courage to since All Night Long by Lionel Richie - however, with the amout of Arak I had drunk previously, my voice had nearly gone and it would have been embarassing if I knew what I was doing or where I was!  The only other notable feature of the night was nearly getting in a fight with a Norwegian who I accidentally knocked his drink into his lap - I talked my way out of it though but not before Ben saying "If we weren't already outside, I'd ask you to step outside". Norway didn't appreciate me pissing myself at that one.   Day 3   Well, technically it was still day 2 as I didn't sleep that night and went to some Aussie Grommets pool and drank till noon. I had lots of jostling with a guy called Chris who I kept calling "Tons-Of-Fun". I learnt a few things about Australians that morning:  - They call toasties "Jaffles" - They hate being the No2 Rugby nation in the world and the mention of Jonny Wilkinson causes uncontrollable rage in the all. - and they don't like it when their mothers are compared to whores.  After noon, I was experiencing some serious heartburn so I went to bed. That evening I woke up on some occasions by either Ben or Scotty running around the place like lunatics but I knew it was an early start the next morning so I kept my head down.  How ironic that I've been in surfer's paradise for 3 days and I still haven't seen the beach!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My last day in Singapore was one of culinary experimentation. I had Indian food for breakfast, Vietnamese food for lunch and Sushi for dinner! All great of course. I didn't do much else apart from meet up with Cassandra and talk about food for ages and about how much I love to eat!  One freaky thing though was that in the shopping mall, there was a competition where 30 people were standing in a room that was freezing cold and they have to stand there for 72 hours in order to win a plasma TV and Air conditioning unit! Freaky!  I got a really early night that night because I wanted to get to the airport as early as possible the next morning..............which I did - not before I spoke to Joseph though (the crazy Indian dude in the room next door), who was telling me how dangerous Bali was and that I should get the hell out of there as soon as possible!  The flight to Bali was pleasant enough - the breakfast was not vomit inducing which was a bonus and I watched Walking Tall with The Rock which was entertaining enough for me.  As I arrived in Denpasar, I met 3 australians - Ben, his sister, Purdey and his mate Scotty. They are all nice people and I shared a Taxi to Legian and they offered for me to share a room with them as Ben has been here plenty of times and knows the cheap places and the area well.  We were staying at the Sandat Bali Inn which in clean and 2 quid a night - result! However, it all got a little bit blurry from there on in.........
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My next few days were spent trying to stay within my budget and getting my photos from my digital camera sorted onto t'internet. As I've been in internet cafe's for nearly 14 hours in the last 3 days, it is clear that it is not as simple a process as I first thought.  I am pleased to say that it is nearly ready, so I'll be sorting out a link to my photo album of the last few months, very shortly.  Yesterday, myself and Dave saw Sina to the MRT station at 6.30am in order to catch her flight, and thankfully she was feeling better than she did the day before (she ate something dodgy (Probably a wasp) and felt terrible and went to bed early). Dave was inconsolable, so we went to see Frank and have a dip in his luxury 4 star hotel pool!   The sun took a while in deciding which hat to wear but, we got a chance to top up on the tan in the morning before Frank had to check out of his room.  While Frank was packing his bags and Dave was having a shower, I had the fortune of playing Volleyball and Water Polo with a group of absolutely crazy Japanese Tourists. It was a lot of fun and I got a picture with them that Princess should be proud of - proper Takeshi's Castle style!  We sat and had a beer with Frank and then tried to be as manly in our goodbye hug with him as possible, as we made our way back to City Hall.  That evening Dave and I went to meet Cassandra in Chinatown and we had a lucky dip of chinese cuisine in the food hall. It was delicious but cockles should never be eaten in any country no matter how hungry you are.  Today, I am the only person on the tour left in Singapore - Sina has flown to Bali with her friend, Frank has gone back to Melbourne and Dave has just left to go back to KL to meet his friend, Mark. Again, thanks to all of you for your company over the last few days and good luck.  My plan for today is to post some things back home and then meet up with Cass for a spot of lunch. After that, I'll pack my bag and get an early night as I have to be at the airport to check in at 7am!  A huge thank you to Cass for looking after everyone who stayed on in Singapore and for getting us all absolutely pissed up.  I'm looking forward to a bit of solitude when I get to Bali - my updates were beginning to sound like an Oscars speech! The good news is that Lisa is definitely coming out to Bali as well and it's a possibility, we may be doing some paragliding! So many extreme sports, so little time. I'm considering base-jumping when I get to LA - What do you think?  Well, that's it for continental Asia. Next time you hear from me, the toilet will start to flush in the other direction - Quick! Call Mulder and Scully!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The next day was Kim and Jen's last day in Singapore. Jen went on some walking expetion of the colonial buildings of Singapore with Dave, which I thought sounded too much like hard work, so myself and Kim went to Orchard Road to look in the shops and check out the prices for cameras. Well Kim was - I was looking at all the different cheesecakes in the coffee shops. I don't think I'll ever find a cheesecake like the one in Cameron Highlands again - Maybe, one day, I'll finally let it lie..........but not today.  Kim and Jen left later that day to go to Melbourne, where, I have been reliably informed, it is freezing cold! Ha Ha! Bali - here I come! Anyway best of luck to both of you and I hope to see you sooner rather than later.  After waving them goodbye, Sina was invited to see her friend, Martin (who is also Swiss-German) who works at the Stamford Swissotel next to Raffles Plaza. Thankfully, myself, Dave, Cass and Frank were invited along too. When we arrived, Martin was busy, probably talking to the president of some country in the Bar or something, but when he was available, he gave us a tour of the Equinox Restaurant at the top of the Hotel.   Well, the views were amazing! You could see all of Singapore up there! It really was an amazing sight and we got so see how the other half lived for a changed. We noticed that Little India where our guesthouse is, looks like a shanty town from above because it is flanked by loads of skyscrapers. Not exactly the Ritz but glamorous enough for my simple needs! Dave asked at one point how much the 5 course meal would be at the restaurant. When Martin said that is was $150 SGD (Which isn't that bad actually!), Dave thought that that could buy 50 Big Mac meals - Bless that simple essex boy!  After that, Cass took myself and Frank to her brother's restarant to take away some free food (Roast Duck and Pork and Hoi Sin,Black Bean and Chilli sauces to dip them into). We took it to Sentosa Island, where Frank was still staying. We got the free bus to Island (even though we should have paid!) and we managed to go and see the last showing of the Musical Fountain Show......which was also free!  The fountain show was amazing but it was very much choreographed for children. Frank was clearly bewildered but I heard him gasp in amazement a couple of times so he must have enjoyed it.  It just goes to show, the best things in life cost nuppence.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It sure is - you get fined for spitting, bringing cigarettes into the city, littering, chewing gum, jay walking, smoking, beastiality, kiddy fiddling.....anything basically!  Anyway, for my first day in Singapore, I met up with my Cassandra who I met in Ko Chang, as she lives here. She took myself and Kim back to the Raffles Hotel and we went to the museum and looked into the history of the entire complex. We attempted to enter all parts of the Hotel but I was soon asked to leave as it a respectable hotel and I was looking rather unkempt at the time. I don't blame them.  After Raffles, we walked through to the new theatre complex that overlooks the harbour side of the city. Many of the locals here dont like the theatre a it looks like a huge pineapple but I think it looks quite funky. We then went into another prestigious hotel called the Fullerton which was very plush and they had a school of Koi Carp in the foyet in which some of them were  (Please imagine this phrase being said in a Bristol accent) bigger than sharks! I think they may be experimenting with genetics and nuclear powers in this part of the world as Godzilla may have met his match with these fish!  That evening, Cass offered to take us all out for a few drinks at some places that she frequents. I'm glad to say to say that she delivered the goods as we started off in Ice Cold Beers, a pub with good music and quite cheap prices. The next stop was the International Food Festival that had been set up nearby and was boasting the Guinness Book of Records Longest Ever Satay Line. I didn't eat the whole thing and Norris Mcwhirter was nowhere to be seen (probably because he died last year) but we did have some hearty food that soaked up some of the alcohol already consumed.  Our next venue was a bar simply called The Bar. It was $15 Singapore Dollars to get in and $3 SGD for every drink (thats 5 pound entry and a quid a drink for those that dont know the exchange rate). I expect the establishment to be out of business this week as we all drank vast quantities until the early hours. The music was great, the gin didn't depress me and Vikki started an ice cube game where all the men got to experiment with their sexuality. Oo-er! So, to answer your question Steve - There isn't much difference between a man's mouth and a woman's mouth - they are the same temperature after all!  The next day, when the hangover wore off, we went to visit Nat and Frank as they were staying on Sentosa Island and Nat was leaving later that day to return to her grandmother who had fallen ill during the trip.  We caught the cable car to the island just to say that we did it really and you do get some great views of Singapore that way too. When we arrived on Sentosa Island, I was half expecting Mickey Mouse to jump out at any time as it is an entirely man-made island resort which is cheesed up to the max. Japanese tourists and fat Americans all over the place!  The Hotel Shangri-La where Nat and Frank were staying is lush and has a huge pool with jacuzzis right on the beach! I am tempted to go and play some volleyball there before I leave as there are nets all the way up the beach.  We had a little dip in the pool and we waved Nat off in her taxi to the airport. Bless her heart - she may be an ocker but, like Rolf Harris, you've gotta love her!  That evening, the troops were looking quite depleted from who was left from the tour. So myself, Kim and Dave made our way to Chinatown for some grub. However, we learned that that particular day was an Indian Holiday and it was their day to shop for everything authentic in Little India, where our hostel is. That would explain why there were 5000 indian chatting right outside my room and in the street then! It's like being back in Roath (Cardiff) but with less scummy students!  So, we made it to Chinatown in the end, and we found a nice Japanese Restaurant (Huh?!). The food was amazing and it's the first time on my travels where I genuinely thought I had misread the menu and it was going to turn out to be the most expensive meal ever. Thankfully it wasn't.  On a tangent, I have noticed a lot of little kids gliding around the subways here because they have half-shoe-half-rollerblade which means they can just cruise around. They rock! I was tempted to get some for Jack or Jasmine but there isn't any flat/smooth ground anywhere near the farm so they would be useless.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My time in Melaka was very nice actually - The sun did shine and I didn't die from the heat, so.. hurrah!  It is a very old city and it was another testament as to how nice Malaysia is, really. We saw St Paul's Castle/church thingy and the portuguese ship that has been converted into some kind of maritime museum.  I got pretty tired soon after though and I'd bought some anti-inflammatory cream for Tom's anus.....sorry, sorry... his foot. That's right - he got it infected during his 20 minutes of jungle trekking in the Cameron Highlands (whereas I remain poison free after trekking for 7 hours - go figure!). So I meandered back to the hostel for a snooze.  The evening was an awesome event. We went to a rooftop restaurant called the Bamboo Hut and I'm pleased to say, it was an all-you-can-eat BBQ. Homer Simpson would be proud of my accomplishments that evening. The food was superb and the entertainment was something you could never experience in Britain.   After a while, a Malaysian Billy Ray Cyrus lookalike, burst into song and would have chats with diners inbetween his awesome repertoire of karaoke treats. He sang many classics such as Sweet Caroline, Brown eyed Girl, YMCA, and Copacabana to name a few! When not staring in disbelief, we were singing along with every offkey tune.   The funniest parts were when his mobile phone would cause interference with his microphone like when it's too close to a car stereo, and when we put a fake birthday request in for Wesley, the tour leader, who was on her way to catch the last showing at the cinema at the time, so Billy Ray chased her down the stairs, guitar in hand, wishing her birthday wishes and exclaiming "I love you, Wesley" and " I wanna touch you" and many other saucy expletives!  The waiter took a shine to Chris and kept calling him Chris Benoit and as I'm probably the only saddo on the tour that still watches wrestling, I found it hilarious! The barman also did a fire juggling trick to the tune of "Tequila" which was a little less entertaining than Dave's dancing.  After the meal, some of us went bowling and I did O.K but got too cocky in the second game and Frank pissed on my chips by turning up the heat in the last few frames while I was pissing about - Hustling swine! The most improved player award goes to my "Potterge", Chris for his outstanding commitment to get better scores than the girls.  That evening I sat and talked to my sister Rach in the garden of the hostel. Everyone else had gone to bed so the wildlife came out to play (rats, geckos, monitor lizards, centipedes and a snake, but that was Dowd's pet). Don't worry Rach, I won't tell mum what you said about the Ping pong trick she can do with footballs! Whoops!  The next morning, we said goodbye to Tom as he had to go back to hospital, so he stayed in Melaka. The rest of us arrived in Singapore just after lunch and we are staying in Little India. The hostel is OK and I'll probably stay until I leave for Bali, but there are many indian men hanging around in towels which is a little weird.  The urban myth is that Singapore is very expensive but that is very wrong - if you go for luxurys and certain items, it's about the same price as back in Britain. Booze is expensive, but food (which is all I'm interested in) is very cheap. The people that started this rumour are either tight-asses, drunkards or from Cambodia.  We all went to Boat Quay for dinner last night and it was great - I finished everyone's meals again and I may pay the price by having to pay for 2 seats on the plane when I fly to Bali because of my humungous ass.  We went to Raffles Hotel for a Singapore Sling which apparently is a must. I didn't have one though because a drink that costs 8 quid is never a must unless it lasts for the whole night (Hmmmm....one singapore sling or 5 bottles of Frosty Jacks cider?).  On the way back from Raffles, we walked past the inverted bungee jump, I made friends with a wee frog by the river, and we watched a man dance with his shadow for over an hour while we drank G&T's - Strange!  This morning, some of the tour group left for pastures new. I woke up late though so I'm sorry if I missed you. Iona and Jo - I'm glad you got to see "The Egg" eventually - not quite a "party-boy" but it passes the time. And Chris - I'll always remember you walking like a spastic. Cheers for the laughs you fruitcake. I wish you all the best of luck in the world - you'll bloody need it!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't have that long left in KL and so I thought I'd do something substancial with my time......so, I went bowling!  It's the first time I've played for 8 months so I expected a score Steve Potter would be proud of - you know......above 100. However, I was pleased to get 5 strikes and a spare and a respectable score of 165. No signs of strain on my robotic leg either!  To celebrate, I bought a few clothing items in the Body Glove shop where it was next to nuppence (but not quite - sorry Rach and Johnny - my pikido skills are wilting in this heat!).  I also found out that Kuala Lumpur literally means "Muddy rivers" in Malay, from when it was a mining town - not exactly a glamourous name. Next I'll probably find out that Paris means "shithole", or Cardiff means "English people Welcome".  I arrived in Melaka last night after the coach journey.....of doom! - The driver was on a mission to make everyone on the coach shit themselves and he was pretty successful, I'd say! - He drove like BA Baracus on speed. He was in two lanes for most of the journey and was shouting at people, laughing maniacally, and generally trying to push other people of the road. The journey was supposed to be 3 hours long and we arrived in 2h 15m! I ain't gettin' on no coach, fool!  The guesthouse where we're staying is called the Kancil Guesthouse and is run by a fella called Dow. He really chilled out and the place is very nice - I have a sunspot/jungle scene right outside my room!  For dinner we went to a chinese food market where we were the only western faces. All you had to do was ask for something and say where you were sitting and they would bring it over to you - it was great! I had the dumplings, unfried spring rolls (which were superb!), fish cakes wrapped in Banana leaves and some mushroom noodles. The whole thing was really nice but there was no point in asking what some of the things were as they didn't speak any english.  After my meal, I was drinking my Guinness and I had my first creative moment in some time - I made a car out of the containers and rubbish left over from the meal and it was something Anthea Turner would be proud of if she was still on Blue Peter and not being such a filthy crack-whore.  Well, today it is raining but I'm counting that as a blessing as the heat was beginning to melt my sideburns. I hope to visit many museums and take photos, and, if I can squeeze it in.......... a few games of bowling!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I left Brisbane with a bit of a hangover. My next destination was Noosa which is only 2 hours away. When I arrived, I was glad to see that it was all quite close together and easily walkable.  There are a lot of activities to do in Noosa, including (apparently) the cheapest place to do skydiving. Instead, I decided to take in the National Park via the beach.  It is very beutiful in Noosa and the park boasted a lot of wildlife but I didn't see that much of it though. You see, the problem with trees is that they're brown. And, you see, the problem with koalas is that they're also brown. I did see a goana (big lizard) in the bushes and wild turkeys and cookaburras.  The coastal walk that I chose was very nice and when I reached the end of the trail, (named Hell's Gate) It was so nice to feel a strong wind in my face, mainly because I haven't been to hardly any places that have been that windy for as long as I remember. It reminded me of being back in Cornwall.  I only spent one night in Noosa though as my Fraser Island adventure was waiting for me at Hervey Island which is where I am at this precise moment.  I have had my briefing for the trip and I'm a little bit apprehensive but I'll be driving a 4x4 and I'm one of the few people with a driving licence so I'm sure I'll be doing a lot of the driving!  I'll update in a few days. I just hope that a dingo doesn't steal my baby! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, I arrived in Brisbane at 6.30 am and, after absolutely no sleep, I wasn't sure what to do with myself.  I got to a hostel called Bunk (which it was a little) which was in the heart of Brisbane's Chinatown and gay community so I felt a bit more comfortable as it was just like being in a gay asia.  I went up to the dorm room I was allocated and turned around as soon as I entered - it stank THAT bad! I opted instead to have a coffee and a bit of breakfast and to muster the courage to face the smell again. I may regret living in luxury (sort of) for the last month or so as I'm not looking forward to sharing dorms with pissheads for the next few months!  After dropping my bag off in the cesspit, I ventured into the city to see what Brisbane had to offer. The answer? Not a lot really! In Bali, the locals would put flowers and other offerings on their doorsteps to please their Gods. Well, in Australia, they do the same sort of thing but with broken bottles. Their gods must be called VB, XXXX and Carlton Draught.  Proceeding into town I noticed that the river is quite a nice area and the walks on the riverside and onto the botanical gardens were very pleasant for a sunday morning stroll. There was also a market at Eagle Pier which was nice to look around and not be hassled like in Bali.   I gabbed a quick snack on the way back to the hostel and ,thankfully, the residents of my room had vacated and the room was aired so I decided to put head down for a few Zzzz's and get some rest.  ............19 hours later I woke up not knowing where the hell I was - I MUST have been tired!  I worked it out and my travelling arrangements for the next 2 months should cost around 500 quid but that doesn't include accomodation or food. I can imagine that this might be a bit more expensive than I originally thought but I may skip a few meals to make ends meet. There's weight to drop off me yet!  My last night in Brisbane was in the bar below the hostel and I met a couple from Falmouth of all places! Scott and Lucy were a couple of misbehavers but it was nice to talk about Plymouth and the South West and hear a good proper-job cornish accent!  There isn't really a lot to do in Brisbane so I have decided to make my way up to Cairns and stop off on a few places along the way.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My arrival back in Kuta was all a little bit sad really. I was still a little bit crook from the Bali Belly and I was sad to be leaving Indonesia as there is so much more that I wanted to see.  But most of all, I was sad to be leaving Lisa as she has become one of my best friends and she is one of the few people in this world that I trust implicitly and would do anything for her.  On another sad note, Lisa has had to go back to finish her para-gliding course and get her pilot's licence, but we heard on the day we arrived back from Lembongan that someone had had a very bad accident and has broken bones and internal injuries at the glide site where we went for the last 2 weeks! The person injured was an idiot but it puts the sport into dangerous perspective. I just wish Lisa all the luck in the world to finish the course safely so that she can go back to injuring herself at ground level.  On Saturday afternoon, I flew back to Singapore and watched Shrek 2 - Jack and Jazz would approve so - Rach - take em to the cinema now! In Singapore Airport I sorted out sending another package back home stacked with Christmas presents - Who'd have thought that I'd have done all my Christmas shopping by August!  I sat down in the bar with a couple from New Zealand (John and Pam) and we watched the Tri-nations game between Austarlia and New Zealand and discussed how bitter the Australians are about being beaten by the English last year - The Kiwis always laugh at the Aussies and say that at least they weren't beaten by the English!  I saw a funny thing when going to catch my plane to Brisbane - A little girl was trying to give some sweets to her mother in the newsagents but they turned out to be flavoured condoms! Her mother was quite shocked and it probably didn't help her embarrassment with me giggling behind her!  I couldn't sleep on the plane to Brisbane so I just did the usual and watched as many films as I could muster.  Am I prepared for Australia? Will I like it? Will I have my appetite back? Well, you'll just have to wait and see wont you. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We were up early to get the ferry back to Nusa Lembongan as it leaves at 8am. However, Lisa had a little problem with the ATM in the Circle K as the power went off and ate her card!   She was not pleased obviously and threatened the manager with her wrath (which is trouser-fillingly intimidating). Thankfully, Made, the guy who we hired the jeep from, had already offered to give us a lift to the ferry and he also took it upon himself to sort out Lisa's Debit Crad by the time we got back as well. He really is one the nicest guys I've met!  We still managed to catch the ferry in time. On the journey we met two Dutch brothers from Curacao (Dan and Klass-Jan) and another dutch guy called Itai (who was a bit freaky to tell the truth - always beware a man with uncontrollable eyebrows!).  When we arrived at Lembongan, the tide was very high so it was a bit tricky to get off the boat without getting soaked! One french woman was crying until her husband came and carried her to the beach which which made me thankful that Lisa isn't a pain in the arse like that!  We opted to spend the day drinking ourselves into a bit of a stupour and we were successful in our mission. Lisa was worst off because she felt she had something to prove, as she was the only woman in the group. The locals called her Mrs Bintang for the rest of our stay.  We stayed at Lembongan Bungalows where Danny welcomed us and gave us a bungalow which a great view over the beach(I went to his 50th Birthday party when I was here before). We also met up with Glen again as he was staying there but he left the next day.  The next day was spent nursing hangovers and eating really well. We went to the Sukanusa restaurant and we booked a dive for the 4 of us (Me, Lisa, Dan and KJ) at 20 pound each for 2 dives! However, as the dutch brothers had a fishing expedition the next day, we postponed it until the day after.  Another lazy day followed but with a difference - I was slowly being poisoned by the locals! I had nothing but bad food all day and my stomach was churning through most of the day.   Just before sunset, we all decided to go out to the shipwreck as it was low tide and easily reached in a pair of flip flops (the water was only knee high at most). We all had a really good time as there was lots of wildlife seen on the journey and the locals were still farming the seaweed until darkness fell.  The shipwreck was impressive to see and we got there as the sun was just setting so there were some spectacular photos. The walk back in the dark was a little bit treacherous though. You see - the things with night-time is that it's black. And the thing with spiky sea urchins is that they're also black. Thankfully, no-one stepped on them.  The following day was not a good day in the kingdom of my bowels. We had a dive planned and I was suffering from another bout of the dreaded Bali Belly! While everyone was getting kitted up for the dive, I had my head in my hands trying desperately hard not to shit myself.  The trouble is that I'm a stubborn bastard as I have Potter blood in my veins so I was adamant that I was going to do the dive. I shouldn't have because I was a liability and a miserable sod as well!  On the boat on the way out I was feeling worse so I had what some professionals would call, A Tactical Chunder. I was sick over the side of the boat and I felt a hell of a lot better after that and I even had the energy to do the dives.  The dives were spectacular and I saw many new creatures including a stingray, trumpet-fish, another turtle and a whitetip reef shark! I was very lucky as the others didn't see it. The only trouble was that I did shit myself underwater which was quite uncomfortable and I was a shit underwater "buddy" to Lisa and I am still feeling the shame for my lack of scruples under the water that day.  I was basically a shell of my former self for the following few days as I had (gasp!) lost my appetite and was generally miserable as is usually the case when a man is ill.  I drank a lot of green tea. I watched Fahrenheit 9/11 (which was truly shocking and brilliantly made) and read my book as there wasn't much else for me do that wouldn't make me cry like a schoolgirl.  My next update will be my departure from Indonesia and my arrival in Brisbane. But I promise that it will be in the next couple of days and not weeks!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Poor Banny! I bumped into him a few days after our first encounter and he has broken his foot and slashed it open when he was surfing. I feel for you my friend, I really do - I've been there man - I feel your pain! Sadly, this means that Banny is on his way back to Britain. In fact, he may already be there. Hope it heals my friend and I'll see you at Christmas, if you don't vacate the country again sometime soon.  Lisa has taken a break from paragliding for a week, so that we can do some diving and so that she can heal from all of her wounds - The "Bali Kiss" (when you burn yourself on a motorbike exhaust) that she received on her first day has just about healed for her to go back in the water anyway.  We both intended to go to Flores and day-trip over to Komodo and Rinca to see the Komodo Dragons but sadly, there were complications -   There is only one flight a day to Flores and they were booked up until the day before I leave for Oz. So we went to try and extend our visas so I could stay longer in Indonesia but my original visa was "non-extendable" so we were advised to leave the country and come back if we wanted to stay longer! However, the security gueard at the airport said he could sort something out for us, but I'm not willing to do any dodgy if it relates to my passport or my money.  So we eventually ditched the idea and we've been told by Lisa's brother that they break the legs of the Komodo Dragons so that the tourists can see them which is frankly not nice!  Instead we drove up to Ubud and then on to Lake Batur and The Volcanoes. It was really nice to be driving outside of Kuta and some of the views were spectacular on the way.   The sad things we saw: The poverty of the villages and how desperate they were for our money/ a dead dog that had been run over but it's tail was still wagging.  The nice things we saw: The "Pur Nama" festival (which means full moon) where the villagers all wore their best and most colourful silk clothes and brought offerings to the temple (of course, I beeped my horn and told them to get the hell out of the way)/ and the views of Lake Batur, Agung and Batur (the volcanoes) and just taking in the sunset.  We got back to Kuta latein the evening and we decided to get an early night as we were going back to Nusa Lembongan the next day. Hopefully to do some diving and to relax on the beach.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Belated Birthday wishes to my brother and to my father who are both a little older and (I hope) a little wiser for the last years experiences and exploits.  Steve - sorry to hear of your social shake-up but your a sexy guy and the receding stopped (for now).  Dad - Glad to see that your still thriving on the stress at work, but lets hope that the next Argyle season can keep that smile on your face a little bit longer before gravity (and Leeds Utd) take their toll.  I love you both so much but I could never tell you to your faces. You understand, don't you?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, its been a while and I thought I'd adopt a trick that Hitler used to use when giving public speeches - let them wait and they'll hang on your every word when you speak!  Continueing from where I left off, I had a huge surprise when I was walking down Poppies Lane 1. I bumped into Banny, a long lost chum from Ridgeway School. He was pretty unemotional but that's probably because I was embarassingly happy to see him! Honestly though, it is always nice to see a familiar face when you've been away for a long time.  While I've been staying at the Masa Inn, it has been under construction for some new rooms and stone and wood carvers have been busy applying their trades at amazing speeds. It worries me though to think about how much these people must be paid! To their credit, they have a clock on the workmans wall that I should have tried to buy off them as a souvenir. Watch out for the pictures when I publish them.  The Masa Inn has proven to be one of the best finds on my travels as it is reasonably cheap, it's cleaned every day, it has two amazing pools and the clientele are reasonably well behaved. The only bad points are that next door to the hotel, they burn their rubbish at random times which, quite frankly, stinks! And there are 2 american girls who have faces like smacked asses and I've so wanted to bitch-slap them upside their head all week!  As Far as the paragliding has been going - Lisa has now done 2 tandem flights and 6 solo flights! She has also accumulated a lot of bruises and when people ask her how she got them I jump in to say "she's got a big mouth - so I made her shut it!". Some people got the joke but some didn't.  I have also done a tandem flight which was another tick off the extreme sports list. It was a very liberating experience and I didn't seem to notice that I only had a sheet above my head - I thought I was just floating in mid air! It was good, but I would want more control over the paraglider to do it again.  On one day out to the paragliding site, a surfer on a motorbike, complete with board and girlfriend, crashed into a jeep right in front of us! I had to swerve to avoid running them over. Thankfully, no-one was hurt badly, but guess what the surfer did next - Did he check to see if his girlfriend was ok, or his surfboard?
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>