<Blog>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, test?
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What an athlete!&nbsp; I've been glued to the tour and every time I think Lance is just incredible, then he just blows my mind and does something even better.&nbsp; I am just blown away after today's stage.   Alright, back to reality.&nbsp; Boring day at work.&nbsp; Good night last night.&nbsp; I went for about an hour ride with a friend who is absolutely out of shape.&nbsp; Fun non the less.&nbsp; It was nice to just have someone else on the trail other then my dog.&nbsp; Not that I mind my dog, but it is nice to have someone that talks back riding with me.&nbsp;   I took the lady to the movies afterwards.&nbsp; Anchorman, all I can say is hilarious, as good as Old School.&nbsp; I really think it's about time someone started making funny movies again.&nbsp; Most comedies, hell most movies suck these days.&nbsp; It's rare that a movie comes along that is any good anymore.&nbsp;   So no big plans for the night.&nbsp; Might just be a rest day, take the dog hiking or something.&nbsp; I get my road bike tomorrow so I will be on that constantly.&nbsp; I don't want to go all out tonight and not be able to ride it tomorrow.&nbsp; So a short hike and then maybe the couch will sound good.&nbsp; "Til tomorrow.   
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday!&nbsp; So I'm done with my long work day.&nbsp; Monday's I work in my office until 3:30 and then bartend from 4:00 to about 11:00.&nbsp; Not a bad time though, it's an easy place to bartend and I'm not getting off in the middle of the night.&nbsp; So tonight is going to be a running night.&nbsp; I want to hit up a new trail though.&nbsp; I've been running the same one the last couple of times, which isn't a complaint.&nbsp; It's got some great climbs and a couple sections of stairs that burn the calves really well.&nbsp; A change of senery would be key!&nbsp; I also want to hit up the track at the local highschool.&nbsp; I have a lot of drills I would like to do (jog the corners, sprint the straight aways)&nbsp; and so on.&nbsp; I'm in this mad dash to kick my own ass into shape.&nbsp; I have a plan of re-entering the racing community next summer, but I would like to bump up to a better class.&nbsp; I also have a goal of a solo 24 hour race.&nbsp; Something I have never attempted before.&nbsp; I have to work on making my climbs and building my legs before I can get over my head.  &nbsp; So I picked up a trainer for my road bike, I'll have my new bike Friday!&nbsp; Unfortunately this weekend is a big festival, The Old Friends Reunion, and a lot of drinking and partying will take place and not too much riding. Old Friends are a local bluegrass band that have been around for about 30 years.&nbsp; Great people and really great music.&nbsp; They throw a reunion every summer which is a huge party.&nbsp; Always a good time.&nbsp;  &nbsp; So I have&nbsp;a few rides set for the following week.&nbsp; Then next Saturday I plan to ride out to my mom's place.&nbsp; it's only 26.3 miles, but it's got some great climbs.&nbsp; Should be nice and brutal!&nbsp; Can't wait.&nbsp;  &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow What a weekend!&nbsp; I took Friday off, so I got an early start.&nbsp;&nbsp; Me and the lady friend went down to the Jersey Beach for the day.&nbsp; It was nice to just lay around all day on the beach. The waves were pretty high for east coast.&nbsp; Lots of people surfing made me quite jealous.&nbsp; The whole trip was great, with the exception of the people.&nbsp;&nbsp; Now I have friends from Jersey (most of which don't live there anymore) but in most cases people there are down right mean.&nbsp; No manners, no regard for other folks.&nbsp; Just concerned about themselves.&nbsp; It's a damn shame to see people living like that, not enjoying other people that they meet along the way.  &nbsp;  Well, not going to harp on that.&nbsp; I got home late Friday night, so we just&nbsp;laid on the couch and watched a flick.&nbsp; Saturday was my work day.&nbsp; I did a bunch of laundry and cleaned up around the house.&nbsp; That night we went out and saw a band.&nbsp; Also hit up the local carnival.&nbsp; Always a good time.... Again!&nbsp; Sunday was the day!&nbsp; Spent most of the day with my mom moving her into her new house.&nbsp; It rained most of the day but stopped around 4:00 p.m.&nbsp; So at 6:00ish I hit the trails.&nbsp; Nice and tacky!&nbsp; Fast as hell.&nbsp; I was only out on a short ride, but it was probably one of my favorites this season.&nbsp; I had a grat wreck too!&nbsp; I love the ones when you don't get hurt!!&nbsp;&nbsp; My front tire washed out on me over a bridge.&nbsp; I knew it would be slick, but I pushed it anyway.&nbsp; my entrance and glide across were perfect, but as I pushed the bars up the next hill before I left the bridge, that front tire just dove!&nbsp; Lots of people out on the trail too.&nbsp; Not a usual thing for me.&nbsp; No one is ever out there which was surprising to run into two people running and a dready guy tormenting.&nbsp; Sorry man!&nbsp; didn't mean to scare ya!&nbsp; hahahahaha&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Spent the rest of the night watching stage 14 of the tour.&nbsp; Man those guys set a pace!&nbsp;     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Crazy day outside, raining, thonder, lightning!!  Loving it.  I have a stream outside my office window that I love to listen to while working.  Well, it's mid summer and it pretty much dried up.  So rain is a nice alternative.  My road bike is in the process of being built!  It's a quick alternative to kicking my ass into shape.  I ran last night with the mutt, a pleasent experience compared to our run last week.  The golf cart incident and all.    Friday I have off, a road trip to the beach for the day with the lady friend is a nice way to end the work week.  Our local carnival is also this week.  Starting tonight.  Big Six and Beer!  Love being a redneck.  That's all for today, off to the local shop to drop off my frame.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah stress!  It creeps up on you and turns your stomach.  Makes you shiver, makes your nerves jump.  Thank god for the bicycle, thank god for music.  I almost took a half day, then the guilt hit in.  Better go back to work.  With only 5 minutes left, I count the seconds.  I'm going to throw on the ipod, turn it up and hit the road.  Tonight I'm going to log some miles, tonight I'm going to ride until I can't feel.   Everything is out of my hands, so it's best to just ignore it.  Ride to forget.  Hopefully tomorrow will be better.  Hopefully tomoroow will hold some answers.  Hopefully tomoroow...well tomorrow is Friday!  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a while. Been busy with work, girlfriend, family and very little riding. This weekend was strange. On Saturday night a guy I knew was killed in a car accident. He wasn't a friend, though I knew him well. Kind of strange, very cocky, loved to start shit. All in all he was a good person. I remember being at a friends batchelour party and him starting with two guys twice the size of him, this kid had huge balls. Not afraid of anything. It was just so damn strange how life was just taken away from him, he was only 22. It really made me think, just as anyone passing on does. I've lost friends my age before, this kid was a bit younger but still. You think, you think about when your time will be up. You think about your funeral, who will show up, what will they say. Will it be 50 years fro now, will it be tomorrow. After hours of thinking Sunday night, I finally snapped out of it. If you dwell on something like that, how can you live life to it's fullest.  I try to live everyday to it's fullest potential. Since I've moved back from Colorado, I question if what I'm doing is right. Am I supposed to be here, was I better off being broke and skiing everyday? I miss the hills, but I love being close to my family. I love my girlfriend who unfortunately will not pick up and move. So I guess I'll stay back east, at least for now.  I need to get on my bike tonight and forget about everything for a while, I think too much. 
    
</post>


</Blog>