<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A thought while surfing VHStrungout.com.....''time to put up a new web page. A thought, fifteen seconds later....FUCK THAT. Blogging makes it EASY!  Steve-O   
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah. That's Right. I'll Tell Ya. We were off last night, sitting around, with nothin to do. All I was doin was thinking about tonite, and while I was doin that, the boys in the band were havin a party up at the hotel. They had about fifteen chicks up there...I was sitting in my room watching TV. If that ain't a buncha bullshit I dont know what is. See the problem is...well..I learned my lesson...see, I was worrying about tonight, last night. Last night I should have been worrying about last night. And the night before that I should have been worrying about that night. Because worrying about tomorrow is a buncha bullshit. Tomorrow may never come. Tomorrow?!? There's no guarantee about tomorrow. FUCK tomorrow! You dig what I'm sayin? Yesterday?!? Yesterday is HISTORY. That's dead and gone. Yesterday ain't worth nothin. because All You Got to worry about......is right here...right now.   Sammy Hagar -     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets see. Prosecutors think he might flee the country. Let's weigh the options, and look at the statistical probability of wacko-jacko being unleashed on an unwilling public again.   Option 1. Prosecutors push this issue. He's forced to stay here, and stand trial. There's a 50/50 chance that he won't be convicted, might be set free. Probability of him terrorizing the U.S. public again: 50%  Option 2: Prosecutors Don't Push the Issue. Michael Jackson Flees The Country. He goes to a country that doesn't have extradition treaties. He stays there, in seclusion, the rest of his life. Probability of him terrorizing the U.S. public again: 0%   Option 3. Prosecutors Don't Push the issue. Michael Jackson Flees The Country. He goes to a country that doesn't have extradition treaties. He lives a public life, molests another child, and has his hands cut off, his face bashed in, then he is castrated and killed by a brazilian mob. Probability of him terrorizing the U.S. public again: 0%    So, mathematically, we have three options. In 2/3 of them, we have prosecutors that don't push the issue. In BOTH cases, we are rid of michael jackson forever. That's a 66% guarantee that we never have to deal with him again. So. Mathematically speaking....   L E T T H E F R E A K G O ! ! !    posted by Steve Kocher at 7:26 PM 0 comments  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did this in photoshop.         
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since June 11, enough people have gone out on the Strungout Forums and bashed Van Halen, bashed, Eddie Van Halen, said he's dying, said he's gonna cancel the tour.  I've tried not to fire back, but dammit, it's just getting my ire and i've had enough.  I finally posted this in response, today.        Okay all, I just finished up in the "tour review" threads, and that thread has strayed from it's intended purpose, so I'm posting this thread here, where it should be [editors note, it's in the "open" forum on the page]. Nobody's telling you not to be entitled to your opinion, and if anyone's taken any of MY posts that way, I'm sorry. What we're saying (or at least what "I" am intending to say is that there's too much speculation going on without any factual basis in it. I'm gonna state MY opinion, for the record, and then I'm not gonna post on this no more, because to be honest, we've all spent too much time "elaborating" and "Guessing" already. Let's look at pure facts. And Let's let them speak for themselves.    Eddie's Missing Notes, and Messing Up On Stage  Okay. Tell me a live musician who's perfect, dead on, for the studio, every time, every nite, every note. If I wanted to listen to the studio tracks played over loudspeakers with a light show, I'd check out the Pink Floyd Laser Show. Part of what makes a live show experience IS the foul-ups, IS the errors, and that's what makes it great. Eddie has not played live on stage in a MINIMUM of six years. The stuff he WAS playing with Gary wasn't NEARLY the Hagar-era stuff we're hearing now, in fact, it was mainly new stuff (which someone pointed out is easier to transition to, and the older stuff, so considering THAT, it's been since like 1995 since he played this material on stage. Boxers who fight in the middleweight class, retire, and come back 8-9 years later in the heavyweight class don't always win their first fights...they attribute it to "ring rust". Why can't eddie have a little "rust", because to be honest, the VH3 era tour played a LOT of "middleweight songs" and it's just NOW that he's returning to the "heavyweight" songs that he hasn't played since "balance/ambulance". I saw him BOTH tours, in 1995, and 1998 . I've heard the bootlegs (all that are available) from this tour. Is there a difference. Yeah. Is it something to take off and run with?...not IMHO. Even the “mighty casey” didn’t hit home runs every time he was at bat. Sometime or another he’s got to strike out….   Eddie's Dying. He’s got Cancer. He looks like sh*t.   I’ve said it before, I’ll say it again. This kind of mess just pi*ses people off. You have a small number of people who claim to know who tell a LARGE number of people that DON’T know (either), with certainty, facts that only the man himself should be credited with saying, IF he ever says them. (Did that make sense??). Let’s face fact. The man has stated he is “cancer free”. He’s even said “I’m not in remission, the cancer is GONE”. That’s a statement unto itself right there. “His teeth are yellow and falling out”. Okay. The man’s pushing 50, and he’s had a cigarette in his mouth every day since he was old enough to get away with buying them. You expected something other? YOU go smoke “X” packs a day for 35 (or more) years, and see what happens to YOUR teeth. Tartar Control my A$$...ain’t no toothpaste in the world gonna fix that. As for his face looking like that? Well. Same difference. Cigarettes will do that to you. A little research and a lot less yacking will accomplish a lot. For a “pushing 50” year old man, to LOOK as muscular and in shape as he does….his teeth should be the least of our concerns.    Eddie’s Gonna Cancel The Tour.  Seems to me a man who was uncertain of his future as a touring artist wouldn’t continue to add dates to the itinerary. To Quote MYSELF (not in exact words..), let’s leave the tour canceling to the promoters and the band. The tour will continue until HE stops it, and Azoff tells us it’s not going to continue. Until then. I’m looking forward to seeing them, and no nay-sayer is going to dissuade me from my excitement or my sheer giddiness about actually seeing them again.     Bashing each other in this forum .  I agree. 100% that people are taking this way to seriously, but that’s not a BAD thing. That shows that there are people out there who REALLY care about the band and the music. We shouldn’t be “bashing” each other over our opinions, and as I’ve said, if it’s come across that way in any of MY posts, it’s not intended that way. Each and every one of us are entitled to opinions, Vin said it. “we are all VH fans on this site otherwise why would we waste our time on this message board”. That’s right, we’re all fans. My take is this, as fans, we owe it to the man who’s making this all possible not to speculate, publicly, what his condition is. It’s okay to say “Eddie missed a few notes”, but to come out here, day after day, hour after hour, and focus on the few notes he missed and attribute it to health problems, or what-have-you’s, is just not giving Eddie, or the band, the respect they deserve from us as fans. For us to go to a show, and scream until we can’t scream anymore, and go deaf listening to him, and then come here…and do this…well…I have no better way of saying it, but we’re two-faced”….and in a way, every one of us, the mods, the readers, the members, and even (SHOCK!) me, are all guilty of it, just by continuing to feed this thing more and more every day. Here’s an idea (Ben? You with me on this?). Let’s not stop people from expressing their opinions. That’s what this board is for, but in turn let’s all stop expressing opinions that are rooted in what may be fiction. Express your opinions about the shows…sure….tell us he missed three notes in two hours….that’s what we WANT to hear….tell us how great it was that you got five-star seats, and how you snuck your camera in and got some great pictures, then post the pictures. I don’t think (again…Ben?) this forum, or this page was intended to be what it is becoming with more and more of these posts. This page, if I’m reading it right, and I’m reading my side-conversations I’ve had with Ben right, is intended to be in TRIBUTE to the greatest rock band of all time, and if we’re going to go out and post stuff that sometimes even tabloids wouldn’t post, well…we’re getting away from the purpose of the page. So, you won’t see me post any more on this subject. You won’t find me reading this dribble about Eddie’s health anymore. You won’t get any response from me on it. I think it’s a dead issue, in my mind, as of…..no pun intended…. right here…right now…because right here…right now….Eddie is king….   In Eddie We Trust. Amen.   Who's with me on this??    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am the proud owner of EVERY Van Halen CD Ever Released (Officially) and some that weren't (official that is).    Van Halen (1978)  Van Halen II (1979)  Women And Children First (1980)  Fair Warning (1981)  Diver Down (1982)  1984 (1984)  5150 (1985) OU812 (1988( For Unlawful Carnal Knowledge (1991)  Live-Right Here, Right Now (1993) (2CD) Balance (1995)  Best Of Van Halen Volume 1 (1996)  The Best Of Sammy Hagar (2003) (2 CD)  Bootleg - East Rutherford NJ 06-23-04 Bootleg - Greensboro NC 06-11-04 (opening night) Tribute - Little Guitars (1998)   
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       .  My wife and I are two of a small number of people that were actually present in the lives of two very good friends of ours as they went through a personal tragedy in their lives, and while it's not a thing to say we're "proud" to have been a part of, it's something to say we're "proud" we were there to help any way we could.  Basing two books on the subject of that tragedy, one complete, and one in writing, we're VERY proud of the accomplishments of the two since the incidents that formed the books (the books being just some of the accomplishments).  We were recently given a copy of the book (and to be honest, while I tried several times to order, much to my shagrin, I didn't try hard enough).  Having completed it in just one day, it's intriguing enough to tell you that not only will I read it again, for "thoroughness",  but you've GOT to go and get it yourself, even if nothing like this has ever struck close to YOUR home, because it's a great besides.... While the book doesn't take DIRECT issue with the murder of the author's brother, well..it does in a way, but in a comparison to the next book...well..how do you say that. I guess I'll end that sentence and say I'm looking GREATLY forward to the next book "White Flame".  It's not an expensive book.  It's worth the read, if there ever was one worth the read.  Also....if you want to "meet" our friends, you can visit their site at  urlLink Freitag Books  and check it out for yourself.     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here listening to Bob Seger.  Yes, I gave up my Van Halen for a few hours.  Enjoying a great weekend off. (Well, saturday at 1PM to Monday at 4PM...that's a weekend off to me....) Got to find some more things to put up on the web page.      Rituals    I've noticed that I'm begining to develop rituals.  Well, no, I guess I'm noticing the rituals that I've always had. For example, Sunday night has become a ritual for the wife and myself. Home baked Chocolate Chip Cookies....big mugs of milk...and Six Feet Under on HBO.  Used to be Sopranos, but that is out of season now....so now it's Six Feet Under season.      Van Halen    I've embarked on a quest to get every album they've put out into MP3 format.  So to Matt(and Anna), and Jamey, and Derek, and my new friend Jon...sometime this week expect an email saying "come and get it". Still growing my collection of "unauthorized concert performances" (BOOTLEGS) as well.      Batman and Robin, Back Together Again    Derek's (Robin) home....It's good to have my boy back. I've missed him being around.  These "week at a time in Waycross" jaunts are killer on someone who only has a few close friends.      Married Life   Bob Seger says...  Some people say that love's a losin game you start with fire but you lose the flame. the ashes smolder but the warmths soon gone you end cold and loneley own your own   Bob Seger, at least in this case, is full of shit.  Married life is great, and seems to have renewed new things and interests that have flickered out or wained over the past seven years between us.     Work   Looks like it's starting to pick back up *THANK GOD*.  No business - no moneyh, the simple rules of retail.  I've decide on a new plan to get back in the game.  Putting it into place January 2005. Enjoy myself between now and then, spend on concerts, spend on life...then start saving pennies...get back through that program, and when the company calls this time and says "let's go..."...I'm going.  No more  Governor's Square Mall Issues ....   Reflection - The Wedding  Everyone's seen the pictures on my page of the wedding.  Nobody realizes just how much work went into that, and not by us...but by everyone else, and so much preparation for just a ten minute thing seems like a waste, but it wasn't. Everyone I've talked to who attended says it was well worth bearing the heat for that timeframe.  And yes, Matt....everyone thought you were the mafia when you walked up...and I was never more proud to be friends with the four of you in my LIFE (And GOOD LUCK in those Job Prospects, as you said).    Family   I'm making a concerted effort to get back in touch with family members I've not spoken with in a while. Some of them wouldn't even know me right now if they did talk to me, as I used to be a way different person when they last knew me.  It's not that I'm out for memories, it's just that with the NEW family I've got (they've been my extended-family for nearly seven years) I relized that the relationship I had with my ACTUAL family had wained to the point of non-existence in some cases.  So, send some emails, make some phone calls, see what comes of it.  What can it hurt.  I've tried and tried with a sibling, and it seems the efforts have just fallen by the wayside, so we'll move on and got forth with other things, but if there's nothing stronger than family, then I'm gonna stand by that if I can help it.  I realized something.   Anyone know what August 16/17 2007 Will be?  One big party, if you ask me!  See....the 16th is my Dad's 60th birthday.  The 17th is my 30th birthday.  Those are two milestones BOTH of us WEREN'T supposed to reach. Doctor's told him he wouldn't make that...YEARS ago...and repeatedly....throughout my life, when he and I would go "at it" (stupid things in stupid years, if you ask me) he'd tell ME that I wouldn't make it (because he wouldn't let me if I kept up the way I was acting).  Well. Guess What. I grew up...and he, as usual, counterracted doctor's predictions.  Screw The Doctors. Screw The Predictions. Looks like we're both gonna make those milestones, and I'm gonna sit there with him and enjoy it too.  Mark my words on that.  And mark the words of Van Halen too..   Last Time Wrong time Outside Out of line But this time's our time Right On We'll let it shine    Well - I've wasted enough time typing and you've all wasted enough time reading.  Time to make the rounds of the familiar sites and turn in.  Peace and Axle Grease!   
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  The Cooler   I can't see why Maria Bello and William H. Macy didnt win more awards for this movie. Aside from the gratuitous sex scenes, which I'm not by any means complaining about, this was a GREAT movie.  It was one I was wanting to see for a long time, and it was well worth the wait. I was disappointed it didnt get a run in more theatres, particularly the one here, because I really did want to see it, on subject matter alone.  If you're a fan of poker, or cards, or casinos, see this movie. It's actually very very good, and it will really be worth it.  It's out on DVD now.   Steve-O 
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've posted this on the VHSTRUNGOUT board, but it's too good not to hit in the blog for permanent record.  Everyone's complaining about Eddie Van Halen losing the "classic" sound, and they're complainign worse about the new Van Halen songs...Here's my response   IMHO, This is a thread I've thought long and hard on responding to. The point remains, there never WILL be another Eddie Van Halen. Can people imitate him? Yes. I've sat here for the past week, every nite, for hours, listening to lazertronic work out pieces of Van Halen songs that nobody else i've ever heard (and I've heard a LOT of guitar players) could ever figure out. Is he good? Yeah. Hell Yeah. Is he Eddie Van Halen. No. I tell you this for a reason (it will work out in a second). The statement someone made on here works both ways. Two unique things define Eddie Van Halen. The first is the fact that he could, in fact, pick up ANY guitar, plug it into ANY combination of ANY rigs, adjust two knobs, and SOUND like Eddie Van Halen. The "sound" is Eddie. On the flipside, as good as Jon (Lazertronic) is, if we picked him up, transplanted him to 5150, in front of Eddie's rig, with Eddie's guitar in his hands, playing eddie's lick, as good or better than anyone else, it wouldn't be eddie van halen Again. The "sound" is pure eddie". The fact that even a great guitar player like Jon couldn't replicate (imitate, yes, replicate no) the sound is the other "defining" characteristic of "eddie" And I'm not by ANY means putting Jon Down. I've seen a lot of Van Halen covers, and tributes, and he's by far the best guitar player I've seen of any of them that supposedly do it, professionally, but my point is, regardless of the rig, regardless of the guitar, regardless of the "sound" some people think he's trying to get away from, it's STILL EDDIE, and that's what we need to appreciate folks, that a man that could've died is back there playing music again. That a man that has enough money in his pocket to have walked away from this business 20 years ago, is still doing it, and is still doing it for the fans. He's not doing it for the money, and damned be sure (someone's got a doctor wife on one of these threads to confirm it) he's NOT doing it for his health. It's all for us, and people are spending FAR too much time analyzing and criticizing the music he IS making instead of enjoying the music for what it is.....VAN FUCKIN HALEN! People can say they don't like the new track. I disagree. Does it sound like "classic" van halen? Not ENTIRELY. BUT. Does it sound like the direction the band was headed in when they left off with "Humans Being"? Yes. It's just the progression of time, and this is a band that said they "Picked up where they left off" and having said that, I think the song represents that. Personally, I think the sound is very MUCH there, you just have to listen for it. All most of us are hearing is the tone of the first six chords that relays throught the entire song....listen to the "music" beneath it. It's there. I promise you. Let's leave the note-by-note analysis of the Van Halen songs to Eddie, and let's all, as fans, not as people on a message board, not as web designers, not as bootleggers, not as Sammy's "RedHeads", or Roth's "army", or the "mad mikey" fan club....not of any anything but fans, sit back, pop open a cold one, relax, and enjoy this while it lasts, because we never know when the opportunity for us to see him, hear him, or admire him may not be there, and when we're talking TRUE musicians, TRUE men among men, Like we are Eddie....that's what we need to appreciate. Don't Hate....Appreciate....  There. I'm off my soap box, out of breath, tired, and going to bed. Nite all!   
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay.  I got my domain. I posted a great page.  Now the "new" has worn off and that page that sat in that folder labelled "steve-o's new site" for months is not so appealing. I think I'm gonna re-design it, but then again , those of you who know my sites in the past, know they undergo changes every other day, so this is nothing new to you. The one I got just isn't "clean" looking, streamlined.  I want it clean and streamlined, so that it's appealing to the eyes.    We'll See. I got 48 hours to get to it...couple days off, so I can work on it.  Steve-0
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know......and my friends, all of them, Derek, Jamey, Jamie, Matt, Ray, all of them, will whole heartedly agree with me I'd bet.  What happened to respect for your elders anymore?  Tonight three grandchildren came in the store with their grandmother. The grandmother had just purchased all THREE of them brand new cell phones.  They needed something done on it, that required grandma to get on the phone. Well, whilst grandma was on the phone, the oldest of the three (14 or 15 years old) proceeded to yell in her ear, talk back to her, and treat her JUST as though a grandmother should NOT be treated.  I finally got sick of it, and told him "hey, that's your grandmother, dude".  he acted as though he didnt care and said "and?".  I told him "And, that woman, two generations back is responsible for YOU being IN this world, and if you don't show her a little respect in MY presence, in MY store, I'm gonna be the one that takes you OUT of this world. Now CAN IT".  He shrugged his shoulders.  I had to say something to him again a few minutes later, asking him for a THIRD time to lower his tone with his grandmother, and finally he left the store leaving grandma to work quietly with us.  I apologized to her for saying something to him, and she told me "it's okay, he needed it".  What the hell happened to the respect that one shows for their grandparents anymore?  If I would have pulled that shit with MY grandmother, I'd have about Five less permanent teeth today.  
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally!  Steve-O Has Come Back.....Online.   As I said in a previous post, I got an email the other morning saying that my domain "www.steveonet.com" that I've been waiting for had finally come available.  I pounced on it FAST, and had it snagged within about 10 minutes of the email coming in.    The site is coming along great.  To be honest, it's been in the works a long time, and sitting in a folder on my hard drive.  I've just updated the graphics and stuff, and got a spot to upload it.    MY dns servers are pointing the domain right. If for some of you you still get the error message, clear your cache and hit it again. I've checked with about five people in different areas of the country, and it's working for all of them! Looks like I'm FINALLY going to get that online presence I've wanted to do for a while now.  Let's get the creative juices flowing again!
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After waiting TWO YEARS for one specific domain name to come available...I got an email this morning telling me that www.steveonet.com is available.  I snagged it within seconds of getting the email.  It's mine. And it will be up shortly. (the page is there...it's just pointed at the domain yet.  More VERY Soon.  Progress update shortly
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm posting a link  urlLink here  for all of you to download the Queen song "Mother Love". And the reason I'm doing it is 1) because it's my favorite Queen song, (and hence, my favorite song by my all-time favorite band is naturally, my favorite song ever) 2) Because I wanted all of you "musical" people out there who read my blog, and send me emails about this or that to see that when you and I get into a discussion about music on the chat line, or whatever (Emily...Brin....Jack...all of you) about an artist having "passion" or an artist "giving it his/her all"....well...I want you to see MY definition of what "giving it their all" means..... Download the song...listen to it. It's the LAST THING Freddie Mercury EVER sang.  And, I'm posting some comments I found about the song by Brian May (the guitarist for Queen) that really drive home the point.       Brian May: "Freddie, as normal, got to some point and said "No,no,no,no,no, this isn't good enough, I have to go higher here, I have to put more into this, have to get more power in," so he downs a couple of Vodkas stands up and goes for it, and you can hear the middle eight of Mother Love just soars to incredible heights, and this is a man who can't really stand any more without incredible pain and is very weak, you know, has no flesh on his bones, you know, and you can hear the power, the will that he's still got. It was tough, but there was a lot of joy when were doing the final recordings, and Freddie did not let it become downbeat. He was always up if it was in the recording studio, always full of ideas and enthusiasm, and great passions. The last thing I ever did together with him was that track, Mother Love, which is on Made In Heaven. It was never finished. He never came back to do the final verse, but to the end, even when he couldn't even stand, without propping himself up, he was just giving it his all. You can hear the, the incredible strength of his voice in that track, and the passion that's he putting into it. And we're making it up as we go along. You know, I'm scribbling words on pieces of paper and he's grabbing them and saying, "Roll the tape. I'll do this one." It's just, he knew that it might be the last time he was ever able to sing and, er, in that case it was. The last thing he ever sang was Mother Love. He was going for it harder and higher and more passionate than ever. He got to the penultimate verse and said, 'I can't do any more. On The evening of November 22, 1991, he said "I'll come back and finish it another day when I feel good.' But he never did. On November 23, He Flew Back To London.  He died that night, and they announced it to the world at midnight.      Brian May sang the last verse of that song in Freddie's place.  Overdubs of the very first Freddie Mercury recording, a song called "Going Back" under the surname Larry Lurex were put on the end of the song, to signify "a return to it all".    See, guys, before you ever preach to me about musical "passion"...or a lack of it, look at the words and actions of the man who, to me, made the GREATEST and most beautiful music in the world, 24 hours before he DIED.   
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got up this morning, with a 'hankerin' for some solid food, for the first time in damn near a week. Wife went off to work second job, so it was just me and the cat today.  Strolled on down to Harvey's...ten bucks poorer....snagged me a loaf of Sunbeam Texas Toast (purposely found the one that was a little stale in the back), Eggs, Milk, Bacon, and Orange Juice, and some Aunt Jemima Syrup.   Whipped me up about four (BIG) pieces of French Toast, made out of that thick texas toast, loaded it down with that syrup and butter, couple of crispy pieces of bacon, and a BIG mug of orange juice.  MMM...that hit the spot.   Experiencing my first trials and tribulations of "bittorrent".  Trying to download a Queen Bootleg (WAIT..you say? NOT Van Halen?...yeah...there WAS a life before Van Halen, and it was mostly Queen...) It's going. S..L...O...W...L...Y.....42K a second, 773 Megs. OY!  Just a note to a couple people.  My Dad.  My Father-In-Law. Rich Baxter, and Big Woo-Tang.  Happy Father's Day (to all!).   Will Check In Later. I got a Sammy Hagar Bootleg To Check out.  Peace! Holla!
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's Now A Link At The Top Of The Page to my photoshop art page.  Take a look at it. Maybe you'll enjoy it.  
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think people want the balance more than ever. You know, plant an Ethiopian, feed the rain forest, save the ozone layer--you gotta have that! "Oh woe is me," as a form of self-dramatization, is always fun. It shouldn't be replaced, but there should be a balance. Sooner or later, it's Miller time! Sooner or later, there is some hallelujah, watusi-tailgate, light-up-the-goddamn-sky-it's-finally-the-weekend, okay? And I don't care whether you wear a cowboy hat or your hair is purple, I don't care if you have a wedding ring or a nose ring, sooner or later, there's Miller time! That doesn't mean simple belly laughs, and it doesn't mean high-brow. It just means, "Wanna go have a drink?"  David Lee Roth
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, tonight I get a phone call at the store. The guy I was working with answered (henceforth referred to as "Joe Shack", cause I dont want to use his name without asking).  The customer asked for me, so Joe gave me the phone.  Immediately this customer goes into a cussing, swearing, threatening tirade over something that happened back in may, that I knew really nothing about.  He told me he was coming to the store and kick everyone's ass. I told him if he didnt stop, I was going to hang up, trying to play "good little calm employee".  He kept going. I hung up.  He called back. This time, Joe answered the phone.  Same guy. Same Scenario.  I heard Joe try..."hey...listen pal..." no effect....Joe hung up.   Ten minutes later, in a store full of customers, I'm trying to retrieve a phone from the back room, and the cordless in my pocket rings.....looking at it, I see Joe's on line one in the front, so I had to answer it. Sure enough....."I'm coming up there and @#$%^&(*&() blah blah blah....@#$%^&*( you little @#$%^&*( and when I get there I'm gonna #$%^&*() you........ I told him, calmly, "Okay sir, I have a store full of customers, you do that, and I'll be sure to have the police waiting for you. Gotta go, bye".  I hung up. Calmly assuring myself that was the end of it.  I still felt uneasy. Something about this guy didn't "register" on the old Steve-O scale of "this guy ain't quite right".  Freddie Mercury's line in "I'm going slightly mad" came to mind...."one wave short of a shipwreck..." So...I finished with the customers I had, and made a casual note to the mall guard "hey..keep your eyes open...". He said he would.  LITTLE DID I KNOW.....apparently this dude called 911 and TOLD THEM he was going to my store to kick my ass.....and I'll be damned if that didn't tip of every cop in this town...think about this....a nowhere town, and school is out, this is FUN to these cops....so now they're posted at the doors..of the mall....and as if he wasn't just a little "OFF"  already the dude actually SHOWED UP, and sure enough, the cops nailed him at the front door, 3/4 ways across the mall from anywhere myself or any of our employees were First he calls three times and threatens the employees. Then he calls 911, and makes a terroristic threat...  THEN HE ACTUALLY SHOWS UP!!!! Go figure.  Well, needless to say... this guy's a little "flicted" as we used to say.  Not quite all there.  For You...sir....there's straightjackets, greenleaf, and this song.     I'm Going Slightly Mad Words and music by Freddie Mercury      When the outside temperature rises And the meaning is oh so clear One thousand and one yellow daffodils Begin to dance in front of you - oh dear Are they trying to tell you something You're missing that one final screw You're simply not in the pink my dear To be honest you haven't got a clue  I'm going slightly mad It finally happened - happened I'm slightly mad Oh dear  I'm one card short of a full deck I'm not quite the shilling One wave short of a shipwreck I'm not my usual top billing I'm coming down with a fever I'm really out to sea This kettle is boiling over I think I'm a banana tree Oh dear  I'm going slightly mad It finally happened - happened I'm slightly mad Oh dear  I'm knitting with only one needle Unravelling fast it's true I'm driving only three wheels these days  I'm going slightly mad It finally happened I'm slightly mad Just very slightly mad  And there you have it     OH. AND IF YOU HAVENT HEARD.  THANK COSBY, JELLO PUDDING POPS ARE BACK. HELL YEAH!  Steve-O 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Guys. I just was sent this file. Apparently this guy used an arcade emulator, called MAME (Jamey..you and I know this one) to create this. I think it's so frickin cool!  I flashed back the minute I saw the first clip! IT ROCKS!  CHECK IT OUT  urlLink HERE 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Steve-O Lesson to the Record Companies, And Our Dissection Specimen will be (Drum Roll..) VAN HALEN! (Duh)  Click  urlLink Here 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did this in photoshop.  I did it for the  urlLink Strung Out Forums  but thought you all would like to see it too.  It was a simple stock photo of an old German church, but i added the stained glass windows and guitars, the altar, etc.     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh wait.  That's the sun. Something I haven't seen since Monday. I saw it tuesday, but I was cursing it as "the big hot thing" as I was riding home, in between vomiting sessions.  Gotta try to go back to work today.  That's gonna be tough.  I'm hardly able to keep down solid foods, and what I DO eat goes straight through in a matter of minutes.  My milkshake, which I enjoyed so much....well..I didnt enjoy it for long.  I also gotta face my boss, who probably has no clue why, for the past three days, I wasn't at work in Waycross, like I should have been.  Fun Fun Fun, 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi All.   Everyone has asked what I'm doing with "pimp" this and "pimp" that. Well, I guess they're right. The "pimps" are just a phase I've grown out of.  It's About Time (thank's Sammy) for a change.  So, I'm going with a great little catchphrase that I've picked out of my favorite song...  Here Is My New Contact Information  E-Mail: hasn't changed  urlLink vanhalenrules@mchsi.com  AOL Instant Messenger:   seventhseal2004   Yahoo! Messenger:   seventhseal2004   MSN Messenger:   seventhseal2004@hotmail.com    And, for those of you who DON'T Know what the "Seventh Seal" is...first...and foremost, it's a Bible verse...Revelations Chapter 8.     And when he had opened the seventh seal, there was silence in heaven about the space of half an hour. .    What It Means is this:   The opening of the seventh seal brought about silence in heaven. The great quietness in heaven depicts the terrible plagues that were to come upon the earth. "A silent note struck the cords of heaven," because of the tremendous compassion that heaven has for the earth. For one half-hour heaven stood still waiting to hear what orders would be given to the seven angels. They were given seven great plagues to pour out upon the earth. Never before nor since, have any judgements as severe as these come upon the earth  This title is also that of a film (and a book) by Ingmar Bergman, which, if you're literary enough to follow it...you should all check out.   Amazon.com says:   Max Von Sydow plays a knight returning from the Crusades to encounter an apocalyptic scenario inspired by the Book of Genesis. He plays chess with Death (Bengt Ekerot), sees a manacled witch, watches a band of flagellants go by--all of it foretelling an inevitable end to life. Unabashedly allegorical and lyrical and existing in a world unto itself, the film is enormously mesmerizing no matter what one thinks of the weighty meanings Bergman has attached to it all.    Not coincidentally, this is also the title of my favorite Van Halen Song. I only knew of this since 1995, but knew of the other meanings far prior.  Most of my signatures on my message boards, and my emails, etc, read:       Broken now, I can't help but feel Someone cracked the seventh seal Nothin' sacred, nothin' left unturned When nothin's simple, then nothin's learned         It's on the Balance album. Check it out.  It's Very Good.   There. I've clarified why I changed everything around.  
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I usually leave the mushy "wife" posts to  urlLink Jamie . He does them so much better than me. But I gotta tell ya this....sometimes you just gotta realize just how much you can love a person before it really sinks in...if that makes sense.  Tuesday, I came home from Waycross, sicker than any human being should be without being in the hospital, and I crawled in bed.  A couple hours later, my wife came home, and stayed with me for hours....she fixed me the little bit of soup I couldnt keep down....she went to the store and got the endless supply of gatorade....she stayed with me and put up with me getting up endless times in the middle of the night....and just when I started to be able to TRY and eat solid food, I craved strawberry ice cream.  She was gone to the store.  I called her cell phone to ask her to get some and dissapointedly heard her cell phone ringing in the next room. She had left without it.  Uncannily, ten minutes later, she appeared with a Strawberry milk shake from Steak & Shake.  How much of a "connection" is that. Guess it just goes to show you, sometimes you don't realize what you've got until it hits you all at once.    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Acme Mapper   You can go out to this site and map any zip code and get satellite images of that town....  It's Bad Ass! Try It
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know. The pictures aren't showing up.  It's not me. The server is showing them. The paths are correct.  The pictures just arent showing up. Hopefully it will resolve itself.   Sorry Guys.  Steve-O
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets just say that the last two days have not been pleasant ones.  I went (as the previous post will show) to a Japanese steakhouse in Waycross and got some food, and about 3AM tuesday morning it caught up with me.  Since then, it's been nothing but EXCRUTIATING pain in my abdomen, and vomiting, etc etc etc.  It just wouldn't stop.  We know it was that food, since it was the only thing I ate, and the other person who ate it got sick too....just not as sick as me.  What's even worse, when it hit, I was in Waycross SUPPOSED to be working at that store in place of a friend who was on vacation (she was already short-staffed).  It was so bad, I couldn't hardly stand up, so I just went back to my in-laws house and tried to wait it out, because I was supposed to work there today too.....and it didn't pass. I called my doctor in Valdosta, and he said to get home into my OWN bed (he said it would help...) and to do NOTHING but sleep, go to the bathroom, and in between drink as much gatorade as possible. He said take as many showers as possible, as hot as possible, as often as possible.  So. I got my Father-In-Law to drive my car home, and his wife followed in her car. We had to "stop" a couple times on the way home (75 miles). When I got to the house, I tried to get out of the car, and it hit me worse....a ten minute "session" in my driveway..... and I had to damn near be helped in to the house.  When I got there...I took a sleeping pill, and four tylenol, washed it down with a half a bottle of gatorade and SAT in a hot shower waiting for it to take effect.  Slept 9 hours....got up....ate a half a bowl of soup, which didnt stay with me long....another sleeping pill, another 12 oz. of gatorade and another hot shower...and out for another 10 hours....Every two or three hours during these sleeping episodes, got up to use the bathroom, and drink more gatorade...Woke up this morning at 8AM.  Took another shower...another sleeping pill, four more tylenol...and woke up at 2PM. Felt REMARKABLY better.  No more vomiting, and my stomach wasn't going in cirles anymore...but my lips were dry, and my fingertips were numb...a BIG time sign of "you need more fluids" so I got a bottle of Pedialyte...and a bottle of Apple Juice and mixed it half and half (Thank you VERY VERY MUCH SHERRY BAXTER!) and drank the entire bottle....not the tastiest thing in the world, but it works... Right now, after a little solid food, and a LOT of gatorade, I'm feeling alright. My abdomen is KILLING me from all the vomiting (muscle spasms I guess) I probably won't stay up long enough to let it kick back in though. Gonna take another sleeping pill, four more tylenol, a bottle of gatorade, and out til tomorrow morning.  Stay away from Fuji in Waycross, and if anyone sees Tim Cavagnaro...give him my regards, as his manager didnt even PRETEND to care.  
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink       Click the picture to see where our seats are for Van Halen! 
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night on my way home,. I stopped at Fuji Steakhouse and got a steak and chicken plate to go.    Shortly after I ate it I started feeling very bad, my stomach was hurting real bad, my head hurt, and sure enough, throwing up ensued.  It could ONLY be the Fuji , because it's the only thing I ate yesterday  Sure enough, I was up all night, sick as a dog.  This morning I got up and my father-in-law told me that it made my mother-in-law sick last time SHE ate there, same symptoms.  I dare not go in there and say something about it...but...I still feel like shit....and I've got to work today for like 10 hours.  So I'm gonna try to get everything I got to do today done by 1:00 when the 2nd shift man gets here, and bolt out of here about that time.  Been on Milk of magnesia and have gone through eight 16oz. bottles of water since 3AM.  Not working.  Fun fun fun! Steve-O 
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw Garfield Saturday Night.  Funny. You should all check it out.  The season premiere of Six Feet Under was last night too. Rather disturbing bit at the end, but nonetheless, VERY VERY GOOD. Everyone should call their cable or satellite provider and order HBO just for this show.   Oh.  I'll be updating from Waycross (If I update at all).  Got to go there and work...three days....starting....right now.  HOLLA!  Steve-O
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      June 4, 2004    SCOTT STAPP AND MARK TREMONTI READY NEW MATERIAL FOR FIRST POST-CREED RELEASES    One of the most successful songwriting partnerships and groups in the history of the music business disbands after nearly a decade together.   New York --- After nearly a decade together, Creed has decided to disband. During their 8 years and 3 albums together (My Own Prison, Human Clay, Weathered) Creed achieved countless Rock & Roll milestones and sold over 30 million albums worldwide. With their unprecedented success at radio and their captivating live shows, Creed became one of the most successful acts to rule the charts over the past ten years.  Creed songwriter/ guitarist Mark Tremonti has decided to join forces with Creed drummer Scott Phillips, original Creed bassist Brian Marshall and former Mayfield Four singer/ songwriter Myles Kennedy. The new band, named Alter Bridge, will release their debut album on Wind-up Records on August 10th of this year. Expect a promotional acoustic tour of radio stations later this Summer, followed by a worldwide tour to begin in late August or early September.   Creed songwriter / singer Scott Stapp has been busy in the studio writing and recording over the past several months. His first post-Creed recording will be featured on an album coming on August 31st via Wind-up Records that will pool together superstar talent, as they individually offer compositions inspired by the film The Passion of the Christ. Simultaneously to tracking his contributions to the Passion title, Stapp will continue to work with producer 7 Aurelius, and has joined forces with Canadian rockers The Tea Party to work on his solo debut.  On the dissolution of Creed, Tremonti commented, "It's kind of sad to end a chapter of your life, but it's also exciting to be starting a new one. We'll always be proud of the music we made with Creed, but Alter Bridge gives me the opportunity to start over with a different perspective and a more evolved direction. This band begins and ends with the love of the music." Phillips continues, "Creed was definitely a once-in-a-lifetime experience, but I'm really excited to be starting over as well. The most significant things that we are taking from the Creed experience are the lessons that we learned. We truly believe that the decisions we've made for our future are the right ones. After writing and rehearsing the new material, we are confident that we've made the right choices."  Stapp shared, "Creed was one of the most amazing journeys through music and friendship I am blessed to say I was a part of. I made memories I can never replace! I just want to thank the fans who supported us and became a part of the Creed experience. We could not have accomplished anything without you!(fans)."   Also in 2004, Wind-up Records will be releasing a Creed Greatest Hits compilation. Details will be made available as plans for the album take shape.  close window    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Today I am publishing my first compilation of mixes and remixes to Van Halen Strungout. It can be found by clicking the banner above, and heading into the forums.  The forums require registration to get to the "bootlegs" section, but it's free, only takes a minute, and is extremely cool.  Once you've registered, head over to the "Van Halen Boots" section of the forum, and look for a link entitled "The Best Of Van Halen Live - Steve-O's Live Mixes"  You can download each song by clicking the "Attachment" link on each post.  Enjoy! 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The simplicities of life are becoming complexities, and it shouldnt be this way.  I've come to discover that the was once and former a race to see who could please the customer the best and it is now long gone, turned instead into a race to see who can be more difficult to get along with, and who can be a bigger asshole.  Why is it that some people feel the urge, or the need, or the necessity (if you will) to make life difficult.  The simple transaction of exchanging money or a handshake for a good or service has now become part of the never ending rat race to see who can piss each other off first.....and you know what....it sucks. People complain of a lack of customer service...it's not a lack of customer service on our part.  They say "serve the customer, or serve the people that do..."...well...how can we serve our customers when the people that serve US are blatantly and flagrantly TRYING NOT to help.    Go figure.  
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took down the original post from Jeff Spindel, and I took down the related posts to it.  If only one of the many readers here (and I'm averaging about 75 a day now) is offended by it, even though it wasn't my words, and wasn't my actions, then it doesnt belong here. There was apparently some confusion regarding just which "Jeff" it was...and rest assured, the Jeff I referred to in all those posts still is scum of the earth, and my only hope is that he'll one day come to his senses, see the error of his ways, and offer the apology that is due....and you can bet I'll just hold my breath until that happens. At any rate. It's gone. Sorry if it offended anyone.   I also took his link off the page, as it looks, to me , like he deleted the blog altogether.  Steve-O
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sitting here, quietly (Amy's sleeping) just typing a few random thoughts.    One day till the start of the Van Halen tour. It really IS the tour nobody  thought would happen. I've grown so fond of their music and their style, that  I'll go on record as saying they are now officially my favorite band. Not  withstanding Queen, naturally, because they're assumed to be in the &quot;zero&quot; spot  (one spot higher than number one). You can, after all, always go back to Queen,  like going home to mother.         First Reagan. Now Ray Charles. This week sucks if you're cool, cause  apparently all the good ones are dying.&nbsp;    &quot;Do it right or don't do it at all. That comes from my mom. If there's  something I want to do, I'm one of those people that won't be satisfied until I  get it done. If I'm trying to sing something and I can't get it, I'm going to  keep at it until I get where I want it.&quot; - Ray Charles        This is a picture fom the hard Rock Cafe, in Orlando.&nbsp; Yes Folks, that  IS what it looks like. That IS actually one of Eddie Van Halen's guitars, and I  WAS that close, and touched it.&nbsp; I'm never washing this hand again.&nbsp;     For all those who wonder, I've gotten the Photo CD's organized from the wedding  and they'll be mailed out as soon as I can get them out.&nbsp;     Steve-O   &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Got to give a very special thanks to one person in particular.  I have to say, one of the most beautiful memories we'll both have of this wedding will be the photos that Kim took.  For this, we will forever both be grateful, as you have no idea (cause I can't post a hundred pictures here)how good they really are. Kim, you're talents are perhaps far more than what even YOU are aware of..and if our wedding was the first stepping stone in what looks to be a promising career in the field....well then we're both honored to have been part of it.   Steve & Amy 
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Well. Where to begin.   I guess, first off, we should start off with a &quot;thank-you&quot;.&nbsp;  Thank you to all of those who made this possible. Thanks to all of you who  attended, and shared this special day with Amy and myself. Thanks to all those  who were gracious in their gifts or their giving.   To those in attendance, I'm sorry it was so hot.&nbsp; We went  as fast as we could, and we made sure to have plenty of punch and cake.     To those not in attendance.&nbsp; Most of you had valid reasons for not coming,  and I thank you for, in advance, telling us you wouldn't make it. Don't worry,  you'll get enough photos on a CD to say you WERE there.&nbsp;&nbsp; Some of you  had a long drive, some of you have tyrant bosses and couldn't get off work.&nbsp;  Some of you (and you know who you are) have poor excuses for not attending, and  for that, you will, for a long time, be the subject of smite and spite. It was,  however, one joyous occasion for all.&nbsp;     Thursday began with a final &quot;single guy&quot; roadtrip with me and the Wootang.&nbsp;  Had a BLAST doing it too.&nbsp; Got all fitted for our tuxes....got them back to  the house and just relaxed.&nbsp;        Rehearsal Dinner   Friday went great, Geoffrey got fitted, and it was damn close to  perfect.&nbsp; Rehearsal and rehearsal dinner at Wongs, enough food to feed an  ARMY. Thanks to Paul Tang for making everything so good!   Saturday morning, up at the crack of dawn.&nbsp; Off to set up  chairs in the park.&nbsp; Already, I could tell it would be HOT.        Before The Wedding (L-R) Me, Best Man Geoffrey, Woo Tang In Front   Back to the Wooten house to get changed for the big event.&nbsp;  Lots of offers to go to Mexico   Off to the wedding. Sure enough. Hotter than we all would have  liked.        The wedding   The wedding went fast...very fast, one because the music quit  working, and two because we wanted OUT of that sun.&nbsp; Off to the reception   &nbsp;       The reception       Amy at Daytona Beach   Then...off to Orlando for some down-time.&nbsp; We had a great  time.&nbsp; Got to take a side-quest to Daytona Beach...       Universal Studios was cool as hell. Lots of pictures, but by far, the coolest  ones are Amy and I in front of our favorite &quot;Stars&quot; on the Hollywood walk of  fame.&nbsp; I got Larry Hagman (He's J.R. EWING!) and Amy got Audrey Hepburn.&nbsp;  Kick ass!       The obligatory picture. For all my homies. I HAD to take this one. That's Dale  Earnhardt Jr's Number 8 Car.   &nbsp;   We went to the Magic Kingdom the next day. Lots of neat pictures  there too, but none anyone wants to see.&nbsp;     That night we went to &quot;Shogun&quot; Japanese steakhouse.&nbsp; GOOD FOOD!   Got up the next morning and came home.&nbsp; Had a good time  altogether.   Time to get back to a normal life again. Back to work.   Thanks all!  Steve-O and Amy  
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         (Picture Tribute By Steve-O)  I see all over the news "Reagan this..." or "Reagan that", and I think to myself "why can't they just let it rest".  Here they go again, like Michael Jackson...like Janet Jackson...like Scott Petersen.  Then I really evaluate what they're doing, and it's nothing of the sort. The one person who actually DESERVES all this pomp and circumstance, and media coverage is actually getting it, when he deserves it the most.    Don't get me wrong.  I'm not a fan of Ronald Reagan. That's not because of any political affiliation, or party lines, but rather because when the world was worshipping Ronald Reagan for ending the cold war, I was only old enough to worship Ronald McDonald for inventing McNuggets.    What I do know, however, is the rich history of what he did, and at my age, I can come to appreciate it further, because in my own way, I know that a lot of the freedoms I have come to know and take for granted, he fought to ensure were mine for the taking, and while I never followed "Reaganomics" or the "era" as it were, I know this much...Ronald Reagan may very well be the reason this country, as we know it, is what it is today, and in his own ways is a contributing factor to every one of our freedoms which we hold so precious. For that...regardless of how old I am or was, I will forever be grateful.  
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Guys. 9PM.  Time to watch the GNR Behind The Music.  Tomorrow- off for Waycross, Wedding, and Honeymoon. Be back In A Week!  Sorry....but you'll all have to live without my wit and humor for that long. Major update when I get back!  Holla! And thanks for all the support!  Steve-O
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      VAN HALEN SHAKE IT ON STAGE FOR THE FIRST TIME THIS DECADE!: Van Halen have just completed their dress rehearsal gig for the 2004 tour kicking off next week. One person at the show was melodicrock.com reader Rob Golenberg, who e-mailed this in immediately upon getting home from the show: "Just got home from the Van Halen dress rehearsal at Sony studios in LA. What a show. They did the whole show and it rocked. Set is cool. Opened with Jump and did a total of 5 DLR era tunes (including Somebody Get Me A Dr.). During Eddie's solo, Wolfgang comes out and plays with him. 2 hr show which will not disappoint! A must see when they go out." The set also features the 3 brand new songs from the upcoming compilation Best Of Both Worlds; namely, It's About Time, Up For Breakfast and Learning To See.
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in bad need of some "chill pills".  First I find out that I might not get the tuxes on time, then I find out I will. Then I find out that one of my closest friends might have made hotel reservations in the wrong town...still waiting on that one.... I just have to keep mumbling...  I am one with the universe I am one with the universe I am one with the universe I am one with the universe I am one with the universe I am one with the universe I am one with the universe...... 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was the 1.99 PPV special on directv.&nbsp; That's my review (and I think I've gave it too much already)  Steve-o 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp; The entire Live Aid show will be available on DVD later this year after Warner Vision won the rights to release the classic concert. It's expected to be released on 4DVDs in November. This is great news for fans, as it's the last performance of "led zeppelin" under the official name, it's Freddie Mercury's finest hour...and I can justify buying it to my wife, because damn JOAN BAEZ is on it.&nbsp; HEH HEH HEH! 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well - I have my domain, steveonet.com.  Last friday. I registered 5150.org, with the same provider.  Today, the domain still isn't working.  They won't return phone calls. They won't answer emails.  They won't tell me why it is they let me register a domain, and PAY for it, when the domain is OBVIOUSLY owned by someone else.....so I just went ahead and cancelled both...if they're not gonna help...I'm not gonna pay them. And I cancelled the credit card number they were being payed with too, so now they can't take the money either.    So. No more steveonet.com No 5150.org.  Back to my blog!  http://steveonet.cjb.net  maybe I'll find a TRUSTWORTHY network provider and get it up real soon   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE SYSTEM FAILS MEGADETH: Megadeth have selected  the first single from their upcoming CD,  The System Has Failed,  due on September 14 through Sanctuary Records. The single will go to metal radio around July 19 and rock radio approximately July 26.  The System Has Failed  was recorded at Phase Four studios in Tempe, Arizona and is set to feature cover artwork by Ed Repka. Joining mainman Dave Mustaine on the recording are drummer Vinnie Colaiuta and bassist Jimmy Sloas. Additional lead guitar tracks were laid down by former Megadeth guitarist Chris Poland.  The upcoming CD will be preceded by reissues by all seven of Megadeth's studio albums recorded during the group's tenure with Capitol Records. Mustaine remixed, remastered and restored each album, all of which will feature previously unreleased tracks as well as demos and alternate mixes, and newly penned liner notes.  The System Has Failed  will be Megadeth's first since the announcement that Mustaine was disbanding the group following a serious accident in early 2002. At the time, it was unknown if severe nerve damage in his left arm would leave him able to perform again.  YAY!   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      urlLink        These are screen caps of my van halen folders on my hard drive (Click them). Now THAT'S a collection!  
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well.  Saturday I got off work at 2PM.  Wife got off at 4.  Took off For Waycross....got there about 6PM (give or take) and went out to dinner with the in-laws.... Had a good time. We went Saturday night, after Dinner, and went to the 911 office in Blackshear (Amy's sister works there) and we got to witness first-hand exactly what happens when some drunk guy in an oldsmobile TANK crosses the center line on one of the biggest highways in Georgia.  First, you get STUCK in Blackshear, because you can't get home...because they've blocked off ALL of Highway 84....next...when you DO get to go home, the traffic is blocked in all but one lane, and you get to see all the cars that the drunk guy (who's now dead) destroyed, and the jaws of life mangled further.  It not exactly a PROUD feeling to know that I got to sit in the dispatchers office and listen to them clean up the first weekend fatality in the ENTIRE STATE....now THERE'S an accomplishment.  Got up Sunday morning, and went and put flowers on the graves of Amy's family (back to Blackshear). I'll tell you what...CREEE-EEE-EEEE-PY...it was worse at dusk..which was the night before..yikes..  Sunday afternoon we went to my sister-in-law's house....had some KICK ASS BBQ chicken, beans, potato salad (Big Ma' and Linda Faye's Potato salad RULES!!), cherry cobbler, oh...too much food.... Had a good time with the kids too....  Monday...got up, went to breakfast with a friend, then went out to his house for a little while, and then headed home.... It was a good time...had a blast. Now it's time to get back to normal daily activities.  Make a little money...  Steve-O   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They say no news is good news. Guess this is good news. I'm Alive.  Nothing else to report.  Just checking in.     
    
</post>



<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well - we're getting the full effects of a tropical storm hitting 200 miles south of us, and we're headed for the second effects of a hurricane that'll hit south of that.  YAY! Lack of business! YAY! Lack of customers! YAY! BORED TO TEARS!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been almost three whole years since I stepped into a room with any sort of semi-talented musicians in a way that was intended to be productive.  It's been almost a year since I last saw Howie, longer still since I had anything to do with V20 or the music. I've never shared the demos we did, pardon the exception of a few close friends...and I swore off ever having stepped into another room full of musicians again.....That having been said, once again, I owe Woo-Tang money from a bet....because once again, I found myself in that situation. My friend Jon has put together the beginnings of a band (AD: BASS PLAYER NEEDED!) He has a drummer, but he's out of practice (and it wouldn't take much go get him BACK into it, very easy).  Jon is an excellent guitar player.....but has to get out of that van halen mindset to really broaden his horizons, and is doing a fantastic job for only having really played outside the van halen setting a few times.  Ruben...whoa....Ruben has got a set of pipes on him bigger than a redneck chevy.  I heard this guy sing...and he blew me away.....soup him  up just a little (and I can teach him that) and I'm convinced he could sing anything.   Just for shits and giggles, not that they're gonna play it or consider it (they might who knows) I wanted to see if I still had what it "took" to start clean with a song they'd never considered and get them all going the same direction, and I picked one I just KNEW they  wouldn't  be able to do..Van Halen's "Top Of The World"....and sonofabitch...in ten minutes, they had it nailed. Ruben had never heard the song, Will, the drummer, probably the same, and the first run through, I halfheartedly sang it for them (and I'm told I "nailed" parts of it...) and in the second running, they had it....and my jaw hit the fuckin floor..... There are enough songs that instantly came to my mind that I'm sure we could put before these guys, and they'd nail them instantly.  At the beginning of the nite, my statement was "i'm not sure he can do that" and at the end of the nite my statements were " I have full faith he can nail that".  And what's even more strange....each one of them, individually, as though they were trying not to let the others know they said it, took me aside, and told me they WANT me back next time. They actually appreciated what I do. It's fuckin amazing. Three years since I felt that urge to be creative in a setting like that, but tonite, I was TOTALLY comfortable getting behind a drum kit and messing around, playing a little bit with the guitar, and even singing. Things Jeff Spindel took two (plus) years to get out of me, I was comfortable doing in this setting, with these guys, within an hour of being there, and what's even better, they made me feel WELCOME...like my input actually mattered. It's gonna be strange to hear what Jon actually thinks of my input, and ultimately, it's gonna be HIS word that tells me whether or not I'm GOING back...beacause it was his invitation that got me there...but I'll tell you what...if I never go back, for whatever reason, for the four hours I was there, to have done what I did, and to be told "dude, you helped us so much tonite"....I can go to bed knowing "yup...part of it is still there..." with the urge to bring back what WAS there "little by little".  Woo-tang was right. I went back it, after I swore it off, and I loved every minute of it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lacy Van Zant fathered three rock singers   . JACKSONVILLE, Florida (AP) -- Lacy Van Zant, father of members of the Southern rock bands Lynyrd Skynyrd and .38 Special, died Tuesday of pulmonary illness. He was 89.  Van Zant died at his Jacksonville home, according to a release posted on Lynyrd Skynyrd's Web site  He was the father of Ronnie Van Zant, the founder of Lynyrd Skynyrd, and Johnny Van Zant, the band's current lead singer. Ronnie Van Zant and two other band members died in a 1977 plane crash near McComb, Mississippi.  Another son, Donnie Van Zant, was a member of .38 Special.  Van Zant, known for his long beard, white hair and overalls, purchased music equipment, drove the bands to shows, lent them money and repaired their vehicles. Early versions of Lynyrd Skynyrd would practice at his home, which he later opened to fans so they could see the bands' gold and platinum records.  "He was the father of Southern rock 'n' roll, as far as I am concerned," Johnny Van Zant told The Florida Times-Union on Wednesday.  Lynyrd Skynyrd will postpone its show Friday in Louisville, Kentucky, to September 26, and its show Saturday in Greenville, Wisconsin, to August 20, according to the band's Web site.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week I made some welcomed additions to my DVD Collection. Most people know I don't buy DVD's unless they're concerts or Robin Williams. This is what I picked up.  Megadeth - Rude Awakening Journey - Live 2001 (Had to re-purchase this one) Bon Jovi - This left feels right (Live) Sammy and The Waboritas - The Long Road To Cabo Tori Amos - Welcome To Sunny Florida  Enjoying them thoroughly! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello me...meet the real me And my misfit's way of life A dark black past is my Most valued possession Hindsight is always 20-20 But looking back it's still a bit fuzzy Speak of mutally assured desturction? Nice story...tell it to Reader's Digest!!! Feeling paraonid True enemy or false friend? Anxiety's attacking me and My air is getting thin I'm in trouble for the things I haven't got to yet I'm chomping at the bit and my Palms are getting wet, sweating bullets Hello me...it's me again You can subdue but never tame me It gives me a migraine headache Thinking down to your level Yea, just keep on thinking it's my fault And stay an inch or two outta kicking distance Mankind has got to know His limitations Feeling claustrophobic Like the walls are closing in Blood stains on my hands and I don't know where I've been I'm in trouble fro the things I haven't got to yet I'm sharpening the axe and my Palms are gettingwet, sweating bullets Well, me...it's nice talking to myself A credit to dementia Some day you too will know my pain And msile its blacktooth grin If the war inside my head Won't take a day off I'll be dead My icy fingers claw your back Here I come again Feeling paranoid True enemy or false friend? Anxiety's attacking me And my air is getting thin Feeling claustrophobic Like the walls are closing in Blood stains on my hands And I don't know where I've been Once you committed me Now you've acquitted me Claiming validity For your stupidity I'm chomping at the bit I'm sharpening the axe Here I come again, whoa! Sweating bullets  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jonn Kerry. You have no right to use the song "dreams". It's not DREAMS....it's  NIGHTMARE with you in office.  TURN OFF MY SONG, BITCH!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>