<Blog>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY...2days man! so damn exctied, i just cut joe and zady's hair...damn good job, ((Joe dont friggin listen to  zady)) tsk tsk, im going to DC fo sho, but im grounded this fucken blow, sry didnt mean to cuss.  im on the fone with this really really big LOSER!...his name is Alejandro.  Yea my mom's best friend's mom passed away today! so damn sad....
      
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hEy guys....well today has been a pretty goooooooooooo0d day! I woke up and made pancakes AGAin, except this time it was for my family, then i did my hair which by the way looks pretty darn good. lol. THEn i went to TARGET to get some last minute things for DC, THEn i went to OLD NAVY, bought some cute clothes, and later on at 6ish Im going to ISLANDS' with homies lol, if you want to join just call me up, rite now im writing my name on my film roles for DC and eating RED VINES mmmmmmmm mmmmmmm good! lol well im outie luv ya'll
      
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS!DRINKING MAKES YOU DO DUMB THINGS! 
      
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEy! 4 MORE DAYS UNTIL D.C.~! ahhhHH im so excited! Im really bored right now...yesterday night I went to Lindsy's Competition for her singing... she did a GREAT job she got 3rd place! i was so proud of her! and then we went to SPOONS and i met this really cute waiter...AND THEN...i went back to Lindsy's house and i ended up spending the night over there, and when we woke up  i made the kids pancakes! mmmmm mmmmm goooood! ((damn im a good cook)) and then i came home...and then zady took me to the AT&T store...my dumb fone broke, so im gettin a new fone fo sho, but i MIGHT get a flip fone! *SO HAPPY* my fone was ghetto! ...haha and now im waiting for my mom...hopfully she'll take me shopping today! I'm SOOOOOO damn boRED! ugh...well anyways im oUTie! call the cell! ((it still works, but it just looks a lil beat up)) ;o)
      
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      *HeArTbRoKeN* Seriously why did it have to end like this... Lying wasn't kool I was nothing but nice to you What Happened? Just be a man and call me and tell me PLEASE!                                        _OUT_  
      
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hola Amigos!...I am soooooooo tired....::::YaWn:::: I went to bed pretty early, i think i was like 11:00pm and woke up at around 10:00am...*hehe*...so i go downstairs to see if zady came home, NOPE he didnt, and i knew he went to  a party last night and he probably got a wEeEeEeE bit drunk...and obviously didnt come home because he was drinking so he spends the night at joes house...i called him at around 10:45 this morning and he answers i think i woke him up...can you say ((HANG OVER)) lol and he makes it even more obvious because when he usually spends the night at friends houses he comes home early like 8:00 early...but not this time..eH anyways as long as hes okay!!!!!! I'm bored already and the day has just begun! i feel like going shopping but im to lazy to get dressed for that, i woke up an hour ago and im not dressed yet...pittiful man well call me up 6.8.6.0.4.7.8! im outie bye ya'll
      
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...So yesterday was a pretty bad day, Skool was gay as always, then Mireya Olivia and I went to the SHHS baseball game...we didn't watch much of that because they suck so we went to watch swimmers((DAMN)) LOL, then i went home, ate dinner with the famila and then went to beccas because Lizzi's here! YAY!...it wasn't fun...i was really fed up with fredrick,Malcolm and Caleb, they really bug me...Then Drew  said some mean stuff to olivia and she started crying and i was with her the rest of the night...Olivia and I are going thru the same stuff w/ guys! UGH its hell i swear...Then when my brother zady picked me up it was about 10:10pm..and we watched the good 'ol Television...and today i woke up at around 10am and took a shower and went for a jog with my doggy, yea yea i know i did things opposite i took a shower then went to sweat then took another one...i tend to do that sometime, you'll just have to forgive me... :op...I have no idea what i'm doing today...so how bout you guys call me up 6.8.6.0.4.7.8....that's my cellie...leave me  a really nice message saying how much you luv me...Well I'm Outie! LUV YA'LL
      
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! This is my First entry... Today was a very crappy day, I never knew a guy could hurt me so badly, i've faced rejection ((ehem OlIVA)) you always say i've never faced it..yea well now i have and it BLOWS, and i was walking to lunch with lindsy and mireya and i just totally fall on my messed up knee then on top of that i had to walk home ((dammit joe j/k)) so yea wasnt a great day, OH YEA i got a D- on my Ham test... IM outie luv ya'll
      
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY YAY ~~~~~~~~~~~~!!!!!!!!! okay if you havent hear im going out with Sean G. hehe im really happy...any ways thats my day! bye
      
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...So I saw Hondro today...hes back to him self...well at spirit he is at least lol...physically..eh hehe love you man...tomorrows the last dance ...I'm crossing my fingers "something" special will happen tomorrow! hehehe im praying!lol anyways YAY 95% on my wallace test! WOO wOOO! hehe 
      
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So yesterday I found out the most devistating news of my life...my bestest friend Alejandro got into an accident...I love him so damn much I didn't know what to think, I didn't know if was okay, If he was going to be there by my side when we graduate Jr. High and High School. I didn't know what to do...Just imagining life with out him was the worst thing I have ever thought in my life...its been two days only and school, LIFE just isn't the same...Yea hearing his voice over the phone and knowing he's really Okay just puts me at eeze...   God wanted us to really realize how much we need You Alejandro, and how we CAN'T live without you you're a big part of my life and of other peoples lives I know you will cherish like 10 times more than you did. And i know you'll charish All Of Your Loved Ones.  I Love You Alejandro 
      
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys...today was an okay day....WOOOOOOOOOO HOOOOOOOOOOOOO testing is OoVvEeRr! YAY! lol...well i got 4 ft on the high jump...wink wink lol sean...thats pretty bad but oh well...yea ...soOooOOo...SEAN YOU BEST TELL ME IF YOU KNOW WHATS GOOD FOR YOU...AND YOU KNOW YOU CANT RESIST THAT FACE OF MINE :O(...HEHEH   so it was really wierd today...i started thinking about who might ask me to Promo...or i might just go stag...hmmmmmm we'll just see if im going to have a prince to kiss in the end... ((i'm crossing my fingers...i hope "the guy" askes me!))  Anyways i gotta jet...going to get my nails done! wedding tomorrow! YiPPie! okay not really                    Look i just flew away in my plane! Bye
      
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys...well it's official...Mrs. Gaer hates my with a passion, she cant "trust" me anymore...oh grief LOL....well i just found out today that my knee is dumb stilll and i might have to drop soccer for good! arg! i refuse to ...NEVER!....anyways Im Out   Oh...Heres a special one to Joe...I'm sorry about the news  Just remember we are all with you through this I know its not easy, but you have a strong soul, you'll make it... just remeber my door is ALWAYS open, no matter what or when...   Just remeber that...I Love You 
      
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...well today was an okay day... everyone seemed to like my hair thats a goo oooo oooo d thing.Cat 6 testing blows as usual....but anyways its my bed time     "Im going mom!"                                               -Gotta Jet-
      
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well...i got my hair cut again today, rather cute i'd say. anywho...Cat 6 testing is really boring...wow i finish so fast, but i have to admit im trying a weeeeeeeeeeE bit because the high school see's it....s0o eh..im not lookin forward to high school as much as i was. but im going to have to do it either way...might as well make the best of it...lets just put it this way...guys suck. i think Mr. Wallace thinks im dumb beacuse i got a B- on his last test...whatevers...Well i gotta jet...bye luv y'all
      
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh by the way! G-R-E-A-T job joe! told you you'd knock em' dead! ...oh and i  really dont want your condoms anymore...you need the protection nOT me!!!!!!!!!!!! lol                     Gotta Jet  
      
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All For You  Nothing I say wil convince you that I love you For some reason you don’t believe me. You don’t want to believe my feeling for you Why? Is it because you’re not sure you can return my love Or is it because you simply don’t feel that way about me Can it be that you’re afraid of love Is it to you like a maples journey? Let me be your map Your compass Let me be your guide, your love Let me be yours Or let me know why it can not be  Id get on my knees and beg for you to love me I’d kill for a chance to win your love To be the object of your deepest affection I’d die for you I’d give blood and precious life for you I’d conquer my fears and yours for you  All this just to convince you that I love you.                          -Ilyana Ari  ...wow i never know a single person could crush me like this. or anyone for that matter,  If your that person and your reading this...Break out of your shell...be honest be YOU!                         I Gotta Jet 
      
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey guys, boring day. i got a really cute dresssss today...not much to say except, GOOOOOD LUCK JOE, YOU'LL DO AN AWSOME JOB TOMORROW ASKIN HER TO PROM! LOve Ya'Ll  
      
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...YAY..im going to SUSHI MOMO tonight, mmmm mmm gooood! lol, today was an okay day, i didnt eat lunch tho! arg that made me angry...hmmm oh well, LINDSY BABE GETWELL SOOOOON, I MISS YOU! HOLY MOLY i threw the discis 55ft today! i was so proud of myslef...okay today was too boring, there isnt much to talk about! im outie love ya'lll!
      
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...YAY..im going to SUSHI MOMO tonight, mmmm mmm gooood! lol, today was an okay day, i didnt eat lunch tho! arg that made me angry...hmmm oh well, LINDSY BABE GETWELL SOOOOON, I MISS YOU! HOLY MOLY i threw the discis 55ft today! i was so proud of myslef...okay today was too boring, there isnt much to talk about! im outie love ya'lll!
      
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WOO WOO back from DC...damn that was an experience of a life time, i wouldnt have changed it for anything, sure there was drama and crying and whining...but behind that on the buses at the dance at the pool in eachothers rooms, that was the fun, getting to know who your real friends are and getting to know new people and your surrounding.  I LOVED IT! wow words seriously dont explain how much fun it was.  although i do wish people that werent there went, i was thinkin about them! I LOVE YOU GUYS
      
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, just got back from Mexico...it was fun except for when i ate shit on the quad...hahah rookie...it was quite an experience..! lol   Din din!   -gotta jet- 
      
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      mexico tomorrow. ummm i still need to pack. and im excited because i get to miss my "LORD OF THE FLIES" final test...good luck to y'all who have to take it tomorrow. lol dont sweat it.    anyways im seriously looking forward to a tan and today i found out that there will be a jeep 4x4 and a doom-bugie AND a 3-wheeler. and im aloud to drive all of them! PARTY! im so excited...anyway. today was good till after school oh wait i made $10 for working with my mom but after that it was EH...i wont talk about it...any ways  -gotta jet- later hater (sorry zady)
      
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yo peoples! Well Finally my scrap book thingy for DC is out of the way, i think i did and okay job, but there's this one "person" i wont even mention a gender and he thinks that starting it the night before it is due will earn him a 100% and on top of that that "person" thought their book was better than mine! psh dream on "person" lol   anyways, grades are looking good, well at least good enough to go to PROMO, i will seriously sneak out of the house so i can go. . .sean going by himself might be a bust lol...  Mexico On Friday! WOOT WOOT! im so excited, i seriously need a tan! ouchy! lol  Note from Zady: hi... ok that's all...  That's my brother for all of you! hahah    -Gotta jet-
      
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey all, Wow it's crazy how people can just blame you for everything they are doing wrong because they are so damn in secure...whatever and thanks Sean and Travis for being there for me, and helping me feel better. . .  it ment the world to me, and thanks stevie my fellow arab! lol MEA for life! lol I hate this feeling i have inside, how much I'm hurting when i never really did anything wrong, all i was trying to do was help that all. Im out.
      
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow..im pretty relieved right now. A friendship is mended again!
      
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YO peoples...hows life been with y'all!?  Im at Lindsy's house rite now and shes getting plump on breadsticks...(not a good idea) lol, anyways movies tonight with kurt and lindsy! OH JOY! lol, and tomorrows my mommy's birthday...and bryan's party if you're reading this bryan i'll try to make it later but im not going to promise anything...  well i have no idea what to write now...so im going to go  _Gotta Jet_ luv y'all!  
      
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys...sry i havent blogged in a while...tryin to keep wup the grades! sucks dude! anyways Lindsy stayed at my house until today! it was pretty fun for the most part and today and yesterday i went to the TRACK MEET it was pretty fun and of course PARKS won...again..lol   hahah it was so funny! i was sitting on the step and michelle was next to me and i just randomly yelled "HEY HOTTIE!" really loud to see what concieted mo-fo would look back and of course it was ALI! that whore-ish scrub that thinks shes all that, but really shes just a fat a$$ slut...anyways shes like "oh dont flatter me like that please" and i was like "dont worry im not" and she gave me the dirtiest look ever possible...it was quite funny actually and annie was freaked out. like ali is going to do something to me...haha funny monkeys! anyways i have a crap-ola worth of HMWK ...so   -gotta jet- luv y'all
      
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yo...Sorry guys i havnt blogged in quite a while...whoopsie dasies! lol Well it's been okay i guess, life kinda blows rite now, well actually it sucks beach balls! and let me tell ya' thats pretty damn bad, but eh it'll blow by soon-or-later! Hope you all are doin' JIp DanDY!   -Gotta Jet-
      
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...well i had a fun-filled weekend...  FRIDAY: i went to TOYS "R" US  to get Greg my fiance his birthday gift...LOL and then i went back home and i spent time with my parents because they were getting ready to go to Las Vegas for the weekend...then at like 5:30 Lindsy came and picked me up and we went back to her house and her parents went out to dinner and shopping at COSTCO! so Lindsy and i were home alone with gracie and greg...and we ordered pizza and then sean and jared came over and we went to the SUNSET LANE PARK...it was fun, i SOOOOOO won on the swings and then travis steve and marcus show up...and then every one was being dumb in a way...pressuring sean and crap but what ever...and then at like 8ish lindsy and i and the kids went back home and travis calls me up and hes like can you sneak out...you have to come back to the park...so lindsy and i said i "forgot" my fone at the park...so we get there and yea...LOL  SATURDAY: TRAVis woke me up cuz he called my cell fone...and i had a missed call and a voice message and it was steve and hes like "im a tiger" it was really funny actually but anyways it was like 8:40 when i woke up and i had soccer tryouts at 9...i jumped out of bed  and got dressed and yea..so i went to soccer tryouts it was quite fun actually...and then i came back home and took a shower and got ready and went to lindsy house for gregs party...(we got married that day) (sry sean) lol anyway...and we had plans to go to the movies and sean bailed (BUM) oh by the way ENVY is a really bad movie...not funny at all...then i went back to lindsys house and spent the night there again and all night till like 12 i was texting w/ sean lol...then i, ZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ!  SUNDAY: GOT ready to go to church with the Davis's, it was very enjoyable...and now im home and im typing this ...on mothers day...oh yea HAPPY MOMMY'S DAY ...my mommy isnt here ...shes in vegas...lol well im out luv y'all  -GOTTA JET-
      
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HI! :)
      
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey....so today was an alright day i guess, it wasnt too hot which was nice...and it was quite funny after skool i was walking out with both sean's and i turn around and BAM my mom was rite there, so i thought to myself "oh glee wats a better time for my mom to meet sean?" so i introduced them...sean looked pretty nervous lol...(i swear she doeznt bite) and then in the car shes like wow ilyana hes a cutie...and i was like ummm thanks mom! yea okay and now im eating ice cream! 
      
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey....so today was an alright day i guess, it wasnt too hot which was nice...and it was quite funny after skool i was walking out with both sean's and i turn around and BAM my mom was rite there, so i thought to myself "oh glee wats a better time for my mom to meet sean?" so i introduced them...sean looked pretty nervous lol...(i swear she doeznt bite) and then in the car shes like wow ilyana hes a cutie...and i was like ummm thanks mom! yea okay and now im eating ice cream! 
      
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yo...Today was an okay day. . . DAMMIT SEAN I DONT WANT UR MONEY! ARgggGGGGG! lol so when i get home i start doing my Wallace notes for 5 sections and im on section three and BOOM my computer restarts on its own....AND yes all of the three sections i did were gone...forever and eternity! i was so pissed so i guess i have to do those dumb things by hand by thursday! that practacly impossible! ugh...Oh and Sean i dont want ur money...cuz it URS! lol    -Gotta Jet- Luv Y'all! 
      
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       ***HOOBASTANK***   ***The Reason*** i'm not a perfect person. there are many things i wish i didnt do but i continue learning. i never meant to do those things to you. and so i have to say before i go, that i just want you to know  i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you  i'm sorry that i hurt, its something i must live with everyday and all the pain i put you through, i wish that i could take it all away and be the one who catches all your tears, thats why i need you to hear  i'm not a perfect person, i never meant to do those things to you and so i have to say before i go that i just want you to know  i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be a reason to start over new, and the reason is you i've found a reason to show a side of me you didnt know a reason for all that i do, and the reason is you 
      
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OMG...it was 101 degrees! thats NOOOTTTT normal California weather...anyways it should cool off tomororrw...I WANT TO GO SWIMMING TODAY...SOMEBODY W/ A POOL CALL ME PLZ LOL....and i have soccer practice today! ugh gayness lol.........................................!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Any ways...i told my mom about sean and I she was pretty chill about it...lol ***************************************  AHHHHHHH! im sweating in an air conditioned house...there's something wrong with that ...im going to go figure out why lol   -Gotta Jet-
      
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey...today was a good day...went to the movies with becca lee sean and jared...13 going on 30 worst movie EVER! haha thx for the request linds...anyways then i found out some dissapointing news from Sean and jared about linds ...w/e and now lee is spending the night at my house and jareds a fagnut ugh i hate him   Gotta Jet bye
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nick Names: By Travis Sturms   sean goodwin-goodie   travis sturms- travass, t-bone   steve l aka sexy steve, stevie, steve-o, little stevie   jared B aka smelly, DJ, j-rod  rachel L aka crazyass   Sarah m aka wierdo  sean moser aka mosley  eric nathan silva aka en
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Your love is... by  urlLink  ChibiMarronchan        Your name is...           Your kiss is...    erotic      Your hugs are...    gentle      Your eyes...    twinkle in the moonlight      Your touch is...    awakening my heart      Your smell is...    exotic      Your smile is...    entrancing      Your love is...    everlasting             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hola guys....   I'm feeling a lil' down right now...i don't know what happened to me...ugh anyways...and i really wanted to see DODGEBALL...word says it's really really funny.... Today was a really bad bad day...long story that i will not share with you guys...anywho...call me guys and keep me company and leave me charming messages for the sick person (me)   -gotta jet- later all
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY GUYS! SORRY I'VE BEEN REALLY LAZY ABOUT BLOGGING DAILY LOL  so summer soccer was great...but i won't even bother to mention how i did...because sean thinks i'm cocky about soccer...which is quite weird because he's a bum himslef! but anyways and today i went to the weight room and ended up hanging out with michelle EN and jared...and saw all the foot ball players...and i'm really sore because EN pushed me to do really heavy weights...but anywho...tomorrow i'm off to watch the boys JV soccer game at SHHS at 2:10 come whoever wants to!   -gotta jet- later all! luv ya!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do You Think I'm Crazy?  FrEaKy4CaNdY28: yes freekykiki: yes LoRaXbOrA: OF COURSE! m1chelle x p4rk: NOPE! EN      dabomb88: hell ya BrendanM90: no tweakedMONKEYman: from what lindsy tells me, yes BoNaNaRaMa8: no HorseyChick121: of course InTeRpOl411: hellz ya CaNnT  tHiNk01: ya u r crazy Cherrychick07: no of course not  Okay Okay I'm crazy, but that's why y'all love me! 
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do You Think Sean Goodwin Is CrazEEE?  tweakedMONKEYman: yes InTeRpOl411: hellz ya not a crazy as me but crazy EN      dabomb88: haha hell ya BrendanM90: YESSSSS LoRaXbOrA: yes HorseyChick121: uhh of course m1chelle x p4rk: yes Cherrychick07: yes i think hes crazy BoNaNaRaMa8: ...ya! imn0tsm3lly: yes sean r. goodwin is a crazy motha f*cka!    AH HA...see i told you sean, you really are crazy! stop denying it...
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey all! what's up....i'm sitting here bored out of my mind listening to lindsy's convorsation with kurt-imous!....it's quiet boring i'd say...but anywho...today was a fun-filled day! well i woke up at 8:30-ish...helped my madre clean up the house cleaned my room. . . then the Davis' came over and we watched the game got drunk ate and yea...then we went to the park...and i'm lazy now..
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YES! SUMMA TIME................... I AM SOOO GLAD I AM OUT OF THAT SHIT HOLE! UGH I HATED IT...ANYWAYS I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO HIGH SCHOOL...so today was alright. ummmmm after school i had to get a physical and no the docter didn't touch me lol. then i went back to del taco and then from there walked with alejandro to lindsy's house but she wasn't home when i got there so i chilled with sean steve(arab) travis jared and en and hondro. then lindsy came and we hung out at sean's house and i kicked e.n.'s ass with those foam sowrds! i am victourios!! *HEHE* then lindsy's mom called and she sounded pretty pissed and said my mom was mad too because i was at sean's house....but she wasn't...i swear she loves you sean! lol and i was making dinner and i see this Tiffany&Co. box on the counter and i opened it and i got a bracelet for graduation and it has my name on it i was soooooO happy. and dude it's really shiny....like as shiny as sean's bling bling! lol   -gotta jet- later guys! luv y'all! call me 6.8.6.0.4.7.8
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey guys. sorry i haven't been keeping up with my blogging. please forgive my laziness... anyways tomorrow is the last day of school. sad day although i havn't yet cried this year. i'm just not the emotional person... i'm really looking forward to a new beggining and new people. and i will truly miss everyone that is moving away...  anywho i am so damn tired and cranky right now it's crazEEEEEE. so i'm going to go watch tv.  -gotta jet- later guys! 
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys!  Omg. Promo was so fun. the music was a 7 out of 10. not too shabby. but i personally dont think there were enough slow songs. 3 in 4 hours. eh thats pretty darn bad. anyways everyone looked cute. and most of the guys looked very handsome. i gotta say alejandro looked PIMP. lol. he even had a PIMP cane. lol....  then the after party that was fun too. haha the police came. and laura freaked out. lol. but the hot dogs were scrumpsious. Thanks KevO for making mine. and becca and kevin. we need to plan this ish we are doing lol. any ways. then lindsy spent the night at my house and we talked till' like 1am. then went to bed then i woke up at like 10:30ish and took a shower. OMG there were like 25 bobby pins in my hiar lol. and then went SHOPPING. lol  -gotta jet- bye all! luv ya 
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys! I just did my nail. OMG it was SOOOOOOOO packed. ugh. lol anyways i'm so excited for promo. it's going to be FUUUN! lol and then a party.. woot woot! lol i hope it'll be fun lol.   Oh and sean. you need to c-a-l-m down about your PE grade. just because you have a B and and S in citezenship. lol ;o)...and don't give me this it doesn't matter you're a girl ish. because it's the FIRST time i've gotten a B in PE too. lol. don't sweat it kool guy. you'll live trust me. lol (and bring your math book tomorrow)  Alright well im going to go find something to do. later guys!  -gotta jet-   *luv y'all*
      
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey all. well today was an okay day. i got a 100% on my scrap book. as did mostly everyone. oh wait. sean goodwin didn't whoops! lol 2 more days until promo woot woot. and i can go to the after party for sure. so count me in laura. and im getting my nails done tomorrow and hair on friday. and yep. and now im tired and im going to hit the sack  -gotta jet- later guys luv y'all 
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       LAZY*NESSSSSSS  
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sorry, i havn't Blogged in forever...i've been really really lazy lately...    &nbsp;  WOOT WOOT   S H H S  Girls Varsity won Summer League!!!!!   i'm too lazy to write anything...    &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sorry, i havn't Blogged in forever...i've been really really lazy lately...    &nbsp;  WOOT WOOT   S H H S  Girls Varsity won Summer League!!!!!   i'm too lazy to write anything...    &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      MAn ohh man...Summer school blows big time...it's so boring...and on top of that sean's in my class lol JK....Teacher is kinda cute tho hehe 0:)...  after school i had 2 soccer games...we lost the first one 2-1 and won the second one 2-0....but those 2 goals didn't go in on me...they went in on bambi...oh yes i musnt' forget...Sean you owe me "something" because i told you i wouldn't let any goals in today...hehe...  and man ohh man...them sprinklers are crazy cool...we ran thru them and got wet...my shoes were bubbling...and when i was on the soccer field girls were like wtf is wrong with your shoes...it was comedy man...  alright well i must go take a shower...i smell like you! 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys...like my new lay out...sorry there's no more chatter box...but at the bottom of each post just go ahead and post a comment and that will be the new "chatter box"...  anyways...today i was at the beach all day with annalise...it was really fun...i got dark! i need more sun...but it's WAY better than before lol...   LEE LEE...i swear Sea Weed  DOES NOT .. kill...lol...  alright well i'm outie hit up the cell luv ya'll
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey all...sorry i havn't blogged in a while...i'm kind of out of it right now...but anyways...  My Next soccer games for SHHS if any wants to are... 7-9 (Fri) at 11:45am and 6:45pm  Go Be my biggest and bestest fan ever!!!   Anyways...i'm just Blah right about now... so i'll just leave...bye   
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       THE GREATEST CONVERSATION EVER CONVERSED BY THE ARAB AND THE JEW...    FrEaKy4CaNdY28: go make out with sean FrEaKy4CaNdY28: haha iM N0t Sm3LLy: okie dokie...if you insist FrEaKy4CaNdY28: haha iM N0t Sm3LLy: O:-)wait what in the world are you talking about...i don't do that iM N0t Sm3LLy: psh FrEaKy4CaNdY28: haha no never iM N0t Sm3LLy: psh...seroius FrEaKy4CaNdY28: i dont do that stuff either FrEaKy4CaNdY28: i swear iM N0t Sm3LLy: no it's for slut! oh mann FrEaKy4CaNdY28: psh who hooks up with people FrEaKy4CaNdY28: thats disgusting iM N0t Sm3LLy: i know...exchaning saliva with another guy/girl...man ohh man...that just makes me want to gag iM N0t Sm3LLy: ewwww  FrEaKy4CaNdY28: gross FrEaKy4CaNdY28: that sounds so lnasty FrEaKy4CaNdY28: nasty* iM N0t Sm3LLy: woah...who ever invented that... FrEaKy4CaNdY28: i know seriously iM N0t Sm3LLy: i know i know...this jew and arab..i think their names are like becca and ilyana but some ppl know them as smelly and poopy iM N0t Sm3LLy: hmmm...might be all one big fat lie tho FrEaKy4CaNdY28: they are such sluts! iM N0t Sm3LLy: dude i know...they even dress like ones...and they were like an ocean of make up iM N0t Sm3LLy: and HOOOKER BOOTS...oh mannn iM N0t Sm3LLy: :-FrEaKy4CaNdY28: hahaha iM N0t Sm3LLy: that was one great convo about tonsle hockey iM N0t Sm3LLy: i very much enjoyed that poopy FrEaKy4CaNdY28: haha me too
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           I AM 32% HIPPIE! 
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           I AM 40% EMO! 
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY ALL! WELL IT'S A NEWWWW MONTH YAY...  I shall tell you about my day yesterday...  My brother and I took my grandma to the airport...she is going to France and the Middle East...aka Back Home lol...then we went to Inglewood..our hometown...lol we had to pick something up for my daddy...then we went to my parents office and then we went back home and at like 9ish zady took me to lindsy's house and well...i wanted to hang out with sean so i didnt go to her house till  like 10 lol...yea!:::i'm an angel:::::lol...and then we hung out and at like 10:30ish sean calls lindsy and asks if kurt was at her house and he wasn't haha...some idiots TP'ed his house and put chocolate on his lawn...quite funny i'd say..lol then at like 11:30 Lindsy and i watch TEXAS CHAIN SAW MASACRE!~ oh man! scary movie wow! i like killed lindsy's hand from grabbing it soo hard! wow...i'm like really scared of TExas now...lol...then we went up stairs and we did go to sleep till' like 4am...just talking...we actually kind of scared i'd say...lol...then when we turned the lights off lindsy starts sceaming hystaricly and yell go away bitch go away...she like saw the killer from the movie in me or something . . . and she kicked me off the bed and now my left side hurts then she like kicks my bed like five feet away and i could't defend my self because i was laughing so hard and i started crying and i got a tummy ache becasue i laughed so hard..lol   anyways...now i'm home alone and i got my 'report card' and i got a 3.8...yes yes GO ILYANA~!...and i get my new fone and shoppping and an awsome summer now! party for me!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!.....alright well i'm outie now! luv y'all!
      
</post>


</Blog>