<Blog>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After much consideration I have decided that the #5 song on my list of favorite love songs shouldn't be Total Eclipse of the Heart. Instead, I think it should be You Got It by Roy Orbison. Just thought I'd notify y'all of the change! Like you guys really care tho.....hehe.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in computer class right now, and it is so incredibly boring. I've been awake for a little more than 5 hours. Stupid spring break, it always messes me up. I'm used to waking up at 10 now, so I have to re-adjust. Waking up at 5:30 REALLY makes the day seem longer. I just can't wait to get home! Then I can just relax...well, if I have no homework. In math today we had a sub, so I didn't do the assignment. Then again I think the majority of our 13 person class didn't do it either, so that's good. I prolly won't worry about it. Kroese is pretty laid back when it comes to things like that. That reminds me...OPERATION TOAST! Oh yeah, that will be fun. It will spice up math class a little bit. hehe. toast. I think we're gonna do that friday, but I'm not sure. I'll have to check back with Erin and Vetta. The brilliant plans I come up with. Me and Erin decided that this week will be SEXPRESSION week. hehe. We always have weeks, but I think that this one will be fun. It's an excuse for our everyday pervertedness. All is well, all is well. Good times in the wagon! (I dunno, Alex once said that...) Yay! I've wasted maybe 10 minutes. Ugh! I think Im gonna talk to my mom today about seeing Josh, cuz that needs to happen soon! I am excited for it. Oh, I found it really funny when I went to go tell Amanda. I was like 'Amanda, I have something to tell you!' and she was like 'What? Are you and Josh going out?' It was really funny. So that made it a lot easier since she guessed it. I dunno. Well I think i've written enough about really nothing, so I shall be going! Away I go! (I really honestly do not know....haha)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The things I do for Josh...haha j/k. He "suggested" I should blog, so I did. Happy? Alex will be pleased too tho. I dunno. Anyways, on to my blogging. Blog is a funny word. Bloggidy blog blog. I dunno. I talked to Josh on the phone for about 3 hours today, and it was nice. We talked about seeing each other (which we really need to do!) I am anxious for that. I just think it's really weird how everything turned out. I mean, we went to the same school for like a year and a half and we never once saw each other. It seems almost too surreal...but I believe everything happens for a reason, so yeah. We'll just have to wait and see how things go. To be honest I was a little scared about the '143' thing with Josh at first, but then we talked about it so all is well. Tomorrow is school and I'm glad. It will be nice seeing my friends again. I don't remember if I said that in my previous blog or not. Oh well....the handfull of people who actually read this are used to me repeating things by now. I don't really have much of anything else to say, so I'm callin it quits.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm...well today is the last day of spring break for me. Oh well, I'll be glad to go back to school tomorrow. I'm tired of just staying at home. It will be nice seeing all my friends again. Hopefully this will be a good week. I think it will. Prom is this weekend, so that will be fun - I hope. Yesterday I was talking to Josh and he asked me what my favorite love song was, and that inspired me to create a top 5 list. Here it is: #5- Total Eclipse Of The Heart by Bonnie Tyler #4- I Wanna Know What Love Is by Foreigner #3- At Last by Etta James #2- Take My Breath Away by Berlin #1- Unchained Melody by the Righteous Brothers It was hard deciding between the Berlin song and the R.B. one to be at the top of my list. Haha. This is probably really boring to read. Oh well, only like 4 people probably read it. Speaking of boring, Martin was being an ass to me last night. We were just talking and then he called me a "library girl" and said that I "am boring and no fun, and find fascination in the most simplest things." What the hell is his problem? oh well. (Oh yeah, and Josh...I figured out what 143 means.) Well, that is it from me for now!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I woke up I thought it was just going to be another boring day. Well, it was until about 15 minutes ago. I got the BEST surprise! I can't share it yet tho, because I promised not to! Oh well, people will find out soon enough! hehe. Now I want to share, but I can't! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, that's right. If two weeks ago somebody told me that today was gonna end the way it did, I would have called them crazy. (I love the two weeks analogy!)  I'm glad this day went the way it did. It's about damn time things went my way! haha j/k. I like this song Ocean Avenue by Yellowcard. It's cool. I like some of the lyrics:  If I could find you now things would get better We could leave this town and run forever I know somewhere, somehow we'll be together Let your waves crash down on me and take me away  I don't know why, I just think it's cool. I don't think I've been in this good a mood for awhile now, and it's nice.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love Rooney. I swear their song Daisy Duke is about rape tho. Oh well, I'm dirty minded...My title reminds me of a book I once read. I forget what it's called, but it was about this black rain that made people want to kill each other and have sex or something. Maybe I'm imagining the "having sex" part. But anyways, in the book a girl gets raped in a bathtub. And then this couple has sex in a restaurant bathroom against the door or something. Oh well, that isn't important. It was a weird book. Oh, and this guy was at a gas station when the rain was falling, and he stuck the gas nozzel down this persons throat and poured gas into them. I then think he lit the person on fire, but I'm not too sure. I read it in like 7th grade. Oh, I think it was called Black Rain. I could be wrong...dammit, I went off on a tangent. I had a reason to blog, and it wasn't about some messed up book I read. Anyways...I sent Josh an email trying to tell him what I thought of our "situation". Basically, the ball's in his court and I'm fine with that. Whatever happens, happens. All I can do is wait to see what it is that will happen...whether it be nothing or something. I dunno. Well, that's it for now from me. Peave! (Don't ask, it's an Amanda thing)
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I'm doing this now cuz Josh basically told me to. Ok, that makes me sound like I'm his bitch. I'm not. Haha...me being Josh's bitch. That is just funny. But anyways...today was a good day. Talked to Josh...and whoever reads this already knows about what, so I wont restate it. I'll just say that I am glad we talked about the stuff that we did. Now I'm just wondering what we decide to do, if anything. I dunno....I guess within time I'll find out soon enough. Well, I don't really have anything much else to say. So I suppose that's it for now. (Happy now Josh???) haha.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My title sounds so wrong, but it isn't. Anyone who reads this knows that my mom's nickname is Stiffy, so all is well. We were at Old Navy today and she totally tripped. It was the funniest thing. We were looking at some shirts (This stupid lady took the shirt that I wanted, and it was the last one in that size. Oh, and she was obviously too big for a medium, but she wanted to try it anyways, because they had no larges either. All they had was that one medium and a whole bunch of XL and XXL. What the heck? Ugh! I so wanted that shirt, but oh well!)...anyways, as I was saying--we were looking at some shirts and somehow my mom's foot gets caught in this string of a bag. Well she goes to walk away and her foot is caught, and it totally causes her to fall to the ground. She was so embarassed! (Then again so was I) I felt bad for her, but not too many people saw, so I suppose all is well. That was totally the highlight of my day so far! Ciao!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was talking to Josh about something (Hell if I can remember now), and I was telling him how I want romance. It got me thinking about how I really want something that only happens in the movies, to happen to me. I want a romantic moment to call my own. I would fall for any guy who did something so romantic. I dont know exactly what I want, but I just want it. Gosh, I'm such a hopeless romantic. *sigh*
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was pretty boring. Did nothing really. Talked to Josh on the phone for a bit, and Holli. Experimented with various hair and make-up looks for prom. Still haven't found a winner. Gosh, my eyes really burn and are watering! I think it was from all the eye make-up. Oh well. That was my day. Later.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, the title is from the song With You by Jessica Simpson. Anyways, today was a pretty good day. I actually had plans! Score! Finished up the prom shopping. Got my shoes, handbag, necklace, earrings, hair accessories, and strapless bra (can't forget that!).  I'm excited about prom. It should be fun. After shopping, I called up Alex so we could "investigate" this field between our houses.  We just decided to walk and meet up with each other. So we did that, and then we decided to walk to Amanda's house and wait for her until she got back from work. Well, we had a lot of time to kill, so we walked all around Big Meadow waiting for Amanda. Amanda got home and so me and Alex hung out with her for a bit inside her room. Then we decided to walk some more. We went to my house so I could show them the rest of the things I got for prom. Then we walked back to Amanda's house, and from there Amanda drove me and Alex home. Yeah, didn't really make much sense, but it was still fun. Anyways...for a good portion of the day I noticed myself thinking about a certain person. It's pretty weird, because I dont even know why I'm thinking about this person. It kind of confuses me, but oh well. Hopefully it's just a phase and will pass on along soon enough. I dont like not knowing why I'm thinking of people. It kinda messes with me. Well, that was pretty much my day. Adios!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight was awesome and weird all at the same time.  Ok, I thought it was going to just be another boring night but then Amanda gave me a call.  She was bored, so I told her to come on over. Well, turns out that today was the day she could LEGALLY drive ppl around, so we decided to go out for a bit. In order for it to be ok with my parents we said we'd just drive around town. Amanda's parents actually wanted her to get some errands ran, so we did that. Then when that was done we decided to just drive around...well we went up into some roads that we didn't know very well and were just driving around listening to music. It was really fun but Amanda was a little nervous since she didn't really know the roads that well and cuz it was dark. Also, it didnt help much that I was talking about serial killers and rapists. We decided to go back into town, cuz Amanda wanted to get something to eat. So we went to mcdonalds and we decided that she would eat in front of our friend Alex's house. So we go to Alex's and Amanda is eating her food when she notices that Ethan's car is in the driveway. We start laughing and wondering why it's there. Being the brilliant ppl we are, we decided to tap on Alex's bedroom window, so we do that and then we run and hide. Well Alex and Ethan come outside and Ethan starts pretending that he's mad (well he was acting like he was mad, but me and amanda kinda thought he was joking but not...so we arent really sure). Then it gets kinda weird, cuz its just the 4 of us standing in alex's driveway. Me and amanda felt really weird, so we decided to leave.  When we got into the car and drove away we decided that was a really stupid idea. Ya live, ya learn. Omgsh...at the store I saw Jory! I am like in love with him! He is way hot! But anyways...that was basically my night. Oh, when we got back to my house I showed Amanda my permit, and she was in shock. good times. Dammit, my mom is nosy. She just came into the computer room, and started reading this. Good thing the part about me and amanda joyriding wasnt visible. She would have had a cow right then and there! Freakin A! That's it. Bada-bing, Bada-boom!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In physics one day, Mrs. Briley was telling our class that if you take diet dr. pepper and put like 4-5 mentos in it, it will fizz a whole bunch. Being curious, I decided to try it out. It works all right. Stupid me just decided to test it out on the kitchen table. Soda got everywhere...mom was not pleased. It was funny tho. Me and my mom went to the store today, and as boring as that may sound, it was actually somewhat fun.  We were walking by the condoms and I was like 'hey mom, um...can u stop for a second. i need to find something.' and she was like 'yeah, ok' it didnt even phase her that i was joking until i had to tell her. haha.  Anyways, I've come to the realization that if you say wasabi in a japanese-ish way, it is really humorous. Hmm...what else? Oh, I got a magazine today with a quiz booklet inside, so I took some quizzes. Lets see...according to one quiz I am tied with being a party girl and party animal. Basically, I like to have a lot of fun. haha. Another quiz says that I kinda care about my looks. I'll take a second glance in the mirror, but I also know when to draw the line. If I were a coffee, I'd be a vanilla latte. I'm full of natural sugar and i'm lovable, geniune, and have a positive presence.  My rock star soul mate is John Mayer because i'm into easygoing guys who are emotionally available and in touch with their feelings. haha. And when it came down to the "Are you girlfriend material?" quiz, I got Miss Taken...meaning I am ready for a relationship-and it shows. I have the confidence that attracts guys and the selflessness i need to really be there for another person. Oh, and the prom dress that fits my personality is the long, sleek gown because i'm sophisticated beyond my years. I tend to be in the spotlight.  Ok, after typing all that, it makes me wonder...who really believes in these quizzes? I just take them because they are fun and its interesting seeing what they have to say about me. Who makes up these quizzes? That is what i want to know. oh well. My sister just made a bouquet of barbies...damn odd.  Aniwaiz, this is getting long, so that is my cue to stop typing. Tomorrow I go shopping, yay! Ok, now I'm done. Later!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've noticed that my past two entries both start with 'Wow' and end with 'Whatever'. That is gonna stop. Repetition is no good. Aniwaiz...even tho I already posted today, I've decided to post again. Besides, the last entry wasnt really about my day...more about prom. Actually there really is no point of writing about my day today because it was pretty boring. I talked to Josh for a bit on the phone (haha....8 inches??), oh and i cleaned my dresser! FINALLY! I was proud. My dog Lacie attacked my dog Missy. Those stupid dogs just need to go away! ugh! Amanda stopped by for a bit while she was taking a walk. I felt lazy when she came over cuz I was still wearing my pajamas...and it was the afternoon. haha. "INSANE IN THE MEMBRANE! INSANE IN THE BRAIN!" I've decided that orange juice and saltine crackers kick major ass. Conan O'Brian...he's the best. haha. I dont know why, but ya gotta love him. It was really weird...when I was cleaning off my dresser, there was a pack of Juicy Fruit gum...but I dont ever remember buying Juicy Fruit. I'm more of a mint type of girl. It confused me...well thats enough from me. Holla!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow...I just realized that there are only 13 days until prom. I still have a lot to do. I don't understand why prom is such a big deal. Society has made it into a huge event with the glorification of prom in movies. Many teen movies involve prom. Why is that? It is just a dance...a "special" dance. What makes it so special? I don't really get it, but I'm not sure I care enough to get it in the first place. Sure, I'm excited for it and what not, but I just don't understand all the hype. Whatever.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, this is my first blog. Pretty exciting. (not really) Martin suggested I make one, and well I had nothing better to do so I listened. Yeah, don't really know what to write. My day was pretty boring...did nothing really. Talked to a few ppl online, and that was about it. Oh, my sister attacked me with this huge spoon, and left a bump on the back of my head. Damn her. Hopefully tomorrow will be more fun...or fun at all. Whatever.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty good day. School was boring as usual. I got homework for the weekend, but I already finished it.  I recently got home from Friday Night Movie Night. Tonight we (Amanda, Holli, Patty, and myself) went to go see Mean Girls. It was ok. I thought it would be different than what it was.  Then afterwards we went to Shari's for some sundaes.  It was fun. On the way home Amanda was driving, and I see a stop sign coming up, and Amanda isn't slowing down...so I'm like "isn't that a stop sign?" Amanda then slams on her brakes just in time and was like "yeah, good job" I found it to be funny. Also, a Cher song came on (we were listening to the 80s channel) and Amanda totally starts singing along, and me and Patty just quietly laugh. It was amusing to say the least. Hmm....other than the events of tonight, today was pretty uneventful. Hopefully this weekend will be better.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kit Kat bars are good...yum. Actually I should cut back on the sweets. I'm going to try to lose some weight. Not much tho, maybe just about 10 lbs. And I'm also going to try to get some better muscle definition. Maybe then I'll be ok for awhile.  Sometimes I think I place too much emphasis on my physical appearance. I really shouldn't tho because it just makes me not satisified with what I have. I always want to be better. It sucks. Anyways...enough about the boring mumbo-jumbo.  Today wasn't too eventful. Nothing exciting really happened. Oh well. I'm just glad that tomorrow will be Friday. I always look forward to the weekends. Oh, that reminds me. I have to send Chubbs a reminder about her appointment tomorrow. That is what a good secretary does. Hey, what can I say? I take all jobs given to me in a serious manner, and I do them to the best of my ability. Good quality, huh? Hmm...I haven't talked to Omondo for awhile now. Actually, lately I haven't talked to Chubbs too much either. Oh well. The show must go on. That reminds me today during computer class I was online reading something, and I read that there is a Jerry Springer Opera, and that it's going to appear on Broadway! Isn't that just insane? I found it to be quite bizarre. Crazy!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided that I really want to go golfing. I also want to be good at it.  Today was a somewhat uneventful day. Oh well. Didn't do too much. Apparently Tommy's mom said Tommy should ask me out. Let me explain...Ok, Tommy made a quote list for me. Well yesterday he showed his mom the quotes, and his mom told him that he should ask me out because I seem nice and funny. I didn't believe Tommy, but then he promised me it was true, and even told me I could ask Bobby about it. I decided not to ask Bobby, but to just believe Tommy. I just find that funny. Nothing else exciting happened today. It was an average Tuesday. Maybe tomorrow will be more exciting.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day has almost come and gone, can't imagine what else could go wrong. Sometimes I'd like to hide away, somewhere and lock the door. A single battle lost, but not the war.....good ol' lyrics to my one and only country song I will EVER like. Hehe...I've shamefully admitted it once and for all! Oh well...Today was a pretty good day. School was okay...I got all my homework done before 4:15, so that was nice. Today in spanish I gave a presentation, and like the whole class laughed because I talked really fast or whatever. That is kind of good tho, that I talk fast, because it works to my advantage in spanish. Or not - that may just be some wishful thinking. In math class Tommy decided to create a list titled  The compiled wisdom of Erica Gerstlauer , basically it is just a page of "quotes" that I say, and he finds worth saving. He's funny. Within just 3 hours, he was able to get about 30 quotes from me. That is about one quote every six minutes. Then he asked me for my number, and said he wanted to hang out something this weekend. I told him I didn't know, but he still made me give him my number. Oh well. Today Ethan made me mad. I was talking to Chubbs, asking her something, and then he's like "hey, this is my time" and pushes me out of the way and starts talking to her. He just thinks he can do whatever he wants, and it really makes me mad. Whatever. Oh, I am now Chubbs' secretary. I get to keep track of her life. Score! Well, that was my day! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an okay day.  A little boring, but I at least had something to do.  I went to my uncle's house for his bday party. People in Lake Oswego and their parties...i swear! Geez! Oh well. When I got home, Omondo came over for a bit. I played her song for her. Gigolo! Oh yeah. We just went over my list of the greatest 80s songs...well, my personal choices at least.  Keep on Loving You  by REO Speedwagon is a good song. Me and Omondo danced to it! Oh yeah! I have to memorize these sentences for spanish class, and it sucks. I can memorize them easily, but its taking the time to concentrate that is getting me stuck. Oh well....I should stop blogging and start memorizing! Side note: Anyone who doesn't think Steve Martin is one of the funniest fellows on the planet should have his head examined! (oh yeah, Chubbs, I'm good!)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was SUPER boring. I spent most of it talking to Josh....and when I mean most...I mean MOST. Oh well. Nothing too exciting went on today. Tomorrow I have to go to my uncle's bday party or whatever. I swear, people in Lake Oswego have too many parties. They aren't even fun. I don't really like my dad's side of the family too much. They all have their noses in the air. Whatever. The only one I really like is my cousin Andy. He's cool and only 4 months older than me. He's a senior. He's going to go to the college that I want to go to (PSU). Marty and Josh think I should go somewhere better...but PSU is close to home. I don't want to go somewhere too far away. I dunno. I have a lot of things to decide. Oh well. Damn, I still have some homework to do. I procrastinate too much...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't blog yesterday because I forgot. I know Chubbs (Alex) gets mad when I don't blog daily! Yesterday wasn't too eventful. I didn't really do much of anything. Chubbs (we got that from Happy Gilmore) and Holli came over and we watched a movie. Oh, they also colored in coloring books. It was funny. Then we got bored so we decided to call Josh. Yeah, that was kind of interesting. Josh thought it was weird, I'm sure. Oh well. Who already doesn't think me and my friends are weird? Hmm...not much else happened yesterday. That was about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so bored right now! Ugh! Oh well. I'm just chattin with Josh and Marty. Nothing too exciting happened today. School was pretty average! Today at lunch was REALLY weird. I was just talking to Alex and she asked if Mark was short for something. And I was like "yeah, my dad's real name is Markington!" Not that funny, right? Well at lunch I found it soooo funny! I was laughing a ton! It was really weird. It was also weird in psychology today. We had a free day, and I was bored, so I was just quietly working. Chris Nugent walks up to me, and he says in a soft caring voice "Is everything ok, Erica?" and I was like "yeah, everything's fine" and he was like "Ok, you just had me wondering" It was really nice and funny. I didn't even think he knew my name. haha. Hmm...interesting stuff. I think Josh thought I liked Theran. haha. Good stuff. Oh well....doesn't matter. Hmm....well I'm running out of ideas to blog about, so I think I'll be going.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I really don't know where my title came from. I had no ideas, and I saw my bottle of Aquafina water, so I went from there. Today was pretty good. It was boring, but looking back on the day, it seemed to have gone pretty well. In Spanish, I was the only one to get a 100% on our quiz...so that was cool. I took a test in calculus today, and I think I did ok. Computers was boring, as always. Psychology was kind of uneventful as well. Physics, we didn't do much. I was done testing my pendulum experiment, so I just talked the whole class time. It was fun. Then we had an assembly on drugs...that was boring. Today I wore my  Kiss Me, I'm Irish  shirt! I got two offers...Steven and Holli. Haha. I showed people my prom pics, and they all said they were cute. Tommy said I looked pretty in them, so that was cool too. I tried to show Ryan the pics today, figuring he'd like to see them since he was in them, but I guess I was wrong. He could have cared less. That is what makes me mad about Ryan. He annoys me all the time, and I'm finding myself disliking him more and more. Pretty soon it's going to get to the point where I wont care, and I'll just let our friendship fall apart. Whatever. I'm going to go shopping with Tera later today, so that should be fun. I don't have too much homework, I just have to study for a physics test....nothing TOO terrible. Hmm...that is really all about my day, so I think I'll be wrapping this up now.  SIDE NOTE: The song We Used To Be Friends by The Dandy Warhols is a good song. I like some of the lyrics:  Now everybody needs some time And everybody knows The rest of the lines In everybody else's show  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a boring day. Hmm....nothing much happened. Went to school, came home, did homework. The usual. Oh, prom pics came today. I think mine looks ok, nothing too exciting. Hmm....that is really about it...today was pretty boring, but still good.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got done registering for the SATs on June 5th. How lovely! I hate taking tests, but oh well. At least Alex will be taking this one with me! I don't actually know how that helps me, but oh well. Today was a boring day. It was just your typical Monday. Mondays are always mundane. Ok, I must be tired or something because I found that to be really funny. I need to get out more, I swear. Today it was really funny. I was walking with Erin in the hall, and I saw Matt. Me and Matt both gave each other a weird look/smile and then we looked away. Erin noticed that and began laughing, and she was like 'what the heck was that?' Ok, yeah not that funny as I retell it. Oh well. If something interesting happened today, I would talk about it, but since nothing did, I think I'll be done blogging for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My title is a song by South. It's really good I think. It's on the  OC Mix 1  soundtrack. I like the whole CD. Then again I like everything about the OC....including Adam Brody! Anyways, today was a typical day. Erin came over and we did psychology homework. That may sound boring, but it was actually fun! We totally did an awesome job on our project! It is kind of sad how excited I am about it, but it really is awesome. We have the coolest eye model, and the coolest story. Juanita Bonita and the Spum-pum! Score!! We are creative! Oh yeah. Obviously I'm in a good mood as I type this...haha. Even tho I should prolly be sad since tomorrow is monday morning. Oh well. I think I'm done blogging for tonight. Night!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You're not bigger than this...not better. Why can't you learn?  Good ol' lyrics from Lucky Denver Mint, by Jimmy Eat World. Let's see...I went to Martin's house today. That was ok. We watched Gothika and I schooled him in 80s music. I'm talking to Josh right now, and he just shared some really interesting information with me. hmm...makes me think. Lets see what else has gone on...oh...I know! I freakin got excluded from Friday Night Movie Night! Whatever....no, I'm kidding. I understand the story. (It's ok Alex...haha). Tomorrow Erin is going to come over and we are going to work on homework. We are so cool! haha. We always have fun together tho, so that is good. I really don't have too much more to blog about, so I'll stop for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My title is a quote from my psychology teacher Ms. Earle. We were discussing in class today how steroids affects penis size. I don't know what prompted her to say that, but she did and it was really funny. Today was a pretty good day. I talked to Martin online for about 4 hours. I am going to go to his house tomorrow to hang out. That should be fun, well I hope at least. I'll have something to do then anyways.  Hmm....what else? Oh, today it was somewhat odd in physics. I don't know, maybe because of what happened yesterday with me and Matt. haha. Sometimes I just do not think! Oh well, it wasn't that weird. It was kind of funny...until Ryan, Theran, and Luther were making some comments. And then I think they told Griffin. Oh well...nothing I can do about it. That's what I get for not thinking things through all the way.  Hmm....there is really nothing else to blog about...so I'm done for tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I have to make this entry long, because yesterday it wasn't long enough, and Alex was not pleased. So, Alex, are you happy now? I hope that this entry will be good enough for you. When I was first typing this, after I typed 'you' in the past sentence, I also typed the word 'answers.' Crazy! Lets see....it is only 10:36, and a lot has already happened today! That is a change.  It hasn't been good tho. All I have to say is that I DON'T FREAKING UNDERSTAND CERTAIN PEOPLE. Always saying one thing and doing another...without explanation. What the hell is that? It's gay! I'm sick of it. From now on, I'm just going to keep stuff to myself, and not share it with people. They don't deserve to know. Ugh! I don't know, and it is making me mad. Oh well. I was supposed to go find Martin today at break, but I had other stuff to do instead. Oh well, I'm sure he didnt care too much. I got an email from Josh today, I hadn't heard from him for about a week. It was nice knowing he was ok, i guess, but it wasnt good to hear that he hasnt been going to school. Bad Josh! Oh well...speaking of school....yeah, I got a 37% on that math quiz that I took yesterday. I'll be retaking that and the other one tomorrow. Hopefully I will improve on them. In spanish today we got new seats because people were talking too much. I was put next to Erin, so that was good. We have too much fun together. Haha. Yesterday she came over for a bit and worked on some homework, but had fun for the rest of the time that we weren't. We tried to mess with Martin online, but it didn't really work. oh well. Hmmm....I wonder if this is long enough for Alex's standards. Probably not...she always holds me to such high standards! It's not fair. No, I'm kidding. I don't know. I'm tired, and me being tired is not good. When I'm tired, I get into weird moods. I am in one of those moods right now. Haha. Oh well. I need to read for psychology, but that would require me going to my locker and getting my book. I should probably do that soon. We may be quizzed on it. DAMN PEOPLE MAKE ME MAD! Ok, that was random, but I felt the need to say it. Hmm....I don't know. I think I will finish this up and then go get my book. Why yes, that is what I shall do! Hmm...I am so bored. I really don't have too much to blog about right now, but I'm just going to go off on something that has been bothering me, and Holli...if you end up reading this...I am sorry, but that is how I feel. Ok...I feel like me and Holli are growing apart. We've talked about this before, and have said that we've needed to work on it. don't get me wrong, Holli is great! I love her to death, too, it's just that sometimes I feel she doesn't understand me. I'll try to tell her something or talk to her about my problems, but I always feel as if she never really listens. It seems to me that it always goes back to her problems. I would just like to be able to talk to her and tell her what is on my mind without having to worry if I'll hurt her feelings. I want to continue being Holli's friend, and work on things...it just feels as if we are growing apart into different people. I find my self not being able to relate to her as much, and I've noticed that when I am getting along with her really great, we're talking about old times. I don't want to always be talking about the old times...because I want these times to be like the old times. they arent tho, and that makes me sad. things have changed, and i honestly dont know how to get them back to normal. i dont know, i just feel as if sometimes no one understands me. i was trying to tell amanda my story of how i felt and stuff, and she was getting all defensive, and completely missed the point. everyone seems to be missing the point....well not everyone. but i find it more harder and harder to be able to fully express myself to people...it seems as if they dont really listen/care. i could be totally wrong, but i dont know. not knowing isnt a good feeling either. i would just like to be reassured that everything will be ok, and that everything is fine now. if somebody would just listen to me talk about my problems, how i truly feel about things, and not tell me what to do, just listen...and not judge. that would be great. i think my biggest problem is actually that i feel holli doesnt understand me as much. and having the feeling of your best friend not understand you sometimes makes you feel that no one else does. i know that isnt true. i just need to have things become better with holli....hopefully they will. all i can do is wait and time will tell soon enough. its just frustrating having all of this inside my head going on, and not being able to communicate it. its awful. oh well. that is the way life goes sometimes...there is nothing i can do about it. hmm....i wonder if this is long enough for alex. haha...that could sound dirty taken out of context. can i touch your cochlea? a cochlea is a bony tube filled with fluid. it is located inside of the ear. haha. i dont know why, but me and erin find that extremely funny. we can be a tad perverted sometimes....actually, take out tad. I am a big pervert when I try. It isnt all the time tho, I swear. Well, now I feel weird talking about how I find myself to be a perv sometimes. So...just forget about that stuff. wow, I think that this has acquired some great length. alex likes the length. haha.....
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stand By Me by Ben E. King is a great song. It's in the movie Stand By Me as well. How appropriate. Today was an OK day. I had a strange experience with my old stalker Brian and one of his friends. They were staring at me through the door while I was in class. I turned around and saw them, and they were just focused on me, and they waved. It was freaky. I bombed a math quiz. That sucks. I have homework I should be doing soon. Ick. I need to stop slacking off.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Adam's Song by Blink 182 -- good song. Anyways, lets see what happened today. Nothing really....3rd period was probably the most interesting by far.  We watched a movie in computers, cuz we couldnt use the computers cuz they were needed to do testing. I asked Mrs. Parker to go to my locker...yeah, I was gone for 50 minutes. I spent that time with Holli and Theran in their 3rd period class since they just have leadership. It was fun. Then Ben came in, so him and Holli were talking...and that left me and Theran. We just talked about various stuff, but it was fun. In math, lunch, and psychology I shared some really good laughs with Erin. We have too much fun together over nothing, it's crazy. Oh, in physics I started a class discussion involving sam and his sexual orientation....so that was interesting to say the least. I didn't think it would catch on with the whole class and everyone would get involved. I felt somewhat bad for Sam, but then I didn't. I dont know. I think I may have annoyed Holli today...not too sure. I think it started when I tried to turn the situation around on her. Sometimes I think she takes things just a little too seriously. Like today when me and Theran told her we were going to be physics partners, and that I was going to ditch her, she believed me. I don't know if she is just really gullible or if she honestly thinks I would do something like that to her, because I wouldn't....she should know that too. Oh well, I don't know. Hmm...that was pretty much the extent of my day. There wasn't really anything to it. Just a little boring with a few funny moments thrown in describes it fairly well.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I've already created my blog for the day....well actually it was a good enough size to be for several days--but anyways. I just wanted to state that I noticed I mention Alex somewhat frequently in my blog. By creating this announcement, I am mentioning her even more. I prolly just mention her frequently cuz she actually reads it. Alex, this post was devoted entirely to you! Yay!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sick of school. I'm almost at the point where I could care less if I didn't get straight A's.  I don't know, maybe it has something to do with the fact that school is winding down.  I am just tired of working hard and still not getting everything. It sucks. And next year is going to be even harder. I don't want to take calc 2, but I think my mom is going to make me. She is set on having me become valedictorian because she says she knows I want it. Yeah, I want it, but if I don't get it, then I will be ok. I just dont want to dissapoint her and my dad. But I also don't want to have an extremely hard senior year. Who honestly wants that? I don't know, I just need to talk to my parents and tell them how I'm feeling, because nothing is going to get resolved until I am honest with them. I'm in computer class right now...free days suck. Tommy is making me mad because he keeps looking up racist jokes. He thinks they are the funniest things....it's disgusting. I tried to give Martin the DVD today at break, but that didn't work out. Oh well, I tried to find him, then I quit. So then I put the DVD back into my locker, and then of course I find him. Yeah, I was too lazy to go back to my locker and get it, so I just didn't deal with it. Nice, huh? Oh well, it's not a big deal. I better not have that much homework tonight. The only homework I might have would be psychology or physics. I have physics homework that I should be doing right now, but I just don't feel like it. Damn, I so used to not be like this. What is happening to me? haha. No, it's not that important. I'll just lie to Mrs. Briley and tell her I was unable to finish it due to "family issues" and if she asks me to explain further, I'll look all sad, and be like "do I have to?" It works pretty good...I haven't used it in awhile tho. I might have to break it out today. I don't know if it's sad or not that I don't care if I lie to a teacher so I won't get in trouble. I know some people (Holli) would never do that because they would feel too guilty. Am I supposed to feel guilty? Do I have a cold heart? Am I asking too many questions that will never get answered? Yeah, I thought so too. Today is Monday...hmm...the last time I talked to Josh, I believe it was Thursday. Wow! That's a record! I don't know why I felt the need to state that. It's not like it's a thing where I have to talk to him all the time or I'll freak out. I only worry...haha. I suppose if I REALLY wanted to talk to him, I could always call him...I dunno. I've never been big on calling guys. (haha...Alex--I always make you call them whenever there is a situation in which I would need to call a guy....did that make sense?) Whoa...the weirdest feeling just came over me. I want to cry, but I don't know why. It's weird...hmmm....I'm highly confused over my state of mind right now. I want to cry....but why? Haha. That makes me sound like I am going crazy or something. I'm not. I've been typing a lot on this blog entry...I must be REALLY bored. WE still have like 20 minutes left of class....geez! I guess I won't be doing my physics work. I need to stop with this procrastinating....it's getting really old, fast. Now, I just really want to go home, and end the school day. I'm just not in the mood to be here right now. I'm not in a bad mood tho. I just don't want to be at school, that's all. Wow, to whoever reads this (prolly just Alex and Josh...haha), I am sorry for the extreme length of this boring entry. I think this is a good time to be ending this....so I shall do that just now.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was Easter, and it was another boring day. This whole weekend was uneventful. Oh well. I'm gonna join Alex's family soon, if mine continues to be boring and do nothing! haha. It's ok tho, cuz it was Alex's idea. That way, also, her red hair wont stand out so much. I dunno. Me and Alex come up with strange plans...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like Pina Coladas, and getting caught in the rain. I'm not much into health food. I am into champagne. Anyways...now that I've said a little bit about myself, I can continue blogging away. Oh...just a few words to CERTAIN people who will read this:  You know you can't hold me forever. I didn't sign up with you. I'm not a present for your friends to open.  No, I'm merely kidding. Those are some lyrics from an Elton John song....haha. I'm in a lyrical mood this evening I suppose. No I won't be afraid, no I won't be afraid.  Just as long as you stand, stand by me. Well, now that I am no longer afraid, we can move on! I'll take you down the only road I've ever been down. You know the one that takes you to the places. Ok, enough of this lyrical nonsense you say?!? Ok! Today was really boring, but I manged to get through it somehow. It was really nice outside, so that was good. I was able to catch some sun...but not too much or I would've burned. Damn the redhair! haha. Right now I'm talking to Alex (yes, I mentioned you in my blog that you read all the time Alex!!).....ok, back to blogging...Actually I really don't have much to say, so I think I'll be ending this before I type any more meaningless mumbo-jumbo....haha. I dunno.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so mad right now! I can not find my disposable camera! I better find it soon, or I'll freaking go on a rampage! I dunno, but it had my prom picks on it, so I really do need to find it. I was gonna finish up the role of film on me...no, just kidding....i was gonna take some pics of my nephews...and maybe one or two of myself. I went into my room, and I couldn't find it! Ah! I think that my mom put it away somewhere since I left it on my bed this morning. I don't know, I'll have to ask her when she gets back from the store. Until then I just have to stay calm. Lets see...today wasn't too exciting. We had flan in spanish class...it was pretty good. Got my calc quiz back....yeah I got a 74%, so I'll be retaking that one. In psychology we just looked at many optical illusions, so that was pretty interesting. In physics we finished up some labs....Sam wasn't there for me to hit on. Oh well. I need to find a different hobby besides hitting on guys when I'm bored. Oh well. Hopefully this weekend will be more exciting, but I highly doubt it...it's partially my fault tho. I had offers to do a few things, but I turned them all down....why do I do that? Martin invited me to this party he was going to, and Tommy invited me to his house to watch some movies...and what do I do? I say no. Why is that? I should say yes more often! That is what I am going to do now....I will no longer say no, but instead yes! I dunno, I'm just rambling now...oh well. I say oh well a lot. Hmm....I should go try to find my camera...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Content (satisfied) and content (subject matter of a written work)....two words, but spelled the same. Crazy! Anyway, now that my stupid ol' observation of the day is done and over with, I can continue my path of enlightenment.....i mean blogging. I dunno, obviously I'm in an odd mood right now. WAIT! when am i not in an odd mood? haha. Before I continue any further, however, I would like to formally state that the clay aiken kid's name is Kurt, not Kirk. my bad. I was close enough....whatever. today was anything but boring. it was unboring. i dunno if unboring is even a word. i will make it a word. i yelled at/talked with ryan today...yeah, i'm really not sure how things are gonna be. whatever. hmm....i was totally in a blogging mode, and full of stuff to say, but then josh had to call and disrupt it! geez, thanks josh! freakin a! ok, im over it now. haha. anyways, back to my day. hmm...a few days ago tommy asked me to come to his house and watch movies with him, and i totally shot him down, but because i thought he was joking. well, he wasnt joking, and asked me again today...i kinda avoided the situation. haha. in physics i was hitting on sam, that was fun. i dont know if he is used to having girls hit on him. hopefully 'operation make sam my friend' will work. haha. i'm not too sure yet. well, that was pretty much my day. on to doing homework/procrastinating!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an average day. I tried to start to talk to Ryan about our fight, but he wouldn't listen...what's new? He never listens to me, nor does he care what I have to say or how I feel. He's good at doing that. Oh well. I got mad and called him a 'fuck face' at lunch today. That's the ticket....impress him with my grand vocabulary that properly displays my intelligence...that will make him see things. Oh well, I was mad. Sam today in physics said I look like Martin. Damn Jew....doesn't know anything! The only thing me and Martin share is our red hair. Other than that, we don't look alike. Oh well. Oh, haha....funny story time! The Clay Aiken Kid (I think his name is Kirk) thinks I am hot. He told Chloe's friend Ariel that. haha. Good times. First I do a kiss and run with him, and then he thinks I'm hot. That kid is seriously blind, I swear. I dunno tho, I just find it funny. Well, I'm gonna go now, other than that my day was pretty much uneventful.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This song Warning Sign by Coldplay is really good! I was listening to it, and the lyrics are fantastic. I don't know why, but this song just really sticks with me. I think it's great. Here are the lyrics:  A warning sign  I missed the good part then I realized  I started looking and the bubble burst  I started looking for excuses   Come on in  I’ve gotta tell you what a state I’m in  I’ve gotta tell you in my loudest tones  I started looking for a warning sign   When the truth is, I miss you  Yeah the truth is, that I miss you, so   A warning sign  You came back to haunt me and I realized  That you were an island and I passed you by  And you were an island to discover   Come on in  I’ve gotta tell you what a state I’m in  I’ve gotta tell you in my loudest tones  That I started looking for a warning sign   When the truth is, I miss you  Yeah the truth is, that I miss you so  And I’m tired I should not have let you go   Ooooooooooooooooo   So I crawl back into your open arms  Yes I crawl back into your open arms  And I crawl back into your open arms  Yes I crawl back into your open arms
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I Go Again by Whitesnake, good song. Anyways (technically 'anyways' isn't a word, it is supposed to be 'anyway' but nobody ever says that)....as I was starting to say...back to my day! It wasn't really that eventful. I dunno, I can't say I was in a bad mood, because that wouldn't be true. But then again, to certain people I wasn't in a good mood either. I guess I was fine, but there were just some parts of the day where I was getting tired of certain people. I kinda got mad at them easily, but oh well. Nothing I can do about it now, so I might as well get over it. Lets see....the highlight of my day..hmm..that would prolly have to be my psychology class. I dunno, that was the class that I had the most fun in today, so I can't really pick a specific thing. I need someone to rant to...well maybe not. Maybe I should just keep it to myself. I dunno, I tend to do that a lot--keep things inside. It's probably not the best thing to do, but I don't think I trust people enough to tell them what I'm completely thinking all the time. I mean, sometimes I do it, but not too often. And when I do, it's usually after I've hit the breaking point. I dunno....I should deal with emotions in a better way. It's weird tho, I always feel like I can best tell people my emotions once they've been completely honest with me. It's like something they need to earn....haha. I dunno, I'm just rambling now. I think that's enough for now....I need to talk to someone or I'm gonna die. haha. I guess that's what I get for not talking much during the day...oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My title was a note that Matt Belding wrote to me today in physics. It was really funny.  That was probably the highlight of my day.  Sad as that may seem. Hmm...what else did I do that was remotely interesting? Not much, I spied on Martin during 5th today. I was really bored. Got new seats in spanish, I sit next to Theran. He was gone today, and he'll be gone tomorrow too for FBLA. Hmm....what else? Oh yeah, I realized today that the reason Ryan sometimes aggravates me and stuff is becuase I find him to be a boring person. haha. Hopefully, he'll never come across this, but if he does, then I'm sorry. It's just how I feel right now. So yeah. That was really about it. So, how about them Blazers?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today has been a slow/fast day. Fast because of the stupid time change, and slow because I've done nothing. I watched the movie Gothika and that was about it. People said it was scary, but I didn't really think so. It was pretty good, but the ending was somewhat stupid. Oh well. I talked to Holli for a long while on the phone too. We talked about prom and our boy troubles...haha. Good ol' girl stuff. I dunno, boys are confusing...let me tell ya! Well, maybe boys aren't confusing, girls just make them that way. I dunno. Oh well....no biggie. That was pretty much my day....boring.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was prom, and I had a good time.  I was so happy, they played my favorite love song of all time! Score! I dunno, as much fun as I had, it kind of felt like something was missing. Dammit, I hate the feeling of emptiness and not knowing why I have it. Don't get me wrong, I still had a really good time tho. The limo ride was funny. On the way there, I sat between Ben and Ryan. When the limo did certain turns or something, I would kind of slide towards Ben. It was funny. On the way back, I sat between Scott and Ryan, and I would slide towards Scott. It was funny to me anyways. I dunno. Amanda and Holli kept joking around that I was hitting on their dates. At least I think they were joking. haha. I'm not sure. I wasn't hitting on their dates tho. So, I'm pretty sure that they were joking. Geez! This is so confusing. The more I think back to prom, the more I can't get over the fact of my empty feeling. I think it has something to do with the fact that I went with Ryan. Ryan is a great guy, but I kind of wished that I went with someone I liked. There were a lot of couples there, and it made me realize that I would love to have a boyfriend....but I'm just not ready for one. I've only really been able to picture myself with one guy, and of course that is the one guy I can't have. Why do things like that always happen to me? Oh well, eventually I know things will have to go my way for once....I hope. I still had a good time at prom tho, so that's good I suppose. Well, that's about it....
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, yeah that title was stupid but I was running low on ideas. I went to Alex's house today for a bit with Amanda and Holli. We did our nails so they would be nice for prom. I'm getting SUPER excited about prom! It is going to be so much fun! Well, I hope so anyways. Hmm....what else did I do today? Oh yeah, I talked to Josh. I told him that I wasn't really ready for a boyfriend, and he seemed to be okay with that. So that is good. We're still gonna be friends tho, so that's cool. Not much else happened today. That was really about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, ok my title prolly doesn't make sense to anyone but me. Oh well. Hmm...yesterday I didn't blog! Oh no! Yesterday I finally met Josh. We just hung out and watched A Night At The Roxbury. I love that movie! Did you just grab my ass? (Ahh...too many memories with that one!) I'm soooo tired, it's crazy. I hope I'm not getting sick. That wouldn't be good right before prom. I am so excited for prom too! It should be really fun. Erin ended up deciding to go, and that pleased me a ton! I'm glad she's gonna come. We're gonna have a lot of fun. Hmm...I don't have too much more to say. I have a lot of stuff on my mind, but that's about it. Don't really feel like going into detail. Maybe later tho. I don't know. Well, I'm out for tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my...the poor apple! Why must you go and try to shoot it? Isn't that rude? How do you think the apple feels?! Oh, in case your memory has failed you, the apple is the fruit with red or yellow or green skin and sweet to tart crisp whitish flesh. Flesh...such an odd word. It reminds me of Jack Beatty, when he once said "The maritime strategy has an all but unstoppable institutional momentum behind it... that has given force and flesh to the theory." Such a wise, wise man! Alas! I am suddenly urged to share a story from the depths of my dear childhood. I was 16 years old. My how the days have grown since then! I was working on the corner (yes, the corner) of our family field. That is where the best worms were! Twas my job to scoop up the soft earth, and search for the worms! My family had acquired a taste for birds, so we needed the worms to bait them in! I however, did not care for the birds. But none of this is important to the story I want to share! So, back to where I started. I was 16 years old. I was walking my cat down the street, and as we turned the corner, we saw a little man. I decided to name this man Yenibs (pronounced "George"), so I call to him: "Yenibs, what are you doing?!" and strangley enough he didn't answer me! It angered my cat, so she began to hoot like an owl. I believe that caught the mans attention for he turned to me and said in his woman-like voice "Young girl, why are you only wearing one shoe?" and I simply replied "Because the other one is on my head!" Yenibs chuckled, and quickly walked away. I miss him. He was my friend. Poor Yenibs! Can one artificially create a banana? Note: The banana fruit is five or six inches long, and over an inch in diameter; the pulp is soft, and of a luscious taste, and is eaten either raw or cooked. Oh dear! How could I forget?!? It completely escaped me! I am unable to eat bananas! One time, as I was riding my kangaroo, I decided to eat an banana. What an awful idea! Something in the banana created a strange chemical reaction in my brain, and it caused me to dance like a ferret while singing old African songs! When I came out of my daze, I realized I was at starbucks wearing a business suit and talking about the NASDAQ (National Association of Securities Dealers Automated Quotation System) with my "friend" Henry. Henry was good looking, I suppose. Something was a little odd about him tho. Maybe it had to do with the fact that he was actually a woman, but I just thought it was funny to pretend she was a man. I'm not sure, but I'll blame it on the banana. They really mess with you! Oh dear, this has acquired much lengh! I best be ending this before they come and get me! They've been after me for awhile. I made them mad with the whole "honey-frog" thing. Did you hear that? Yeah, neither did I!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I didn't do much. Lets see...I woke up to my mom throwing the phone on my bed saying Josh and Holli called. I decided to call Josh back first, so I did that only after about 3 minutes of being awake. We talked for awhile, and then I proceeded with my day. The day was very uneventful. I talked to Marty for a bit, and I'm pretty positive that things will be ok. I worked on my essay for school. Tomorrow I will be finishing some of it up, while also continuing with the rest of my homework. At about 8:30, Tommy called me and asked if I wanted to come over to his house and watch a movie. Having nothing else to do, I figured that it was ok. So I went over there for a little bit, and we watched a movie, and he tried to teach me again to play chess. He had tried once before, without success, and this time was no different. I just don't understand it! Oh well. So to summarize this whole stupid blog...today=boring...tonight=somewhat eventful.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from Amanda's house. We watched A Night At The Roxbury! Score! I love that movie! It is really funny. I need to start doing my essay soon. I'll work on that tomorrow. Well, I don't have too much to blog about, so I'll be going.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past few days I haven't been doing much. I've just been going to school, and thats about it. Nothing else. Actually, on Monday after school me and Erin went on a date. She treated me to dinner. We both ate huge plates of French Toast. It was really fun. We've just recently started hanging out together outside of school or school-related things. It's cool. We get along really well. Today I didn't do much. I made Amanda laugh a whole bunch tho. We were talking about something as she was driving me home from school, and I said "Amanda, you should get a For Sale sign and put it in your car, but don't sell it." and apparently she thought it was one of the funniest things. Her reaction to it was so funny. She just kept laughing. It was great. After school Tommy called me, and asked if I wanted to go to his house and watch a movie with him. I was like 'No, I'm sorry. I'm not feeling good' and he was like 'oh, what's wrong?' and since I didn't want to explain, I was like 'you wouldn't understand' and tommy was all like 'is it special girl stuff?' and I just laughed, and he was like 'that's gross..why'd you tell me that? you could have just lied to me' and then we both laughed, and he was like 'well maybe some other time then' and laughed some more. it was really funny. Oh, yesterday in math it was really funny. Vetta and I were talking, and we noticed that my bangs were really long, so we decided to cut them. I asked kroese where his scissors were, and then i asked if Vetta and I could go to the bathroom. He gave me the WEIRDEST look, so I was like 'oh, my bangs are long. we're gonna go cut them!' and he just laughed. so after we cut them, we're walking out of the bathroom, and I'm like 'thanks vetta...i couldn't have done it alone' and this guy hears us, and he just shakes his head. it was really funny. well, that is really all that has been going on. maybe i'll have some interesting things to blog about soon! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I thought I had overcome being sick. I was mistaken. I was once again in bed all day. Oh well. I think I just need to take it easy these next few days, and I should be fine. Well, I have nothing to really blog about, so I'll blog later.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amanda came back for awhile tonight. We played Jeopardy and listened to music and just were being dorks. it was fun. jeopardy...ah, good times with that! i dont know. haha. well, thats really it from me for today!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I hung out with Amanda for a bit. We went to Fred Meyer and tried on some clothes. After that we decided to get some ice cream. Well, we were in her car when I noticed that I had spilled some chocolate ice cream on my sweatshirt. I was like "oh shit" and me and amanda just start laughing because I said it really funny. Then, as we were laughing I burped, and that somehow added to the humor. We both keep laughing so hard that it almost hurts. It was great. Well, then we finished our ice cream and were heading home. Little did I know that Amanda would take me to Tommy and Bobby's house. I was SCREAMING at her in the car to turn around but she wouldnt. So then she decides to call first, and she asks for Tommy, but he's in the shower, so then she asks for Bobby. She asks if Bobby would mind that I came by to say hello, and Bobby said he didn't care. So then, Amanda takes me there, and makes me go say hey. Well, since Tommy was in the shower, I just visited with Bobby for about 5-10 minutes, but then I decided it was weird enough so then we left. I'm not really sure what Bobby thought of it all, but oh well. I made it clear that Amanda took me their against my own will, so maybe he doesn't find me to be weird, but Amanda instead. Anyway, after that we are driving home and we pass Scott. He was on his way to work, so I was like "follow him!" and so Amanda turns around really fast and we begin to follow him. We catch up to him at Ricky D's (where he works) and Amanda's all like "we followed you" and Scott was all "I know, I saw you" so Amanda kinda got mad that she listened to my suggestion. We decided that we were even now. Hmmm...I wonder if Tommy will ask about me going to his house. Hmm..oh well. That was the extent of my evening so far, but I don't think it will be getting anymore exciting. I'll blog tomorrow maybe.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I stayed in bed because I was sick! It wasn't very fun! Oh well. My day wasn't that eventful. So I really have nothing to blog about. Hmm...I guess I'll blog later when I have more to talk about.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty good day. I don't have any homework for the weekend, so that is always nice. School was kind of uneventful. I was supposed to talk to Marty at lunch today, but I had a Key Club meeting, so I couldn't. I felt bad because he wanted to talk to me about something. Oh well. I guess I'll find out later. Oh, after school I was talking to him on the phone, and then it beeped, so I switched lines. And who was it on the other line?! Bobby! Yeah, so we're talking, then a half hour rolls by and I realize that I forgot about Marty!! I felt soooo bad! I told Marty what happened, and he was mad. I don't blame him, but I really did feel bad. Oh well. I just thought it was weird that I talked to Bobby. We never talk, and then he calls me to talk...it was just weird. Oh well...I'm not complaining! After I told Marty I was sorry sooo many times, I went to Amanda's house. I got to drive on the way there. Sure, it was only down the street...but that's like a record for me! I did a really good job too! We watched Never Been Kissed. I LOVE that movie! It is so awesome! Then after that, I came home and here I am! I hope that tomorrow is a good day. I think it should be.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night after I blogged, I got this phone call from someone. It turns out that it was bobby and him and tommy were driving around Big Meadow trying to find where I lived, and said that it would just be easier if I told them. So I did, and they drop by my house, and we hang out for about 5 minutes. They couldnt come inside tho because their little brother and sister were in the car. It was funny tho, cuz Bobby was like "erica arent you gonna ask us inside?" and tommy was like "we can't, the kids are in the car...maybe next time" and so him and bobby said that they will have to come over some other time. It was very interesting! It seemed so weird for that to happen tho, but hey, I didn't mind! haha. Now for today....hmmm....this morning amanda came over and i straightened her hair. my mission for lunch is to find scott and ask him what his plans are this weekend and if he prefers pie or cake. i really want to know. haha. im weird, but hey, i know that. i have a math test that i need to study for tonight, because i need to get an A on it. well, this blog is getting kind of boring for me to type, so i'll be going!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from the science fair at school. Surprisingly, it wasn't that bad! It was actually somewhat fun. First of all, me and Holli got 1st place for physics! We got a nifty blue ribbon! Score! What else? Oh yeah, I got a lot of interaction with Bobby tonight! Even better! The best part tho was when he blew me a kiss goodbye! Kick ass! Sadly, I didn't know science fairs could be so fun! Well, that was my evening!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm...my mood has improved since yesterday so that is good. I have been REALLY tired lately. And for anyone who likes math, here is an equation to show that: Erica + tiredness = badness. It is quite simple really. When I got home from school yesterday I went straight to my bed and fell asleep for a bit. The storm yesterday was pretty cool. I love thunder and lightning. It kicks ass. I went out in the rain yesterday and played in it for a bit. That was fun. Today I have to be at school from 6 to 8 tonight for the lame science fair. Oh well. Sadly, I would have nothing better to do anyway. I need some sleep...hmmm...I've recently discovered that I like the song Take Me Out by Franz Ferdinand. It is a cool song. The music video is a little weird however. I SHOULD REALLY be doing homework for physics right now, but I'm not. Oh well. Hmm...I haven't checked Josh's blog yet today, but then again I won't be surprised if he hasnt updated. Oh well. I need to figure out what my plans are for this weekend. I might do something with Holli and Erin during Friday since we wont be having school. Also, I MIGHT do something with Amanda on saturday, and tera. However, that one im not really sure about. If we dont do it this saturday, we will some other time tho. Hmm...well I think I'll be going so I can do my stupid homework.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored and in computer class. I don't know, today I'm in a weird mood. I'm not really into the whole "interaction with other people" type of thing. I just don't see the point in it right now. Too many people are getting on my nerves (ok, only maybe 2). I'm just tired of stuff. I don't even know the point of this blog, so whatever. I guess it's just a super long way of saying that I'm not in the mood to blog, and I may not be for awhile. I don't know tho. We'll see how things go tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty good day. I went to Marty's house. We watched House on Haunted Hill. Ok, that movie is so retarded. However, it taught us that in tough situations, the ghost of Chris Kattan will save you. Don't ask. Haha. Oh, and I FINALLY figured out what Marty's GPA was! I was proud of myself! I don't really know why I would be proud, but yeah. Haha. Hmmm....not too much else happened today really. Oh, Jory was at the high school, and I didn't even go to see him! What is that?!?! Ugh! Oh well, I really don't care that much. Hmm....that was really about it for my day. Overall, I think I had a really good day!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was the field trip for my physics class. It was actually pretty fun. I have a few bruises, but they'll heal soon enough. I think I ate too much cotton candy. Oh well. Tonight Amanda, Alex, and Holli came over for movie night. We watched the movie Grind. It was pretty funny. There was this character in there named Matt, and he totally reminded me of Matt Belding. It was funny. ADAM BRODY was in it!!!! SCORE!!!! I know Amanda has taken a new quote from that movie! (greetings from the interior)haha. good stuff. well that was basically it for today!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, me and chubbs planned on going to the play at the high-school. well, we were 20 min late, so we decided to go next thursday. steven and caitie were late too...so me and alex got into her car and were joking around about following them. me and alex were just driving around (well alex was doing the driving), and we decided to go to the park. after awhile, who shows up?!? steven and caitie! it was really funny. but then me and alex realized that we should get home soon, cuz my parents might wonder why it took us so long to get back. so we go to my house, and tell my parents how we were waiting at the high school for awhile cuz we thought the play started at 7:30, not 7. they bought the story, so that was good. then me and alex just hung out at my house for awhile. it was fun. well, that was my evening. it was actually somewhat eventful! score!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing much has been going on. Today after school Holli came over for a bit. We were supposed to do some physics stuff, but we didn't understand. So then we just hung out. After she left, I talked to Marty on the phone for a bit. Then Amanda came over, and we played Jeopardy a few times. It may sound sad, but its strangely fun. I don't know. Tomorrow is the physics field trip, so that should be interesting. We have to do these experiment things, I don't know, it sounds pretty stupid. Oh well. At least I won't be at school. Well, that was pretty much the extent of my day. Maybe I'll blog tomorrow, maybe not. Who knows?
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an ok day, I suppose. The morning started off being ok. We starting watching Buscando a Nemo in spanish class. I've never seen Finding Nemo, so that's pretty cool. I understand pretty much what we are doing in math, so that is good too. Computers was really dumb. Good thing I only had to be in there for about 15 minutes. Ok, Mrs. Parker now says we can't even go on the internet at all because of some virus going around or something. I dont really know because I wasn't listening.  And then I had just finished my assignment, and I was just about to save when all of a sudden, it closed down on me. So then I told Mrs. Parker what happened, and she just told me to write her a note saying I completed the assignment. So that's good. Then I went to some thing for juniors about colleges and what-not in the auditorium. I didn't pay too much attention cuz me and tommy kept messing around (not in that way..haha).  Lunch time is when my day turned interesting. I'll start with the funny part first, and then I'll get into the non-funny part. Ok...the funny part deals with me and Theran. We decided to "noodle" the pretzel stick. Ok, by "noodle" i mean, Lady and the Tramp style. So we do that, and then for the shortest second, a little portion of our lips slightly touched, and ryan was convinced that we kissed. we totally didn't! i just wonder if he will tell lori. but theran was saying that lori wont believe ryan, and that lori likes me anyway, so as to not worry. i'm not too sure tho.  now as for the other portion of my eventful lunch time...somehow the convo turned into who has been drunk and stuff before, and theran was like "i bet erica hasnt had any alcohol" (or something like that)and i whispered to him "um, you're wrong" and then he didnt believe me, so he called ethan over cuz i said that ethan knew the story...so he asked ethan about it, and was like 'well, she wasnt really drunk, she more or less just had a good buzz' (this happened like a year ago, and when it did, i told ethan about it but no one else) and then holli was convinced that i was lying, and kept asking me about it. and well since it embarasses me to talk about it, i told her about 4 times that i didnt want to discuss it at the current moment...so then about 5 min pass and then she's like "you're kidding!" and im tired of her never believing me, so i throw down my hand (as i threw down my hand, my food fell) and yell 'Holli....fuck...im not kidding! ok, can we just drop it?!' and i'm about to cry, and she just looks at me, and then she walks away from the table...and then in physics she asks to talk to me about it, and i'm like "i really don't want to talk about it, ok?" and she was like 'well, i dont understand' so then im like 'holli, please, not now' and then after school she was telling me how she was mad at me because i was the one who threw my food at her (when it fell out of my hand and didnt even hit her) and embarassed her in front of the whole table...when in fact she was the one who was embarassing me cuz she wouldnt drop it, and then she was like 'why didnt you tell me?' and got all mad at me and said that i made her mad because of my reaction, and she couldnt understand why i was mad at her. it's really stupid, but it still makes me mad! ugh! oh well....that was really all the exciting points of my day. I'll blog tomorrow (maybe). 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good ol' 80s lyrics. I dunno. Tommy never called on Friday night, but that is really ok. I just ended up going to bed early. Catching up on some sleep was good for me. Today I took a practice SAT out of this book I have, and I only got a 1150 on it. My goal is to get around a 1300-1400 on the actual test, so I should study/practice some more. I don't really have too much to blog about. Today I watched Big Fish, and that was good.  I'm only blogging for Chubbs because I know she gets mad when I don't. Well, that is really about it. I'll blog later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty good day! Kind of boring, but there were fun moments as well! Lets see....what were some of the good stuff? Oh yeah.....TOMMY ASKED ME OUT ON A DATE! I don't know why I am so excited about that....considering I told him I didn't know. Why did I have to do that? He may not even call!  So, oh well.  I just don't know why I am always scared to do stuff with guys. I totally shouldn't be. Girls my age are supposed to go out with guys and have fun, not just stay home. I'm such a loser. Oh well. I know that eventually I'll do stuff. This weekend shouldnt be too eventful. I'll just be stuck at home doing nothing, as always. I'm listening to this song called Honey and The Moon, and for some reason, it really put me into a deep-thinking kind of mood. It made me a little sad too. I don't know. I just feel that I'm incapable of making the right decisions sometime. But then other times I totally feel that I made the right choice and have no regrets. I really don't even know what I am trying to get at right now. Swedish Fish are good....right, Chubbs? Speaking of Chubbs...I haven't really talked to her too much these past few days. Hmm.. Oh well. I'll blog later.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha.....ok, my title doesn't really make sense. well, it kind of does considering im wearing my hood right now. but anyways...on with my day. my day has been pretty uneventful. in spanish class we ate ice cream that mrs. roth made. it was chocolate and was good. i liked it. in math we were doing stuff that takes FOREVER to do. i only got 2 and half problems done in a half hour. that is how long it takes! it is easy stuff, but it is just very time consuming. oh well. so i have some calc homework to do tonight. erin might come over tonight so that we can work on calc. that would be good because we work together very well. oh, i havent read josh's blog yet! oh no!....ok, i took a pause and read it. haha. good stuff. i dont know. hmmm.....what else? im not really sure. amanda witnessed me leave egypt and check into the border (im sure no one but me and amanda understand that). so i guess that is good. hopefully i'll be able to cross the border soon.  i still need to figure out a lot of things, and that makes me mad. i wish that sometimes i just knew all the answers. things would be so much easier that way. oh well. i know that in time i'll come to the right decision. i just dont know if im patient enough to wait until that time is right. i guess i dont have a choice tho. i mean i need to wait. there is nothing else i can do but wait. and while i wait i might as well make the most of what i have. well im done blogging now, so i shall be going. i'll blog later today maybe...not too sure tho.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After school today I told my mom that I had watched The Exorcist. She was actually ok with it.  At first she seemed a little mad, but then we talked about that and related things and she said she was fine with it. That is good then....haha.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm in computer class right now. I've been sitting here for about the last 10 minutes just staring at the screen deciding what to write. I still don't have any ideas really. Oh well. I just read Josh's blog, and reading about the sugar thing made me think of what I once did when I needed to stay awake...haha. Josh knows that story. Today at break I was talking to Marty and I felt like a mother or something because I was scolding him for not going to class. Oh well. It was funny, Marty said hi to Alex and she was all like 'why do you fucking talk to Erica?' She said it jokingly of course, but Marty's reaction was funny. I just realized that Josh and Alex are probably the only ones who read this. Maybe sometimes Holli, but I'm not really sure. Oh well. She probably doesn't. I just think it's Josh and Alex. So you guys are the coolest of all my friends! OK? haha. I don't know. Oh well. Right now I should be doing calc homework, but I really don't feel like going to my locker and getting my book. I'll just take it home tonight and actually do homework I suppose. Wow, what a concept! Crazy! I can't wait until May 14th. That should be fun since we are going to go to Oaks Park for physics class. I might ask Stiffy if she wants to be a chaperone, but I'm not too sure yet. My mom is really cool, so I wouldn't mind. However, I just don't want her to overhear any Matt Belding jokes because that would be bad. And I know some might happen, because they always seem to do. She must not know about that. That reminds me...I am so tempted to tell her that I watched The Exorcist. I really wonder what she would do. Maybe I'll wait a few weeks, but I know that I eventually will tell her. I figure that if I wait a few weeks I can't get in trouble, because obviously I'm fine after seeing it. Oh well. I don't know. I just think it would be funny seeing her reaction. I really wonder what she would do.  Tommy right now is telling me how there are many sides to him, but I think he is full of crap. Oh well. And I just asked him to show me more of his sides and he accused me of just trying to get him in bed. yeah...that is it....sure. Oh well. I've been thinking a lot lately about guy stuff, and it is sometimes confusing. Damn it! Oh well. I just hope that I will get everything sorted out in time. Hopefully that time will be soon because I am getting really impatient. If only there was a way for sure to determine exactly how I feel. I don't even know where to begin, I'm that lost. I want to talk to someone about it, but I am afraid to also. But I need some help or something. I really want to get things figured out. And when things are figured out, I know that I will be much more relaxed and stuff. Oh well. I just really need to figure things out as soon as possible, because if I don't then I am going to drive myself crazy! Hmm....I think that I will be going now, because I really have nothing better to do.  Maybe I'll write some emails to people, or just browse various sites. I could always go to my locker and get my homework, but I'll save that for later. I need more stuff to do after school. Hopefully I'll hear more about that job at the mortgage company for this summer. That would be nice. I could picture myself working in an office environment. I'm good with that kind of stuff. And Amy is really nice, so I would enjoy working with her. With my luck however, it probably wont work out. I just need more things to go my way for once. It would be nice to have that happen every once in awhile.  Oh well, my time eventually will come where everything is going great. Until then, I'll just have to deal with the way things are nice...which isn't too bad. I'm pretty happy overall. There are just a few things that I would like to become improved. Nothing too major tho...so yeah. De nada. (I really have no idea why I just said "you're welcome" in spanish....but I really don't care either.)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's think. Thinking is good. Good is the opposite of bad.  Bad people go to jail. Jail is where my daddy is. ok....I don't know. I'm weird. Moving on! Yesterday I went to Marty's house. We watched The Exorcist. Yeah, I really don't understand why my mom said I couldn't see that movie. It wasn't scary at all. A little weird, but I didn't see the big deal to it. Oh well. After Marty's house, i went to Holli's house. It was the weirdest thing! I was talking to Holli and I stuck my hand in my back pocket and I felt a little piece of paper from a gum wrapper. I take it out and unfold it, and I notice there is a phone number written on it. I can't remember whose number it is, or why the hell it is in my pocket, so Holli suggested I call it.  Wanting to solve the mystery, I decide to do just that. Out of all the people whose number it could be, it turned out to be Josh! Isn't that crazy? I thought it was really weird. I have no idea why the hell his number was in my back pocket. It makes no sense to me. It was really weird. Oh well. Me and Holli also called Harley and talked to him for a bit. I haven't talked to him in a long time, so it was nice. He should be coming home late this summer. I miss him. Oh well. This summer I may get a job working at a mortgage company, helping to do office work. I'm not too sure yet tho. Hmm...well that was the extent of my weekend so far. My grandparents are over right now because they are going to eat dinner over. So my plan is to be on the computer so I don't have to talk to them too much. They are kind of boring. Oh well. I'll be sorry I didn't spend enough time with them once they die. Awful, but true.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just woke up, so I decided to blog. I didn't go to bed until 3 in the morning. haha. It was because I was talking to Marty on the phone. Today I have a dentist appointment at 3:40. In a weird twisted way, I like going to the dentist. Later tonight, around 6, I'll be going to Holli's house with Amanda and Alex. We're gonna watch movies. It should be fun. When I get home I might blog, if anything funny happens. I make no guarantees, however.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a fun day. I spent it with Amanda. We just hung out at her house, prepping for her garage sale. She bought Aaron a birthday card, and she decorated it as well. Too funny. Oh, we saw Alex and Audra at Hi-School Pharmacy. There was a tennis thing tonight, but Amanda didn't want to go, and Kaila did, so she had to drop her off. Earlier, Alex called for Amanda and wanted Amanda to come, but she was set on not going. So we try to drop off Kaila, without being noticed, but I don't think it worked. Oh well, it was funny. Also, when Amanda was trying to take me home, she decided to take the long way...a nice 20 min detour. It was so funny. Basically, today was a fun day.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a boring day. I saw my mom fall off the treadmill when my dad turned it on super high speed. It was great. I found Jory's email address...even greater. Oh yeah!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok...Alex and I have a new fascination for shit. We love the word, and we like talking about it. What can I say? We're odd. I had a good time last night. There were some pretty interesting parts (who is your pee buddy?), and some fun parts (where the hell is my shirt? haha). I dunno. I didn't get much sleep at all. I fell asleep around 4:15, and I woke up at 5:30. Around 2:30 I think, I woke up Alex to tell her to turn off the light and tv...so she did. We didn't realize until later that I had woken her up to do it, instead of me doing it myself. Alex loves me as a friend! yay! I dunno. I'm gonna go watch a movie at Anna's tonight, but I'll be back later. Oh yeah....JORY THINKS I'M COOL!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an interesting day. I helped put banners up for Key Club from 9:30 until 1 today. Alex and I worked with this older guy named Ken, and he was kinda creepy. He touched Alex's leg...hehe. After that I did nothing really. Then around 6, Alex stopped by for about a half hour. We talked about some stuff, and shared some weird laughs.  As I'm blogging right now, I am talking to Alex and we are gonna watch a movie together. I'm gonna go to her house now...so I'll blog tomorrow maybe.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just watched Office Space, and my title was my favorite quote from the movie. Don't know what I liked about it so much, but yeah. I think everyone needs to see that movie.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day. I woke up at 11:15, and then at 11:30 Alex called me. We decided to meet up in the field to discuss things and what not. To make a long story short...me and Alex hung out until about 5:30. We watched Along Came Polly, had a water fight with Nikki and Noah, got some ice cream, and just had a fun day.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty good day. I hung out with Amanda for a bit, and I picked up my photos. We went back to her house for a few minutes, and then we went to Marty's house. It was nice seeing him. Amanda is one crazy girl, I swear! When I got home, I talked to Josh on the phone for awhile. I also talked to Holli too. Lots of people interaction today...good stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just talking to Josh, and he was telling me that he observed a blogging trend that I have. He said that generally on "fun" days, I blog before 10 and on "boring" days, I blog after 10. That boy has too much time on his hands....well better time on his hands than something else. I dunno. I'm in a weird mood kinda. I talked to Alex today for a bit, and that was nice. She should be back tomorrow, and that is even more nice. I dunno. Haha. Today me and Amanda went to Hi-School Pharmacy for a bit, and to Subway. That was really the only thing that I did. The rest of the day was boring. Oh well. Hopefully tomorrow will be better.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I saw the movie Dodgeball with Holli. That movie is very interesting to say the least. There were some disturbing parts (pizza, anyone?), and some parts that were very funny too (if you can dodge a wrench, you can dodge a ball). Other than that, my day was very boring.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a kinda boring day. I hung out with Alex for a bit. We got some ice cream and talked about plans for this upcoming weekend. Amanda came over for a little while and we played some Jeopardy. Good stuff. Other than that, my day was pretty boring. Let me just say...it is going to take some getting used to Anna and the boys living in Molalla. Yikes!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a fairly boring day. Stayed home and watched Chloe while my parents helped Anna move. Talked on the phone to Josh, Martin (like 4 times), Alex, and Amanda. Then I went to the apartment to help unpack, and Amanda came and joined in. Anna gave us the task of helping to record a message for her answering machine. Me and Amanda came up with some weird ideas, but in the end Anna just kept it simple. Oh well. Hopefully tomorrow will be more exciting.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a sun-filled fun day. I woke up at 11, so that right there was nice. I never sleep in that late. Holli and Alex came over. It was nice seeing Holli because I haven't seen her since school got out. It was also nice seeing Alex since I haven't seen her since Tuesday. My dear Chubbs! We just hung out and went swimming. Good stuff. Alex and I showed Holli the "fort" as well. I think Holli liked it. It was fun. Other than that, I really didn't do too much today. Tomorrow will be boring tho, but oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I spent all day with Mika. It was great catching up with her. Today I went to Marty's house. We watched Dude, Where's My Car? That movie is so dumb, but I love it. It is even better because Hal Sparks is in it! Oh yeah! Speaking of hot guys, I am going to try to make a resume tomorrow so I can turn it into Hollywood Video. That would be cool if I had a job there. It would be nice having the extra money. Good stuff. I got my report card back today, and I'M RANKED #1! I'm pretty sure that Bri is too, but I'm glad that I finally caught up. The past two days have been good, to sum things up. Tomorrow Alex and Holli should be coming over. That should be fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a fun day. Once again I hung out with Alex and Amanda. I also got a really bad sun burn. Oh well. Tomorrow I'll be doing something with Mika, so that should be interesting. I'll have to blog about that later. Oh....today at Hollywood Video, I saw Jory! Mmm....so hot! haha.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a fun day! I spent it with Amanda and Alex. We were going to go to the mall because Amanda wanted to look for bed frames and bathing suits. Well on the way to the mall I decided to show Amanda and Alex where I used to live in Lake Oswego. I showed them my house, and then I decided to see if my old friend Mika was home (we used to be neighbors). She was, so I got to see her for a bit. It was nice because I haven't seen her in quite awhile. I think it has been a little more than a year. We are going to try to do something on Wednesday. So anyway....we go to the mall. Well along the line somewhere, Amanda's plan of finding a bed frame got lost. So me and Alex just follow her around while she looks for bathing suits. It was fun. We did some weird things, and took some weird pictures, but it was all really fun. Even Amanda said she had a good time, and needs to take the both of us again. After that, I decided to go get some black licorice ice cream with Alex. That was fun too. After the ice cream we were walking home, and we decide that we want to watch a movie. We want to watch one that Amanda owns, so we call her, and Amanda says she'll come pick us up. Me and Alex, being the bright ones, decide that it would be funny if we just sat down on the sidewalk and waited. Of course we embarassed ourselves, but it was all in the name of fun. So we go to Alex's house, and watch the movie. Then after the movie, we decide to go through the field and take the sign that says "Be prepared to stop", which we've had our eyes on for awhile. It was dark, so it was the perfect time to take it. On our way there, we heard something in the grass, and it scared me, and I jumped behind Alex and grabbed onto her. It was so funny. Well, after we got the sign and were out of visibility we just kept laughing and Alex fell. It was so freakin funny! We decided to put the sign in the fort, and going in there when it was dark was way scary. It was really fun tho. Then after that, I went back to Alex's house for about 20 min, and then went home. Today was a really fun day!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My title was my favorite line from the new Harry Potter movie. I saw that movie today. It was pretty good. Also today I went to Amanda's house with Alex. Her parents graduated from PSU, so they had a BBQ. We got to meet some of Amanda's family. It was actually really fun. We met her aunt and uncle, and they are really nice and funny. We plan on going to their house up in Washington sometime this summer. They invited us, and it sounds really fun. We'll get that planned later. Between Amanda's house, and the movie, my day was pretty much filled. It was a good day overall. Actually so far (knock on wood) this summer vacation (all 5 days of it) has been pretty good. Hopefully the rest will be good, if not better!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a pretty eventful day. Let me see if I can remember everything. Ok, well it started out that me and alex were going to go look around the garage sales in big meadow. well we got distracted from that and decided to do other stuff. we walked around big meadow, and into the section where they are building new houses. we went into one and took a picture of ourselves in front of the fireplace. why? we dont know. then as we were walking back to my house, i took a picture of someone's house, and me and alex plan on anonymously sending it to amanda. haha. good stuff. so then we went back to my house, and we got some soda and went back to the field. wow...i just realized that i am describing all of this in detail when in reality only about 3 ppl read this, and one of them is alex. oh well. so then after the field we decided to go to subway. so we go to subway, and then after we go to ricky d's to get some ice cream. we got the licorice ice cream, which made our mouths turn a deep shade of green. it was awful. so then we went to the park, and then the library. we left some notes in random books. it was embarassing when we first walked in because tommy's mom was there, and she saw my mouth, and she was like 'licorice ice cream?'. i suppose it was kind of funny too. then we were walking back to my house, and we came across this HUGE pile of rock and dirt, so we decided to climb it. on my way down, i tripped and i slid down the pile. it hurt, but it was so funny too. i'm such a klutz. throughout the whole afternoon me and alex took various pictures. it will be interesting when we get them back. haha. well that was my day up until now, and i doubt it will get anymore exciting.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day. I went to the Rose Festival, and that was fun. After that I hung out with Vetta for a bit. We went to Tommy and Bobby's house. We started watching the movie Miracle, but it was boring, so we stopped. We didn't do much else. That was pretty much my day. Oh...quote of the day: Never trust a Carnie.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday night was pretty fun. Alex came over first and we were just hanging out looking at my music collection. We have decided that I have a wide variety. Then Erin came and we decided to go show Erin the "fort". Well, as we were about to leave Amanda asked if she could come over and hang out for a bit, and I told her that we were going to the "fort" so she said to call her when we got back. So Alex and I show Erin the fort, and she seemed to think it was cool. We walk back to my house and we notice Amanda's car parked in front. We go upstairs and open my sister's door, and inside is Chloe and Amanda sitting on Chloe's bed watching TV, with Amanda in her prom dress. It was so funny! She just decided to wear her prom dress. It was great. Sometime this summer Me, Alex, and Amanda need to go somewhere wearing our prom dresses. It would be fun. So after awhile Amanda leaves, so then me and Erin decided to have some chocolate ice cream. Well, I was being a dork with it, and smeared it around my mouth to make it look like a mustache. Alex said she needed a picture of it, so me her and erin walk to her house to get alex's camera. as we were walking, i had the ice cream on my face. it was so funny. so we get the camera, and on the way back we decide to go in the "fort" again. well we went all the way back, and we noticed an opening to the field. so we go through the opening and walk in the field and we walk forward for awhile, and we notice another "fort". this one was scary tho because it looked someone lived there. we got scared so we ran back to the main path in the field. the grass was really wet, so we got all wet. it was fun. me and alex decided that we need to go back on a nice day and check out the second "fort". it was really fun. then we came back to my house and just watched movies and hung out. today was boring, so i really feel no need to blog about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a great day. The fact that it was the last day of school made it the best! I think I managed to pull all A's, so that is good. I cut it close with calculus tho, because I had an 89.6%, but Kroese rounded up to an A. Hmmm...what else? Oh yeah! Marty sent me flowers! It was such a great surprise! I loved it! Tonight should be fun too. I'll blog about that later tho.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kind of a lot has happened since Friday. Since Alex was with me for pretty much all of it, I don't feel the need to go into detail. Hmm..I'll blog about today tho. It was a half day, so after school I was bored and called Amanda to ask if I could come over and clean. So I did that for awhile, and then I showed her the "fort" in the field. We met Alex there, because Amanda dropped us off at the middle school so me and alex could walk home with chloe. so we walk chloe home and along the way we show her the "fort". then we ran in the tall grass. haha. it was fun. then alex came back to my house where we made a list and some visuals for my mom to persuade her into letting me have an all night movie night tomorrow. then we played some james bond on nintendo. we felt like boys, but it was fun. so tomorrow night we're gonna try to have some ppl spend the night and watch movies. it should be fun. i'll talk more when more happens. haha.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good ol' Chubbs...ya gotta love her! Today I took my Spanish final. I did good on it, I got an A. I think Mrs. Roth enjoyed mine and Omondo's sidenotes. haha. Then I had people sign my year book. Good stuff. Oh, today in physics we had our egg drop lab. Katie and I kicked ass! None of our eggs cracked! Score! Well, tomorrow I have the SATs, ugh! That's all folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, tis the first day of June! Today was a fairly good day. In spanish, we played Jeopardy, and my group KICKED ASS! Oh yeah! In math, Tommy had a chipmunk, so we got to play with that for awhile. It was a baby, and it was so cute! Lunch was fun too. Erin and I got into a cake fight. Holli had made cake because it was Ben's (or as Amanda would say, Jamin's) birthday. Well, me and Erin shared a piece, and we made a mess of it! She threw some at me, so then I got her back, and so on and so forth. It was fun, and messy. Those were really the only highlights of my day. Other than that, it was pretty normal. Tomorrow I have to give a speech in psychology about interpersonal attraction. I finished the paper yesterday, and I have decided to put it in here. Read it if you like, or don't. Doesn't matter to me--it is nothing exceptionally good. Well, I'll blog later.   Interpersonal Attraction  A man and woman have fun together on their first date.  They laughed at the same parts in the movie, agreed quickly on a restaurant because they like the same kind of food, and enjoyed the conversation.  As the evening draws to an end, however, the woman wonders whether to agree to a second date.  She thinks he is a nice guy, a good person, so why doesn’t she feel especially attracted to him?  As a man enters his apartment, he notices his neighbor leaving her place and they exchange smiles.  Once inside, he wonders why he finds her so attractive.  He knows nothing about her, but he always thinks about her and what she is like.  What is it about her that he finds increasingly appealing? In another scenario, a woman finds herself attracted to a coworker based solely on his exceptionally good looks.  He is clearly wrong for her, but she is captivated by his physical appearance.  Could she really be falling for Mr. Wrong just because he’s good looking?    Liking someone but not finding them “romantically” attractive, becoming attracted to the “familiar stranger”, and favoring someone for his or her good looks rather than deeper qualities seem like all too common cases.  This is due to the fact that most of us find many different people attractive in different ways (Weber, 2003).  In social psychology, attraction is described as an attitude of liking (positive attraction) or disliking (negative attraction).  In interpersonal attraction, one can see that there are many factors that attract us to particular people as potential friends or partners.  The four main determining factors of interpersonal attraction include physical appearance, similarity to ourselves, evidence that our attraction is returned, and proximity (Rathus, 1998, 472).  Physical appearance plays an important role in interpersonal attraction.  This is because we generally tend to notice a person’s appearance before anything else.  Since people have different perceptions, there is no single answer for physically attractive “standards.”  However, there are some things that are viewed as attractive to many cultures.  An example would be a smiling person, for they are generally perceived as more attractive than a person who is frowning.  In a study done, British and Japanese people were asked to identify features that they found to be attractive.  The facial features found in “attractive” women include large eyes, high cheekbones, and narrow jaws.  In another study, infants were studied to see what they found to be attractive.  It was determined that the longer the gaze towards a person from the infant, the more attractive that person was.  Infants, as young as 2 months, preferred faces that were also rated by adults as most attractive.  This evidence suggests that we may be born with a predisposition to find certain types of physical features attractive (Rathus, 1998, 472-73).    Facial features are not the only aspect studied dealing with physical attractiveness, but as well as body shape and type.  Preferences for body shape vary greatly, and there is a great deal of variation in people’s standard for attractiveness of body shape.  This includes both the shape we prefer for others, and the shape we perceive ourselves to have.  In a study done amongst college students, men and women were both asked to describe the “ideal” body shape.  Most of the men said that their body shape was near the ideal standard, while most women thought that they were heavier than the ideal shape.  This suggests that females are more likely than males to incorrectly think they are too heavy to be attractive (Rathus, 1998, 473).  There is also evidence that physical appearance has a greater role in the attraction of males to females than vice versa (Gale, 2001).  Other people’s physical appearance influences perceptions of our own attractiveness as well.  When observed simultaneously, people of average attractiveness tend to be judged more attractive when they are with a same-sex person who is very good-looking, but they are thought of as less attractive when with someone who is unattractive.  When observed sequentially, however, the reverse effect occurs.  In heterosexual relationships, although people’s overall impressions of a man appear to be influenced by his partner’s physical attractiveness, the same effect does not hold for a woman (Franzoi, 2003).    Besides physical attractiveness, it is also noticed that there is a tendency to be attracted to others who are similar to us in particular characteristics.  This is known as the matching hypothesis. Friends and partners also tend to be similar to one another in race, ethnicity, age, level of education, and religion (Bersheid, 1988, 92).  In fact, similarity of attitudes is a key contributor to attraction in both friendships and romantic relationships.  People also gravitate to others who are like themselves in terms of characteristics related to affiliation, including sociability, friendliness, and warmth (Gale, 2001).  Being attracted to people similar to ourselves can be traced back to the fact that people desire cognitive consistency or “balance” in their thoughts, feelings, and social relationships (Franzoi, 2003).  It is only natural that we want to be around someone who shares similar views and feelings, but we also like to be around people who like being around us as well.  Another major aspect dealing with interpersonal attraction is called reciprocity.  Reciprocity is the mutual exchange of feelings or attitudes (Rathus, 1998, 474). Interpersonal attraction theorists view reciprocity as an important contributor to the emergence of positive feelings among persons (Hallinan, 1999).  It makes sense for one to want to spend time with someone who enjoys his or her company as well. If given the choice, most people wouldn’t prefer to spend time with those that don’t like them compared to those that do.  Research has even shown that people are more open, warm, and helpful when they are talking with strangers who seem to like them (Rathus, 1998, 474).  If led to believe that another likes or dislikes us, we may behave in ways that confirm that expectation (Franzoi, 2003).  For example, Blau argues that an interaction is rewarding when the partner in the social exchange communicates approval of the person (Hallinan, 1999).  Reciprocity is, therefore, an important stabilizing factor in an interpersonal relation.  Proximity is another category that helps shine light onto the mysteries of interpersonal attraction.  Obviously, in order to meet, two people must share close proximity.  The sharing of this space will help one to get to know a person better. In some cases becoming more familiar with an individual can lead to a dislike of that individual. More often, though, getting to know someone leads to a deeper relationship with that individual (Bersheid, 1988, 85).  The case of proximity could be the cause of the attraction that the man held in the scenario towards his female neighbor.  It is logical that people develop feelings towards those whom they are in close contact with.  Interpersonal attraction can be better understood by studying the factors that compose the subject.  The components including physical appearance, similarity to ourselves, evidence that our attraction is returned, and proximity all help to make sense of the riddle in which attraction is hidden (Rathus, 1998, 472).  Every component, in a sense, is intertwined with the other.  Proximity will determine the number of times we come into contact with a person.  Before knowing anything about the person we come into contact with, we see their physical appearance and judge the attractiveness of it.  If some attraction is there, we may pursue them further and get to know them better.  Soon enough, we will be able to tell how similar the person is to ourselves.  Then if we want to continue any form of relationship with them, we will determine to do so or not based on the way that they perceive us.  If everything goes well, we will have a new friend or companion.  It may seem like a complicated process at first, but when broken down into smaller fragments, interpersonal attraction is not only easily understood, but it is also fascinating as well.  Interpersonal attraction is the reason and science behind everyday relationships, making it an important aspect to comprehend.    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Felt like spicing up the title a bit with using my grandtacular spanish skills.&nbsp; Why that title? I dunno...I guess it was a good choice cuz of the joke I tried to play on Alex. That is right Alex, I tried to play a&nbsp; joke on you, but you already know that. I think it worked. You were getting mad. Mad...good. Goodness! That reminds me....I talked to Reggie for a bit last night (well like 1 in the morning online).&nbsp; We probably talked for a good half hour to an hour. I haven't talked to that kid for awhile, so it was fun. We were both in good moods, and decided to spread the goodness. I talked to Marty until like 5 in the morning on the phone...now that was crazy. That would also explain why I woke up at 12:30 today. Amanda would be dissapointed! Oh well. Hmm...I think I've done my job of blogging enough about nothing for now. G'day to y'all! 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I temporarily forgot about my blog. Oops...that darn Erica! On Friday I went to Hooters with Amanda, and later I hung out with Marty, Sam, Frank, and Eddy. Both things were fun. On Saturday I went to Marty's house, and that was fun as well.&nbsp; Sunday and today I did nothing. Tomorrow my favorite aunt is coming over, so that should be fun. She's cool. Hmm...not much of anything exciting has gone on, or else I would blog about it. Until next time... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today has been a fun day so far. In the morning, around 9:30, Amanda came over. I got dressed and ready, and then we went to go "run some errands". First, we went to her friend Sheri's house so Amanda could pick up some clothes she had left there. She has talked about Sheri before, so it was nice finally meeting her. Then we went to the mall because Amanda needed to get a bathing suit top. Let me just say that the fat kid didn't get the low carb pizza this time! Oh yeah! haha. After the mall we stopped by Marty's house to pick up some CDs. We stayed there for about 20 minutes, maybe, and then we went to Alex's house to pick up another CD. When we were there, I had to do some "dirty work" for Alex. The things I do! Jeeze, I'm such a good friend! haha. So far that has been my day, but I doubt it will get any more exciting. Tomorrow Marty is coming over, and on Friday I'm going to Hooters with Amanda, Aaron, and a friend of Aaron's choice...possibly Winslow. Basically what I'm trying to say is that I'll have more to blog about later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The ship was a    rockin'  and a  rollin' ! I began my journey as a young&nbsp; girl  trapped in a  man's  body. It was a  dark night  in Arkansas. There is nothing like being in the wrong body on a dark night, let me tell ya. Never was I so    confused    in my life! In search for some&nbsp;   juicy peaches   , I began crawling due to my childish nature. Any onlooker would have been most   confused   due to my appearance. None of this is making sense, you say? You are right to think such a thing! None of   this makes sense   and it is all because of a   very   good reason. I am lying to you. Yep, I lied. Why did I lie? I thought I would spice things up. Spice...makes me think of the   Spice Girls  . Ginger was my favorite. I once recall hearing that ginger root is good for sea sickness.   I just can't     do it captain!   What is love? Baby don't hurt me, don't hurt me no more. I walked across an empty room. I felt the earth beneath my feet.     You had me at hello .   &nbsp; Mama always said life was like a box of chocolates...ya know what? Life is like a box of chocolates, and I'm going to eat every fucking chocolate in that box!   THIS IS NUCKING FUTS!     
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I spent the day with Alex, and a little portion of it with Holli. It took six hours for Alex and I to watch Silence of the Lambs, and to acquire some sushi. In the evening we hung out with Marty, Sam, and Frank. Interesting times, let me tell ya. On Wednesday, Marty came over to my house. Oh! Amanda can now drive people again! Yay! Other than that, not much has been going on. I need an exciting life.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't been up to too much lately. On Monday I hung out with Alex and Amanda for a bit. We watched the first two installments of "I love the 90s". Today Amanda came over, and we watched the second two installments....haha. Logan lost his very first tooth today! I was so happy. Not much else has been going on. Tomorrow Marty is coming over, and that's about all I have planned. Sometimes my life can be really uneventful....oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Friday I spent the night at Tera's house. It was pretty fun. On Saturday I went to Marty's house, and so that was fun too. Today I did nothing because I wasn't feeling too good. Tomorrow Amanda will be coming over in the evening for some Jeopardy and I Love the 90s. That is what has been happening in the wonderful world of Erica lately. I'll blog more later when I feel up to it.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent the day at Amanda's house. We just hung out and had fun. Also, we shared some good laughs. She apparently thought it was really funny when I was looking at Midnight, her cat, and asked why the other cat wasn't named Noon. I think I make Amanda laugh a lot, but that is good. Today was fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight Alex and I spent some "quality" time with Sammy Harrison. Haha. We accompanied him on a shopping expedition. As odd as it was, it was fun too. There were some pretty weird/odd moments, but that just added to the greatness of it all. Perhaps Alex and I will have to do it again sometime.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marty called me today, and that was an awesome surprise! I haven't talked to him since Friday, so it was nice hearing his voice. Tonight I went to Sapphire's (Alex's) house. We watched Big Brother 5, and The Butterfly Effect. That movie was weird, but it wasn't too bad. It was different seeing Ashton Kutcher play a part like that tho. Tonight was fun...need Echo (I) say more? OH YEAH, THIS IS MY 100TH ENTRY! YAY ME!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lately, I haven't been up to too much. Yesterday was the 4th of July, but I wouldn't have been able to tell by the way I celebrated (or didn't). To make a long boring story short, Anna and I decided to go see the Notebook and Stepford Wives. The Notebook was good. It made us cry. After that movie was over, we had about 15 min to spare, so we decided to go to Burgerville to get some food because we were hungry. We really didn't have time to eat, so we decided to sneak the food in when we watched Stepford Wives. It was a little weird eating in the movie theater like that, but it was fun. Stepford Wives was an ok movie. I had thought it would have been better, but oh well. Then after the movies we went back to Anna's apartment and I spent the night. So that was my exciting 4th of July celebration. Today Amanda came over for a bit and we hung out. I might do something with Alex later, but at this time I'm not too sure. I haven't talked to Marty since Friday because he is on vacation, and I didn't expect to miss him as much as I do. I'm used to talking to him everyday, and I don't like not being able to. Oh well, I'll manage. Hmmm...well I think I'll be going now, because I don't feel like being on the computer.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an okay day. I saw Spiderman 2, and I liked it. The best part of the movie was HAL SPARKS! He was in it for maybe one whole minute, but that was the best minute in the movie. Other than that, my day was pretty boring. Oh well. Hopefully tomorrow will be more exciting.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day. I went to Marty's house, and we watched a movie and just hung out. I had a good time. When I got home, Amanda came over to apologize to my parents about last night. I feel so bad for her, because she is so hard on herself. Amanda handles things in a very adult way, and I admire that about her. Hopefully she'll be better soon, because it hurt my heart to see her cry today. Well, other than that, my day was average.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My laugh    i   s getting messed up. T   h   ere are maybe like 3 people who read this, and one of them is watching me as I type right now. Th   a   t is right....you know who you are!!! Today Holli and Alex came over and we hung ou   t   . We rode bikes down to Amanda's house. Amanda is in Utah. Utah is a state. Holli is jaded, according to Al   e   x. MOMMY, WHEN WILL DINNER BE READY? The answer....PRETTY SOON. Chloe embarrassed herself today. She    j   iggled her boobs as she walked into the computer room, and she saw Alex. I suppose she forgot that Alex was here. Alex is a freak! She ate all the flavors    o   f the nasty Harry Potter jelly beans....without even flinching! Me, on the other hand, had a vomit one, and I almo   s   t did just that. It was gross. Hmm...well t   h   at is about it for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm on a search...for a new perfume. Since I'm running low on all of my favorites, I have decided to pick up a new one. Yep...I'm just that cool. Tonight was a little eventful. I cried for awhile cuz of an "event" that took place between me and Marty. Everything is ok now, and that makes me beyond happy. Hmm...not too much else has been going on. I'll blog later within the next couple of days because I'm sure I'll have more to talk about when that time comes. Why? I dunno. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>