<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everyone.  There isn't much I want to tell you today. I'll have lots to tell you tomorrow.  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everybody! Just wanted to say hi and have a great day!  Today I played dodgeball and I kicked it from the base (far away from the school) all the way to the bike rack (right beside the school). Three people ran home and I won the game for us!  A couple more days and then it's Spring Break!  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everybody I got my report card today!  I got all ones and twos, except for one three, but a three is still considered good! My mom is very happy with my report card.  I am getting better at my skateboard.  Yesterday I met a whole bunch of neighbourhood kids.  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello.  We had two subsitutes today in school. The first one was nice. The second one was not as nice. She got mad at us a lot.  I can't wait to get my report card tomorrow.  No school on Friday!  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello.  We had two subsitutes today in school. The first one was nice. The second one was not as nice. She got mad at us a lot.  I can't wait to get my report card tomorrow.  No school on Friday!  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just wanted to say hi everybody!  I had a subsitute teacher today, and we had 10 minutes for gym class because one of the kids was fooling around.  I'm feeling a little bit better today, but I'm tired.  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everybody!  Here's my new blog. I hope you like it.  The only reason I am writing right now is because I am home from school with a runny nose, an upset stomach and a whole bunch of other junk!  While you are here it would be very thoughtful of you to sign my guestbook and check out my links.  That's all folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey How's it going?  This is sk8rboy's new blog!  Stay tuned...  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, Sorry for not blogging the last couple of days. I was a little busy. My fish likes blowing bubbles and then eating them( did you know my record of staying up late is 7:45 a.m ). I going to a wedding in the May  Long weekend. Well,   That's all folks 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi.  I've been pretty busy lately.  My mom got a Betta Fish that she named Jaws and I thought he was pretty cool. So I used my own money and bought one. His name is Ricky. He's red and he lives in a small tank in my bedroom. I've already had to clean his tank once because he poops a lot. Mom helped me do it. He eats a lot and he likes to push the rocks around in the tank.  We learnt a new note for the recorder - a. Now I know another song. It is the B and A Blues.  I've been teaching some other kids how to do PowerPoint in Computers. It's really easy and I like the things you can do with it.  I started a new research project. My friend and I are doing a presentation on Texas and the Alamo. My friend has been there before. We went to the library yesterday to start our research on it.  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everybody how y'all doing. I'm doing good.  On Easter Matthew found more eggs than I did and he ate them faster than me too!  Last Monday I went to a friend's house and we had a huge water fight. At the end everybody was soaked.  I went back too school last Tuesday, Spring Break is over.   We went on a field trip on Thursday to Leighton Center. It's a museum where Mr & Mrs Leighton used to live. Mr. Leighton was a famous artist. Mrs Leighton started a school for art. I made a weaving while we were there.  On Friday we started recorders I only know one note and that note is b. I can play a song called Just B.  That's all folks
     

    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everybody sorry for not blogging the last couple of days I was a little busy. Yesterday my Grama came and she brought peanut butter squares ( secret recipe ) and  chocolate chip cookies ( super good ) .  It's almost Easter and I can't wait   Well That's all folks
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Everybody!  Spring Break just started. No school until the 13th.  My Grandma is coming soon for a weekend visit. I can't wait. She's from BC, of course. From where we lived before.  Today we did no work at school. I rode my bike to school, but it was snowing this morning. Someone took an April Fool's prank too far and put vaseline on the monkey bars, the gliders, and even the handles and brakes of my bike. Our class got an apology letter about it. I think everyone did.  I'm doing a Power Point Presentation for COR (community of readers), in school. My partners are ****** & ******, & me. It's coming along really well. We've put some mini-clips and animation on it, and they're really funny.  I don't really have any plans for Spring Break, I'm just going with the flow. I'm going to look at XBoxes over Spring Break. I really want to buy one! I'm also hoping to get better at skateboarding.  That's All Folks!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Everybody  How do you like my new blog template?  I am having my second test on Monday in recorders. I didn't do very good on my first test because I didn't get a book to practice with because there wasn't enough copies. But now I have one. I've practiced a lot, and I'm really good at it.  Ricky (my fish)is doing good. He's a fat little pig fishie.  The Flames play tonight. Every time I say "open me a can of whoop-ass", they win. I've said it a lot today.  This is my new closing   GO FLAMES GO!   PS I hope no Shark fans are reading this.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>