<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ehz...i like to thank janice for all this yah...hahaZ...hMm....haiZz...i today dunno why jus feel darn siaNzz....like got no mood to do anything....jus feel like sleepin lazin around n jus dun do anything....today durin amaths...i was like noddin away sia....jus dunno why now a days amaths soo sIanzZ....jus can't absorb anything....even zhisen also fell asleep sia..hahaZz.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyy. if u dun like dis skin tell me arh. hahahaha. =X now already gonna 12 ler. me wanna sleep liaoz. continue doin ur blog tmr. tmr den change change abit make nice nice for u. lOlx.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HARLOW.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      aLl fUn hAs to cOme to a End...  haiZz... tmr will be the official start of the exams le...pianGz.... still not yet in exam mood yEt leHz..hahaz... yeAh hahaz.... i finally passed both mY cHEm n  A maThs..hahaz... but both barely scrapped passed....hees but i guess its better than nth...hahaz.. ;p   hahaz...sorri can't reply u my phone no marney le......   PLEASE CUT HERE      ---------------------------------------------------------------------------- >:  hahaz....kkae....gd luck....
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cRazEe aSsumpTioNs.....  wahz 2dae emaths test hard like dunno wad... i'm gonna fail my first... aft sch went to e5 n slack den lucas runnin around gettin rape by water..hahaz.. nice try laRz... hahaz chester lol.... den RAIN....nice try loRz cannot eat canteen close kuku darn hungry.... at lasT thE raIn stopped... went to J8 wif levin stephanie n austin... food at last..hahaz... den took bus to tuituion wif steph....hahaz...  dun make faRny assumptions laRz steph...hahaz... ;P   ... dun piss me laRz.. wad gay tis gay that...nb go screw a tree laRz....kns
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      15 aT lAst...hahaZ... fRi was the most significant date on the world...hahaZ...juz kiddin..but it was my b'dae.. at school dunno how many ppl wish me n whack me...aft sch still kana rape by zhisen, gerald, chester.... in e5 levin somemoRe recOreded in His cam....kuku sia...hahaz..  6.30 went to Bugis too MeeT them foR diNnEr at seoul...as gerald was late...hahaz =P..... thx yah rage for the wOuNderfuL soundtrek.... while waitin for our table we went to walk around... took pics wif lev, jan, xp, mien, howard....hahaz but i didn't get any?!? got our tables n the fEasT beGan...not forgettin the 200+ bill...hahaz...we ate n ate...nice try laRz gurls for the funny stuff u wan me to eat..hahaz....  aft eatin we went to walk sum more....hahaz...kuku den the guys go push me into the fountain thingy at bugis...kuku sia all wet...  walked to esplanade den the guy again dunno wad they doin run here run there...run up 3 storeys den sit there???... fianlLy reachin esplanade we sat by the river crapin bout stuff from wad happen when one dies to planets?? bout 11+ took cabby wif jasper, lev n mien home...the stupid driver darn kb..hahaz..  SAt.. no one around.... wah ... ytd all never come....  david came aft the speech dae rehearsal, jasper n levin never come...left me alone..weak stomachs laRz....hahahaz...=p  2dae... nth much laRz....   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaZ....ytd i reran 2.4 sia wif zhisen barefoot...hahaz thx sia if zs never ran den i got no one to chase liaoZ....resULt :10.55 mins sia....hahaZ...song but my pOor fEet was BlasTed wif blisters wah darn pain stand also can't stand, stIlL waLk... every sTep w@s pURE aGony...  thx for ur concern...hahaz can't reply cos me phone no money  :P  2dae darn hot sia...jus as bad as ytd... wah GeoG test not enough time sia...kuku lah..but i still think can scoRe laRz....hahaZ hOPes...got back PhYsiCs.....wahahahaZ....i paSsed sia...barely... 25/48....hahaZ....OoOo....  one moRe DaY......
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "What is one value or belief that you hold on to in life? Why?" hMm.... One of my beliefs in life is that you should always try to have fun and enjoy yourself in whatever you do, a little hard to do so while having certain lessons though. It would be a waste of time if I had to do something I had completely no intrest in, but sometimes when I do it and while I did it I enjoy myself then I would start to think otherwise, at the sametime wanting to do more and better in that certain expect. Many people feel that life's a drag at times(me too =P) most likely due to certain setbacks and factors one os not able to enjoy what he or she is doing. Repetition is also one such factor, wouldn't you feel that doing the same old boring thing over and over again would kill all live in it?? One could try diffrent means to convey the same message, that way people would feel fresher rather than to stick to the same old boring routine.     hahaZ.... Good fri finally got time to settle lots of unfinish stuff ;) Wah... i went to see the chinese sinseh fellow cause me leg was hurting for quite sumtime aft playin soccer wif the scouts...hahaz... he was like twisting my leg like sum kindda toy..hahaz....hurt like siao.... den went to eat thai food wif me mom...hahaz food was like so spicy that i ended filling myself wif water rather than food n me poor mom had to stuff herself wif the food...hahaz..   ytd went for scouts wif me wrapped up leg..hahaz... rather sianZ.... could not do anything jus floatin around like a wonderin spirit... aft that went to HQ for meetin...hMm...didn't expect it to be s0o peaceful was expectin to shoot n be shot at....hahaz...eHz thats all....  eRm... hahaz... thx for ur care eh though we haven't tok much since that time i'm glad its over..hahaz...   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LOnG LonG aGo..... hahaZ...its been a long time since i ever hanged out with levin, jan, zhihua n wanling like that sia.....study in sch....hahaz....=p... i attempted to do my amaths but i was stuck....then while tryin to solve the darn question i got a headache n slipped to loner modE !?!?.....  anyway i had a great time....hahaz.....levin patience is a virtue....hahaz....craps.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sUper tiRed...  wah today go for scouts had alot of fun durin PT..hahaz.....then it the sPeeCh daY rEheaRsal thingy??? stood there under the sun like sum kuku idiot sia...all the orders also not clear... GuiDes wait a few mOre yeaRs laRz..... tOday jOnathan b'Day...hahaz....got a surprise cake for him he look rather touchEd....like he would cry any moment....hahaz... =P  aft scouts i go meet levin...kuku sia sabo me...never tell me that they were there....den go look for jasper...haiZz...but then the company there also not any bEttEr...so decided to spend me sAt alone at home...hahaZ.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ~ sCrEw thE sCrEweD?? they are always wearing that stupid mask grinnin at ur face cursing ur back...    mS choong suX u stupid nut constatly treatin us like a bunch of sissys...wTf man...u wanna implement ur fancy rules yet u dun work with them ?!?.... if ur so0o0o busy wth ur bloody NE stuff den drop scouts laRz...kuku kns... u eXpect us to disgRace ourselves with one farkin pole in the ground???  Burn iN hElL u bLooDy bItch.... jUs hope we disgrace oursElves again tmr durin the rehearsesal...kns constantly say we never perform...fark it sia u like got do much like that.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My 2 in 1 entries Mr OnG    1st online journal questions :my views on the english language...   1) Yes...i like the language i guess this is mostly due to the fact that since young it's been the most commonly used language for me. I think i like it more than other languages such as chinese most likely maybe because i seem to be able to pick it up more easily and i'm able to excel in it giving me the urge to further do better. On the other hand i never had proper grounding for my chinese therefore i'm unable to do as well, partial due to that i also started to lose interest in the subject. Its much easier to learn compared to Chinese as the drive and interest is there. I could be totally engrossed reading a english novel, but if you were to ask me to read a chinese book, even a short story will set me flipping thru the pages of a dictionary at every phrase. In the end i would just give it up. English would be my prefered language of communication as it is internationally known plus i can't commute well in chinese therefore i rather stick to english.  2) How would you like English lessons to be conducted if you had a choice?   English lessons should be more interactive. Now a days the focus is on the written work rather than a persons oral skills. So what if a person is able to write a novel yet he is unable to communicate with the publisher well to get it publish.     o-->  The event i would like to write on would be Singapore's independence. Singapore used to be a british colony at that time, the people had no say over political issues therefore didn't really had a good standard of living. Yet the people were also overly reliant on the british thinking that the british would settle all external matters for them. When WWII came the Japanese were invading SEA which at that point mainly consisted of western colonies, the british then were still arrogant over their 'impregnable' fortress. Soon colony after colony started to crumbble all over S'pore then came our turn, the british ended up retreating back to england leaving S'pore in the lurch after being defeated time after time. It was then that the people of S'pore realised that we can never count on others to run and protect your own country. After the Japanese surrendered the british came back once again but this time the people want their independence they want to run their own country. So after several tries, S'pore fianlly acheived independence on 1965, a time where the people could proudly sing the national athem of S'pore an say our country's pledge, from then on S'pore only progressed under skilled leadership.         -> a pEaCefuL @pRiLf0oL...who aRe u tRyin tO fOol...  today...jus the same as any other day laRz i guess....had a little fun with lucas after school...hMm n he's one oF us liaoZ...hahaZ...haiZz... there are time where i wonder how screwed up sumppl can rEalLy be....lots tO thInK aBout....  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tImE is oF the eSsenCE~  went bEach rd wif jaSper yEe lianG.. wEnt tp buy clotH.. wEnt back to sch got stupidly long sTiCk wif pointy end.. uSe a needle n threAD n seW my flaG togetHer.. feel like sum stupid siSsy hse wife..hahaz.. *pleNty of thiNner?? hahaz jaSPer..  au yoNg made them piCk cans from thE recycLE bin to cleAn them?!?! ask uS to be a paRt of suM laME pRoject of hIS.. NO WAY!! screw off..  mEet the nEw n taNned(defintely muCh betteR lookIn) nIck cHoo!! hahaz.. bUt he's still as laME as evER hahaz.. weNt to suM clinic calLed lifeline?? to mEet daryl.. hahaz fever... went to makan den went hoME.. sleEp sleEp.. feEl siCK hahaz.. but i'm not  =P snIfF* sniFf*  lOts of thiNgs i wanna dO.. 2* kayakin course.. rockclimbin.. hike.. camp.. gO out wif u =].. so maNy thinGs so lItTle tiME..ARR..  hahaz dats all.. pAnadols are unhealthy.. dun woRry too much i'm fine deAR..luv u=]
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gReAt s'PoRE sAlE~  hahaz 2dae was a mad one.. meet jaSper at bUgiS(agaiN) hahaz walk a awhIle den went to cITy den i bought a book.. den went to HMV bought a CD.. hahaz 2 iteMs le jaSper slow siA.. hahaz walk n walK den go suntec den gO orcHard hahaz jaSper back home.. went tO CK TanGs eat ice Cream darn nice sia.. soO thick n cReamy =P  wAlk to hEeren hopin to get slipPers but duN haVE my siZe sob sob.. anytime bAh.. den the 2 oF us boTh bougHt a shiRt eaCh from DCP.. i got a white n he got a grey.. hahaz..  waLk waLk.. weNt cine makan.. BeEFbowl again hahaz thx for the treAt brudder..  aiyOz u never study wasted sia shoUld have goNe out toGether.. hahaz.. another time bah aft tmr can le..  hahaz 3 itEms to 1 leHz jaSper.. waLk waLk.. leG paIn le hahaz.. went esprit.. waLk waLk.. gO far east den wEnt to gElare eat ice cReam on waffles hahaz.. wtf 60 cents jus for choc sauce?!?! hahaz.. darn sonG sat on the red couch thingy darn comfy.. hahaz sorRi dEaR =P i'l treat u kZ..  den we both bth le took mRt hoMe.. hahaz spent more on food siA..hahaz jaSper go buy ur bass bag bah.. hahaz  WTC cumin le dIE siA.. kukuz patrol slackin i one mAn show.. wad is tis RAmbO arZ.. nbcb... hahaz..  aFt tmR den its over le jiao you kz.. luv u deaR.. nitEz..
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2daE flaG daE darN lame sia..hahaz aft collectin our cans me n luc went to mEet jan n wl at OG den crap awhile den go earn my first 10 cents.. hahaz den later miEn n ly came oso den ly darN entHu keep goin around askin 4 donaTions.. den the other 3 girls slack hahaz.. den aft awhile when i tink onli eArn bout leSs den 5 den we went to bugis walk.. my goD dey take neo prints den me n luc weRe like o.0  ..hahaz...  wenT to eAt n i ate 2 beef bowls darN hungry den kana sUan like dunno wAD sia..pianGz.. all luc fault to let ly take my phone..hahaz den contD to slaCk den look 4 pink shIrt for cb chenG ...hahaz.. aft more slackin went to return our cans den go home..hahaz.. siAo de dey caN waLk 4eva maNz..  aiyOz dun care tt person laRz jan he can make all the noise he wants laRz...  hahaz ate n ate like sum cRazy fool at hilton.. hahaz my mom brought me to eAt jAp bufFet..hahaz..   hahaz me Gay?? nah i dun think soO luv ur nEw bloggie deAr.. luv u =] jIao yoU for ur chi kz its only 2 more daEs den we can go out le..
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sLeEpy eVergREen~  dun noe wads wif me tis few days darn sleEpy... den go sch play sOme boArd gAme for finAnciaL plannin...hahaz kinda fun laRz.. the kukuz chen dun give work like will die liddat pianGz 50+ ques for the holidaes MadNesS... stupid damien gif me holiday hw oso... den mus come back on de 7 for emaths fiLe.. 4~6 wTc, 7 emaths, 9~11 psA hiKe(yeh at laSt) pianGz where got time too go out sia... hees back mus hurry rEcover oTherwIse she dun let me go hikE..  there are dogs that only bark too much but dun bite when needed to n jus whimper.. these are useless bastards..  i mus make time to spend wif her.. a promise i won't break.. luv ya  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      pIzzA anyone??  gOsh today durin chi lesson darn tired sia.. 1st time the class so dead.. den eng do dunno wad lame oral gradin rubBish.. hahaz den today levin moses jasper david n lots more all never come sch nice try loRz.. den durin receSs craM wif the lowEr sec wad is the sch thinkin man?? den agian clash wif norm tech ppl tis time is those blardy sia lan sec2s.. screw up losers man.. thank ur balls that i didn't order chicken noodle or u'l be part of the gravy short fark..  hahaz den went to the hall to see OUR wondErfUl cheerleadin team.. pianGz noisy like dunno wad sia.. hahaz den got sum siao ppl tryin to be jing lin fan club..hahaz.. den watch movie.. ghost ship NC16 lehz hahaz.. den change to X man 2.. i wonder if its pirated?? blur like nobody's business den half way got prob.. den change aGain to Homerun at least thats a better choice but den watch yi ban den go home le..  went to meet her kana suan 1st round by janice.. den again by zhisen james priscilia n de hui.. pianGz hees but i enjoy ur company =] take a good rest yaHz n dun tire urself out..
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sOcCer fRenZy.~  hees 2day interclaSs socCer deN me n gorDon play for e1 cos e2 no one play socCer de.. waHz den aft 1st maTch aGainst 3T1 i got iNto a fiGht le.. retArd norm tech muslim bastard not happy cannot go pass me den kpkb waHz den kick me summore fark u bloody halal eatEr.. may u choke on pork.. den play aGainst 4T1 again got ppl not hapPy wif me.. wtf?! man does my face write i hate u norm techs i dun think so.. i mean u guys are ok but jus sum of u have that screw up mentality thats jus throws ur name to the drain.. what wanna fight?? say wad target me but can't do a thing u ball less fark head... hahaz aiyoz who care laHz wads done is done.. all that matters is that we entered the semi-finals hahaz.. who says nerd can't play socCer..hahaz..  eHz ur darn kukuz lehz cos of 1 mistake ur wanna disband i darn dissapointed lehz even ur mike stand oso sad sia...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      H@pPy bElaTed xp n hAppY 15 kevin!!  2day moRnin meet luc n mien at potong pasir mrt den went to harbour front.. aft meetin up wif the rEst went to sEnTOsa..hahaz.. thx to levin we got off at the wrong stop n hAd tO waLk liKE sIao.. bUt luCkly Aft seeIng 2 aNg Mos hiTchin a ride on a Lorry we oso dId the same...hahaz darn cool... finalLy reacHed paLAwan we dumped our stuff n had lots of fun den the gurls went to rent bikes...hahaz..den we saBoo kevIn by takin his pants off n played monkey wif it...hahaz... ehz keVin.. luv ya'll or jus only luv u??huh?? hahaz... den i left wif lucas early... hahaz...  i enjoyed meetin u though we kinda didn't noe where to go but i still enjoyed ur company.. =]  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'l nEVer gEt iT....  today woke up by shermien's msg at 10...hahaz for once she actually woke me up..hahaz.. my mom super kukuz went to the petrol kiosk NTUC thinkin that its the same jus b'cos there is a sale?? typical s'porean... hahaz... went to eat lunch near bugis aft that walked there alonee...took a bus home n when i got of at my hse levin say he wanna go out ask me to choing to YCK?? wth!? went all the way he say go sembawang to meet eugene n mark can't he ever tell me in advance?? hahaz go there they tok about prefect thingy i was so extra...haizz went home...  todays jus not my day.. i guess if i want the rainbow i'l have to first wait in the rain...  tmr go sentosa but i wonder if it will turn up well.. lucas lets stick to the plan yahz.. :P  ff7 advent children is so cool...hahaz...  eMotiOnly sTreEsed n uNwElL :| 7.15  11.30 hees gosh i'm jus soo happy =]    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eXaMs ovER at LasT....  yEah man the kukuz exams are done wif hahaz... but how the result will show is a diffrent case hahaz tis time exam dun really feel like it...hahaz... mus go choing before the results comeout den die le...hahaz  yTd aft the eXams levin n lucas comeover AgaIn hahaz... den the stupid levin like never eat for dunno how many daes liddat eat n eat... hahaz... i went for tuition den go meet shermien levin kevin n jasper at PS... den we roamed about hahaz kukuz sia... bout 1+ go home den me n shermien's wallet fell into the pond dunno thingy hahaz all her fault for pushin me...hahaz...den tok n tok till 4+...siao de...  today went back to sch for briefin wahz the discipline like dunno wad shit den alot ppl take their owm time to come...kns... den went meet lucas n went davids hse he got party... now i jus got home n i'm super sleepy...hahaz nitez to all...  niao ren...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gLObal warmin??  sHeesh.. these few daes hot like dunno wad sia..  waSted my mornin.. mom ask me to pack my rOom den keep askin me to throw tis n that.. hahaz..  weNt to eat lunch.. aRz kana stuffed wif fo0d.. all of dem neveR eat much den keEp givin mE fo0d.. like i'm sum ruBbish bin sia.. juz keEp floodin.. hahaz.. visiTed my grandma again.. eh hMm.. not gettin any better.. one of her toe has alreadY rottEd away.. heaRd from one oh mY auntS that the useless uncLe of mine will be comiN back sOon from the UK.. he beTter not cauSe any trouble agaiN.. uSeleSs craphEad.. u dun deseaRve my respect ~pui~ wHoo went to swIm.. majoR coOl down.. supEr sonG.. hahaz..  tmr??  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      reCiprocal~  pHew at laSt managE to ruN from it aLL.. went out wif jaSper.. to oRchaRd.. he wEnt to the toliEt to put wax daRn long sia.. lonGest ever for a guy..hahaz.. walKed at taKa.. den he say that if u buy crocodile products it eat up ur moNey..intrEstin.. nEver belived in animaL products anyway.. cruelTy.. paSsed LV.. saw ppl quein to get in.. who queues to enter a shoP?? especiaLly when it's so ex.. weiRd.. waLk.. waLK.. wenT to sony gaLLery.. arz i wan a cam.. saw the phone he changin to.. nO comMents~ waS thinkin of watchin a movIe.. no tickEts.. went to play lan..hahaz.. play till his head pain sIa..hahaz.. aRz got pusHed into memory lanE sia.. kukuz..  i gueSs wad u give is wad u get in retuRn.. its juz a matTer of time.. its onLy soOner or laTer.. a rather vicious cycle.. juz like wads hapPenin to everythinG ard us.. thE enviromENt issn't gettin anY better wif all the poLLution n civilisation.. soCiety.. it's nth but anotheR downwaRds spiral.. a bottomless pit..  miz u
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      patHetic mE~  arZ its beEn awhiLE.. today go mEet nick choo to pass hIm his fiLm.. ran into the socCer junkies(eugene, butt etc).. kana sUan.. nth else to rEally lOok foward to..   i coUld only stare at my own hanDs n mock myseLf.. sHit.. i'm useLess.. if only they wouLd move yet theY beAR the weiGht of leaD.. unLeSs i do sumthinG soon.. its nth but a dowNwaRds spiraL.. fAding away..  sorRy..
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cRushEd~  tiS is tHe woRse day of mY holidaeS so faR.. ARRRRRGH.. woke uP wif a stiff bAck..knn.. retARd reumathism..farked up.. my mOm tooK my blardY phone cos i fElL asleEp wif it?!?! scRewed up.. goT my speCs felt dArn bloody gIdDy.. buS ride for 45 mins.. feeL like pukKin.. aRrRRgH.. wAs tryin to get back my breaTh den my farked up sis comEs along.. whenEver did i say that i haTe my sch.. sCrew u bitCH..kns.. wad motivAtion?? motivate urselF always comin home makin a scene complianin that mom sent u to the wronG courSE.. ur the one regrettIn ur acTions not mE..daRn heLL.. piSsed~daMn.. Blame it upon a rush of blood to the head..  hOpe tmr wiLL be betTer.. =] 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      brAin dEad~ Hees ytd wenT to geT my nEw specs done.. n my mom bought yEt another nEw paIr of sunGlaSses.. n shE saYs i spenD alot.. wtf maN..  tody was kinDa dull day laRz nth much to write bout cept that i went orcharD wif my cuZ..  rElac jaSper it mayb hard but u nevER noe when it'l chanGe for the betteR..  take caRe aRz.. miz u.. rem i'm always there for u.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'Ve lost mY leGS n saNity~  hahaZ PSA oVer at lAst hope u guys pasS man.. if not all the money wiLL go doWn the draiN.. nICk keep up thE good work man.. dun caRe bout timo he's jus a load of cRap..  PSA~> test of the endurance of the mind n body.. n the motivation among the grouP.. but if aLL eLse faiLs u'll zOom around.. hahaz.. moNey really does open up moRe dooRs.. that's waD ppL so dARn greeDy.. "a angEL wif 4 wheeLs came to our rescuE.. hahaz.."  didN't noe that s'Pore still has soO many sceiniC plaCEs.. kept takin pics hahaz.. wish that she was there.. =P  its at the daRkeSt houRs that u see how farkEd up certain ppL are.. damn bLoodY self centred fark heads..  hees soRry i forgot such a impt day.. lo0kin forward to that daY.. luv u deAR.. =]
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oUt at laSt~  wEe.. woke up rather eaRly 2daE but stIlL achin all over.. o0o0o.. wenT her hse watcH tv.. meEt jaN at bishaN.. wenT cine bouGht tickeTs for the 3.50 shOw.. lotS of tIme to kILL.. wEnt to BK makan speNt like an hour plus there.. hahaz.. den finally time came le den go watch movIe.. hahaz darn farNy cept for the springy cloWn paRt.. eRr can't stand cloWns dunno afraid of them.. den weNT takE neoprint.. the machIne sux man camera plaCed at all the kukuZ angLEs.. hahaz.. aRz.. no money le..gaWd.. den wenT to heeRen.. jan lefT to meeT forgot who le.. den waLk awhile den went home le..  jan wad's wif the papa thinGy.. hahaz... heEs wanted to hold ur hand but not brave enough..hahaz will soOn.. luv u deaR.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uneVen tan..burNt..voIceleSs..BESt PL..~WTC~  aRr back fROm the camp le..hahaz last night slp uNtil song soNg.. tis is tHe mosT slaCk camP i've bEen i mean jUs keEp doin pusH up veRy xionG meHz?? jus hand cramP ba le wad.. den go geT deEp heaT can le wad..  hahaz got beST PL award cos my pAtrol was like 0.0  ..den really darn pathetic..  bryaN~> hates beehoon n broccoli?? brings a smaLL puny jacKet insteAD of a poNcho?? layoUt pianGz.. kEvin keoNg~> ever cRaPpy.. aLways tokkin back.. smaRt ass dunno wad columbus clouds thingy.. maTthew~> bLur.. hahaz but not tOo bad for a firSt timEr.. wen shiUn~> nth to say bout i'm quite dissapointed wif ur performance as a APL..  jaSper.. flasH caRd.. elephaNt hakA chEeR sia.. hahaz.. darN crazy...eh daviD finGer~ring..   whOo at last its over can go out le.. hahaz yeh man.. miz her like nuts.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      caMp fiEstA~  aRr.. tmr go caMp le.. sHe oso in caMp.. haiZz.. miz her..  scARed sia my patRol totally neVer do anythinG.. diE le..  hees nth muCh to say.. gOin to slEep le.. muz rest..  mIz u s0o.. luv u deaR..
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      beAch rd aGain~  o0oo.. slept till bout 12+ todae.. hahaz den met up wif jaSper den went to lavendar meeT auggy n gaNg.. aGain..hahaz.. den kana trick by them den went uP n doWn the escalatOr like soME fooL..  wEnt bEach rd to buy stuFf... on the wAY laMed wif theM.. hahaz. jaSper yelLow face.. hahaz the seNoiRs stiLl as laMe as evER sia.. tHey can suan until diE de... hahaz..  blEw all my money on the survival kit..hahaz... den weNt to daryL's hse.. niCe place man.. den went there plaY CS daRN funny sia.. stupid auggy keep hoggin the com... den ate at his hse den stupiG jaSper kEep complain the fo0d spicy.. hahaz..   eh den nth much le.. went home wif auggy.. den dats all..hahaz.. caMp comin le.. mus prep mentaLly PSA comin too.. nitEz luv dear..
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nEw montH. nEw stARt~  wAsted my moRnin agAIn.. went to geraLd hse.. waitEd.. he's stiLl aslEep.. wtf..  wenT to mEet daVid n hiS patrol.. lamed arOund.. ate n eat..  jaSper came.. did some wOrk..  lefT to meEt hEr.. weNt mos.. ran inTo ppl.. did my chi work tog.. thx =]  groUp of ppL walKed pasSed outside.. kukuz ahmAd took pics wif his phonE.. lamEr..  a group of ppL ran into us.. 2 sat wiF us.. 1 of theM is sO dArn blOody lame..  leFt.. bougHt stuff.. sEnt her hOme.. saW tryin tO be 15 auntIe.. hahaz.. ;P  enJoyed myselF.. luv u deaR..
     
    
</post>


</Blog>