<Blog>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i actually have a blog? haha well we'll see how long i keep up with this..............
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the word  ‘love’  is said too often too easily too much too cheaply  taken for granted  used  to achieve some other intentions  to express other vague emotions    not understood    why?      
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      life's taken an unexpected turn, i'm happy as it is right now.......... Talked to an old friend whom btw i've never met before (how bizarre *grinz*) all these yrs we never clicked as much as we did ytd, would not happen if we tried earlier. 'all in it's time' is probably my slogan for now i must keep reminding myself that.   I swear God has this sense of humour. I feel right now as if He's taking me for a drive. Although, He keeps me up with His 'jokes'. You probably wouldn't understand what I'm talking about, might as well hahhahaa.... all I asked for in one guy He manage to spread in quite a few, characteristics coming from totally unexpected direction. My life's becoming one big korean drama *laugh*.   In search for love itself He had shown me a lot. No matter how much I grumble I do realise that this grace time is much needed and I will eventually get there and find the 'one' or one of the 'ones', someone said to me one that she believes there are more than one the 'one'. maybe it's true... whatever it is I'll be here waiting, I'll try to be patient though it's hard sometime..... 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I want to be free of this ridiculous worldly affair............ but how? how do i undo all damage done? how do i erase mammories, get rid of worldly needs? be content with myself as it is? i should be, i try to be. sometime i manage to but at other times i can't. i'd get disturbed by the most ridiculous trivial things. things that shouldn't bother me anymore. why am i so sensitive? why do i think too much? i have other things, bigger things in life that i lose focus of from time to time, why??
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    just moi&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm tired..........  I just wanna go home..................
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      and hide from everything.   that's what i feel like doing right now.  *stress*
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i've fallen out.................  it was just a matter of time. as expected.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was standing over my baked pasta earlier...... if  only i have ppl to share it with....... tough thing being away from home, from your family....  in context of mother's day. mothers are the most selfless ppl. they give and give and give..... even without realising it themselves or realised by others sadly. and yet.... how many of us, at one stage in our life was ashame of our mothers? mom come on let go of my hand! what if my friends see....... then ou grow up and THEN sometimeyou wish your mom could hold your hand but she's not there.  mom gells a family together. at least i think so even if you don't. not saying dads aren't important. dad's the back bone of a family but moms gell everyone together. i want to be a mom too.... one day...... if given the opportunity. it is a blessing to become a mom as much as a mom is a blessing to her family...... or at least i think so :O)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For those of you out there who are in love and lucky enough to have each other, do realise how blessed you are........  please do not take the fact that you are with your love for granted.  not everyone's that lucky.................
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      picnic was......... oh i can't describe it in one word..... ok imagine...... green grass.... cool air, warm sun........ on a hill under lots of big ancient trees, the river in the distant...... jazz in the air (brought my boom box along hehe)...... pancakes, ice cream.... laughters...... more laughters...... and even more laughters.... especially when this guy patrick started throwing spoonfulls of fresh cream with closed eyes (the i dea is it hits whoever it hits hahahhaa) but somehow the biggest dollops ALWAYS landed on lizzy....... or when lizzy, pat and lindsay tried posing for a cool pose photo, a soccer ball hit lindsay at the back of her head!! hahahahaaaa was the funniest moment!! oh photos! took them with my semi auto non digi though so gotta wait for me to finish the film and develop :O) perth..... could be a great place...... with the right company *smilez*...... i will miss all this one day if i move away.  Sometimes such times feel like gems you found on the road as you walk along the road of your life, to be collected and kept carefully in that little treasure box in your chest and you want to hold on to them with your dear life coz you can lose everything in life but no one can steal memories........ that's why i think when i get old rather than getting alzheimer and lose my little gems or forget ppl that i love even! i'd rather die..... *smilez* well..... that's my sunday so far..... been sitting on my desk otherwise trying to get some work done. it's beautiful outside. 25 degree.... all blue skies and breeze. perth is btw one windy city. the air is hardly ever still. i'm lucky to always be near the river. the swan river. live on the shore of it, drive along it, walk along it.... see it, breath it every day. just one of those days. when i'm just thankful for what i have :O) one gem of a day............  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm sick and tired of always feeling sick and tired!!  to quote anastacia's new song  how appropriate........  *groan*
     
    
</post>


</Blog>