<Blog>


<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Howstuffworks "How Nuclear Power Works"   › Introduction to How Nuclear Power Works › Uranium › Nuclear Fission › Inside a Nuclear Power Plant › Outside a Nuclear Power Plant › Subcriticality, Criticality and Supercriticality › What Can Go Wrong › Lots More Information › Shop or Compare Prices   Nuclear power plants provide about 17 percent of the world's electricity. Some countries depend more on nuclear power for electricity than others. In France, for instance, about 75 percent of the electricity is generated from nuclear power, according to the International Atomic Energy Agency. In the United States, nuclear power supplies about 15 percent of the electricity overall, but some states get more power from nuclear plants than others. There are more than 400 nuclear power plants around the world, with more than 100 in the United States.   The dome-shaped containment building at the Shearon Harris Nuclear Power Plant near Raleigh, NC   Have you ever wondered how a nuclear power plant works or how safe nuclear power is? In this article, we will examine how a nuclear reactor and a power plant work. We'll explain nuclear fission and give you a view inside a nuclear reactor.     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Colorado State University Internal Combustion Engines Web Site 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Aircraft Engine Design 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Howstuffworks "How Gas Turbine Engines Work" 
     
    
</post>


<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Manas: Culture, Indian Cinema: Sholay 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Internet Movie Database (IMDb.com): Top Movies 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Classic Movies 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AKA  born: Benjamin Earl Nelson  Born  Sep 23, 1938 in Henderson, NC  Years Active    Genres  Rock   Styles  Soul, Brill Building Pop, United States of America, Pop-Soul  Instruments  Vocals  Tones  Earnest, Elegant, Sophisticated, Stylish, Passionate, Plaintive, Exuberant, Cheerful, Sentimental  Labels  Atlantic (11), Sequel (7), Atco (6), Rhino (5), K-Tel Entertainment (4), Half Note (2)  Charts & Awards  Click here for Billboard Chart Positions & GRAMMY Awards  See Also  All Movie Guide Entry  Product Purchase Click here to buy sheet music        by Steve Huey  From the groundbreaking orchestrated productions of the Drifters to his own solo hits, Ben E. King was the definition of R&B elegance. King's plaintive baritone had all the passion of gospel, but the settings in which it was displayed were tailored more for his honey smooth phrasing and crisp enunciation, proving for perhaps the first time that R&B could be sophisticated and accessible to straight pop audiences. King's approach influenced countless smooth soul singers in his wake and his records were key forerunners of the Motown sound.  King was born Benjamin Earl Nelson in Henderson, NC, in 1938, and sang with his church choir before the family moved to Harlem in 1947. In junior high, he began performing with a street corner doo wop group called the Four B's, which won second place in an Apollo Theater talent contest. While still in high school, he was offered a chance to join the Moonglows, but was simply too young and inexperienced to stick. He subsequently worked at his father's restaurant as a singing waiter, which led to an invitation to become the baritone singer in a doo wop outfit called the Five Crowns in 1958. The Five Crowns performed several gigs at the Apollo Theater along with the Drifters, whose career had begun to flounder in the years since original lead singer Clyde McPhatter departed. Drifters manager George Treadwell, dissatisfied with the group members' unreliability and lack of success, fired them all in the summer of 1958 and hired the Five Crowns to assume the name of the Drifters (which he owned).   The new Drifters toured for about a year, playing to often hostile audiences who knew they were a completely different group. In early 1959, they went into the studio with producers Jerry Leiber and Mike Stoller to cut their first records. A song Nelson (still performing under his given name) co-wrote called "There Goes My Baby" became his first lead vocal and the lush backing arrangement made highly unorthodox (in fact, virtually unheard-of) use of a string section. "There Goes My Baby" became a massive hit, laying the groundwork for virtually every smooth/uptown soul production that followed. Over the next two years, Nelson sang lead on several other Drifters classics, including "Dance With Me," "This Magic Moment," "Save the Last Dance for Me," and "I Count the Tears."   In 1960, Nelson approached Treadwell about a salary increase and a fairer share of the group's royalties. Treadwell rebuffed him and Nelson quit the group, at this point assuming the more memorable stage name Ben E. King in preparation for a solo career. Remaining on Atlantic, King scored his first solo hit with the stylish, Latin-tinged ballad "Spanish Harlem," a Jerry Leiber/Phil Spector composition that hit the Top Ten in early 1961. The follow-up, "Stand By Me," a heartfelt ode to friendship and devotion co-written by King, became his signature song and an enduring R&B classic; it was also his biggest hit, topping the R&B charts and reaching the pop Top Five. King scored a few more chart singles through 1963, including velvety smooth pop-soul productions like "Amor," "Don't Play That Song (You Lied)," and the Italian tune "I (Who Have Nothing)." In the post-British Invasion years, King had a rough go of it on the pop charts but continued to score R&B hits. 1967's Southern-fried "What Is Soul?" was one of his last singles for Atco; seeking to revive his commercial fortunes, King departed in 1969.   A 1970 album on Maxwell, Rough Edges, failed to generate much attention, and King was forced to make a living touring the oldies circuit. In 1975, Atlantic president Ahmet Ertegun caught King's act in a Miami lounge and invited him to re-sign with the label. King scored an unlikely comeback smash with the disco track "Supernatural Thing, Part I," which returned him to the top of the R&B charts in 1975 and also reached the pop Top Five. While he was unable to duplicate that single's success, King recorded several more albums for Atlantic up through 1981, and also collaborated with the Average White Band in 1977 on the album Benny & Us. After leaving Atlantic a second time, King toured in a version of the Drifters beginning in 1982. In 1986, "Stand By Me" was prominently featured in the Rob Reiner film of the same name; re-released as a single, it climbed into the Top Ten all over again. In its wake, King returned to solo recording, issuing a new album every few years all the way up through the '90s. He also guested on recordings by Heaven 17 and Mark Knopfler, among others. King's 1999 album Shades of Blue (on Half Note Records) found him branching out into jazz territory, performing with a big band and guests like Milt Jackson and David "Fathead" Newman.      
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! Directory Movie Titles > Rocky Series 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Eye Of The Tiger lyrics: Artist Survivor   Artist Survivor  Album unknown  Song Eye Of The Tiger   Soundtrack : rocky iiI (1982) Risin' up, back on the street Took my time, took my chances Went the distance Now I'm back on my feet Just a man and his will to survive  So many times, it happened too fast You trade your passion for glory Don't lose your grip on the dreams of the past You must fight just to keep them alive  * It's the eye of the tiger It's the thrill of the fight Risin' up to the challenge Of our rival And the last known survivor Stalks his prey in the night And his fortune must always be Eye of the tiger  Face to face, out in the heat Hangin' tough, stayin' hungry They stack the odds Still we take to the street Fot the kill with the skill to survive (Repeat *)  Risin' up straight to the top Had the guts, got the glory Went the distance Now I'm not gonna stop Just a man and his will to survive (Repeat *)  The eye of the tiger (4 times till fade)   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Steven Seagal 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yun-Fat Chow 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Helen Hunt | Mad About Helen 
     
    
</post>



<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink India's second fastest supercomputer commissioned - Newindpress.com   India's second fastest supercomputer commissioned Saturday April 24 2004 00:00 IST  CHENNAI: The Institute of Mathematical Sciences (IMSC) here commissioned `Kabru', the second fastest supercomputer from India.   With the full commissioning of `Kabru', a 288-CPU (144-node) node Linux cluster, the Institute has joined the worldwide Teraflop Supercomputer Club.  Kabru is not just the second fastest supercomputer but also the fastest one belonging to an academic/research organisation in the country, according to IMSC.  The only other machine faster than this in the country is the 574-CPU cluster at Intel, Bangalore.  The IMSC director R Balasubramaniam said Kabru was the result of the Institute's efforts to improve its research in the field of `Lattice Gauge Theory'.  According to the head of the design team Professor N D Hari Dass, the main objective in `Lattice Gauge Theory' research is to calculate the properties of fundamental particles such as protons and neutrons.  ``And at the moment the only reliable way of doing this is through large-scale computation.''  In order to have a ``powerful computer'' capable of performing large-scale computations, the director said the Institute requested the government to allot money under the Tenth Five Year Plan.  The Department of Atomic Energy allotted money towards the end of 2002 and `Kabru' was completed within less than two years.  ``Our aim was not to produce a supercomputer,'' the director said.  ``But we were able to create a world-class supercomputer at half the cost of similar computers. As of now we have no commercial plans,'' he added.  Professor Hari Dass said he is ``extremely happy'' with the product which has ``far exceeded our expectations''.   As per a release, Kabru's entry had been accepted by the worldwide body ``Top 500'' for further evaluation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Technology Review: Single-Molecule Logic Proposed   Single-Molecule Logic Proposed  Technology Research News  March 25, 2004  Researchers from the French National Center for Scientific Research (CNRS) and University College London in England have devised a scheme for designing logic circuits within individual molecules.   The scheme could eventually be used to produce small, fast computers and to store large amounts of data in very small spaces. The method could also be modified to make sensors for detecting individual molecules.  The researchers' plan calls for connecting a pair of benzene molecules to two gold electrodes. The molecules contain nitrogen-oxygen side groups whose rotational positions can represent the 1s and 0s of computer information.  The researchers' simulations show that the setup would allow for simple two-input logic gates like AND and XOR. The molecular circuits also have the potential to perform more complex functions, according to the researchers.  The logic scheme works because depending on how the side-groups are rotated, they are coupled or decoupled from the cloud of electrons associated with the benzene molecule. The side-group positions represent inputs and two side groups provide the requisite number of inputs for the two basic logic gates.  Rotating the side groups changes the interference pattern of the different paths electron waves can travel through the molecule, which changes the electrical conductance of the molecule. The conductance levels represent the logic gate's output.  Practical applications for molecular electronics are more than a decade away, according to the researchers. The work appeared in the January 23, 2004 issue of Nanotechnology.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink embedded, rtos, dsp, fpga, compactpci, and more - eg3.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Embedded Systems Programming - Embedded.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Microcontroller.com - Embedded Systems Supersite 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Embedded Systems Internet Resources 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Biting the IPv6 silver bullet - Opinion - Express Computer India   Biting the IPv6 silver bullet      Even foresight has its limits. Unlike the shockingly myopic "640K should be enough for anybody" statement (which Internet folklore incorrectly attributes to one Mr William Gates), the task force working on the Internet Protocol (IP) in the early 1970s provided for something like 4.3 billion IP addresses (via a 32-bit address space) in the current avatar of IP on which the Internet runs—IPv4. Now surely that number should’ve been enough for everybody. But the growth of the Internet has boggled even the most prescient minds, and as IP-enabled devices extend to the realm of the mobile phone and home appliances, 4.3 billion seems like a hugely embarrassing underestimation.   The problem is compounded by an inequitable distribution of addresses, with the US hogging about 70 percent and the rest of the world left to scrounge around for the crumbs. India has been allocated about 2.2 million IP addresses, while China has something like 28 million.   About a decade ago, an announcement by the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) stating that the world would run out of IP addresses near about the year 2008, created a furore everywhere. The solution suggested by the IETF was an evolution to IPv6 (also called IPng, for ‘Next Generation’). With a 128-bit address space, IPv6 would provide for 3.4 times 10 raised to the power of 38 addresses (3.4 x 1038); that’s 340 undecillion (trillion trillion trillion) addresses—be assured, it’s a number way beyond anything planet Earth will ever need.  But back then, the IPv6 protocols were still being perfected. So network engineers came up with ingenious workarounds to enable the re-use of addresses. One is DHCP, the Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol, wherein a few addresses are dynamically assigned to a large number of hosts of which only a tiny subset are online at any given point in time. The other is NAT or Network Address Translation. Using NAT boxes, all the nodes and devices within an organisation—up to 257 of them—appear to be a single device to the rest of the network and utilise a single IP address.  With NAT in full flow, the spectre of address shortages kind of faded, and so did the urgency to move to IPv6. But like any honest-to-goodness workaround, NAT had its limitations and also created a new set of problems. Without getting into technicalities, suffice it to say that NAT and DHCP don’t really matter if all one wants to do is a bit of Web browsing and e-mailing. But that was yesterday. Today, more and more businesses and individuals demand a unique presence on the Net which is ‘always-on, equally-connected and easily-reachable’ without being tied down to a single service provider. This means unique IP addresses. Further, the 3G mobile world and IP-enabled devices demand unique IP addresses to ensure true end-to-end, bi-directional communication—something not possible when hundreds of devices are hiding behind a single IP address using a NAT.   So, not surprisingly, the IPv6 chant has been gradually rising to a crescendo, especially in countries like Japan, Korea and China, which see real benefits in migrating to IPv6 because of the imminent proliferation of 3G mobile telephony in their countries and the IP-enabling of every device and the kitchen sink in their home. And in the process, a not unpleasant fallout would be a reduction in US dominance of the IP address space. Small wonder then that the Japanese and Chinese governments have fixed deadlines for complete migration to IPv6 by 2005.   Of course with IPv6 it’s not just a matter of addresses. In developing the evolutionary protocol, the IETF has ensured that many of the inadequacies of IPv4 have been done away with. In the area of security, there’s now innate support for IP Security (IPSEC), and a robust authentication header for data packets that provides almost infallible authentication and integrity checks, thus preventing host masquerading attacks (Beware, all ye vile spammers!). Another major feature is address autoconfiguration, allowing mobile devices quick acquisition and transition of addresses, and plug-and-play connectivity for an unlimited number of devices in a network. With autoconfiguration, mobility and the ability to identify each device individually, the application development opportunities are mind-boggling. And best of all, there’s no need for a stroke-of-midnight rip-and-replace—IPv6 migration can be gradual, and co-existence with IPv4 can be indefinite.  And what of India’s IPv6 progress? We have an IPv6 Forum India (ipv6forum.org.in), which is active in holding an annual summit, generating awareness and conducting trials. There’s also a moderately active discussion group with about 45 members, but there’s a need to step up the momentum of IPv6 activity considerably, if India is to be anywhere near the frontrunners in adoption.  IPv6 might not be the silver bullet panacea for all internetworking ills. But it’s a bullet that we’d do well to bite sooner rather than later. Any takers?  Val Souza, Editor  valsouza@expresscomputeronline.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Linux Today - Linux News On Internet Time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Microsoft outlines identity management roadmap  Microsoft outlines identity management roadmap         By John Fontana Network World Fusion, 05/25/04  San Diego - Microsoft this week laid out the roadmap for its identity management platform, including federation services that will ship next year and eventually provide Web single sign-on features.   Microsoft plans to announce the roadmap and the renamed federation service during the second-day keynote at Microsoft’s annual TechEd conference Tuesday morning.   Advertisement:   Formerly codenamed TrustBridge, the technology is now called Active Directory Federation Service (ADFS), Microsoft said. It will ship next year as part of the Windows Server 2003 Update, codenamed R2, and allow users to federate identities between corporate boundaries.   Federation lets an identity credential issued by one company be used for access to a partner’s network.  “ADFS will be one of the biggest splashes in the identity management space we make this year,” says Levon Esibov, group program manager for directory and identity services.   ADFS will become the cornerstone of Microsoft’s adoption of Web services security protocols on the Windows platform, supporting authentication and authorization services between disparate systems and across corporate boundaries.   ADFS will eventually provide the Web single sign-on capabilities that Microsoft’s identity platform currently lacks. Those capabilities are now provided by third-party partners including Netegrity, Oblix and Open Network. Before Microsoft can claim single sign-on capabilities, however, support for Web services protocols, such as the Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML), must be prevalent across vendors’ identity products.   ADFS will support WS-Security, an OASIS standard, as well as protocols Microsoft is developing along with its partners such as WS-Trust, WS-Policy, WS-Secure Conversation, WS-Federation, WS-Authorization and WS-Privacy.   On Monday, Microsoft unveiled its Web Services Enhancements 2.0, a package for developers that includes those same protocols.  Microsoft’s work on federation protocols is in competition with work being done by the Liberty Alliance, which is using SAML as the foundation for a federated identity framework. Microsoft officials say they plan to eventually interoperate with the Liberty specifications.   The ADFS enhancements are the leading edge of a series of incremental upgrades to Microsoft’s identity management platform, which revolves around Active Directory, Active Directory Application Mode and Microsoft Identity Integration Server (MIIS).   The roadmap includes the next version of MIIS, which will ship next year. MIIS 3.5 includes a feature called “declarative provisioning,” which will eliminate the need to write provisioning scripts, user self-service features, and audit reporting. It also will establish the server as an application platform.   The biggest change is that MIIS 3.5 for the first time will eliminate the requirement that users deploy the server with the aid of consultants.   Before the 3.5 release, Microsoft will ship Service Pack 1 for MIIS later this year. It will include a set of new management agents for connecting to identity and other data stores. Today, MIIS has some 20 connectors. The service pack will add password synchronization capabilities, a management agent SDK for building custom agents and will incorporate workflow and approval features.   The identity roadmap also stretches to Longhorn server, which is slated to ship in 2007. Microsoft will add manageability enhancements to Active Directory and a digital ID service called Identity System, which will provide users with a portable identity that can be used with consumer and Web services.   RELATED LINKS     Identity management research center Latest news and analysis.  Network World on Identity Management Sign up for our free e-mail newsletter.  Breaking identity-management news  Microsoft outlines identity management roadmap 05/25/04 Microsoft Tuesday laid out the roadmap for its identity management platform, including federation services that will ship next year and eventually provide Web single sign-on features.   RFID expectations vary 05/24/04 Retailers expressed divergent views of the revenue-generating potential of radio frequency identification technology at last week's Retail Systems conference.   Could the cards hold the answer to our identity needs? 05/19/04 As I said last issue, there will always be people who object to letting any of their identity data be stored by a third party, no matter how tightly it ...   IBM announces ID management partnerships 05/18/04 IBM said it is partnering with four companies that make XML security products so that their products will work easily with IBM's Tivoli Access Manager management software.   Your identity in a double-lock safe 05/17/04 It's time to get back to our discussion of where identity information should be stored, particularly information you may want or need to share. You want the data to ...   More articles »  
     
    
</post>


<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Wi-Fi Networking News: Cisco Intros WLAN Switch Module   Cisco Intros WLAN Switch Module Cisco introduced today its wireless LAN services module, an add-on to its Catalyst 6500 switch that integrates support for WLANs: Coupled with Cisco APs (wireless access points), the platform offers some of the functionality of other WLAN switch platforms but has some drawbacks. One of the most important capabilities that Cisco executives stressed during a Webcast this morning was the ability for users to roam between APs in 50 milliseconds—fast enough to support voice. The client is authenticated at the AP where traffic is sent through a secure roaming tunnel back to the Catalyst switch, which could be located anywhere in the network. As the client roams, its IP address stays the same, so voice calls, VPNs, and other applications aren’t interrupted when the client associates with a new AP.   Because all traffic travels through the switch, roaming might not always happen in under 50 milliseconds. Cisco tested roaming between two APs that were located in Perth, Australia. The APs were connected to a switch that was located in Sydney, a distance away from Perth that is similar to the distance between Los Angeles and Miami. The handoff time increased to around 250 milliseconds, slow enough for an audible blip in a voice call. But applications are not dropped during that time.  Cisco also said that it is releasing an upgraded version of its wireless LAN solution engine (WLSE), Cisco’s management software for APs across an enterprise. The new version not only detects rogue or unauthorized APs, but can remotely disable the switch port that the rogue is connected to. Also, with the new software, customers can set their Cisco APs to scan-only mode. Customers who may not be ready to deploy a WLAN may still want to ensure that rogue APs aren’t being deployed. “Over time they will deploy a WLAN, and the same APs they use for scan-only can be used as regular APs,” said Bill Rossi, general manager of Cisco’s wireless unit. (Airespace, a WLAN switch developer, has a similar offering, which has the added feature of deassociate signal bombing a rogue AP to prevent clients from successfully remaining connected to it.)  The upgraded WLSE also supports instant AP deployment without having to configure the AP before adding it to the network. When the switch module recognizes that a new AP has been plugged in, it alerts the WLSE system, which sends the configuration file to the new AP. In the previous version of WLSE, the management software would monitor as well, but this newer method provides a more direct and instantaneous configuration.  The WLSE also optimizes frequency use. IT managers can set thresholds for capacity or coverage, and if the network exceeds those thresholds the engine will boost or decrease power in individual APs to optimize the environment. The WLSE also supports self-healing, so if one AP goes down, other nearby APs increase coverage and change channels to cover the open spot.   The switch module supports as many as 300 APs from a single switch and only works with Cisco APs. End users cannot roam between APs that are attached to different switches, however. Executives said that capability should be available some time in the future.   Cisco also introduced a new AP series, the Cisco 1300, that can be deployed indoor or outdoor.   Many of the capabilities of the new platform are also offered by the startup WLAN switch developers. Cisco has an advantage because it’s a large, established company with a large base of Catalyst switch customers. Cisco also touted the fact that its platform can support 300 APs, a number it says is far greater than that supported by other WLAN switches.   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sponsored By: GE     ___________________________________________________________     MIT's Technology Review Wednesday Update May 5, 2004 ___________________________________________________________ Inside Today's Update: + Robot Sex  + Humanoids for the Home  + Innovation Futures: How Much is Google Worth?  + Second Look: Search Beyond Google  + Mismatch Boosts Solar Efficiency  + From the TR Blog      -One for the Road      -Is U.S. Losing the Innovation Race?  ___________________________________________________________  Robot Sex  Is your Roomba a boy or a girl? The Roomba, of course, is a clever house-cleaning robot. And whether or not you think that gender belongs in our mechanical creations, writes columnist Simson Garfinkel, has a lot to do with your vision of how these creatures will fit into our future. It certainly takes more effort to make a robot that's gendered than one that's asexual. But engineers just want to have fun. Building gender into robots might be a way for the robots' designers to express their playfulness and creativity. And just like speech and vision, gender will make robots more compatible with their human masters.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/wo_garfinkel050504.asp?trk=nl     ___________________________________________________________  - advertisement -  Who would you turn to if you had to protect a bank, a casino or  an industrial plant? GE security systems are among the most  sophisticated on the planet. That's why customers from governments  to high-risk clients rely on our technology to keep them safe.  Learn about our state of the art security capabilities and other  projects currently under development.  Visit us at Imagination at Work     ___________________________________________________________  Humanoids for the Home  A herd of "entertainment robots" is jamming upscale-Tokyo-store shelves. And the toys are just the beginning. By 2010, the Japanese government hopes, full-fledged, humanoid robots will be common sights in middle-class homes.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/innovation60504.asp?trk=nl     Innovation Futures: How Much is Google Worth?  What will be Google's market capitalization be following its initial public offering? Right now, our readers say there is a 25 percent chance that at the end of the day of its IPO, the reigning search engine king will be capitalized at $20-25 billion. What do you think? Join us in predicting the future of technology and business.  http://trif.technologyreview.com/bk/market/grpIndex.html?_gid=15   &trk=nl  Second Look: Search Beyond Google  As Google comes to the brink of an IPO, take a close look at Technology Review's feature article from last fall on the future of search technology. Senior Editor Wade Roush showed precisely where the fabled search engine company excels-and where it is vulnerable to competition from Microsoft and a gaggle of startups.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/roush0304.asp?trk=nl     Mismatch Boosts Solar Efficiency  A mix of several metals and oxygen could lead to relatively inexpensive, highly efficient solar cells.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042704.asp?trk=nl     From the TR Blog    One for the Road  Thanks to some innovative new technology, concerts can live on long after the encore ends. A new service called eMusic Live will soon allow concert goers to purchase portable hard-drives containing the night's performance. Blogger David Kushner cites this development as the latest evidence that bands can exploit, rather than fear, new technologies.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1386   &trk=nl   Is U.S. Losing the Innovation Race?  A report that Europe and Asia are forging ahead of the U.S. in scientific publications, and in the granting of science and engineering PhDs, raises troubling questions.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1387   &trk=nl    ____________________________________________________________ Beyond the Curve: Macroeconomic Trends Affecting Entrepreneurship in  Massachusetts. May 8th, 2004 Cambridge, MA. How are public and  private markets evolving and what does this mean for entrepreneurs?  In what environments are breakthroughs being created? What areas are  likely to yield a disproportionate share of successful ventures?  These are the questions that every entrepreneur faces. Come find  the answers at the MIT Enterprise Forum Spring Workshop.  http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/spring04/MIT_forum_spring_04.htm       ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS  Technology Review respects the privacy of its readers. Advertising Information http://www.technologyreview.com/media/index.html      Privacy Policy http://www.technologyreview.com/gen_info/privacy.asp     _________________________________________________________________ Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved. One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142     d=6188&uid=a9076addcf>  22&mlid=6188&uid=a9076addcf>  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Financial Express: Govt Lifts Spectrum Barrier  Here's some good news for GSM-based cellular operators. In a major policy move, the government has decided to allocate spectrum beyond 10 MHz to global system for mobile communications based cellular operators.   GSM-BASED CELL COS TO GET SPECTRUM BEYOND 10 MHZ FOR A PRICE    Govt Lifts Spectrum Barrier     MAMUNI DAS    NEW DELHI:  Here’s some good news for GSM-based cellular operators. In a major policy move, the government has decided to allocate spectrum beyond 10 MHz to global system for mobile communications (GSM)-based cellular operators. It has also specified the new spectrum charges.          Looking for a Bride Groom    of Age 18 - 25 26 - 30 31 - 35 36 - 45 46 - 50 Above 50                Prior to this, the policy specified charges only up to 10 MHz of spectrum provision. In effect, cellular operators could not seek spectrum beyond 10 MHz.   The move comes as a boost to Bharti Tele-Ventures and Hutchison who have been seeking spectrum beyond 10 MHz for some of their circles. The additional spectrum will be given in the 1800 MHz band.   Incidentally, radio frequency spectrum is a scarce, natural resource required for provision of wireless services.   As per a recent government order, cellular operators with 10 MHz of spectrum and over 15 lakh subscribers can be allocated spectrum upto 15 MHz—though in two lots of 2.5 MHz each. When contacted, wireless advisor to the government PK Garg confirmed the same.   Now a look at the spectrum charges.   As reported in eFE earlier, spectrum charges for these segments are ‘higher and different’ than that for up to 10 MHz.   First, the additional spectrum will be released on a city basis — even for state circles, these additional spectrum chunks will be provided on a per city basis. Operators who would use 10-12.5 MHz of spectrum, will be charged 5 per cent of their adjusted gross revenue (AGR) as spectrum fees on an annual basis. Operators who would use 12.5-15 MHz of spectrum will be charged 6 per cent of AGR.   At present, the cellular operators are allocated spectrum on an annual basis.   They are required to pay 4 per cent of AGR for 6.2-10 MHz of spectrum usage, 3 per cent for 4.4-6.2 MHz and 2 per cent of their AGR for upto 4.4 MHz of spectrum usage on an annual basis.   It may be recalled that around August last year, a committee formed to study efficient use of spectrum by global system for mobile communications (GSM)-based cellular operators, had suggested that the government considers allocation of spectrum beyond 10 MHz in 1800 MHz band for operators. The operators can apply for spectrum beyond 10 MHz, after reaching a 12 lakh subscriber base.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Sasser net worm affects millions   Sasser net worm affects millions     Sasser spreads through networks by itself  The Sasser worm is continuing to cause disruption for large numbers of Windows PC users.  The first version of the malicious program was discovered on 1 May and since then has spread widely across the internet.   Some security experts estimate it has infected more than a million PCs and knocked out many computer systems.   Unlike more recent viruses, Sasser does not travel by e-mail instead it makes its way around the internet unaided.   Shut down   In at least seven cases, disruptions at large companies have been blamed on machines infected by Sasser.   The virus can infect PCs running Windows 2000 and XP that are not patched against the loophole it exploits.   According to anti-virus firms machines running Windows 95, 98 and Millennium Edition can help spread Sasser even though they cannot be infected by it.   The security firms urged users to install the latest security patches from Microsoft and advised home broadband users to install and run a firewall.   The virus is called a worm because it searches out machines to infect by itself without any help from users.   So far four variants of Sasser have been seen in the wild.     Sasser struck almost exactly 4 years after the Iloveyou bug  The latest version, Sasser.D, scans so aggressively for new computers to infect that it may cause networks to become congested with packets of data and slow down.   Poor programming by Sasser's creator makes infected machines shut down.   Microsoft and many security firms have released tools that help people find out if they are infected and to help them remove the virus from their system.   Users hit   Early reports suggest that home users will be hit hardest as many broadband users do not have a firewall fitted that would protect them from malicious programs like Sasser.   F-Secure said that many large companies had already installed the patch for the vulnerability Sasser exploits which may limit the ultimate spread of the worm.   Those that had not patched have been hit hard.   The head office and 19 regional offices of the UK Maritime and Coastguard Agency have been hit by the worm. The Agency said the disruption would not affect search and rescue work.   Taiwan's national post office said 1,600 of its machines were hit by the virus which forced more than 400 of its 1200 branch offices to revert to pen and paper.   The disruption left customers queuing in long lines at many of the company's offices, according to television reports.     Unpatched versions of Windows XP are vulnerable  Two Hong Kong government departments and some hospitals on the island were hit by the virus.   In Australia Railcorp trains were halted apparently because a virus disrupted the radio systems and stopped drivers talking to signalmen.   Also in Australia Westpac Bank staff were forced to use manual methods to record transactions as the virus made computers unusable. Two other banks reported infections.   Finnish bancassurer Sampo said it had temporarily closed all its 130 branch offices as a precaution against Sasser.   US airline Delta would not comment on reports that the virus caused disruption to its schedule.   Patch available   Microsoft played down reports that millions were being infected by Sasser.   It reported that almost four times as many PC owners were downloading patches for security problems now compared to autumn in 2003.   A patch for the vulnerability Sasser exploits was first released on 13 April and then updated on 28 April.   Holidays in the UK, parts of Europe and Japan may also help to limit the spread of the worm.   Some security experts said that using Sasser removal tools may not end the trouble because many of those caught out by it have also been infected by other viruses.   Creators of other malicious programs are trying to cash in on the success of Sasser.   The latest version of the Netsky virus, the 29th variant, travels with a file that claims to be a cure for Sasser sent out by anti-virus firms.   Inside this version the creators of Netsky claim that they were responsible for making Sasser too.     --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Have you been affected by the Sasser worm? What can be done to stop the spread of of worms and viruses like this one? Send us your comments on the form below.    Always taken IT for granted and assumed viruses attacked corporations etc when individuals have a vendetta. Never considered firewalls etc for home PC. Not quite sure what to do next or indeed how much it will cost to fix. You see all these downloadable fixes but the problem with my PC is that it is running far too slow to download anything anyway, shuts down before download is complete, or simply does not let me get on to the appropriate screens. Anyone got any tips? - fortunately can maintain my internet access from work! O, Wales    Cause: Windows is very sick! Prediction: This is not the last attack. You will hit again and again and again. Temporary Solution: Install the patch for this from Microsoft and patch for next after next attack and so on. Permanent Solution: Drop the sick Windows completely. Switch to a Linux based computer or install Linux Desktop on your existing computer and have peace in mind and in the world. Good luck. Sagara Wijetunga, Singapore     Why do we always only hear about new Windows vulnerabilities when they are exploited   Colin McKenzie, London UK   Why do we always only hear about new Windows vulnerabilities when they are exploited? If the issue of the patch got the news coverage that the worm has, many more people would be protected in time. I update Windows regularly, but no more than monthly. If I didn't have a firewall, Sasser would have caught me by now.  Colin McKenzie, London UK  A fried of mine was infected with the Sasser virus, I removed it using Norton's removal tool, the pc is now updated and is running sweet, but it was quite a pain to remove it. Had to use Safe Mode on XP to remove some of it, then had to create a new account on the pc to enable the rest of the removal as in the standard account the pc would keep shutting down. Not much fun..... Robert J Wilson, Herne Bay, Kent   Oh for goodness sake, pay peanuts, get monkies. Buy an Apple Mac and remain totally immune to all this rubbish. Factor in the cost of rebuilding,reformating, security updates, time wasted, data and documents lost, cost of virus checkers and AppleMacs complete with Microsoft Office for the Mac are VERY cost effective. Companies and Businesses that follow the herd instinct and stay with Windows deserve all they get. Arthur Lowe, Melbourne, Australia   Pretty primitive worm really. Spotted within a minute of it first running - easily detected due to ADSL connection activity when no programs open. Check Task Manager processes, a process called avserve.exe (which I don't recognise) is running. Stop the process, locate and delete the file, download Microsoft patch to prevent re-infection.  Graham Fewster, Huntingdon, UK    Patch, or face the consequences   James Atack, Paris, France   We should think ourselves lucky that once again the writer of this virus let us off the hook. Despite the high number of infections, the virus has a relativley benign payload. If ever a similar virus appears on the scene that actively destroys data, then the financial loss will be huge. Patch, or face the consequences.  James Atack, Paris, France  Common sense prevails here, buy a firewall, or download a free one of of the net and run Windows update often. Take 5 minutes out of your day, run Windows Update, update your firewall and antivirus definitions, and you'll be fine. Blair, Edinburgh, Scotland, UK   No comment on the 'poor programming' by Microsoft that caused this vulnerability in the first place?  Alex Hawdon, Huddersfield, UK    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           ___________________________________________________________     MIT's Technology Review Monday Update May 3, 2004 ___________________________________________________________ Inside Today's Update: + The Sound War  + Chung: Biochip Plan B  + Annals of Nanotubes I: Tiny Drive Shaft  + Annals of Nanotubes II: Stronger Composites  + From the TR Blog: Speculation over Google's Future Ends...and Begins  + Monday Poll ___________________________________________________________  The Sound War  Two very different inventors have staked competing claims to a potential audio revolution-the ability to direct music or speech to a single person in a crowd. This "directional sound" technique uses an ultrasound emitter to shoot a laserlike beam of audible sound so focused that only people inside a narrow path can hear it. Elwood "Woody" Norris, of American Technology Corporation, and F. Joseph Pompei, of Holosonic Research Labs, have harnessed the same scientific principle to create competing directional-sound systems, and each insists his version will transform acoustics. Who's going to capture this technology's potential billion-dollar market?  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/schwartz20504.asp?trk=nl      ___________________________________________________________  - advertisement -  DELIVERING INFORMATION SERVICES  July 26-31, 2004, Harvard Business School Executive Education,  Boston, MA U.S. Acquire the strategies and skills necessary to  build, implement, and manage information technology for maximum  shareholder value. For more information, visit:  http://www.exed.hbs.edu/programs/dismtrh/index.html    ___________________________________________________________  Chung: Biochip Plan B  Cynthia Bamdad is still on her first startup, so she has yet to chalk up a major entrepreneurial victory, but her life is full of the lemons-to-lemonade stories that investors love to hear. At first glance, writes columnist Joe Chung, there is little remarkable about a 51-year-old scientist with a successful invention behind her striking out on her own. What is unusual is that 15 years ago, Bamdad was an artist and stay-at-home mother with five school-age children, no higher-education degrees, and no scientific background whatsoever. Now she is founder and CEO of Minerva Biotechnologies, which is developing a hyperefficient nanotech biosensor that Bamdad hopes will help find cancer cures and Alzheimer's therapies.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/chung0504.asp?trk=nl     Annals of Nanotubes I: Tiny Drive Shaft  An altered carbon nanotube could serve as a molecular drive shaft. Next up: a molecular gear for the shaft to drive.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042304.asp?trk=nl     Annals of Nanotubes II: Stronger Composites  Magnetic fields align carbon nanotubes mixed in a resin, boosting the strength of the composite material.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042604.asp?trk=nl     From the TR Blog: Speculation over Google's Future Ends...and Begins  Search engine king Google's announcement last week that it will indeed go public put an end to months of hype. Blogger Wade Roush says that with founders Sergey Brin and Larry Page retaining their majority control, it looks as though the famously secretive company will keep innovating in risky new areas even as it faces up to new levels of accountability and openness.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1385   &trk=nl  Poll: What should be done about professional athletes' use of performance-enhancing drugs?  *Test more athletes for drug use more frequently  *Regulate the use of performance-enhancing substances so that at least  everyone has access to the same substances  *Lift all restrictions, and let athletes give themselves any edge they can  Cast your vote and leave a comment at http://www.technologyreview.com#poll  ll>   ____________________________________________________________ 2 FREE TRIAL ISSUES of Technology Review  Find out why The Washington Post called Technology Review: MIT's  Magazine of Innovation, "the clearest and most ahead-of-the-curve  tech publication..."  SUBSCRIBE TODAY at:  http://www.technologyreview.com/new/nl?trk=nl       ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS  Advertising Information http://www.technologyreview.com/media/index.html      Privacy Policy http://www.technologyreview.com/gen_info/privacy.asp     _________________________________________________________________ Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved. One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142      d=6188&uid=a9076addcf>  97&mlid=6188&uid=a9076addcf>  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spend a lot of time talking with Microsoft customers around the world, and one thing I consistently hear is that the growing complexity of today's computing systems is driving up costs and limiting the potential of information technology to work on the toughest business problems. In fact, a study by the consulting firm Accenture reported that IT professionals spend up to 70 percent of their time maintaining existing systems.  The IT world of today is dramatically different than it was just a decade ago. IT systems are much more complex, with computers and software distributed throughout the organization and often around the world. Employees rely on laptops, mobile phones and smart handheld devices to stay in touch with the people and information they care about. Security technologies and policies are required to keep company data safe and ensure that critical systems can run without disruption. Partners and suppliers use powerful Web services to connect their business processes and work more efficiently. And customers have come to expect real-time information about inventory, billing and shipping delivered securely over the Web.  As computing has rapidly extended beyond the "back office," it has added significant value across organizations - from information insight to sophisticated business analysis. Yet, with this vast new capability has come increased complexity. Today, many business customers try and cope with this through IT outsourcing and additional layers of management software, which often add complexity and inflexibility.  I believe our industry has a responsibility, and an opportunity, to dramatically simplify the computing environment by seamlessly weaving together all of the devices, services and multiple layers of software into a coherent, efficiently managed technology framework.   By designing computing systems that can be managed much more easily - or even manage themselves - we can vastly increase efficiency, reduce business overhead, and empower IT managers to spend more time making computers really work for their company - connecting business processes, empowering employees and creating real business value.  As a subscriber to executive emails from Microsoft, I'd like to share some additional insights with you regarding our manageability strategy.  DYNAMIC SYSTEMS INITIATIVE  Over the past several years, Microsoft, in partnership with other IT industry leaders, has been making significant investments in an effort we call the Dynamic Systems Initiative (DSI). The goal is to build a comprehensive set of solutions for the Windows platform that can help automate the design and management of the increasingly complex and distributed computing systems that customers need today. Doing this will free up valuable IT resources to work on higher-value projects, and make computing simpler and more cost-effective for organizations large and small.  Specifically, DSI is about doing three things really well:  - Building software development tools that help IT managers and software-development teams design computing systems that are inherently simple and inexpensive to manage. We call this "design for operations."  - Enhancing the Windows operating system platform with powerful management technologies suited for complex and constantly-changing IT environments, such as automated deployment, configuration and monitoring.  - Building easy-to-use, scalable solutions that cover every aspect of the management experience, with real-time feedback on system performance and a high level of automation.  Windows Server 2003 is at the core of DSI, and is already helping customers become much more productive and efficient by solving basic manageability problems.  Building on this foundation, we have developed technologies and services that further simplify deployment, management and security. One of our most important manageability solutions, Systems Management Server 2003, helps companies efficiently deploy and manage their software in a systematic way, so they no longer have to individually ensure that every server and PC has the right set of applications. Microsoft Operations Manager 2000 improves performance and streamlines management by identifying "IT health" issues automatically - so IT teams can identify problems and solve them quickly and efficiently.   We are also working to create a continuous feedback loop of information between developers, IT administrators and end-users, so that software developers get real-time information on the performance of their applications, allowing them to more accurately identify problems and solve them faster. We have built this kind of error-reporting technology into many of our major products, and it has driven tremendous improvements in our own software quality. With our Corporate Error Reporting tool, for example, large companies can now put the same technology to work on their own custom-built applications.  For software developers, we are building technologies that help them work more closely with IT managers to envision and design applications that work well in today's distributed and complex computing environments. We are designing the Visual Studio 2005 system of development tools to make it easier to build management into applications from the ground up, ensuring that they are simple and inexpensive to operate after they are deployed.  Through the Microsoft Operations Framework, we are offering guidance that helps organizations develop an optimal management strategy. And we are offering a series of services and solutions built on our management technologies through a program called Microsoft Solutions for Management.  Customers like Motorola are realizing significant benefits from these technologies. By using Windows Server 2003 and these powerful management solutions, Motorola estimates it saved 247,000 hours and $11 million in annual software deployments in 2003. Motorola was able to significantly consolidate and simplify its computing network and increase performance and efficiency of its Web servers. Software updates that previously took months to roll out can now be completed in less than a week.   PARTNERING FOR MANAGEMENT  The success of the Dynamic Systems Initiative requires a collaborative effort among Microsoft, our partners and standards organizations, to ensure that we are meeting customers' diverse needs. We are building our management solutions so they can integrate more easily with the diverse platforms, applications and tools that IT managers use today. For instance, we have created a framework that enables customers to use the capabilities of Microsoft Operations Manager to ensure the health and performance of their Windows computers, while continuing to use existing management systems.   We are working with partners to make it possible for Microsoft customers to manage UNIX, Linux and Mac computers in conjunction with Systems Management Server 2003, and to manage hardware devices such as desktops and servers through solutions that update hardware-based software components using the same familiar interfaces that an administrator would use to update software applications.  We are collaborating with partners to make existing business applications easier to manage on the Windows platform. For example, we're collaborating with Siebel Systems to make it possible to manage their eBusiness applications using Microsoft Operations Manager.  We are also engaging across the industry to learn how we can continue to evolve and further improve our management solutions. At last month's DSI Design Preview in Silicon Valley, a wide range of customers and partners gave us valuable feedback that is helping shape future generations of our management platform.  THE MANAGEMENT ROADMAP  Microsoft's Dynamic Systems Initiative is fundamentally about helping customers optimize their IT investments, while simplifying, and lowering total cost of ownership. We are committed to delivering value through smart software that enables customers to manage their own environments - creating the strength and flexibility that helps them optimize their IT investments.  Over the next few years, we will continue to deliver advanced solutions, such as System Center 2005, which bring our existing management tools together and add enhancements that simplify and optimize basic IT management tasks. With the next version of Visual Studio, we are giving IT managers and developers the tools they need to create and collaborate on software and services that are simple to manage. We are continuing to evolve the Windows Server System with cutting-edge advances in manageability, reliability and security, making it the best foundation for an efficient IT infrastructure.  While there's still a lot of work to be done, I believe we are making great progress, working with partners to simplify and automate the way customers can design, deploy and operate distributed systems. And we're committed to continuing to deliver improvements in our platform that will help customers do even more with less. These management improvements will help us address the issues customers face in this new era of IT - delivering the value companies want without the complexity they fear.  More information on the Dynamic Systems Initiative, including customer case studies, is available at www.microsoft.com/dsi.  Steve Ballmer  To cancel your subscription to future executive emails, please reply to this email with the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line. To contact us, write to us at One Microsoft Way, Redmond, Wash., 98052. To manage your Microsoft.com subscriptions, please sign in at the Microsoft Profile Center here: http://register.microsoft.com/regsys/pic.asp. To see the Microsoft.com Privacy Statement, please go to http://www.microsoft.com/info/privacy.mspx.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You are receiving this e-mail at neil@guyfromld.com because you  subscribed to the BigAdmin[sm] newsletter. To update your communications  preferences, please see the link at the bottom of this message. We  respect your privacy and post our privacy policy prominently on our  Web site: http://www.sun.com/privacy.  ===================================================================   April 2004, Vol 3 No 4 http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCr042TjS0mOFWHOFzT http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCs042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  The BigAdmin Newsletter is a monthly e-mail informing system administrators and developers of the latest events, news, resources, and information available on the BigAdmin and Solaris[tm] Developer Web sites.  ===================================================================  ISSUE HIGHLIGHTS  * BigNews and Announcements         - Introduction to the Domain Name System by Eric Rinker         - Unofficial Installation Guide for the Solaris Operating            System, x86 Platform Edition by Alan DuBoff, Angel Camacho,            and Michael Riley         - Using Solaris Live Upgrade Software for the x86           (and SPARC) Platform Edition by Alan Duboff * Techie Toolbox         - File Management * Solaris Developer Corner         - Determining Free Physical RAM and Using It to Improve Your           Application by Greg Nakhimovsky         - XPert Q&A on Sun[sm] Software Express Program for the            Solaris OS         - Ask Jonathan  * Community Submissions         - Keep Your Submissions Coming! Get Cool BigAdmin Merchandise           by Submitting Articles and Tech Tips, and Start Collecting           BigAdmin Bucks 	- Implementing Persistent IP Forwarding on Solaris Systems 	  by Michael Peters         - Disaster Recovery Plan for Sun[tm] Servers Using VERITAS           by Joel Andrews         - Selecting the Correct Printer by Fabian C. Toller         - Moving a Data-Laden Disk Between VxVM Disk Groups by           Jez Spencer * Offers and Events         - SunNetwork[sm] 2004 Conference: Shanghai, People's Republic           of China; June 2-3, 2004         - Solaris 7 OS System and Network Administration           Certification Exams Ending * MOTD Round-Up  ===================================================================   ------------------------- BIGNEWS and ANNOUNCEMENTS -------------------------  * Introduction to the Domain Name System by Eric Rinker    This tutorial is designed to help system administrators set up   and configure their own DNS servers. The article focuses on   the specifics of installing ISC BIND 9.x.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCt042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    * Unofficial Installation Guide for the Solaris Operating System,    x86 Platform Edition by Alan DuBoff, Angel Camacho, and Michael   Riley    This informal guide was written to help you install the Solaris   OS, x86 Platform Edition, on a variety of x86 hardware.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCu042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  * Using Solaris Live Upgrade Software for the x86 (and SPARC)    Platform Edition by Alan Duboff      Author describes how to use Solaris Live Upgrade software to   boot between multiple environments such as Solaris Express   releases.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCv042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   -------------- TECHIE TOOLBOX --------------  This month's topic: File Management  Auto FTP: Sample script and method to FTP files from one machine/host to another machine. http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCw042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  Find File Owners: This script finds all files owned by all general users and saves the list of files in /tmp. http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCx042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  File System Check: This script checks the file system, and if the capacity exceeds the number (threshold) passed as the first argument to the script, it alerts the MIS sys admin. http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCy042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   ------------------------ SOLARIS DEVELOPER CORNER ------------------------  * Determining Free Physical RAM and Using It to Improve Your   Application by Greg Nakhimovsky      The author explores how application programs can find the   amount of free physical memory that is available, with   recommendations on how to take advantage of this information.   Specifically for the Solaris OS, the article provides a routine   to get the currently available physical memory.     http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bCz042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    * XPert Q&A on Sun Software Express Program for the Solaris OS    There's still time to send in your questions and ask BigAdmin   XPert, Jackie Bao, about the Sun Software Express Program,    where you can preview the new technology in the Solaris 10 OS.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bC_042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  * Ask Jonathan     The Sun Developer Network is launching an interactive   conversation for developers call "Ask Jonathan." Engage in an   open, shared conversation with Jonathan Schwartz at any time   and from anywhere in the world. Send your questions, comments,   and suggestions to Jonathan, and he will respond in a monthly   column.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bC$042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  --------------------- COMMUNITY SUBMISSIONS ---------------------  * Keep Your Submissions Coming! Get Cool BigAdmin Merchandise   by Submitting Articles and Tech Tips, and Start Collecting   BigAdmin Bucks    We are accepting Articles and Tech Tips from the community   of BigAdmin users. Submit content to the site, and if we use   it, you can accumulate BigAdmin bucks to use toward cool   prizes. Articles and technical tips are highlighted in this   newsletter!   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD1042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    * Implementing Persistent IP Forwarding on Solaris Systems by   Michael Peters    This Tech Tip shows how to enable persistent IP forwarding for   routing purposes.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD2042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    * Disaster Recovery Plan for Sun Servers Using VERITAS by   Joel Andrews    This plan is designed for systems using VERITAS Volume   Manager and VERITAS File System with Sun Fire[tm] V880 servers.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bOB042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Selecting the Correct Printer by Fabian C. Toller    Here's how to choose a default printer using the LPDEST   variable.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD3042TjS0mOFWHOFzT  * Moving a Data-Laden Disk Between VxVM Disk Groups by Jez Spencer      Find out how to safely transfer data when reorganizing your   VERITAS Volume Manager disk groups.  http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD4042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   ----------------- OFFERS and EVENTS -----------------  * SunNetwork 2004 Conference: Shanghai, People's Republic of   China, June 2-3, 2004    If you use the network for business gain, you cannot afford to   miss this event. Meet business leaders. Tap the expertise of   globally renowned experts. Attend keynotes to get an overview of   how Sun technologies can attack cost and complexity in the   data center, accelerate network service deployment, and unleash   mobility with security.   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD5042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    * Solaris 7 OS System and Network Administration Certification   Exams Ending    The Solaris 7 OS System and Network Administration   certification exams will no longer be available after June 30,   2004. Purchase your Sun voucher and schedule to take any   Solaris 7 System or Network Administrator exam at an   Authorized Prometric Testing Center today for $150 (USD).   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD7042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    ------------- MOTD ROUND-UP -------------    http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD6042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Dynamic Reconfiguration for High-End Servers is a two-part   series of articles: Part 1--Planning Phase (PDF) provides an   introduction to Sun Fire 15K/12K server DR and details the   planning phase. Part 2--Implementation Phase (PDF) describes   the implementation of DR operations and presents best   practices.  * Supporting Multiple Page Sizes in the Solaris Operating   System (PDF). This Sun BluePrints[tm] article explains how to   engage the MPSS feature and how to analyze the performance   effect.  * Download Today: Sun Java[tm] System Application Server    Platform Edition 8 featuring support for JavaServer[tm] Faces    technology. It is free for both development and deployment.  * Oracle Developer Days are free workshops on topics such as   Grid Computing; Java 2 Platform, Enterprise Edition (J2EE[tm]);    Linux; and Web Services. Held in April and May in the U.S.  * Sun Alerts 57509, 57454, and 57508: Read about three   vulnerabilities that can allow unauthorized access to a system   running the Solaris OS. See all current Security Sun Alerts.  * Sun Software Express for Solaris 03/04 (s10_52) is now    available for download. Check it out!  * ApacheTop and iftop: This article covers ApacheTop, which   is used to monitor Apache in real time and generate a top-like   output, as well as iftop (which displays a table of current   bandwidth usage in a top-like format).  * A Sys Admin magazine article describes the Sun Software    Express program in detail, explaining how the program works    and what is included.  * Tru_to_Solaris Migration Tool for C/C++ Source Code can help   you port files from Tru64 or HP-UX to the Solaris OS.  * The Wiley book Distributed Storage Networks: Architecture,   Protocols and Management discusses efficient management of   stored data focusing on architectures, protocols, and   management techniques.  * The Sun BluePrints article Performance Forensics (PDF)   discusses how to address system performance complaints with   predictable and accurate results.  * Sys Admin Magazine's IPQoS article discusses the facility in   the Solaris 9 OS for network traffic management.  * eWEEK reports on tests of the Sun Fire B1600 Blade Platform    in the article Sun Scales Up Blade System.  * Enterprise Network Design Patterns: High Availability (PDF):     This Sun BluePrints article discusses the design of network    architectures.  * The Sun Fire V210 and V240 Server Maintenance &   Troubleshooting Course gives you tips on hardware components,   software requirements, and diagnostic tools.  * The Perl Template Toolkit is a book designed to help you easily   produce PDF, XML, and other formats in addition to HTML.  * A new O'Reilly book, Security Warrior, covers reverse   engineering, SQL attacks, social engineering, antiforensics,   and advanced attacks against UNIX[R] and Windows systems.  * A Sun BluePrints book, Migrating to the Solaris Operating   System: The Discipline of UNIX-to-UNIX Migrations, presents   a methodology for migrating from existing UNIX platforms to   the Solaris OS.  * Read about a security vulnerability in Check Point's    FireWall-1 HTTP Security Server that could allow a remote hacker    to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges.  * A ServerWatch article, Sun Spurns Reboots with Solaris Upgrade,   talks about dynamic resource pools and expanded disk set   support in the Solaris 10 OS.     More details at:    http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD8042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    -------------------------------------------------------------------    Thanks for tuning in to the BigAdmin Newsletter.    Best regards,   The BigAdmin Team    ::::::::::::::::::::: We make the net work ::::::::::::::::::::::    HOW TO CONTACT US   If you have questions or comments about this newsletter, please   reply to this message or write to us at: bigadmin.news@sun.com    ::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::    ALSO ON SUN.COM --------------------------------------------------   My Sun Portal:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bD9042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Products & Services:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDA042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Business & Industry Solutions:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDC042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Support & Training:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDB042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Downloads:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDE042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Documentation:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDD042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   Sun Store:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDF042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    Resources for:   * Developers:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDH042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Solaris Developers:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDG042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * System Admins:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDI042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Partners:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDK042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Executives:   http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDJ042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   * Press:    http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDL042TjS0mOFWHOFzT   ------------------------------------------------------------------   Sun Microsystems, 4150 Network Circle, UMPK18-113,   Santa Clara, CA 95054 U.S.A.      Trademark Information: http://www.sun.com/suntrademarks/   Java, J2EE, J2SE, J2ME, all Java-based marks, and Solaris are    trademarks or registered trademarks of Sun Microsystems, Inc. in the   United States and other countries.     To update your Sun subscription preferences or unsubscribe to Sun  news services, go to http://see.sun.com/Apps/DCS/mcp?r=70042TjS4AxEF0120003bDM042TjS0mOFWHOFzT    ----------------- annmn:[742TjS042TjS4AxEF0120000042TjS0mOFWHOFzT]      
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                       urlLink           ___________________________________________________________ urlLink           MIT's    Technology Review Wednesday Update    April 28, 2004    ___________________________________________________________    Inside Today's Update:    + Patent Litigation: The Sport of Kings                              + ATMs Go beyond Cash   + Tiny Rotors Spin into Place   + Spoke Polarization Tightens Focus   + From the TR Blog: Nintendo Nostalgia?      ___________________________________________________________         Patent Litigation: The Sport of Kings    Patent litigation is a growth industry. During the twelve-month  period ending September 9, 2003, U.S. patent owners filed 2,788  patent infringement lawsuits, a 13 percent increase over the same  period five years earlier. Similarly, in 2003 the United States  issued 187,487 patents, a 22 percent increase over 1999. Indeed,  patent litigation has become the sport of kings. Sure, there are  staggering legal fees and the risk of a company imploding. But  Douglas J. Kline, a leading patent litigator, says that patent  lawsuits are not as bad as you think.    urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/wo_kline042804.asp?trk=nl            ___________________________________________________________     - advertisement -          Discover New Sources of Profitability with the DELTA MODEL        MIT's Sloan School will offer its acclaimed Executive Program in   Corporate Strategy June 13-18. The program is anchored in the   Delta Model, a new strategic management framework developed   at MIT and widely hailed as a groundbreaking force in corporate   strategy development and customer bonding.    urlLink http://mitsloan.mit.edu/corpstrat       ___________________________________________________________         ATMs Go beyond Cash       What sells movie tickets, cashes checks, lets you add minutes    to your cell-phone account, and spits out a stack of crisp twenties?    It&rsquo;s your neighborhood ATM&mdash;now equipped with a new computer that&rsquo;s    more like a multimedia PC than the familiar dumb bank terminal.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/innovation30504.asp?trk=nl          Tiny Rotors Spin into Place      Tiny, free-floating magnetic rotors arrange themselves into useful    configurations when set spinning.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042104.asp?trk=nl          Spoke Polarization Tightens Focus      Scientists are figuring out how to get around what was once considered    a fundamental limit in how tightly a beam of light could be focused.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042004.asp?trk=nl          From the TR Blog: Nintendo Nostalgia?      Every generation has its music: from Duke Ellington to Buddy Holly    to the Beatles to AC/DC to.... Super Mario? Henry Jenkins comments    on videogame themes as the the soundtrack of our lives.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1377&amp;trk=nl              ____________________________________________________________     Entrepreneurial Eye for the Tech Guy. Panel discussion presented     by MIT Sloan CNC. Dr. Rodney Brooks, Director of MIT&rsquo;s Artificial     Intelligence Laboratory will challenge 5 accomplished vc&rsquo;s and     entrepreneurs on how to bring to market recent breakthroughs     in intelligent robots. May 20th 2004, 6:00 pm. Santa Clara, CA      urlLink http://Fab5.mitsloancnc.org                                                                   ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS  Advertising Information   urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/media/index.html    Privacy Policy   urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/gen_info/privacy.asp   _________________________________________________________________  Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved.  One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142                 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                      ___________________________________________________________ urlLink           MIT's    Technology Review Friday Update    April 30, 2004    ___________________________________________________________    Inside Today's Update:    + Nano Weapons Join the Fight Against Cancer                               + Kurzweil's Rules of Invention   + Innovation Futures: SCO vs. IBM   + Optical Quantum Memory Designed   + From the TR Blog:   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- Putting a New Spin on Computing   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- Calling Peter Parker   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- So Much for Secure Access      ___________________________________________________________         Nano Weapons Join the Fight Against Cancer    Imagine being treated for cancer with a couple of visits to your  doctor. He simply gives you an injection and then a couple of  weeks later runs infrared light over your body to activate  cancer-killing agents and excise the tumor. Sound like a Ray  Bradbury novel? Don&rsquo;t tell Naomi Halas that. She is the Stanley C.  Moore professor of electrical and computer engineering and professor  of chemistry at Rice University, and she has more than imagined  it&mdash;she&rsquo;s been developing the process since 1997, when she invented  miniscule particles with huge therapeutic potential. She calls  them nanoshells. It's just one of the research efforts under way  to deploy tools of the ultrasmall realm for the diagnosis and treatment  of tumors.    urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/wo_harney043004.asp?trk=nl            ___________________________________________________________     - advertisement -      On May 24-26 The Institute for International Research presents     Best Practices &amp; Tools for Managing the Front End of Innovation     Regarded as the greatest opportunity to improve innovation,     featuring Teresa Amabile, Harvard; John Seely Brown, Xerox;     Clayton M. Christensen, Harvard; &amp; Eric von Hippel, MIT.      urlLink http://www.iirusa.com/frontend/index.cfm/Link=1/NewSection=Yes/prioritycode=M1604MIT        ___________________________________________________________         Kurzweil's Rules of Invention      More than 30 years of experience have given prolific inventor    Raymond Kurzweil a few insights into how to ensure that your    inventions have their day in the sun. First, he writes, learn    the seven stages in the evolution of a technology: precursor,    invention, development, maturity, false pretenders, obsolescence,    and antiquity. And focus above all else on getting the timing right.     urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/kurzweil0504.asp?trk=nl          Innovation Futures: SCO vs. IBM      Will The SCO Group succeed in its lawsuit against IBM in    District Court in Utah? According to the participants in Technology    Review's Innovation Futures predictive markets, there is a 94    percent chance that SCO will come away empty-handed--with no    damages awarded to it. What do you think will happen?&nbsp; Join us in    predicting the future of technology and business.      urlLink http://trif.technologyreview.com/bk/market/market.html?_sym=SOFTWARE03&amp;trk=nl           Optical Quantum Memory Designed      Quantum computers that use photons rather than atoms or electrons    are appealing because the equipment needed to handle them can be    relatively simple. Researchers at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory    have overcome one critical challenge by designing quantum memory    devices that will briefly store photons.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_042204.asp?trk=nl           From the TR Blog       Putting a New Spin on Computing      Electrons may be merely amorphous clouds of charge, but somehow    they still manage to carry a spin. IBM and Stanford announced this    week that they're joining forces to study how to tap this phenomenon    for a new era of &quot;spintronic&quot; computing.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1381&amp;trk=nl           Calling Peter Parker      The California State Highway Patrol wants researchers    to develop a &quot;spider gun&quot; that would quickly extrude a web, which    could serve as an ad hoc safety net for stopping suicidal jumpers on the    Golden Gate bridge.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1382&amp;trk=nl           So Much for Secure Access      A resourceful hacker has figured out how to build a handheld device that    can clone your proximity card without your ever knowing it.      urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1384&amp;trk=nl          ____________________________________________________________     Beyond the Curve: Macroeconomic Trends Affecting Entrepreneurship     in Massachusetts. May 8th, 2004 Cambridge, MA     How are public and private markets evolving and what does this mean     for entrepreneurs? In what environments are breakthroughs being created?     What areas are likely to yield a disproportionate share of successful     ventures? These are the questions that every entrepreneur faces. Come     find the answers at the MIT Enterprise Forum Spring Workshop.      urlLink http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/spring04/MIT_forum_spring_04.htm                                                                             ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS   Technology Review respects the privacy of its readers.  Advertising Information  urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/media/index.html    Privacy Policy   urlLink http://www.technologyreview.com/gen_info/privacy.asp   _________________________________________________________________  Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved.  One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142                
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: NewsForge: PayPal API Release Aimed at Web Services, OS Developers  "PayPal Developer Network director Dave McClure told NewsForge the initial three API calls are just the beginning of a series of APIs the company will release over coming quarters..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-13-019-26-NW-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxPlanet: IBM Workplace - A Good Thing for Linux?  "IBM Workplace, a new application management model launched this week, is bound to spell changes ahead for Linux developers, administrators, and desktop users. Just what kind of impact should the Linux community expect...?"  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-13-018-26-OS-DT-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ___________________________________________________________     MIT's Technology Review Wednesday Update May 12, 2004 ___________________________________________________________ Inside Today's Update: + The Language of Pattern Recognition  + Woz Goes Wireless  + Innovation Futures: Google vs. Yahoo!  + Dots Pinpoint Cancer  + Chaos Seems to Aid Learning  + A Speed Limit for Computer Viruses + From the TR Blog     -Not Such Sound Science     -NY Drops the E911 Call     -Touring Chernobyl  ___________________________________________________________  The Language of Pattern Recognition  Ask a businessperson, "What exactly do you do?" and the answer will probably be, "I make decisions!" Ask a scientist, and the response will be, "I discover truth!" Actually, writes venture capitalist Howard Anderson, both of them are on the same quest-the search for patterns.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/wo_anderson051204.asp?trk=nl     ___________________________________________________________  - advertisement -  Please mark your calendars for our May 19th event, Does IT Still Matter?,  a Harvard Business School Publishing virtual seminar and debate featuring  Nick Carr & John Hagel. Join us for 90 minutes of head-to-head debate as  Carr and Hagel argue the merits of IT today-is it a commodity like electricity  and the telephone or so fundamentally different from those earlier technological  advances that it can continue to create advantage and bottom-line benefits  for one's organization? Wednesday, May 19 from 12:30 - 2:00 p.m. (ET). Visit  http://www.krm.com/itdebate3   for details or to register. ___________________________________________________________  Woz Goes Wireless  Steve Wozniak-the legendary engineer behind the first Apple computer-now wants to combine wireless technology with GPS to help ordinary folks track loved ones, pets, and more.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/hiltzik0504.asp?trk=nl     Innovation Futures: Google vs. Yahoo!  Will Google have a bigger market capitalization than Yahoo! at the end of the day of its IPO? 53% of those playing Technology Review's Innovation Futures game say "No." What do you think?  http://trif.technologyreview.com/bk/market/market.html?_sym=GOOGLE03   &trk=nl  Dots Pinpoint Cancer  Special semiconducting particles called quantum dots could help simplify the search for cancer.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/massave0504.asp?p=3   &trk=nl  Chaos Seems to Aid Learning  A computer simulation shows that chaotic nerve signals may play a key role in learning motor skills, providing a potential boost for robotics and communications technologies.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_050304.asp?trk=nl     A Speed Limit for Computer Viruses  Limiting the pace at which a computer can make new connections could slow the spread of worms and viruses enough to make outbreaks manageable.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_050504.asp?trk=nl      From the TR Blog    Not Such Sound Science  Opponents of governmental regulations have often claimed the mantle of "sound science"-implying that those who insist on, say, reductions in greenhouse gas emissions, or restrictions on smoking in restaurants, or bans on dioxin emissions, are wooly-headed quacks. But who's really subverting science?  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1400   &trk=nl   NY Drops the E911 Call  Every month, New York state's cell phone subscribers pay a $1.20 tax that's supposed to be used to fund development of a cell phone 911 system. But it looks like it's not working out that way.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1402   &trk=nl   Touring Chernobyl  The radiation isn't too bad as long as you don't spend too long there, and where else can you find miles and miles of apartment buildings, stores, roads, and everything else that goes into a modern society? Everything, that is, except for people and electricity.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1403   &trk=nl   ____________________________________________________________ Entrepreneurial Eye for the Tech Guy. Panel discussion presented  by MIT Sloan CNC. Dr. Rodney Brooks, Director of MIT's Artificial  Intelligence Laboratory will challenge 5 accomplished vc's and  entrepreneurs on how to bring to market recent breakthroughs  in intelligent robots. May 20th 2004, 6:00 pm. Santa Clara, CA  http://Fab5.mitsloancnc.org       ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS  _________________________________________________________________ Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved. One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: GNOME, May 11, 2004  Today's GNOME apps: GNOME CPU Frequency Scaling Monitor 0.1.3 and MlView 0.6.3.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-12-010-26-NW-GN-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Financial Express: ISRO Defers Edusat Launch To August  Indian Space Research Organisation has postponed the launch of Edusat, the spacecraft dedicated to education, earlier scheduled for mid-July to early August. Edusat will be launched on board a geo-synchronous satellite launch vehicle.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.financialexpress.com/fe_full_story.php?content_id=58960  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: The Register: BBC Develops 'Alternative' Codec  "Just when we think that the codec wars are just about over, the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) has released a codec that works differently from other existing systems..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-11-015-26-OS-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux Gazette: Benchmarking Filesystems  "In order to determine this I used common operations that Linux users may perform on a regular basis instead of using benchmark tools such as Bonnie or Iozone. I wanted a 'real life' benchmark analysis..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-11-018-26-OS-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Wardriving as a Proxy for Wi-Fi GPS Location  Quarterscope converts Wi-Fi cards plus a wardriving database into a virtual GPS receiver: A few weeks ago, Wi-Fi Networking News talked to Ted Morgan, the founder and president of Quarterscope, a company which had just won an award at the cellular industry's big trade show for location services, finishing behind well-established Ekahau. Quarterscope's product is software that uses a database of wardriving records that it matches against the signals received by a Wi-Fi radio to produce an approximate set of coordinates, like a virtual GPS. "What got us started down this path is the density of public and private hot spots," Morgan said. "No one realizes just how many of these access points has been installed. They see the sales numbers, but they don't extrapolate the fact that people are going home and plugging them in." Morgan said that they have primed the pump of their database using existing information from research groups, hobby wardrivers, and collective databases. "We're aggregating from lots of different existing sources today," he said. Wardriving uses "stumbling" software like NetStumbler to record all of the network names and unique access point hardware addresses at regular time slices, like every second, combining that information with GPS (Global Positioning Satellite) receiver coordinates tied into the same laptop or handheld. Quarterscope is starting its own stumbling efforts by installing wardriving devices on vehicles in metropolitan areas that drive random paths, such as delivery vans. "If you have somebody who is scanning for a full day, in metro areas, they can scan over 5,000 a day, particularly in downtown areas," Morgan said. Oddly, he said, certain kinds of vehicles don't work because they drive similar routes every day, such as police cars. "if you really look at what a cop does all day, it's pretty revealing." Morgan said that they've had  legal advice as to whether passively scanning or pinging for a beacon violates any laws int he U.S. "We've gotten consultation on the whole process, and it&#8217;s very clearly within legal bounds," he said. "If we have any concerns, it's more on a perception side of things. You can go to the FBI Web site and they very clearly state that passive scanning is fine. The problem is if you connect into somebody&#8217;s network." Quarterscope's software generates a virtual serial port on a Windows system, and uses the NMEA GPS protocol. it works with a variety of mapping...  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003334.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Under the skin of digital crime  Computers have become a key tool for the criminal classes, explains security expert Neil Barrett.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/technology/3701671.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Avocent Offers Wireless Control of Remote Workstations  Answering the cry of system admins everyone, new system controls up to 16 servers over 802.11a with AES encryption: If you ever visit a server room, you see monitors and keyboards piled up or hung or inserted all over the place. These keyboards, video displays, and mouses (KVMs, in brief) are controlled through switches that are plugged into the servers. Avocent's AutoView Wireless cuts those cords and extends the range, removing clutter and wasted space from a valuable server room. With multiples of this unit, which lists at $595 each, admins can connect up to 16 servers to two workstations so that two admins can connect to the same set of 16. Some details are blurry that I'm trying to get clarification on: is there an intermediate KVM server to which the transceiver is connected? If you have several sets of 16 servers, can a single transceiver at the admin's station switch among those sets?...  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003329.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: KDE, May 9, 2004  This Mother's Day's KDE apps: EventWatcher 0.4.1, KLinkStatus 0.1.0, KNetLoad 2.2.1, eric3 3.4.2, amaroK 1.0-beta3, konjue 0.1, knoda 0.7-test1, MIKonq 0.3, KXDocker 0.17, and gwenview 1.0.1 - 1.1.2.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-10-009-26-NW-KE-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: GNOME, May 9, 2004  This Mother's Day's GNOME apps: Guikachu 1.4.0, gi8k 1.2.2, and GDM 2.6.0.2.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-10-008-26-NW-GN-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Financial Express: India Banks on Galileo Satellites  India will be investing $200-250 million in the European Commission's Galileo global satellite positioning and navigation system.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.financialexpress.com/fe_full_story.php?content_id=58871  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux Magazine:  Software Packaging with RPM  "This month, let's review the basics of package management and outline the process of creating your own RPMs..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-07-004-26-OS-SW-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux.com: SysAdmin to SysAdmin: Using Ximian Tools for System Maintenance  "Have you ever needed an automated solution that requires very little administration intervention, works on possibly different flavors of Linux, and doesn't require software with 'phone home' functionality...?"  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-07-005-26-OS-HL-NT  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Vivato Announces 802.11g Switch  Vivato formally announced its next-generation 802.11g switch today: The 802.11g device that the FCC approved just three weeks ago will ship this summer. Pricing isn't indicated. [link via Daily Wireless]...  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003316.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: KDE, May 6, 2004  Today's KDE apps: KAlarm 1.0.7, Katalog 0.2, kiosktool 0.3, KIso 0.4.3, kim-browser 0.2, GwenRename 0.9.6-beta-1, Quanta Plus 3.3 Bleeding Edge 2, KolourPaint 1.0.2, and kbootsplash 0.3 Alpha2.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-07-012-26-NW-KE-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           ___________________________________________________________     MIT's Technology Review Monday Update May 10, 2004 ___________________________________________________________ Inside Today's Update: + Five Killer Patents  + The 2004 TR Patent Scorecard  + Global Invention Map  + Squeal Stopper  + Nano Wires Make Tiny Compasses  + From the TR Blog     -Making Votes Count     -E3 Mayhem     -Technology's Uncle Walter  + Monday Poll  ___________________________________________________________  Five Killer Patents  Technology Review selects five of the most important U.S. patents issued in 2003. These inventions-which range from a safer lung biopsy technique to software for fighting telephone-transaction fraud-will profoundly influence their fields for years to come. http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/patents0504.asp?trk=nl     ___________________________________________________________  - advertisement -  HARVARD BUSINESS SCHOOL EXECUTIVE EDUCATION  "Leading Product Development," June 28 - July 2, 2004  Acquire the know-how to design and implement innovative,  action-oriented solutions to improve product development for  sustainable advantage. For more information, visit:  http://www.exed.hbs.edu/programs/lpdmtrh/index.html     ___________________________________________________________  The 2004 TR Patent Scorecard  Technology Review's annual Patent Scorecard ranks the U.S. patent portfolios of 150 top technology companies in eight industry sectors. The good news is that even as technology-based companies have suffered through layoffs and business closings, their sheer inventiveness has not waned.  http://www.technologyreview.com/scorecards/?trk=nl       Global Invention Map  Invention is exploding globally, but only in certain hot spots. This exclusive Technology Review map shows where the patenting action is around the world.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/map0504.asp?trk=nl      Squeal Stopper  A material that grows when voltage is applied could silence an automobile's brakes.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/prototype50504.asp?trk=nl      Nano Wires Make Tiny Compasses  Coating a nanowire with magnetic nanoparticles yields a device that could provide a sense of direction on a very small scale.  http://www.technologyreview.com/articles/rnb_043004.asp?trk=nl      From the TR Blog   Making Votes Count  With another close presidential election looming, the state of California is moving ahead with a ban on electronic voting machines that don't provide a verifiable paper trail. Wise move, writes blogger Alyssa Danigelis: "Americans need reassurance that they-not faulty machines-will be picking the president."  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1396   &trk=nl  E3 Mayhem  Attending the Electronic Entertainment Exposition--a.k.a. E3--is like walking inside a video game for three days, writes blogger Dave Kushner. The music is cranked. The skateboarders are flying through the air. And it seems like every model and stripper in town is dressed in a cat suit or commando outfit, working the booths. What surprises will be in store for this year's E3, which runs this week in Los Angeles? http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1394   &trk=nl   Technology's Uncle Walter  Wade Roush explains why the Wall Street Journal's Walter Mossberg is the same kind of guiding patriarch for technology users that Walter Cronkite was for TV news viewers.  http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/blog.asp?blogID=1395   &trk=nl   Monday Poll: The governor of Massachusetts wants to make the death penalty available in that state as long as there is incontrovertible scientific proof-e.g., through DNA analysis-of a person's guilt. What do you think?  *I support the death penalty, even under current standards of guilt  *I'm generally against the death penalty but would support it in cases where there is absolute proof  *I oppose the death penalty, even if there is absolute proof of guilt  *There's no such thing as absolute proof--science is fallible because it is applied by human beings.  Cast your vote and leave a comment at: http://www.technologyreview.com#poll  ll>    ____________________________________________________________ Stay ahead of the technology curve with Business 4Site -  The Summit for Business Solutions - June 15-17, Los Angeles, CA.  Go face-to-face with HP, IBM, Microsoft, Toshiba, Intel and more  REGISTER TODAY - FREE MarketPlace Pass or 15% conference discount  Use Source Code: NJ4ATR to redeem your discount  http://www.business4site.com/registration.html?source=NJ4ATR       ___________________________________________________________ NEWSLETTER TOOLS  ________________________________________________________________ Copyright 2004 Technology Review Inc. All rights reserved. One Main Street, 7th Floor, Cambridge, MA 02142   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: GNOME, May 6, 2004  Today's GNOME apps: Epiphany 1.2.5, libgsf 1.9.0, Gnumeric 1.2.12, Metacity 2.8.1, libxml++ 2.6.1, libxml++ 1.0.3 (stable), ooo-build-1.1.55, and Muine 0.6.0.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-07-011-26-NW-GN-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: GNU, May 2, 2004  This weekend's GNU app: GNU Automake 1.8.4.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-03-007-26-NW-SW-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Release Digest: GNOME, May 2, 2004  This weekend's GNOME apps: gtkmm 2.4.1, glibmm 2.4.1, gnome-u2ps-0.0.3, GTK+-2.4.1, GLib-2.4.1, gnopernicus 0.9.1, Rhythmbox 0.8.2, gnome-gcj 0.18.0, Bakery 2.3.3, GNOME Music Quiz 0.1, and ooo-build-1.1.54.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-03-008-26-NW-GN-RL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New York Times: Technology: Illuminating Blacked-Out Words  Researchers at a conference in Switzerland have demonstrated computer-based techniques that can identify blacked-out words and phrases in confidential documents.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/05/10/technology/10crypto.html?ex=1399521600&amp;en=1ff921ef003d104a&amp;ei=5007&amp;partner=USERLAND  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Google revamps blogging service  One of the leading names in blogging is overhauling its service in an attempt to widen its appeal.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/technology/3694691.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New York Times: Technology: I.B.M. Takes Aim at Microsoft With Server-Based Software  I.B.M. plans to announce a software strategy for corporate desktop personal computers and hand-held devices - one that is firmly anchored in the company's strength in data centers.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/05/10/technology/10ibm.html?ex=1399521600&amp;en=eee7575e044d7554&amp;ei=5007&amp;partner=USERLAND  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Intel focuses on new 'super' chip  US chip maker Intel scraps two existing projects to focus on a fast chip which produces less heat.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/business/3695369.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Wireless Confusion  Fixed broadband wireless is in the spotlight, now that 802.16 and WiMax are being written about in the mainstream press: But that attention seems to be adding a lot of confusion to the market, particularly about the difference between different technologies. The Financial Times ran a story about PCCW's launch of broadband wireless in the U.K. but said that the network would use WiMax gear. In addition to the fact that there is no WiMax gear yet, the network will be built with equipment from IPWireless, which doesn't aspire to be WiMax. Strangely, PCCW doesn't even mention IPWireless or the type of technology used in its press release about the launch, which came out yesterday. IPWireless followed up today with an announcement of its own that adds a bit more information. There seems to be a lot of confusion especially around the 802.16 and 802.20 camps and some of it may be caused by some of the companies involved. For example, I was once told by an 802.20 member that IPWireless was active in the development of that standard. I talked with an IPWireless spokesperson at the time who I understood to say that IPWireless had moved to the 802.16 camp. However, she recently contacted me to say that IPWireless has never been part of the 802.20 effort and while the company has an engineer who attends the 802.16 meetings, the company is not active in the 802.16 development effort and does not at this time have plans to build to the 802.16 standard. At the same time that the 802.16 and 802.20 efforts work on developing their standards, some of the member companies are also developing and selling their own systems, which sometimes adds to the confusion. Flarion, for example, is one of the founders of 802.20 and is conducting trials for Nextel and Vodafone. But the 802.20 standard is far enough away from being complete that Flarion can hardly call its current equipment 802.20-based.  So Flarion and companies like IPWireless are each in their own category. Generally, it's great that the fixed broadband world is getting a lot of attention but companies and journalists have to be more careful about the facts. The space is confusing enough for folks who are just being introduced to it....  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003322.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: 802.11i Security Ratification Coming in June  Ephraim Schwartz reports that 802.11i is expected to be ratified in June: The IEEE 802.11i protocol is the update to 802.11 security that includes all of the interim measures found in WPA (Wi-Fi Protected Access), and also adds a longer, strong encryption key using AES and fast handoff through quick reauthentication among access points. AES has higher computational requirements, and Schwartz points out that some devices will need replacement. WPA was a stop-gap based on work in progress in 802.11i, and issued by the Wi-Fi Alliance in an attempt to make older equipment backwards compatible. The elements found in WPA didn't require circuits other than those used for the older, broken WEP encryption standard. If you hunt, you can find firmware updates for almost all 802.11b devices ever produced. What Schwartz doesn't mention, though, is that virtually all Wi-Fi chips shipped since the end of 2002 (including virtually all 802.11g chips) contain the processing core and other elements necessary to handle AES. They just need firmware upgrades. Schwartz talked to several major vendors, who pointed out their timeframes and upgrade plans, but he omitted chipmakers like Broadcom, Atheros, GlobeSpanVirata, and other consumer/enterprise OEM vendors who would have told him that AES is baked in and just ready for ratification to activate. The Wi-Fi Alliance has said that it will certify 802.11i under the name WPA2. Schwartz also notes the 802.11e's improvements in throughput and resource management for bandwidth won't be finalized until the end of this year. The Wi-Fi Alliance will certify the throughput (Wireless Multimedia Extensions) portion of 802.11e before the full standard ratification, he reports....  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003320.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Tiny robot walker made from DNA  Scientists have created a microscopic walking robot using only the building blocks of life: DNA.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/science/nature/3690115.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Sun Microsystems: The Sun Java Desktop System, Release 2 Arrives  "Today, Sun releases Java Desktop System, Release 2, the next version of Sun's affordable, comprehensive, and secure enterprise-class desktop solution..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-04-022-26-NW-DT-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: The Cloud Allows SIM Authentication  The Cloud customers can now get authenticated using SIM cards: Transat Technologies enables the service. SIM-based authentication is already being used by some hotspots in Europe and is expected to be a widely used authentication method there. Because Europeans use GSM for their cell phone technologies, they are already used to the concept of the SIM card. They can use the same SIM card for their cell phones and for hotspot authentication, which also means they could receive a single bill for both services. Some of the early SIM-based WLAN authentication solutions are pretty rudimentary. They involve the user sending a message from their cell phone to get a code that allows them to access the WLAN. But the more sophisticated solutions include a SIM card reader on a laptop. The SIM card authenticates the user but also applies encryption and security to the communication between the client and the network. That is likely the offering Transat is delivering for The Cloud. At the CTIA Wireless I.T. show last fall I talked to a handful of companies that are touting SIM-based authentication tools, including some of the big SIM card makers. While they're looking for a U.S. market, most weren't terribly bullish that the authentication method would take off here because people aren't widely used to the concept of using SIM cards. Even GSM users in the U.S. don't often realize that they have a SIM card....  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003305.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New York Times: Technology: U.S. Is Losing Its Dominance in the Sciences  Foreign advances in basic science now often rival or even exceed America's, according to federal and private experts.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/05/03/science/03RESE.html?ex=1398916800&amp;en=f37a1c973069b2a8&amp;ei=5007&amp;partner=USERLAND  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Intel's Next-Gen Wi-Fi Debuts Next Week  It's quite a bit late, but it's still coming to the party with all of the cash it can carry: Dothan and Sonoma arrive on May 10: Intel's next-generation Centrino system, which uses the processor dubbed Dothan and a system known as Sonoma, will be unveiled May 10. The system includes the updated Wi-Fi mini-PCI module, the Intel Pro/Wireless 2200BG, which supports 802.11g, and by implicit extension, 802.11b. Intel has the 2100A, which is an a/b module, but no a/g module. This internetnews.com article indicates that Dothan's smaller chip process increase power consumption and thus Intel can't spike performance without killing battery life, a big no-no after the huge improvements found in Centrino, which can stretch an included battery to four to six hours, or two to three times the normal life found in pre-Centrino models. A year ago, when Centrino debuted, Intel received a drubbing for shipping 802.11b with it instead of looking to the future. They've had many delays in getting Sonoma to the market, which has pushed their 802.11g availability back at least six months from what was envisioned a year ago. But, still, the public associates Centrino with Wi-Fi, and thus Intel's goal was achieved. Never mind that Broadcom has shipped most of the consumer cards and gateways, and that it scored deals with laptop makers that have a lock-in of several years because of corporate sales that don't allow for mid-stream component changes....  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003301.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Green Hills: Linux Security Controversy, Part III  Not only is Linux unfit for defense operations, Dan O'Dowd cries, but there's no way to get it fit either. Part III of O'Dowd's infamous white paper series.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-03-024-26-OP-DV-PB  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: internetnews: Big Blue Aiming 'Stinger' at Oracle, Microsoft  "Following months of previews and testing, IBM released in open beta the most complete version of its next-generation Stinger database software Monday..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-03-021-26-NW-HE-SV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scobleizer: Microsoft Geek Blogger: Gates tells CEOs to blog   On a day when Bill Gates tells his CEO friends that blogs and RSS are cool, it seems appropriate to link to Dare Obasanjo&apos;s " urlLink history of blogging at Microsoft " post.  urlLink Joshua Allen  deserves the credit for being the first Microsoft blogger. He took a lot of hard knocks changing Microsoft&apos;s culture. Now it&apos;s popular to blog at Microsoft (and approved by our top execs). Three years ago that wasn&apos;t true at all. It&apos;s funny, I remember telling Joshua he was "the face of evil" -- it&apos;s interesting how tables have turned. Thanks Joshua!   Here&apos;s the relevant links about Gates talk today:   Mary Jo Foley:  urlLink Gates pushes &apos;power to the people&apos; message .  Reuters:  urlLink Microsoft&apos;s Gates touts blogging as business tool .   urlLink Transcript and slides from Gates speech today  (look for the Channel9 slide!) Guardian:  urlLink It&apos;s the human touch that slicker official communications can&apos;t match .  Seattle PI:  urlLink Gates touts the merits of blogs in speech to CEOs    Oh, and BillG: when you gonna blog?   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://radio.weblogs.com/0001011/2004/05/20.html#a7493  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scobleizer: Microsoft Geek Blogger: The real RSS debates   Over the past few months I&apos;ve covered the fight between RSS 2.0 and Atom for the hearts and minds of developers.   I&apos;ve totally been missing the boat.   There are several other far more serious fights coming in the syndication space. Here&apos;s the fights that are coming:   1)  Full text, or just a small synopsis, in the "description" tag?  Why is there a debate about this? Because some webloggers and content generators believe that readers will only visit their site if they don&apos;t put the full content in their feeds.   2)  Designers vs. Readers.  Some designers (and content producers) believe that they should force readers to view their content with the font that the designer picks, color scheme that the designer picks, along with branding (er, logos) and color/blinking advertisments.  urlLink Conrad Agramont&apos;s feed , for instance, uses a different font from most of the other feeds I read.   3)  What to call it?  Some people don&apos;t like the name RSS. Others don&apos;t like the name Atom. Even Google is having trouble settling on one. Evan Williams today said Atom +is+ RSS. Hmmm. More confusion ahead. Other developers want to call it something else.   4)  What to do with the XML orange icons.  Some developers believe it&apos;s confusing when you click on an XML icon and get a bunch of XML code. So  urlLink they  want to put up a pretty HTML page that&apos;ll explain what RSS is.   So, what&apos;s my opinion?   On the first, you should ALWAYS include full text in the feed. Why? Because you&apos;ll get far less traffic if bloggers don&apos;t read you and don&apos;t link to you. We can send a ton of Google traffic your way (three links from "A list" bloggers  will guarantee you first page appearances). The feed that does it worst? Microsoft&apos;s own Slate. I unsubscribed and will never visit their HTML (and, you never see me link to them, do you?)   On the second, feed producers should ALWAYS leave the reader in control. Please, no special fonts, no special colored backgrounds, no CSS, no branding. Thank you. Why? It&apos;s easier to read. Imagine if the New York Times put a different font on each article.   On the third, this would take care of itself if news aggregators had the ability to automatically sense whether or not there&apos;s a feed and present the choices to me in some sort of UI.   On the fourth, I hate it when webloggers don&apos;t have their syndication feeds as an XML icon. The XML icon is easy to find, and its behavior is easy to learn. NewsGator lets me right-click on any XML icon and choose "subscribe."   But, I know these points will cause violent disagreements. So, let me have it! What do you think?   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://radio.weblogs.com/0001011/2004/05/20.html#a7497  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxInsider: Linux Thinks Big  "How do you introduce a mainframe to the world of modern IT? According to IBM, you run Linux on it..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-19-014-26-NW-HE-SV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet: Embracing the Art of Hacking.  Wired News:  urlLink Embracing the Art of Hacking.   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.wired.com/news/infostructure/0,1377,63506,00.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Fedora Core Advisories: tcpdump, cvs, kdepim, neon, subversion, kdelibs, ipsec-tools  Security advisories for Fedora Core 1 and 2.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-20-010-26-SC-RH  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Wi-Fi Paranoia Too High?  David Pogue wonders if the concern about Wi-Fi security is at too high a pitch for home users: Pogue's email column, archived online, this week questions whether there's too much focus on security. Now, I'm the first to agree with him that people with home wireless networks that aren't near neighbors have nothing to fear. Even if you have near neighbors, enabling WEP or WPA, as Pogue recommends, lowers your risk from low to nil. (WEP's key weakness that enables a cracker to break a key and access a network could require weeks of network monitoring to extract enough data to carry that out. It's only a quick crack on high-usage business Wi-Fi networks.) But Pogue doesn't separate out different risk scenarios. My colleague and co-author on The Wireless Networking Starter Kit, Adam Engst, wrote an excellent essay on how to decide the level of exposure you have and how to mitigate it which parallels Pogue on the home networking side, but is more granular on risks outside the home network. Pogue opens his piece talking about public Wi-Fi: "It's just so glorious to be standing in an airport, hotel lobby or city street, open your laptop, and discover that you can go online at cable-modem speeds without hooking up a single cable." But the rest of his column focuses on home networking risks where I generally agree with his take and his recommendations. Out in the wild, the risks are quite high that someone could be monitoring an open free or fee-based Wi-Fi hotspot network -- it's probably 1,000 to 10,000 times more likely that someone is using software to monitor a hotspot than a home network. I have a piece of software that I can run that automatically captures all passwords passing over any network connection, Wi-Fi or otherwise, that requires me to press a single keystroke to activate. You should never conduct unsecured transactions over public hotspots using FTP, email,  or the Web for this reason: it requires no effort to capture those passwords, and people may capture them idly. At the very least, your email password should be secured via APOP (authenticated POP), which creates a one-time use token for access. Your email would still pass in the clear, but your password would be protected. Better, try to use SSL for email (POP and SMTP), or read your email with a Web browser using an SSL...  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003357.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxDevices: Munich/MIT Survey: The Development of Embedded Linux  "Unlike commercial surveys from market research companies and analysts interested in how and where embedded Linux is used, or vendor market shares and revenues, this survey aimed to discover how the embedded Linux development process actually works..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-20-004-26-OS-EM-MR  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: Writing Scalable Applications with PHP  A follow-up to April's print article, &quot;Real-World PHP Security&quot;.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7593  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Times of India : Infotech: Health-Science : New evidence of an expanding universe   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/cms.dll/html/uncomp//articleshow/686464.cms  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Fedora Core Advisories: mailman, neon, cvs, kdelibs  Four security advisories from the Fedora Project.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-19-019-26-SC-RH-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yahoo! News - Technology: Mozilla Open-Source Browser Suite Reaches RC2 (TechWeb)  TechWeb - Among the changes made since RC1 debuted in April are the ability to fine-tune the browser&#039;s pop-up ad blocker, support for Secure Password Authentication within the e-mail client, and reworked cookie dialogs.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/tech/*http://story.news.yahoo.com/news?tmpl=story2&amp;u=/cmp/20040519/tc_cmp/20600121  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: informIT: User-Level Memory Management in Linux Programming  "Because dynamically allocated memory is such a basic building block for real-world programs, we cover it early, before looking at everything else there is to do..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-19-006-26-OS-HL-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxDevices: ARM Unveils Multi-Processor Core with Linux SMP Support  "ARM Ltd. will unveil a unique multi-processor core technology, capable of up to 4-way cache coherent symmetric multi-processing (SMP) running Linux..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-19-008-26-NW-EM-HW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Times of India : Infotech: Chip flaws decline: IBM   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/cms.dll/html/uncomp//articleshow/673964.cms  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Boing Boing: Read this and understand the P2P wars  Timothy Wu is a law prof at the University of Virginia, and a very clever copyright reformer to boot. When Timothy and I last met, he was called Timmy, and we were both students at ALP, the hippie alternative school in Toronto that we both attended until grade eight. One of the weirdest coincidences in my life to date is that  two  alumni of a tiny school in Toronto would both end up moving to the US to pursue something as obscure as copyright reform. Back to Tim(my)! His latest paper, "Copyright's Communications Policy," has me absolutely floored. Tim traces the history of copyright law, the way that we've spent a century undergoing a once-a-decade copyfight, in which representatives of inventors faced down representatives of artists and duked it out in the courts and Congress.  The parallels to today's fights are downright spooky. For example, the first music pirates (the recording industry, who ripped off sheet music) got this proper dressing-down from John Phillip  Sousa , who told Congress: These talking machines are going to ruin the artistic development of music in this country. When I was a boy...in front of every house in the summer evenings, you would find young people together singing the songs of the day or old songs. Today you hear these  infernal machines going night and day. We will not have a vocal chord left. The vocal chord will be eliminated by a process of evolution, as was the tail of man when he came from the ape. I mean, I though Jack Valenti's  urlLink Boston Strangler  testimony was over the top, but clearly, Jack took his cues from Sousa et al. Thirty-odd years later, the another group of pirates -- radio broadcasters, who refused to pay royalties for the music they file-shared over the airwaves -- violated Godwin's Law  decades before it was formulated ,  comparing the entrenched rights societies that served the recording industry (the pirates of their boyhoods) to Adolph Hitler. Tim runs down the history of cable versus broadcasters, and other copyfights down through the ages. He does so clearly and engagingly, in ways that non-lawyers and non-historians can readily grasp. And when it's done, the most amazing thing is the certainty that copryight-disrupting technologies every bit as wooly as file-sharing have been invented over and over again, and that the P2P fight is not a  new one -- that piracy is the  norm , not the exception. If you want to understand the P2P fight, read this -- it is the most concise, thorough and engaging text on the subject to date. urlLink 560k PDF Link   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.boingboing.net/2004/05/15/read_this_and_unders.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: The Official Samba-3 HOWTO and Reference Guide  A valuable resource for advanced users looking to deploy Samba in a production environment.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7113  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux Exposed: Understanding and Attacking DNS  "Securing the trust relationship and building a reliable server can create a reliable and secure DNS structure for the system administrator behind your corporate and private communication requirements..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-14-004-26-OS-SW-NT  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxInsider: Asian Governments Start to Speak the Same Language on Linux Implementations  "Could Asia become a Linux stronghold? It's positioning itself to become one, as governments here try to limit their dependence on the Windows operating system..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-14-007-26-NW-BZ-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: LinuxWorld: "Thunder"--N. America's Fastest Linux Supercomputer  "A Linux cluster deployed at Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory and codenamed 'Thunder' yesterday delivered 19.94 teraflops of sustained performance, making it the most powerful computer in North America..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-14-006-26-NW-HE-SV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Private spaceship almost in space  A privately-built manned spacecraft has reached a record altitude of 64km on one of its last tests.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/science/nature/3713119.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: Linux on the Mainframe  A must-have reference for those implementing Linux in a mainframe environment.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7074  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wi-Fi Networking News: Caught on Camera: Sensational Security Flaws  A Denver TV station demonstrates the insecurity of wireless networks at the Denver Airport: A reporter and a security analyst sat nearby a hotspot user and were able to steal his email. They approach the user and tell him that anyone could do the same. The story says that the reporters got his cell phone number, social security number, and Visa card number. We're curious about why he was sending that information in an email. The story is typically sensational for a local news station but the point is made--users should make sure they have a secure connection like a VPN if they're sending that kind of information. If such security measures aren't available to them, they shouldn't send that information....  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://wifinetnews.com/archives/003340.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: ipfilter on GNU/Linux: Is It Finally Here?  ipfilter now is available for GNU/Linux, but it's not quite ready to replace your current firewall setup.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7595  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux Journal: Scripting GNU in the 21st Century  "Most people tend to encounter shell scripts as attempts to write portable utilities that run properly on most, if not all, UNIX workalikes..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-28-008-26-OS-HL-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: internetnews.com: A New Cocoon from Apache  "The Apache Foundation released the latest version of its largest Java based project this week, an XML publishing framework known as Cocoon..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-28-026-26-NW-SV-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: IT-Analysis: IBM's Linux Push  "Since then IBM has made the transformation to become a Linux company, (in so far as any vendor can). All but two of IBM's cross platform software products now run on Linux..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-28-024-26-OP-BZ-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: PC World: Hard-Core Fedora  "More on moving to Fedora Core and making it work for you. Also, a new distribution and another desktop environment..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-29-007-26-RV-RH-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: internetnews.com: Novell's Big Linux Year  "A year after launching its Linux support with Netware 7 and six months after acquiring SUSE Linux, networking software maker Novell is seeing the fruits of its strategy pan out..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-26-021-26-NW-BZ-NV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: HelpNetSecurity: Security in an ERP World  "Every good hacker story ends with the line: 'and then he's got root access to your network and can do whatever he wants.' But the story really doesn't end there. This is just the beginning of the real damage that the hacker can inflict..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-26-007-26-OS-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: cat /dev/DiBona/brain: Spreading the Wealth and Walking the Walk  If you care about more people using Linux, put it in their hands.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7597  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet: IBM Opteron Intellistations arrive Friday.  The Inquirer:  urlLink IBM Opteron Intellistations arrive Friday.  And you can even get Linux preinstalled on them.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=16151  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet: VoIP goes Mobile.  TheFeature:  urlLink VoIP goes Mobile.  "[The MG-3 is] a little plastic box stuffed with microchips, which you plug into your broadband connection and existing phone line. Then, when you want to make a long distance call with your mobile, you just call your home number. The MG-3 will recognize the mobile&#146;s number using Caller ID, and connect you to i2 Telecom&#146;s VoIP network. You get a second dial tone, and you can make your overseas call." So to get cheap long distance you need a cell phone, a regular phone line, and broadband? Sounds like a way to go broke saving money.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.thefeature.com/article?articleid=100667  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet: IBM Opteron Intellistations arrive Friday.  The Inquirer:  urlLink IBM Opteron Intellistations arrive Friday.  And you can even get Linux preinstalled on them.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.theinquirer.net/?article=16151  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Boing Boing: Hardening an httpd for the rapture  RaptureReady is a site devoted to getting ready for the end-times: this is from the FAQ: How do you plan to maintain this site after the rapture? I have no master plan for maintaining Rapture Ready all the way through the seven-year tribulation. After the big event takes place, I expect RR to last several months. After all, the internet was designed to survive a nuclear war. It should be able to survive the great catching up of all believers.   urlLink Link ( Thanks,  urlLink Harley ! )  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.boingboing.net/2004/05/23/hardening_an_httpd_f.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: The Register: Microsoft Loses Lindows Appeal  "Microsoft has been refused permission to appeal its case against Lindows..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-24-011-26-NW-MS-LL  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: The Inquirer: L OS Releases 64 bit Linux  "The company says it has taken three years more than 1500 Linux programmers and developers and 37 key hardware manufacturers and researchers to write L OS..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-24-006-26-NW-HE-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yahoo! News - Technology: Boeing&#039;s 7E7 to Tout Technology Advances (AP)  AP - The first new American commercial jetliner to be built in more than a decade won&#039;t be the biggest or fastest passenger plane in the sky.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/tech/*http://story.news.yahoo.com/news?tmpl=story2&amp;u=/ap/20040521/ap_on_hi_te/boeing_s_new_plane  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet   urlLink Peter Biddle's NGSCB/Palladium Update from WinHEC (PowerPoint)  shows how Microsoft's thinking on trusted computing has evolved in the last year.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://download.microsoft.com/download/1/8/f/18f8cee2-0b64-41f2-893d-a6f2295b40c8/TW04008_WINHEC2004.ppt  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Journal: Reducing OS Boot Times for In-Car Computer Applications, Part II  Part II breaks down the boot process into nine steps and analyzes the time cost involved in each.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=7594  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linuxlookup.com: Fedora Core 2 Review  "Having played around with SuSE 9.1, Arch .6 and Slackware 9 with the 2.6 kernel, I was interested in seeing how the Fedora team did with this release..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-24-004-26-RV-RH-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Flexbeta: Suse Linux 9.1 Professional Desktop Review  "This review covers the latest release of Suse's Professional Linux Operating System, version 9.1. This release marks an interesting development in the battle for distribution dominance..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-24-005-26-RV-SW-SS  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linus Torvalds: Linux 2.6.7-rc1  Changelog, links within.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-24-009-26-NW-KN-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scobleizer: Microsoft Geek Blogger: A view of Microsoft's blogs from the China office   One of the frustrations working in a big company is if you aren't working at the headquarters you don't feel like you're really part of the company.   I felt that when I was an employee of NEC (about 115,000 employees). I didn't even know who the CEO was.   But blogging is changing this in a big way. But in an unexpected way too.   It also lets those of us at the headquarters see what's happening out in other offices. For instance, Jian Shuo Wang is a Microsoft employee in Shanghai, China.  urlLink Today he writes about how he sees Microsoft's bloggers .   Blogs are letting us build relationships that are pretty deep. Now, if I ever have a question about the Chinese market, I know just who to ask. And, I bet that Jian Shuo knows a few more of us back at headquarters to ask when he has a question.   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://radio.weblogs.com/0001011/2004/05/23.html#a7577  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: Surfing speed gets hardware help  Special hardware can help firms overcome some of the internet's speed limits.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/technology/3736893.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: EU 'confident' of star power site  Europe's research boss says the EU is still confident that France will host the largest fusion reactor in the world.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/science/nature/3735017.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       BBC News | Technology | World Edition: CCTV goes wi-fi to fight crime  Wireless CCTV cameras are being tested in London to see if the technology can help fight crime.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/click/rss/0.91/public/-/2/hi/technology/3726335.stm  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scobleizer: Microsoft Geek Blogger: Ballmer says Microsoft must work harder   Haaretz.com:  urlLink Steve Ballmer, in Israel, says Microsoft must work harder .   Damn, does that mean no more Xbox Live on Saturday nights? :-)   The article gives quotes from SteveB on topics from Google to source code leaks.   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://radio.weblogs.com/0001011/2004/05/22.html#a7540  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yahoo! News - Technology: Microsoft Tech Ed 2004 Overview (Ziff Davis)  Ziff Davis - Microsoft&#039;s annual Tech Ed 2004 conference opens Monday in San Diego, and offers practical information for enterprise developers, software architects and network managers. Here&#039;s a look at the show.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/tech/*http://story.news.yahoo.com/news?tmpl=story2&amp;u=/zd/20040521/tc_zd/127857  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet   urlLink VLC 0.7.2  claims to support H.264. I wonder if there's any other software out there to interop against.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.videolan.org/vlc/  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hack the Planet: Chelsio Debuts 10-GigE HBA.  Byte and Switch:  urlLink Chelsio Debuts 10-GigE HBA.  With three TOE announcements in three weeks, I wonder if there's another boom-bust cycle coming.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.byteandswitch.com/document.asp?doc_id=53224  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Boing Boing: Dumb tech-support explanations  Great open-mic question on Ask Slashdot: what's the worst bullishit "explanation" you've ever gotten from tech support? My cable modem connection had stopped work. Given my ISPs track record, this was unremarkable, but after it continued for 2 days, I decided to call the tech support number. After supplying my ID number, the support person told me that my connection was intentionally shut off because I was broadcasting a widely-circulated Windows virus. I promptly informed the tech support person that I did not use the Windows operating system on any of my computers, and that I could not possibly have the virus I was accused of having. The support rep immediately told me that I had the virus, and that they would not turn my connection back on until I jumped through their anti-virus hoops. I argued for almost 10 minutes with this neophyte that I could not use their Windows anti-virus on my Linux systems, and that even if I could, it would not do a damn bit of good. Did it matter? Of course not. Finally, in order to get my connection back on, I agreed to perform their anti-virus tricks "to the best of my ability", and install Windows just so I could "remove the virus" from my system. The rep actually thought this was an excellent resolution to the problem, but for some reason didn't believe I would actually do it (could have been my vehement renouncements against the entirety of Microsoft's products). After another 5 minutes of cajoling, I convinced her to turn my connection back on so I could get the anti-virus tools, and access Windows Update.  urlLink Link   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://www.boingboing.net/2004/05/21/dumb_techsupport_exp.html  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scobleizer: Microsoft Geek Blogger: Gates tells CEOs to blog   On a day when Bill Gates tells his CEO friends that blogs and RSS are cool, it seems appropriate to link to Dare Obasanjo's " urlLink history of blogging at Microsoft " post.  urlLink Joshua Allen  deserves the credit for being the first Microsoft blogger. He took a lot of hard knocks changing Microsoft's culture. Now it's popular to blog at Microsoft (and approved by our top execs). Three years ago that wasn't true at all. It's funny, I remember telling Joshua he was "the face of evil" -- it's interesting how tables have turned. Thanks Joshua!   Here's the relevant links about Gates talk today:   Mary Jo Foley:  urlLink Gates pushes 'power to the people' message .  Reuters:  urlLink Microsoft's Gates touts blogging as business tool .   urlLink Transcript and slides from Gates speech today  (look for the Channel9 slide!) Guardian:  urlLink It's the human touch that slicker official communications can't match .   Oh, and BillG: when you gonna blog?   urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://radio.weblogs.com/0001011/2004/05/20.html#a7493  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Linux Journal: Writing Scalable Applications with PHP  "This article takes you, the professional PHP developer, one step further, by providing detailed explanations and reliable source code that illustrate the steps to follow in order to develop successful PHP applications..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-21-012-26-OS-HL-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: PC Pro: Sun Java Desktop System [Review]  "...Sun's Java Desktop System (JDS) is an all-in-one product at a knock-down price..."  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-21-004-26-RV-DT-SW  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Linux Today: Tanenbaum: Some Notes on the "Who Wrote Linux" Kerfuffle, Release 1.1  The author of Minix asserts his position on who wrote Linux and delivers a revealing look inside his interview conducted by AdTI's Ken Brown.  urlLink Read Complete Article   urlLink http://linuxtoday.com/news_story.php3?ltsn=2004-05-20-013-26-OS-CY-DV  ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- You can manage your account by logging into  urlLink http://rss.blogstreet.com 
     
    
</post>


<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Air Combat Information Group Forums - Forum Index 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Russian Avionics 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Su-30MKI Complete Info - Vayu Sena 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Project Vetrivale [www.bharat-rakshak.com] 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Indian Weapons 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Aircraft Specifications - Bharatiya Vayu Sena 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Ballistic Missile Defences   HOME  >IAF TODAY >BALLISTIC MISSILE DEFENCES IN INDIA   THE IAF TODAY  Ballistic Missile Defence for India  By Dr. Sanjay Badri-Maharaj  --------------------------------- One of the best articles I have read on internet about Ballistic missile defence for India  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Indian Air Force [Active Aircraft] 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BrahMos - Advantages   Long flight range with supersonic speed all through the flight   Shorter flight times leading to lower target dispersion and quicker engagement   Varieties of flight trajectories   ‘Fire and forget’ principle of operation   Higher destructive capability aided by the large kinetic energy of impact   Higher effectiveness against ship defences   Canister for transportation, storage and launch      Superiority of the BRAHMOS Supersonic Anti-ship Missile over a Subsonic Long Range Anti-ship Missile    In Velocity   by 3 times  In flight range   by 2.5 - 3 times  In seeker range   by 3 - 4 times    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BrahMos - Missile and Technology   BRAHMOS is a Supersonic Cruise Missile that can be launched from submarine, ship, aircraft and land based Mobile Autonomous Launchers (MAL). The missile is launched from a Transport-Launch Canister (TLC), which also acts as storage and transportation container.   Primarily BRAHMOS is an anti-ship missile. It has the capability to engage land based targets also. The missile can be launched either in vertical or inclined position and will cover 360 degrees.  The BRAHMOS missile has identical configuration for land, sea and sub sea platforms. The air-launched version has a smaller booster and additional tail fins for stability during launch.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Venik's Aviation - Plasma Stealth    Plasma stealth technology  Last updated: January 10, 2004    Many aviation enthusiasts have heard about the so-called "plasma stealth": using ionized gas to reduce the radar cross section of an aircraft. Some consider this to be science fiction - a Romulan cloaking shield. However, sarcastic remarks aside, "plasma stealth" is quite real. At least in theory. Interactions between EM radiation and ionized gas have been extensively studied for a variety of purposes ranging from radio communications to astrophysics.   Plasma is a highly complex topic with many unanswered fundamental questions. Nevertheless, a plasma stealth device for combat aircraft has been offered for export by Russia in 1999. While the theoretical possibility of reducing an aircraft's RCS by wrapping the airframe in ionized gas flow is not in question, the technological aspects of such methods represent considerable interest. How is it done? There are many possibilities running from "simple" electrostatic discharges to complex and power-hungry plasma lasers. The following collection of resources is unlikely to answer specific technical question, but it may provide you with a push in the right direction.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Project 75 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Advanced Technology Vessel 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Shishumar {HDW 209} Class 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Sindhugosh {Kilo} Class  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink LAND-BASED BALLISTIC MISSILES 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink T-90S Main Battle Tank 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Armoured Vehicles 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Army ORBAT 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Kargil War 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Tu-22M BACKFIRE (TUPOLEV) - Russian and Soviet Nuclear Forces 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Air Force Technology - Tu-160 Blackjack - Strategic Bomber 
     
    
</post>


<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Technology Review: Ethanol Yields Hydrogen   Ethanol Yields Hydrogen  Technology Research News  March 8, 2004  Fuel cells that convert the chemical bonds between hydrogen atoms to energy are about three times more efficient than combustion engines that burn hydrocarbons. And fuel cells powered with pure hydrogen carry out the conversion cleanly.   The trick is finding a cost-effective way to produce hydrogen without polluting the environment.  Researchers from the University of Minnesota and the University of Patras in Greece have devised a way to extract hydrogen directly from ethanol, which would make for a renewable energy cycle. Ethanol is produced by converting biomass like cornstarch to sugar, then fermenting it.  The researchers' method is relatively simple, and an ethanol-to-hydrogen converter designed for home use would be not much larger than a coffee mug.  Ethanol is fairly flammable, and the process of extracting hydrogen from ethanol destroys the catalyst traditionally used to extract hydrogen from hydrocarbons like oil.  The researchers solved the flammability problem by using an automotive fuel injector to vaporize a mix of ethanol, water and air so quickly that there's no time for flames to start. They solved the catalyst problem accidentally, by trying rhodium-ceria rather than the plain rhodium used to extract hydrogen from fuels like natural gas and diesel.  The method is ready for use now, according to the researchers. The cost of ethanol is currently about fifty percent more than gasoline. Eventually wood chips, grass clippings or crop wastes could be used to make lower-cost ethanol.  The work appeared in the February 13, 2004 issue of Science.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Technology Review: Material Boosts Thermoelectricity   Material Boosts Thermoelectricity  Technology Research News  April 5, 2004  Scientists have been searching for decades for more efficient ways to convert heat to electricity. Thermoelectric materials generate electricity when heated and turn cold in the presence of electrical current.   The measure of success for converting materials is the ZT factor, a formula that includes thermal power, electrical conductivity, thermal conductivity and temperature. A ZT factor over three would make thermoelectric power generation competitive with home refrigerators and power generators. Forty years ago the best ZT factor in existence was 0.6. After four decades of research, it stood at one.  Researchers from Michigan State University, the University of Michigan at Ann Arbor, and Aristotle University of Thessaloniki in Greece have discovered a new family of thermoelectric semiconductor materials that raises the bar considerably. The researchers' material has a ZT factor of 2.2 at 527 degrees Celsius, which may be high enough for practical electricity generation.  The high temperature rules out refrigeration applications, however.  The researchers' material is a mix of silver, lead, antimony and tellurium. One of the keys to its utility is very tiny areas, or nano dots, where the crystal structure of the material is rich in silver and antimony and surrounded by a silver-antimony-poor region.  There is evidence that the material could be further improved, according to the researchers. The work appeared in the February 5, 2004 issue of Science.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Solar Neutrinos   Solar Neutrinos: @    April 20th 2002, 1:20 pm Eastern Daylight Time  Sensitive measurement by SNO observes solar neutrinos in a new way Sudbury Neutrino Observatory Collaboration to announce first scientific results Monday 18. June, 2001 Group members:  Richard L. Hahn Minfang Yeh J. Keith Rowley (retired) Zheng Chang   Neutrino studies currently are a very hot topic in science. Why? Because there are strong indications from several experiments that the neutrino has new properties, such as non-zero rest mass (so-called "New Physics") that are not included in standard theories of elementary particles. Theory may have to be recast to explain the experimental results.  Neutrinos and the sun.  The neutrino was proposed by Wolfgang Pauli in 1930, but it took 26 more years before the neutrino was actually discovered (detected). Pauli proposed the existence of the neutrino as a solution to a frustrating problem in nuclear beta-decay that was studied in the laboratory, namely  that examination of the reaction products always indicated that a variable amount of energy was missing. Pauli concluded that the products must include a third “almost invisible” particle, one which didn't interact strongly enough for it to be detected. Enrico Fermi called this particle the “neutrino” (for the "little neutral one"). In 1956 Reines and Cowan discovered the neutrino interactions in their experiments at a nuclear reactor (Reines was jointly awarded the Nobel Prize in physics in 1995).  Today, neutrinos are known to be tiny, possibly massless, neutral elementary particles, which interact with matter via the weak nuclear force. The weakness of the weak force gives neutrinos the property that matter is almost transparent to them. It is fascinating that the neutrino, which was “invented” to solve a laboratory nuclear physics problem, must also be invoked to explain energy production in our sun and in all other stars. We now know that nuclear fusion and decay processes, which occur within the stellar core, produce copious amounts of neutrinos. As shown in the figure, the standard solar model predicts that these reactions produce several groups of neutrinos, with differing fluxes and energy spectra. The figure also shows the ranges of detection of existing solar neutrino experiments in different shades of blue, to illustrate that they sample different portions of the solar neutrino energy spectrum. Three of these experiments, plus a new one, are discussed below.  Since neutrinos rarely interact with matter, they pass through the sun and the earth (and us) virtually unhindered. Other sources of neutrinos include exploding stars (supernovae), relic neutrinos (from the birth of the universe) and nuclear power plants. For example, the sun produces over two hundred trillion trillion trillion neutrinos every second, and a supernova blast can unleash 1000 times more neutrinos than our sun will produce in its 10-billion year lifetime. About 65-billion neutrinos from the sun stream through every square centimeter on the Earth every second, yet we are oblivious to their passage in our every-day lives.  BNL and Measurements of Solar Neutrinos.  Radiochemical Neutrino Detectors          The field of solar neutrino research had its birth in the BNL Chemistry Department, where Raymond Davis and colleagues developed a radiochemical method to separate and detect the few radioactive atoms formed by capture of solar neutrinos in a huge target. This first solar neutrino experiment, in the Homestake Mine in South Dakota, used the isotope, 37Cl, as the target in 680 tons of an organic liquid, perchloroethylene. Neutrino capture on the 37Cl, with an energy threshold of 0.814 MeV, produces radioactive 37Ar, a gas, which is removed from the target, purified, and counted. The results of this experiment revealed a "solar neutrino problem": The number of measured solar neutrinos was only about one-third of the value predicted from solar theory (note that popular accounts are available on the Web about the development of the field of solar neutrino research).      Another radiochemical neutrino detector was developed at BNL, using 71Ga as the target. Neutrino capture on the 71Ga produces radioactive 71Ge with an renergy threshold of 0.233 MeV. This 71Ge can be  emoved from the liquid target in the form of gaseous GeCl4, chemically purified, and converted to GeH4 gas for counting. Two gallium detectors based on this scheme were constructed and operated. The BNL Solar Neutrino Group participated in GALLEX at the underground Gran Sasso National Laboratory in Italy, where 30 tons of gallium in the form of a 100-ton aqueous solution of gallium trichloride served as the target; SAGE at the Baksan Neutrino Observatory in Russia instead used 57 tons of liquid gallium metal. The results from both gallium experiments confirmed the "deficit" of solar neutrinos, by observing only »60% of the expected neutrino flux. The GALLEX experiment ended in 1998. Subsequently it became the Gallium Neutrino Observatory, GNO, which uses the original GALLEX target. BNL is not a member of GNO.  From these experiments, and the Kamiokande and Super-Kamiokande neutrino detectors in Japan, the consensus has developed in the scientific community that the reason for the observed deficit of solar neutrinos is that the neutrinos “oscillate”. In other words, the electron-flavor neutrinos that are produced in beta-decay processes in nuclear reactions in the solar interior can be transformed into the other two known neutrino flavors, those of the muon-neutrino and the tau-neutrino. These neutrinos are not produced in the sun’s nuclear reactions. In this scenario, the measured solar neutrino flux is artificially low since these other neutrino flavors are not readily observed by most neutrino detectors, and certainly not at all by the radiochemical neutrino detectors. Note that for this process to occur requires that at least one of the neutrino types must have non-zero rest mass. Since the current Standard Electroweak Model carries the assumption of massless neutrinos, proof of the existence of neutrino mass would be a major new discovery, leading to major changes in the theory – what has been dubbed “New Physics”.      “Real-Time” Neutrino Detectors  SNO, the Sudbury Neutrino Observatory                  SNO is a new solar neutrino detector that was  constructed in Canada to search for definitive evidence of this postulated new neutrino physics. BNL joined this collaboration in early 1996. The SNO neutrino detector began taking data in October 1999.  SNO was designed to detect neutrino interactions as they occur in real time with energies > 5 MeV. It is situated in a specially constructed underground clean area, at the 6800-foot level of the Creighton mine, which is operated by INCO, the International Nickel Co., near Sudbury, Ontario. The detector contains 1000 tons of ultra-pure heavy water, D2O, in a 12-meter wide transparent acrylic plastic vessel, surrounded by 7000 tons of ultra-pure light water, H2O, which acts as shielding. The D2O, with a value of about $300 million, is being lent by the Canadian Government. In the H2O, 9600 photomultiplier tubes (PMT’s) surround and view the acrylic vessel, detecting the Cerenkov light produced in the D2O by neutrino interactions and thus measuring the neutrino energy-spectra and fluxes.  Although SNO is not a radiochemical neutrino detector, chemistry still plays a crucially important role in the SNO project. For the detector to function properly, the amounts of radioactive impurities, such as those in the U-238 and Th-232 decay chains, and Rn-222 from the mine air, must be reduced to extraordinarily low levels (e.g., 10-15 gram Th per gram D2O). Other chemical contaminants must also be removed completely, since both the D2O and H2O must be optically transparent to allow the Cerenkov light to reach the PMT’s .  The deuteron in the D2O in SNO makes it unique among neutrino detectors, since it can observe all three neutrino flavors. The electron neutrino is the only flavor that can convert the D into 2 protons + a negative electron. This electron provides the signal for the so-called "charged current" (CC) neutrino reaction. However, all three neutrino flavors are equally effective in breaking apart the D into its constituents, a proton + a neutron. This neutron provides the signal for the "neutral current" (NC) interaction. If SNO were to measure the NC rate to be greater than the CC rate, this would be definitive proof, a "smoking gun", for the existence of neutrino oscillations. The cause of the solar neutrino problem would be the transformation of some of the solar electron neutrinos into the other flavors. The physics community is excited by this prospect for new physics. A spin-off of such a result is that massive neutrinos could account for the "missing mass" that is required for a closed universe.  Preliminary results from sno were presented in June 2000 (SNO at the Neutrino 2000 Conference). The time is fast approaching when SNO will present its first results in an article to be published in the open literature.  LENS, the Low-Energy Neutrino Spectrometer    Many theoretical scenarios of neutrino oscillations predict strong effects at low energies, in the region of    One such detector, Borexino, is being built in Italy with the goal of detecting the main neutrino line from Be-7 line by observing elastic scattering in a liquid scintillator. Note that elastic scattering has contributions from both the charged-current and neutral-current neutrino interactions.  Another concept is LENS, the Low-Energy Neutrino Spectrometer, which has the ambitious aim of doing  real-time spectroscopy of the lowest energy, and most intense, solar neutrinos, those from the pp continuum below 0.42 MeV. The basic idea of LENS is to detect the charged current by neutrino capture in a target with a very low Q-value, such as 176Yb. Since LENS will also be able to detect Be-7 neutrinos, comparison of the signals from LENS and Borexino has the potential to provide definite evidence of Be-7 neutrino oscillations.  The basic neutrino signature in LENS is a delayed coincidence  e + 176Yb --> 176 Lu* + e-                                            æ  176 Lu + g where the occurrence from the same location in the detector of pulses from the electron and the g ray within a time interval of some tens of nanoseconds in principle provides a neutrino-capture tag. This coincidence tag, proposed a long time ago by R. Raghavan, provides an excellent method to overcome the huge natural backgrounds that occur in the 1 MeV energy region .  The design of such an experiment is still under active investigation in the recently formed LENS International Collaboration. The basic idea at present is to use an organic liquid scintillator loaded with Yb to ~ 10% to detect the neutrino signal. Recent progress in LENS R&D has shown that this scintillator can indeed be produced in a stable form suitable for neutrino detection. It is estimated that the LENS detector will require 10-20 tons of natural Yb.  This work is supported by the DOE Office of High Energy and Nuclear Physics.   This page was revised on January 30, 2003 
     
    
</post>


<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink President Kalam's address - The Times of India :   "'I am climbing and climbing, my lord where is the peak of ambition,  I am prodding and prodding, my lord where is the treasure of knowledge, I am sailing and sailing, my lord where is the island of peace, Almighty, bless my nation with sweat, toil and vision,' recited the President, a native of Tamil Nadu and a lover of Tamil poetry."
     
    
</post>


<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Latest News and Financial Information | Reuters.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sun’s mantra for network computing: Big gain, No pain  STANLEY GLANCY / Singapore    Celestine Tan  COMPLEXITY, consolidation, standardisation, scale-up and scale-out were the buzzwords at the Asia South Data Centre and Storage Media Symposium hosted by Sun Microsystems at Singapore. The message was clear: help customers save huge amounts by simplifying their data centres. This involves everything from choosing the right architecture to consolidating storage.   The right architecture for Sun would involve simplifying design and deployment as well as management and operations of the data centre. Aptly, the theme for the event was ‘Big gain, No pain—Investment Protection for the Data Centre.’   What are the typical issues faced by chief information officers and chief technology officers today? “The top issues for customers would be business continuity, security, revenue generation and cost reduction,” says Kaliprasad Naidu, director, Infrastructure Solutions, APAC, Sun Microsystems.   Most companies have already made significant investment in creating IT assets, but due to factors like a large variety of non-standard configurations, upgradation of systems has become a serious problem. Most enterprises are still stuck with the one-server, one-application model.   Elaborates Ken Won, director, Enterprise Systems, Products Group, Sun, “Customers are interested in standardisation and in reducing the number of vendors they work with.” Consolidation and standardisation enable remote monitoring and systems administration. Standardisation also reduces the need for a huge support staff at the back-end. Even application deployment is simplified due to standard configurations and common processes.  These are the very issues Sun has been looking at addressing through its recent innovations. Over the last year the company has launched a series of new products and solutions, all intended to reduce complexity and total cost of ownership (TCO) for the enterprise customer. The effort has mainly been on introducing products that can be integrated for its customers—be it the Java Desktop System, Java Enterprise System, Java Mobility System or the now famous Java Card System. This means that the products should not only work together but that they should also work with standard-based products from other companies. Incidentally, Sun is among the top 15 global companies when it comes to investing in R&D. According to Celestine Tan, director of marketing, Asia South, the company has spent $1.9 billion in R&D activities.   Sun seems especially aggressive about its recent innovation, chip multi threading (CMT). Throughput computing or CMT is expected to more than double processor performance as it focuses on increasing the amount of work a processor does instead of focusing on clock speed. The company believes the way to do this is by dealing with the memory latency problem. When a thread must wait for memory, the affected core will simply start processing another thread. With a CMT processor there are multiple individual threads of execution. What this means is that when you have more than one thread per processor you can dedicate the threads to individual tasks.   Sun expects to dramatically improve performance by delivering CMT processors. With the release of UltraSPARC IV, the company says it has increased application throughput by at least twice compared to today’s processors. Over the next couple of years, Sun plans to work on introducing radical CMT designs that will provide up to 15 times the application throughput of current processors.   But the company has no plans of stopping at that. Moving beyond 2005, Sun is looking at shipping system processors that will do 30 times as much. This gels perfectly with Sun’s strategy of reduced TCO for the customer while doing away with complexity.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The designs of BITS Pilani - India Computes - Express Computer India   The designs of BITS Pilani  India is seen emerging as a centre for designing, developing and fabricating high-class semiconductor chips, and BITS Pilani is getting ready for that day, says SHIPRA ARORA  BIRLA Institute of Technology & Science (BITS), Pilani ranks among the best engineering institutes in India as far as the talent pool is concerned. Now the institute has also found pride of place among the best in terms of technology infrastructure; it is not only on par with the IITs, but also institutes across the US and Europe. BITS has set up a broadband gigabit network called Neuron as part of BITSConnect, a global movement of BITS Pilani alumni, faculty and students. In a fine example of industry-institute cooperation, BITSConnect has commissioned a $50 million VLSI Lab initiative; the project aims to conduct semiconductor research and development.   VLSI project   The project for the VLSI design lab—called Oysters Lab (OLAB)—is underway, making it the first campus-based VLSI design facility in India. OLAB is a distributed VLSI lab that will connect all BITS campuses (Pilani, Goa and Dubai) with an industrial centre at Bangalore. Around 2,000 sq ft of space has been allocated for the lab at the Pilani campus. The Bangalore Extension Centre is intended to facilitate industry collaboration.   The lab, which is a collaborative effort between stakeholders like BITS, BITS Alumni Association and industry, will boast of some of the best-in-class Electronic Design Automation (EDA) tools. These tools will support Full Design Flow, RTL to GDS, embedded design and board design. It will also house a powerful and scalable compute farm that will be accessible over the Neuron network. A large scalable NAS storage will be accessible over the network. With such advanced computing infrastructure and EDA equipment to provide very large scale integration and embedded design, the lab will rank among the best in the country.   OLAB objectives   The Oysters Lab at BITS will embark on pioneering semiconductor R&D work in the country, and a key objective will be to create intellectual property in the area of VLSI and embedded design. Says Dr S Venkateswaran, vice chancellor, BITS, “OLAB will usher in silicon technology research and a chip development revolution in India.” This quite effectively sums up the thinking behind the VLSI design lab. Rajendra Khare, managing director, Broadcom India points out that the focus areas for research at the lab will be aligned with the research activities at BITS. The institute is presently conducting research in the areas of networking, intelligent transport systems, biochemistry and MEMS, and OLAB will bolster it.   Vinod Agarwal, chairman and chief strategist, LogicVision, feels that there is growing opportunity in the area of semiconductor research with the emergence of a large number of applications which require the designing of complex chips. These include applications in the areas of telecom, wireless (such as mobile phones) and gaming, as well as digital products like TVs, set-top boxes, etc. The aim of this lab will be to develop chips that are meant for Indian applications.   Industry collaboration  Apart from the high commercial value of the project, the high point of the initiative is the strong industry collaboration it has received. This will give a push to promoting India as an R&D destination. Some of the industry participants in the project include OpenSilicon, Broadcom, LogicVision, Magma, Mentor Graphics and Sun Microsystems.   The lab will work closely with industry to draw experts. It is believed that someone will be appointed from the industry itself to spearhead the lab. With this, industry will be able to conduct sponsored research at Pilani. It has also been projected as an extension of BITS Pilani, a virtual university that will promote active industry collaboration with a special focus on flexible education for working industry professionals. Initiatives and collaborations on such a large scale are very common among universities abroad but are very rare in India.   The backbone making it possible  The OLAB initiative comes close on the heels of the setting up of a broadband network. The first project undertaken as part of the BITSConnect movement, Neuron provides the essential infrastructure not for only running the lab but also providing high-end connectivity across the institute’s different campuses. Neuron is a gigabit backbone providing broadband access, IP telephony, streaming media and video conferencing facilities in student rooms, hostels, staff quarters and guest houses; it also provides 802.11b wireless access in the campus. The network connects all BITS campuses across Pilani, Goa and Dubai, making it one of the most technologically-advanced networked campuses globally. As part of the project, Cisco has deployed over 240 IP phones. The 3-tier network architecture consists of core, distribution and access layers. Long Range Ethernet and wireless access is available at select areas like the hostel, cafeteria and library. This whole project has been implemented by Wipro.   Impact   The network will have a positive impact on both teaching and research work at BITS. “This fresh infrastructure will enable the BITS Distance Learning Programme Division (DLPD) to offer media-rich content to over 7,500 students. We can now look forward to a successful expansion of the virtual university concept allowing students, faculty and organisations to collaborate with no geographical and time-zone constraints,” says Venkateswaran.   Apart from the distributed VLSI lab, the institute’s virtual university will ride on this network. BITS’ research in the areas of IPv6, and its Multimedia Operating System and Ubiquitous Computing Research initiatives, will also get a fillip with this new development. On the learning front, the institute will have complete online courseware along with hybrid delivery of on-campus education. Neuron enables students to have 24/7 unrestricted access to the Param supercomputer, in addition to the server and application farms running advanced tools like CAD, VLSI, etc. It also allows live video streaming of remote lectures to students’ rooms, interactive real-time multicasting of lectures, as well as advanced education and presentation systems on top of this infrastructure. In terms of distance learning, the initiatives enable BITS to bring more courses and a larger number of students under the ambit of distance education. Though not finalised as yet, the infrastructure might also be leveraged by nearby schools and villages.   Neuron: Technical highlights  Highly redundant 3-tier network architecture consisting of core, distribution and access layers  Wires-up all areas of the campus with more than 20 kms of cable  4,000 voice grade 10/100 access points  Long Range Ethernet and wireless access available at select areas  Cutting-edge network security via latest technologies like SHCP Snooping and Dynamic ARP Inspection  Advanced routing technologies to manage ISP bandwidth across BITS campuses  Video on Demand and scheduled video multicasting  In technical collaboration with Wipro and Cisco      OLAB advantage   Best in class EDA tools supporting full design flow, embedded design and board design  Powerful computing farm which is scalable and accessible over the Neuron network  Commercial value of over $50 million  Focuses on the research areas of networking, ITS, biochemistry and MEMS  Strong industry collaboration and Bangalore extension counter for staying close to the industry  Experts drawn from all over the industry  Sponsored research       Neuron: Impact on teaching  Complete online courseware—hybrid delivery of on-campus education  Students have 24/7 unrestricted access to the Param supercomputer, in addition to various server and application farms running advanced educational tools  Live video streaming of remote lecture rooms  Interactive real-time multicasting of lectures  Enables advanced education and presentation systems on top of this infrastructure      shipra@expresscomputeronline.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Search Engine Rivalry Brings Improvements   Search Engine Rivalry Brings Improvements  1 hour, 45 minutes ago  Add Technology - washingtonpost.com to My Yahoo!     By Leslie Walker   The rivalry between Yahoo and Google escalated last week as the two search engines rolled out improvements to Web-mail and discussion-group services designed to lure users from one service to the other.   Yahoo's big move was to slash prices on its paid Web e-mail service (mail.yahoo.com) by as much as 33 percent: A plan with 25 megabytes of message storage now costs $19 a year, down from $29, and one with 100 megabytes goes for $49 instead of $59. Later this summer, Yahoo says it will upgrade its free Web-mail service from 4 to 100 megabytes of storage, while giving "virtually unlimited" storage to customers who have already paid for the portal's extra-cost mail services.   Yahoo's shift came in response to Google's plans for Gmail, a free Web-mail service that will provide users 1 gigabyte of storage in return for letting Google show targeted ads alongside messages. Gmail (gmail.google.com) is planned for release in late summer or fall.   In a meeting with financial analysts Thursday, Yahoo also disclosed that it will soon provide a downloadable "desk bar" program that will let users run Web searches and access a bunch of other Yahoo services outside of their Web browser. The portal also said it's about to release new search features to help people find local businesses.   Google, meanwhile, revamped its Google Groups service to challenge Yahoo Groups (groups.yahoo.com). Previously, Google provided access only to Usenet discussion groups, but now it also lets people create and manage public or private mailing lists, as Yahoo Groups does. Yahoo's service offers more features, including space for storing photos, but Google Groups 2 (still in a test state at groups-beta.google.com) offers one unique option -- users can highlight favorite discussion topics with a star so they can easily find them on their next visit to the site.    Google revised yet another service last Monday, when it redesigned Blogger.com, the Web-log tool it bought last year. The new version aims to ease newcomers into the art of "blogs," or online journals, with a set of design templates and a personal-profile system that links new authors to other bloggers who share their interests.    On the same day as the Blogger relaunch, Google itself started its own "Google Blog" (www.google.com/googleblog). But its authors on the search site's executive team promptly raised the ire of veteran bloggers by posting items anonymously and revising previously published material. "You just don't do that with a blog, according to half the Google Staff and all the Blogger folk," the blog confessed in a posting Friday. But the Google team noted its blog is an experiment and said it will continue to offer a mix of anonymous and signed postings.   Free Concert Online   Yahoo's Launch music service is offering a free Webcast today of the "We Are the Future" humanitarian concert being staged in Rome by Quincy Jones. The four-hour concert starts at noon; performers include Norah Jones, Alicia Keys, Herbie Hancock and Patti Austin. Watching the webcast requires the Windows Media player.   launch.yahoo.com/wearethefuture/   Opera Sings a New Tune   Opera Software released an new version of its Web browser -- an alternative to Microsoft Internet Explorer favored by some advanced Web users -- last week. Opera 7.5, which includes a streamlined interface and adds support for RSS news feeds and Internet Relay Chat, sells for $39 or can be used in a free, ad-subsidized mode. It's available for Windows and Macs as well as the Linux (news - web sites), FreeBSD and Solaris operating systems.   www.opera.com   E-mail Leslie Walker at walkerl@washpost.com.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - 'Buffalo Spammer' Sentenced to 3-1/2 to 7 Years   U.S. National - Reuters   'Buffalo Spammer' Sentenced to 3-1/2 to 7 Years 2 hours, 13 minutes ago  Add U.S. National - Reuters to My Yahoo!  WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A New York state man who sent out millions of "spam" e-mails was sentenced to 3-1/2 to seven years in prison, the state attorney general's office said on Thursday.  Howard Carmack, known as the "Buffalo Spammer," received the maximum sentence for 14 counts of identity theft and forgery, a spokesman for New York Attorney General Eliot Spitzer said.   Carmack sent out 825 million bulk e-mail messages using stolen identities and forged addresses, the court found, and was the first defendant to face charges under the state's new identity-theft statute.   He was found guilty in April.   The forgery conviction fetched the longest sentence, while the other convictions drew shorter sentences of one year to four years. All will be served concurrently, Spitzer spokesman Brad Maione said.   Carmack could be out in 3-1/2 should he behave in prison, Maione said.   Internet provider EarthLink Inc (Nasdaq:ELNK - news). won a $16.5 million judgment against Carmack last year, and EarthLink officials testified in the criminal trial as well.   "We're satisfied that today's sentencing sends a strong message to spammers, and EarthLink will continue to investigate spammers and work with law enforcement," said EarthLink assistant general counsel Karen Cashion in a statement.   Unwanted bulk messages now account for roughly 83 percent of e-mail traffic, according to filtering company Postini Inc.   Many of Carmack's alleged activities are illegal under a national anti-spam law that took effect in January, seven months after he was charged. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink 'Key peak still in Pakistani occupation' - The Times of India   CHANDIGARH : A former Indian Army officer has claimed a few strategic peaks in the Kargil sector of Jammu and Kashmir , including the crucial Point 5353, were still under occupation by Pakistani forces.   Brig. Surinder Singh, who was dismissed from service in June 2001, also claimed the Indian defence establishment had misled the country by claiming it had gained control on the peaks in Kargil, where India and Pakistan fought a brief border conflict in 1999.   Singh was sacked after being embroiled in a controversy with his superiors about alleged lapses and intelligence failures that led to Pakistan-backed intruders occupying strategic features along a 140-km stretch of the Line of Control.   He asserted he had proof that Point 5353, a hill in the Drass sector of north Kashmir , was still under Pakistani occupation.   "I have evidence of this claim including satellite images," he told reporters.   Singh said the alleged inaction of the defence and political leadership during the Kargil conflict was only the tip of the iceberg.   "The defence establishment had misled the nation about getting every intruder out of the Kargil sector. I can give proof of this to whatever committee the new government at the centre sets up," Singh said, noting he had written about the matter to Defence Minister Pranab Mukherjee.   Singh said he had asked Mukherjee to order a thorough probe into the Kargil conflict and issues that were deliberately hidden by the previous coalition government led by the Bharatiya Janata Party. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>