<Blog>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's about to happen! Sophomore student government elections for the 2004-2005 school year are quickly coming upon our class. I'm one of roughly 15 students who is running, so getting a position on the four-person government will be difficult. I am prepared for a loss, even though I hope I win. I hoped I got into Blue Key. I hoped I got a 4.0 GPA. But it just doesn't turn out that way.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Out of pure curiosity, I have decided to venture into the world of blogging. Why? Because I'm currently pretty bored and it always seems like when I have a good idea or funny comment no one is ever around to hear it. For instance, I'm thinking currently of the sophomore student government. I suppose they're a nice group of guys and gals looking from an onlooker's perspective, but they're such morons.  So, here's my proposal: regime change. It seems like whenever someone hears the word "regime" they duck under their desks and scream "mommy." We need all 4 people replaced for any true originality, which seems impossible due to the fact it most likely is impossible. It'd be fun to campaign for a regime change especially running around campus with red-lettered signs saying "We want regime change!"  Next, there's this idiotic idea to have people in swimsuits, in a pool, in the dark, on inflatable objects, in a pool. Fun? We think not. (Notice my odd use of the word "we." We is just me, but it sounds twenty times more substantiated if you use "we." I assume someone out there must agree with me.) Foremost, this would require people to be  in bathing suits . Talk about a good idea gone wrong, but I like to tell the full truth which is three out of four people you don't want to see half-naked. Secondly, this would require getting wet which isn't bad in-and-of-itself, but there will be that 60-second period in between one running from the student center in wet clothing to the dorms or to a car in the middle of the night and it'll be cold. Lastly, you can't trust immature people. Some jerk will bring a watergun, I can guarantee it.  I've got a list of goals, it's long, but not  as  long as my list of things to do. Two good examples on my list of goals include staying fully clothed as best to my ability and staying dry. This would strictly go against those two fundamental principles. My world would seriously come to an end, maybe. In conclusion: there are people you'd like to see half-naked, but the number of people you wouldn't want to see half-naked out number the number you would. That's the dilemma. Seriously, it's not like a wild spring break where it doesn't matter what you can be a fat slob in a Speedo, because no one will remember you. (FYI: I am  not  the fat slob.) These people are maniacal, judging bastards, commonly referred to as my "peers." I use the term loosely of course.  I hope someone will enjoy this blog, because I had fun writing my first edition. Just to be clear, all of what I am writing is true but has a somewhat bitter, funny tone. Also, I'm keeping this blog with accurate spelling and grammar. I hate people who cannot spell. Hopefully, I can get some cool photos to go along with my blogs too, we'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, I know I may not have posted in forever, but now that it is summer I am going to start posting daily as soon as cool stuff starts happening! I haven't precisely decided how to use my friend's and enemy's names. Should I make up different names for these people? If they found this blog, should I care? I don't know, but I sort of want people to know about it.  As for the beginning of my summer. It has started off pretty well! I went to the mall yesterday and forgot to pickup khaki cargo shorts. Not like I don't already have a pair, but they're wrinkly. I hate wrinkles and clothing that hasn't been worn at least once. I'm picky. I can't believe I forgot. I did pick up a book, Lab 257, and a video game, Project Gotham Racing 2 (PGR). I've been meaning to pick that up, but I was busy when it came out. The original PGR was by far my favorite racing game ever. The sequel is a huge step up, but it can be extremely challenging. It definitely tests your patience.  Tomorrow, I am supposidely going to see The Day After Tomorrow and go out to Ruby Tuesdays with my family. But a friend also invited me to a Halo session Monday night, which I obviously wanted to attend. Not only for Halo, but to get out of this house. I know, I left it on Saturday and Friday for about 6-7 hours total, but it'll drive me crazy soon. At least I get my driver's license on June 2, I can leave whenever I get the urge. I haven't told my parents about the Halo thing, because I always doubt it will pan out. I also heard something about paintball, but I've never played and don't have the equipment, but I never miss an opportunity to make an ass of myself. I'd like to go to that too, but I don't know when that is either.  I am a bit confused. I am also planning on opening two web sites over the summer. I am halfway done with the first one (it's much smaller). It allows you to select and change your online mood. It'll also all you to add people to your mood "friends list." So whenever you change your mood, or just visit the site, you can find out how everyone's doing. It sounds easy to do, but it's more complex than you'd imagine. The other site is a bit underwraps now, it's a combination of Neopets, Tropico, and Grand Theft Auto. I'll keep posting!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've finished an entire 17 hours of community service, who's happy for me? Now only 23 to go. I've felt so tired today and didn't get anything done. But tomorrow will be different! I need to pick-up something nice for Gemma's birthday present and I need to get new pair of jeans, because my current ones (that I used to love) are falling off my ass constantly. I suppose I've lost some weight since going vegetarian. It also gives me an excuse to go to the mall.  I'm weird. I'm a guy, yet I somewhat enjoy the mall. I also like clothes. It's said I cannot afford more. I'm going to get these when I go tomorrow ( urlLink link ). They look amazing, hopefully they'll look even better in the store.  Over the weekend I went to Albany, NY with my best friend to an arena football game. It was a blast, we had an amazing time. It's a very exciting city and the drunks really made it quite an experience. Why do the most wasted and ugly people always want to dance? This is beyond me. There was no one good-looking on the trip perse, but New York has no lack of attractive people in general. I love New York. When I searched for "Albany colleges" I was a bit disappointed nothing came up that would suit me. I'm still keeping my fingers crossed for NYU.  I love New York. The city and the state. There's so much excitement and everyone's busy and it essentially never sleeps. It has a certain "aura." You become happy just by stepping in the boundaries. I had another smaller talk with a friend of mine about going to college. All he said during the entire conversation was how he'll miss his friends. This ticked me off in 2 ways. First of all, this friend only hangs out with freshmen and other over-hyped ADD children. Secondly, is he trying to imply I have no friends?  Maybe I'm just too self-absorbed. I'm upset my all-so-intresting friends haven't actually done much of anything this summer. Best friend was in Australia, so it's sort of an excuse. We saw Shrek 2 as well as the Albany trip. My other good friend (name withheld) hasn't talked to me like at all. We never see eachother during the entire school year and now it's like nothing. He's just working or talking to JP I suppose. It's aggrivating. I'll definitely see him on the 4th of July.  I'm pondering dirty-blonde highlights. Any comment? Talk to no one later.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You want to see my driver's license? I could if I got one. I failed. This has got to be one of the most embarassing moments in my life. The man said I did "very poorly." At first, I though he was kidding, you know how people say you did awful and then say "Congradulations, you did it!" but not in this case. Apparently I was worse than I thought.  Alright, so we go to the Wilkes-Barre DMV in Hanover and my mom and I wait for like 20 minutes. In the meantime, I get very, very nervous. I look around the car and see the parallel parking portion of the test, and it looks very tight/difficult from where I'm looking. And I'm keep cursing to myself, wishing I had practiced it more.  It begins. He says to turn on the right/left turn signals, hazard lights, brake lights, and locate the emergency brake. All of that worked, except it took me a split second to figure which way to turn the bar (up or down) to make the turn signal go right or left. I felt like such a moron, and my nervousness was getting worse.  The parallel parking is the first part of the test, I do it flawlessly on my first try. Or so I thought. This guy is like a mute and only gives directions and never any details. So I say, "Is this good enough?" And he says, "Why are you so close to the car behind you?" So I put it in drive and move the car exactly in between the two vehicles. I ask, "Here?" He's like, "That's good enough." At this point, I'm like what the f*ck? I'm no perfectionist, but that's pretty damn good. I'd like to see you do it in a 4-door Volvo.  The second part is the road driving section. Apparently, as I was turning onto the road out of the DMV, I got so caught up in not getting in a crash, not speeding, not using my turn signals, etc. that I missed a very critical speed sign right at the turn that said 25 MPH. Mind you, this is in an industrial park in Hanover where the trucks are easily going 40 MPH or higher. I miss this sign and go at ~35 MPH for the duration of the test.  I am still considerably nervous. This guy is mumbling directions to where he wants me to drive and I have to try to make it perfect without a lot of time to think. We drive around a little. The only part at this point where I think I might have messed up was braking a bit too hard by making a left into a small parking lot. No big deal I thought, no way he could flunk me for that.  Long story, made a bit shorter, I saw a speed sign for 35 MPH on the way back and I am relieved. Ee get back to the DMV. He told me I did "very poorly." I must have a hell of a shocked faced. I thought I did fairly well, considering I know people with licenses now, and their certainly not the safest of drivers. He said I failed to use turn signals while parallel parking (true, but give me a break), went above the posted speed limit (later I realized I missed the posted sign while trying to make a left, very confusing because it's 35 MPH one way and 25 MPH the other), made a yield on yellow (he said what I did was legal and safe, but still "should have waited"), didn't stop before the white lign (I believe I did, but I was really nervous, so it's possible), and didn't have both handles on the wheel at all times.   The last part really ticked me off and when he showed me how I "supposidely" did it, he wasn't even close to what I did. Normally when diriving, I have my left hand at the ten o'clock position (in order to turn) and my right hand "circling" the lower bar at the five o'clock position (to "stabilize" my driving). Or course I realized this was wrong before I took the test, and I remembered the stupid ten/two o'clock position for my test, but I must've accidentally switched back momentarily. For sharp turns, I don't see how you can have two hands on the wheel every single fraction of a second. It's my belief you should use the steering wheel the best way that works for you.  Everyone really anticipated me passing. I was hugely disappointed for 3-4 hours. I'm kind of over it now. I rescheduled for next Thursday. I hope I don't get the same guy. I know there's really no point in practicing, but I don't know any other way to ensure I don't fail again. Wish me better luck next time!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Summer has been great! Lots of fun and parties and no shortage of drunks for amusement purposes. The fourth of July didn't go exactly as well as I had hoped. A cousin of a friend stopped by who was short, fat, and arrogant. He was trying to convince me that meat eating was normal. It was frustrating. Especially since he was fat and I didn't really want to say it to his face. I attempted to show some self-restraint.  Besides that, I've been to another good friend's house like all this week. I think today marks the fifth consecutive day I have technically been at his house. It's good fun, playing Halo and staying up until your eyes won't do anything but shut. It's had pretty horrible effects on my body, I'm eating a lot of junk and weird times and haven't had a really good night's rest in forever. That's especially weird considering it's summer.  I also ventured to the mall yesterday. I picked up the most awesome pair of  urlLink jeans  that mankind has ever beheld. Another kick-ass belt and some dark-colored undershirts. It feels amazing to look good. Unfortunately, my parents think I've gone anorexic over the past few weeks, which isn't true, but I've gone on a fairly restrictive home-brewed diet as well as exercise.  I also went bowling at another party at the very end of June, which was quite exciting as well. Nothing too eventful. I'm now pondering whether to drop my web site subscription. I'm burning "debt" fairly quickly. I've already dropped by $12.95/month Asheron's Call subscription. Now it's probably the same with my web site one. I want a lot of things and these subscriptions are really hurting me monetarily. I get a lot more enjoyment staring at myself in my tight American Eagle jeans that costed $48 than attempting to code some stupid computer language on the internet. Of course, I couldn't have fit into those jeans a month or two ago. I'm also pretty vain, but it's really quite fun. I'll try to post later. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>