<Blog>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The beginning of the week has been so queer. yesterday, they brought in a "motivational speaker" and we got to miss some of class. Missing the class was cool. The rest my friends, was not. The assembly actually confused me a little. They had these guys and they were all "YOU CAN BE WHO YOU WANNA BE!!" and I was like, "uh, kay...". So then they had the guys karate chop some bricks in half. I guess that, if you believe you can crack the bricks, you can (even if you've never had formal training!). They also did this weird little music video type thing to a satisfied song. All in all it was very strange. Then later when I got home, I had a lesson with BOB. I don't mind BOB but, he's a little different. So I was in the room, and he gave me a piece of paper and I flipped it over and it had some words written on it...Then he told me to read them outloud really fast.  I am we Todd did  I swear it took me like ten minutes to finally get it, and now BOB probably thinks that I'm actually retarded.  Today! ah, lets ponder about the day. we had a late start, so that was cool French still sucks ultimate butt Lunch was good. I like those new goldfish crackers with extreme flavor. I won the English competition, now I don't have to take the test tee! Rachel is in Florida, so Erica is my lab partner, she's not so bad   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, Mondays. The best day of the week to have a complete mental breakdown. Luckily, this didn't happen until 3ish. I got horrible headache around French class time, and it was so nasty, that I had trouble seeing clearly. Then, I got home and realized that I was about to vomit. BUT THEN I realized that I had no house key, thus leaving me out in the cold. All I really wanted was a nap in my nice cozy bed. So I tried to lay on the bitter cement porch and fall asleep, but it was just too damn cold. Right then I started balling my eyes out. I just didn't understand why I wasn't in my bed sleeping. It was so sad. But, now, my brain has stopped its rhythmic pulsating in my fragile skull, leaving nothing but peace and quiet. Tomorrow is a new and better day. No worries, breathe in and out.  but before I go... A quote from Jimmy Page to Brett Scallions "Hey man, good luck with your band" "Thanks! You too!"  Well I thought it was funny.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find people to be most unsatisfactory. You know? They're either total incompetent morons, or completely and utterly boring. Now, I am sure that I am not the most thrilling person in the universe, and certainly not the smartest. But I don't know why I cannot accept people as easily as others can. I guess I'll have to sleep on that one, as I cant find an answer right now.  I also would like to make a note about this: "That's dumb, you should do this instead." These statements made by certain people make me want to kill the certain people who say these kind of things to me. These certain people should realize that I do not care what they think I should do, because I  will do  what I want to do, and nothing you will ever say could  ever  change this.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am terribly bored. I am compelled to do something crazy to undo my boredom. I woke up at like 7:30. I watched TV, and of course there was nothing on. And for some unknown reason, Comedy Central has completely stopped airing SNL and they have replaced it with (not so humorous) Mad TV. I do not know why they did this to me, but I am certainly not happy about it. SNL and I had a special bond-I feel like I am cheating on SNL by watching Mad TV. Anyway, So I went out to lunch with my mother today. Now that was entertaining. I would elaborate, but I am far too exhausted. My friends have abandoned me, and my quasi-friends are nowhere to be found. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a day of misdemeanors and mischief. At 9:00 Megan, Chelsea, Mary, Amy and I toilet-papered my ex-boyfriends house. It was totally fun. Why did we do it you ask? Well, we (I) wanted to put dog shit in paperbags and set them on fire on peoples porches, but NOOO thats too mean. So we did the next best thing. David (the ex) is currently married to some girl named Brittany. And frankly, we are quite tired of it. So after we were done with the durrrty deed, we called his cell and sang "in the jungle" and told him to wipe his ass (which he could do with all the TP in his yard)  heehee.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright: Lets do this  my principal MR KURTZ is old and lonely. People rip on him all the time. THIS HAS GOT TO END. Reason being: Last Monday, I saw poor old Mr Kurtz at the gas station. He parked his little red Volvo, walked into the station-store, and came back out. WITH A MUFFIN. He then proceeded to eat the muffin all by himself in his car. It was the saddest thing I have ever seen. So, you heartless people need to stop dissing Mr Kurtz
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bonjour! (I learned this word in French class) My good friend Chelsea had a proclamation today: In America, when people have s-x*, they tend to scream "yes!". In France, people having s-x must scream "oui!" (pronounced:"wee"). So right now somewhere in France, there is some woman on some guy screaming "WeeEEEEwEEEeeeEEeWeeEEEE!!" at the top of her lungs, like she's on a highspeed roller-coaster.  Funny huh? Thanks Chels.   Anyway, nothing else really happened today.   although   I did receive a horrid new nick-name from my science teacher: "Hug-n-Kiss". Amanda Hug-n-Kiss. A MAN TO HUG AND KISS. I have never heard anything more inapprop. in my life. Thanks to   you   MR THOR.  *This post was edited for parental blockage pleasure
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my fellow bloggers. This is my very first entry and I did it without breaking my computer (this is improvement from the last time I went on-line). Today, I went to school, and it sucked butt. I was forced to endure public humiliation in phys. Ed. by getting into shorts and playing volley ball (needless to say, our team totally lost). I also went to French class (against my will of course) where my moronic teacher blabbed on and on about conjugating verbs...IN FRENCH. We don't know how to speak French. That is why we are taking the class. der.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i had to go to the       DENTIST omg it was so scary, i started crying in the car on the way there. And i was crying when i got there. i dont know why but i was just SO nervous. Any way, today i am going out with rachael and her parental units for dinner. i think it will be interesting. tomorrow is the relay and i am so excited.....not. its suposed to rain all goddammed day.  im outie yo
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "youpi" means "yay" in french. i learned that word today. that's about it for my use of brainpower.  Ok, so at lunch this girl named Delia (maybe i am spelling it wrong, i dunno whatever) started sitting with us. She totally doesn't like me. God, she could at least TRY to make it inconspicuous.  I forgot how to play most of those White Stripe songs i learned from BOB yesterday. I should've written them down.  Oh, and i also forgot that the bandies had a concerto today, and i'm not there, so they might be all mad at me tomorrow.  sigh...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that You Don't Know Jack is one of the best games ever. I just got done playing a round, and i don't know what it is, but it cracks me up. You should all go out and buy it. Anyway Today i found out that the other french teacher at our school is getting sacked next year. THIS MEANS I HAVE MRS. MICHELS FOR-EV-VER!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHG WHY GOD? WHY DID YOU DO THIS? I DID NOTHING DESERVING TO DESERVE THIS!!!!!!! whew. ok that's be-yetter. Also there's this new hot guy who i like a lot who works at Handels. Also this weekend I saw a good movie. Lauren didn't like it because she has no soul. OH and today we had an ASSembly and people danced! weee-haw! Uhmmmm K i think that's all for now, sorry for the lame post but i want to watch Knock First LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I had two tests that i was completely unprepared for. it was not good times. Also Mr. Thor somehow got hold of a Timberstone Year book where in my picture, one eye is WAY WAY smaller that the other eye. (this happens in every picture but that year it was especially bad). So he felt that it would be OK if he made fin of me about it.   It wasn't.       HEY?!? Here's a list of "good things in 2003/4"  10. martha stuart goes to prison 9. Bobby BROWN back in prison 8. Demi and Ashton...this is not really good, but it's pretty damn funny 7. Mr. Vens *swoon* 6. Jack White goes to the big house 5. Von Bondies pansy-front man doesn't go to prison 4.5 Micheal Jackson going to court 4 MAYBE going to prison 3. Wes Scantlin spends the night in Toledo jail after sucky brown show 2. Mr. Kurtz muffin-----not in jail. (in kurtz's brown) 1. RISA SMELLS LIKE BROWN  whoopi!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry that I haven't been posting everyday like a good little blogglinTM (Chelsea Kopfman). Ah, gee whiz, there's just so much to ketchup on! heh. Ok so the other day I leave my books on the kitchen table and I call my dad at school and ask him to drop them off. SO later in the day I come in and out of the office asking those evil-pyscotic-mutant-demonspawn-mostgodawful-attendance office ladies where the hell my friggin books are. YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY TO ME????? "well, if they aren't on the counter, we DONT HAVE THEM". And, apparently they were not on the counter. So my dad is all upset when I call him and tell him that I didn’t have my homework/books all day so he calls the evil-pyscotic-mutant-demonspawn-mostgodawful-attendance office lady and yells at her too.  YAY! The next day I go in DEMANDING my books AND a written excuse from them for my missing homework. I did it. I BEAT THE SYSTEM. HURAHHH!  'Aight dawgs. ...And you want me to tell you about a little snippet from today as well you say? I'D LOVE TO!  I was walking with ChelseaKopfman in the hallway today and there was this guy standing in my way chattering away with his girlfriend and ChelseaKopfman was lucky enough to side step them, but as I was getting closer, I kinda push-trip-shoved right between them and almost fell down. AND before that at lunch, I was conversing with JackieZuriech and I moved my hand across a deadly piece of wrapping paper that I covered my books with and I cut my wittow finguh. AND when I was in the hallway with RachaelHoglate I wasn't watching where I was going and I hit my funny bone* on the door and was like "ooowwww". Twas a day of cuts and bruises. OH and in gym when we were "working out" I got off of a machine and I hit my leg causing severe** bruising and possible internal bleeding***.    * Why is it a funny bone? It is most definitely NOT funny when you hit it. It hurts. ** Maybe not severe, but it felt like it was maybe going to be a bruise a little. *** I made this part up. TEEHEE 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That was the title of a "just updated" blog. I thought it was note-worthy. Anywho, today I had a CRAP load of homework. And Stupid (aka Mrs Michaels) gave us a friggin worksheet to finish, and a friggin test to study for. CHA RIGHT. Then, the lovely Mr. Vens gave us homework, and Mr. Carr gave us a CRAP load of homework, and so did Ms. Lesbian. So I got home at 2:30 and JUST finished my HW two minutes ago. Is that crazy or what? AND I don't know where Micki is, but I want dinner. Also, Fern, this kid in my lunch hour, is looking pretty cute. That was irrelevant, but who cares? This is my blog and "whatever whatever I do what I want".
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today  me, my father, and my mother are having dinner. together. at six tonight. Now, the last time we had a "family" dinner must have been eight years ago. Something must be going on that I am totally unaware of. Maybe the planets are aligned? I don't know, but it's definetly NOT good. Anyway, that horrid woman the faculty at Southview High School call a teacher (MRS MICHELS *shiver*) was not here today. HURRAH! So French class was tolerable today.  I also have some startling news. Are you ready? I am no longer in love with John Jellinger. NOW I am in love with my algebra teacher. Mr. Vens I have to go in early on Monday morning to take his quiz. I also have no idea how to do any of the problems on this quiz. So I'm hoping that he'll help me out a little bit >insert romantic fantasy here Ahem  Toodles
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the Brittney Spears concert. It was pretty fun, Brittney didn't really sing a lot of the time, BUT DAMN that girl can dance. The show set-up was kinda neat too, there were awesome pyro-technics and a creepy guy who looked like Boy George on a bad day. They played my favorite Brittney songs, and all in all, it wasn't half bad for a pop show.  So I skipped school today because nobody would drive me back to Toledo at 12:00 in the morning. My Grammy took me shopping and I got shoes. Yeah, I know you wish YOUR Grandma would buy you shoes.   Don't deny the Granny-love Peace out yo 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      School is starting tomorrow. Whaaaaaaaa! It's actually very depressing, in fact, I am crushed. At least summer is comming IN TWO MONTHS yeah baby. My kitty Lola (Binkiss as I say) is sitting on the computer desk. She never has to go to school. You know what she does all day? She lies around the house, sleeps, eats, and poops. She's so lucky dammit.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so today I was watching one of my favorite movies "Dude Wheres my Car" and I was totally cracking up  all by myself in the living room. It's just so dumb that it's one of the greatest movies ever.  here are my favorite quotes from the movie  "Ooh, a lama..." "Dude, that's not a lama, it's an ostrich" "DUDE I JUST TOUCHED KRISTI BONNER'S WHO WHOS!!!" "Shibby"  They just crack me up!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TESTING TWO THREE...  TESTING TWO THREE...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is Easter. I am a jew, but we do Easter cuz Micki is a non-jew. I'm not sure what she is. We went to a country club for an early dinner, and it was kinda gross. So i had mashed potatoes and corn Is there an E in potatoes? I am too lazy to run spell check. Anywho, I also got an Easter basket, it had The Goonies DVD in it. I love that movie, "HEY YOU GUUUUYSSSSS!". Now that's comedy.  Well I think I am done for now. BYE!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, Stu goes to church...again. I go tanning, and Chelsea ties bows around napkins. It's gonna be good.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Fasha took me to White Castle today so I could try one of their tiny cheeseburgers it was so gross, I almost died.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh*  All of my friends spent the night together yesterday. I was at my mom's house. If I'd have known that everybody was going, I could've stayed here. I'm glad that they informed me about their plans. It was really super nice of them.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bonojur Mes Amis! Aujourd'hui j'ai vu une grosse fille sur Bay Watch. C'était un sympa changement! (fnar fnar fnar). Quoi encore?? Je suis dans une bonne humeur...  J'ai eu ma coupe de cheveux hier tellement maintenant il est beau et lisse! Et Aujourd'hui, Je décore des oeufs de Pâques avec Micki, c'est tres amusant!!!  hmm, that's about all the brain-power I can use today bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok guys I think I'm under control now. No worries I did my yoga, and I'm centered. I'm kinda sleepy too.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder if a person could survive without any other human contact. It would be really hard, but I bet they could do it. "People are like parasites, they feed off of other's humiliation and suffering. When they've had enough, they just hop off and find new victims..."-Dr. Phil I'm glad Phil is here, he always cheers me up. Not.  Shouldn't I be happy that I am on spring break? I hate school. I don't have to go for ten days. But I am still not happy, there's got to be an explanation for this. In fact I even know what it is, but I just cant type it out.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ya, know...Mick was supposed to take me tanning an hour ago, but she fell asleep god dammit. Now, she's gonna be all "oohhhh im sorry, i forgot" and i will be pale and sickly forever.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok I think that I might be in serious need of some anti-depressants. Maybe I should go to the doctor. HOW can I be a psychiatrist if I have issues of my own? But maybe because I am aware of my personal issues, it makes it different. My Big Fat List of Issues: 1. I am very non-confrontational 2. I never tell anybody how I really feel 3. I keep everything inside, until somebody asks me directly what's wrong, and then I have a total breakdown and start crying and I feel like an idiot. 4. My issues are not as big as I make them out to be, it's just a habit of mine I guess. 5. I am very insecure 6. I have some wired social anxiety thing where it makes me nervous to be one on one with people 7. I want to cry whenever a teacher calls on me and I don't know the answer 8. I almost always feel like everybody is putting on a facade around me  Oy. Maybe I should tell the my parents about this list, but I'm not going to. (see #2).
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ITS SO COLD IN MY HOUSE. IM FRICK'N FREEEEEEZING.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe I'm just screwed up, but sometimes, I feel like everybody is against me. Maybe, I'm just being melodramatic, but sometimes, I feel like my friends hate me. I have been conducting an experiment you see. For the past four weekends (Friday night through Sunday at five-ish), I have not called my friends. I do not go out of my way to e-mail them, or stop by. I respond to their instant messages, and say 'maybe we can do something tomorrow' or something of that nature. My friends do not call me, e-mail, or stop by either. Therefore I have done nothing with my friends for the past few weekends. HOWEVER...My friends do hang out with each other. That means that one of my friends, would have to contact another friend to make plans. Thus, my friends will call each other, but not me. I hope that if my friends are reading this, which I don't think they do, that they do not take any offense to this. After all, this couldn't be your fault, it must be mine.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see the Lion King play today at the Masonic. It was pretty cool. Our furnace also broke today. It's pretty cold. My Fasha fixed my CD player. It was pretty awesome.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ohhhhhh OWwwwwwwW EeeeehhhhhEEEEEEee OOOOOOhhh  never eat at Ventura's.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Where do my friends go on the weekend? This is the question I frequently ask myself on Saturdays. I could just call them up and ask them, but, they are never home. Even when they say that they'll call me, they don't. Then on Monday mornings when I ask them what they did all weekend they say "oh well it was really cool. We did this and this and this and this and this and this and this"  I mean really. Would it rip all the vital organs out of their bodies if they called me and said "hey manda, do you wanna hang out today?" I guess so. So I hung out with my parents all day today. whoopi for me.      Ugh! I just cant get over it. If I had one dollar for every friend that didn't call me, id have 7 dollars.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank GOD. Today was the last day of hell for a whole 10 days baby. So here are the highlights by periods of the day 1. Colored 2. Colored 3. Played volleyball, and was pile-drived by a stoner we call "snarfy" 4. Looked at my hott teachers butt 5. Gave a presentation on Hitler (it was a party...Not) 6. Ate crepes and  ripped on Madame Michel 7. Ate lunch (my mom packed me graham crackers, a smooshed PBJ and marshmallows. Its a good thing there were crepes earlier) 8. Played the sentence game 9. Wrote a story about little Atom and his friend Mr Molecule  YAY! So anyway, during chemistry, I was staring at my hott guy (John) through the lab window, and I think that I might love him. He's just so damn hott. Alright, now, maybe I've never actually spoken more than three words to him at a time, but I think there is still a slight possibility that he's secretly pining over me too. Maybe like .99% ? Wow! That'd be so cool. I'd be like "JOHN I love you, will you have my baby?!" no, ok not really, but, still, it'd be neato.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I've seen Jackie's top ten bands list, and I just have to say one thing. HERE'S MINE! heehehe  10. Death Cab for Cutie 9. Sum 41  8. Incubus 7. The Hives 6. The White Stripes 5. Cold Play 4. Ok Go 3. The Red Hot Chili Peppers 2. Nirvana  drum roll pleeeze.... 1. Weezer! *cheer*  Keep in mind that this is a continuously fluctuating list. This is just as of 4:27 today.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My disc-man broke when I was getting on the cheese wagon today. I almost cried, tears welled up in my eyes and everything. I don't know why though, its not like I used it everyday, or somebody who died gave it to me. I guess I just really liked it a lot. I miss it :( Anyway, today when I was playing volleyball in phys ed, I was about to bump the ball (it was commingn right to me, I totally would have hit it perfectly) and this big-boobed, loud, obnoxious, dumb girl totally like, shoved me out of the way "MINE!", she yelled. It was not hers. It was mine. Apparently her big stupid uniboob was blocking her vision. I was  OMG I just took a break from my blog to get a cupcake, and they are SO good, that I don't even care about Nicole and her huge uniboob! hmmf, oh well! Ahh, now that my day is finally better (thanks to this wonderful pink cupcake goodness) I wish you all a good day, and a scrumtrelessent night!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One double cheese burger at Mc.Donalds: 0 dollars Two Krispy Kreme doughnuts: 0 dollars Movie at janky theater: PRICELESS
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night Jackie came to get me at 7:15. I wasn't home, i was at China House. (Yes, it was tasty) Anyway, so i got home and there was a message from her and she was freaking out because i wasn't home, even thought she SAID that she was getting me at 7:30. heehee So her mom finally comes to get me and she drops us off at the janky Secor theater. The movie that we wanted to see didn't start until like, 10, so we had a really long time to kill. So we had NO MONEY (because i had movie passes) and we had NO CAR. We decided to head over to McDonalds. On our way there this dumb guy ran over a massive puddle and spewed dirty water all over us. but we were ok. At McD's There was this rather large black woman taking orders, and Jackie just sort of slipped in and TOTALLY snatched a value meal right off of the counter while she wasnt looking! *score* then after her Mcdinner, we walked over to Krispy Kreme where apparently, there's "free doughnut time" So we were looking at all the good doughnuts and this girl just hands us two free ones!! *score* Then we saw this lady come in and she was all eating 500 doughnuts and it was all over her face and she was like "ahhhhhh". heeehee. Then we were looking for gum or something, and i found a hollywood video card in my purse so we decided to go over there and rent some movies. Then once we got there we decided to get games instead. So we wandered over to the counter and this asian video nazi decided to not let us rent our game. i was upset, but by that time it was time to see the movie. YAY
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday: After i got back from the mall I had to go to a BBQ. After the BBQ, I was off to Megan's to spend the night. We had a good time. Jessica picked us up and took us to MeyjerS and we painted THE ROCK. I wrote "I heart E.N." and Megan wrote the same for R.K. Then we were going to do some damage to a certain somebody's house, but some people decided to run back to the car, so we couldn't do it. (did that make sense?) Anyway. Megan and I might have gotten a tad...er..."happy" from the spray paint. She was making really scary piano faces, and i thought it was so funny, i practically peed my pants. But it wasnt actually that funny. heh.  Sunday: I TALKED TO E.N. and he said "You know Maxwell's coffee shop? I might end up there tomorrow...you should come" OH MY GOD. I almost had a hernia. So then i took my dad past the rock and somebody duct-taped my heart. i was crushed. Megan also spray-painted over hers cuz she was embarassed. SIGH. anyway, i'm going out with Jackie and Delia might come too. We are going to go see yet another movie. Like i don't spend enought money as it is. Chelsea made me kind of mad because she didnt take the tape off of the heart. (sorry i just felt i needed to say that). Ok well i guess thats all.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So at school friday they had this thing called 'fun day'. which is a lie, because it was actually only like, 'fun hour and a half'. They had battle of the bands, and they all sucked arse until Poon Tang came on and they were awesome. my buddy EN is in that band. it was hott. anyway so then i went home on the cheese with Rachael and we got pizza and later Delia and Divya and Lauren and Jack came over and we went to see Troy. TROY IS THE LAMEST MOVIE. It was like three hours of Brad Pitt beathing the crap out of people in leather skirt like things. Personally, i don't find brad pitt very attractive, but, whatever. it still sucked. so delia and i had to keep from dying of bordem by throwing reeses peices at people below us. *Sigh*. anyway then we went back to Rach's house and had a good 'ol time.  Micki picked my up at 11 from Rach's then when i got home Lauren F. called and wanted to go to the mall with me and stu. so i had about twenty minutes to get ready. so i speed showered and then we were outie. i bought some cute stuff, i've been home for a half hour and in about another half hour i have to go to a BBQ. There is simply not enough time in a day. let me tell you!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I'm A 1970s Geek     You've decided for the world that it's time for a change. JOIN THE GEEK REVOLUTION!      urlLink find your geek decade at spacefem.com    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             you are mediumseagreen  #3CB371         Your dominant hues are cyan and green. Although you definately strive to be logical you care about people and know there's a time and place for thinking emotionally. Your head rules most things but your heart rules others, and getting them to meet in the middle takes a lot of your energy some days.  Your saturation level is medium - You're not the most decisive go-getter, but you can get a job done when it's required of you. You probably don't think the world can change for you and don't want to spend too much effort trying to force it.  Your outlook on life is brighter than most people's. You like the idea of influencing things for the better and find hope in situations where others might give up. You're not exactly a bouncy sunshine but things in your world generally look up.         urlLink the spacefem.com html color quiz      
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not a lot actually happened today, which i guess is a good thing. Most people seemed to get really hyped up at the end of the year. i just get stressed and distracted. Exams are coming up, and i just got a D on my last math test, so i might actually have to take home a textbook and cram. I feel so overwhelmed sometimes, like there is just SO much to do. But usually, it's nothing and i get stressed for nothing. *sigh*  IN OTHER NEWS: I have developed an ear infection. It hurts. E.N. has no idea that i may like/love him. E.N. has no idea who i am. This could be an issue... I have to go to mommy dearest's house tonight. UGH.  Good news: I am finished with my art exam so i dont have to come in that day im busy all weekend megan loves kevin.  teehee
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I was awarded with two things! The first was the actual award, "Cougar Pride award" which is basically a sympathy award for dumb kids who try hard, or smart kids who are in classes with dumb kids (me). Mr Thor nominated me. I'm ashamed.  The second award I received was the "trust award". I got this one because I trusted Corey to help me out with my English teaching thing, and he didn't. So he screwed us both over. I will never get this award again, because this trusting thing has happened SO many times, that I might just stop trusting people all together. yay for me.  I still have no idea what's going on in math.  On the bright side though...im going to see my buddy (EN) at his concert tonight, and it should be fun cuz hes a total fox.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      P.S. no sign of Elenun today i was really looking forward to seeing him i may even like him. a little. i dont know yet. ahhhh what should i do? please comment
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah Tuesdays what do i say? world studies what a bore creecy and her mole blocked the door French class really sucks Maybe Mrs. Michels will get hit by a truck English was of course fantastic but we had homework, it was...craptastic? Algebra was wonderful, although i admit, i have no idea whats going on Mr Vens is a hottie so i dont care if i get questions wrong My day was fun but now its done i hope you liked my poem.   man, that only took like a minute!!! im super talented
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Elenun IMed me. And it of course was a disaster. But, it's okay, I'm breathing again, and it's going good. Gooooood.  On a somewhat lighter note... i just asked the parental units to rent me To Kill a Mockingbird and they totally think that i am going to use it to like, cheat or whatever. Um, der i've already read the book. I don't need the movie for that. i have to teach my english class on wednesday because my teacher is too lazy to do it himself. jk, something about somebody's shoes...  BUT  I dont get to see BOB tomorrow. It's so sad. He was looking forward to seeing me. Aww, sorry BOBBO.   BUT We do get to play tennis in gym, and i love tennis so it's "aight"
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so this whole thing with elenun has got me twitching like a maniac. god, its not even a big deal. But i feel that if i dont make a good first impression, things could burn up in flames, because he seems like a first impression kind of guy. this could possibly be the extended hand to awesomeness if i dont F it up.         please god, dont let me F it up
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He lied to me last night. I was watching SNL, and he told me that WEEZER was going to be the musical guest. So I stayed awake to watch it, and i am sad to report, that there was not even a hint of WEEZ in the whole show. No, thick black glasses, no Buddy Holly, no nothing. Christopher Walken, I will have my revenge.  Anyway, so i was feeling much better this morning when i woke up, so i went downstairs and poured myself some cheerios. They were excellent. THEN i was looking at the back of the box, and it said "LOOK INSIDE FOR A SPECIAL PRIZE!" so i was totally stoked. I reach in, and there's a Shrek watch!! Its actually really ugly, but it's the thought that counts right? thanks Cheerios, you've made my day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So around sevenish i went to megan's house to spend the night. We don't really ever do anything at her house, but it's always a lot of fun. Tara had a party at her house and she didn't invite us, so we spied on her through Megan's mom's window with binoculars. it was funny. Then reeeeeally later like on Saturday, we were talking to Evan Fitzpatrick on line and we played end-of-the-world for like ever, it was also great fun. WE were also planning on doing something with Ryan around 4 in the morning but plans fell through because he was harrassing Megan, so we "accidently" forgot to meet him. Oh well! P.s John is a hottie P.s.s being lactos-intolerant sucks major buttage
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So thank god today was friday. i went to school and it was not so fun, because ninth period, the last period of the day, the time that is wonderful and sacred to me 2:25...WAS TAKEN AWAY FROM ME. I was sitting in class chattering away with Rachael and all of a sudden Mr Kurtz is all "well, uh excuse me teachers and students there is an emergency weather warning so please keep students in the classroom" Man was i pissed. So i finally get home at like THREE and then i watched Pirates so it was good. Johnny Depp is the coolest.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn. i wish i had one of those new fangled digital cameras. they're neat. if i had one, then i could put my picture on my profile like a normal blogger. so if anybody would like to buy me a camera...well, that'd be great. thank you and come again.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SHE'S GOT THE URGE!!! natural botanicals... SHE'S GOT THE URGE TO HERBAL! SHE'S GONNA HERBAL IN THE SHOWAH for another half an hour... SHE'S GOT THE URGE!  tah-dahhhhh  We have a two hour de-lay we have a two hour de-lay whoo-whoo! that's right bi-yatch i got to sleep in and it was VONDERFUL
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, this is like the third time ive tried to get to this site. its impossible. it keeps freezing and whatnot. but its ok. i'm a survivor (im not gonna give up! heehee) any who, today i saw BOB and it was good. we worked on the rhythem that i don't have and he said, and i quote "Have you been practicing?????!!!!!". He was very excited, because i have indeed been practicing. yay for me. we only did that for like 15 minutes because i finally got the hang of it. then we talked about Festarama, and he said he was playing on Saturday night while we were there. thats weird because i almost went in the little tent thing to see who was playing. Also today, i got a present and it was fun, because i LOVE presents. they are just so...so...well, they make me happy. and what else happened... hm, nothing i can think of right now, im in a good mood, so lets not spoil it. Hey i just left for a sec cuz the doorbell rang and it was my mom. she brought my purse. yay
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well my resolution to be nicer to people started out fine until French when somebody made me very VERY angry and I didn't feel like being nice to people anymore. But tomorrow is a new day and I will prevail. Plus IM going shopping tonight and it will be better. Shopping therapy. yay. I like how it is outside right now, its warm but pouring rain and really loud thunder and lightning-ing. hmmm, well I guess that's all for now.   oh and I have decided to take gym during the school year next year. I hope it doesn't suck too bad.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so I have to get another 1/2 credit for gym class. I can do this a few different ways. but there are serious drawbacks to all of them: 1. Take it this summer: missing family vaction, staying home alone for a week 1.5 Take it second session: dont know whos gonna be there 2. Take it next year:changing sched. and being all sweaty and disgusting during classes 3. Take it next summer: missing out on $1500 bucks, pissing off granny. (that could be REALLY REALLY dangerous) 4. Take it junior year: out of the question  SO i totally have no idea what to do. help me out guys.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I saw a movie with Megan and Chels. "Mean Girls", the one with Lindsay Lohan. IT really opened  my eyes. I think that people think I am mean. Which, I'm not. In class, when people like, say hi to me or something, i usually dont say anything. Instead i'll like wave or tilt my head up. So the my May resolution is to be nicer to people. Anywho, the movie was good. I give it one thumb up. Today, I really want to go shopping but, Megan doesnt really like the mall and Chels is with Sara, and Lauren is probably with Jessica, and Stu probably has family obligations. That means i won't be going to the mall. I will be online shopping. yay. well im outie. Ps. i don't like how blogger is all wierd now.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Boef is beef in french. (yahoo, i know one whole word!) Speaking of French...I am being forced to take an honors french class next year and it blows major chunkage.  Anyway, we are done running in phys ed thank the lord. and i even passed the mile test. by like a minute.  well today was Tiny Stu's birthday and i have major boef (beef with Lauren and Jessica, they totally left from my lame "party" early. Hey, maybe it was really bad, but it was Stu'f freaking birthday. I mean come on people, if not for me, stay for Stu. And Cake.  Cake is tastey.  Mmmm
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That girl who's going to the party, Delia...she doesn't even like me. It was horrible today at lunch, Jack and Rachael both went to the bathroom, and i had to sit there with her. and it was silent. DEAD SILENT. It was awful.  Whatever. I don't know why i am freaking out about this
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I have been dieting for the past two weeks, I'm on weight watchers. It isn't so bad. And, I have been in a better mood all week, so I think that maybe it's starting to kick in mood wise. (The book said that it would do that). Anyway, so we started the "jogging" *coughRUNNINGcough* unit in phys.Ed. and today Slave Master Glinka made us run for thirty seconds, and then walk for thirty seconds the whole friggin period. It may not seem difficult, but whooweeee, it is when you are out of shape. And Chelsea didn't want to go to yoga today, which is fine with me, but i wanted to just say that we were doing yoga, but then instead of going into the yoga room, we could just use the machines. Oh well. I also saw BOB today. BOB says that i need to practice and stop slacking. BOB says that i must know the three songs that he taught me how to play today, "or else". "Or Else" in BOB's case, couldn't be much. I told him to stop threatening me, or i might have to call my lawyer.   So in other news, this girl at our school Sam, Ben's girlfriend, is having a house party. Jackie and Delia are both going. Rachael was invited too, she asked me if I was going, but I honestly do not think that i am cool enough to go to this party. I mean, Jackie is cool, she was invited personally. I don't know about Delia, but whatever, she's going anyway. What happens if i get there and the people are all "ugh, who's this annoying freshman, trying to hang out with us cool kids???". I think that i might cry. And that my friends, is why i am not cool enough to be going.  outie
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, the 24 hour relay challenge.  It all started...*doodle oodle loo doodle oodle loo*  Rachael and I arrived at Olander at 8:30 on Saturday morning. We met the rest of the team, and set up our sleeping bags and stuff. Then all of the teams gathered around to sing the national anthem before the opening lap. During the song, i saw Jake. JAKE!!!! I love Jake, he's so hott. He's only an eighth grader, but he looks MUCH older. So while we were singing, he shouts "USA" really loud and totally embarrases me. But I don't mind. The relay starts and we do our laps and what-not.  Chelsea and I take a little break to watch the band preform, while other people do their laps, and the lead singer, Brandon, doesnt know the words to the songs he's singing, but hes very attractive, so it doesnt really matter. We tye-dye our T-shirts and then we go back to the tent.  Around five, Chris, Lauren and Jessica just HAVE to leave. So once they left, we did a couple more laps, and some other stuff happened...LIKE ALEX and SARA. Sara who i strongly dislike, and Alex who is cute, smart, and funny are practically oogling in my face. this upsets me.  Later around seven, chels and i hit the kareoke place. where chelsea falls madly in love with Ben. For this, i cannot blame her. Ben is ridiculously good-looking. We stay forever to watch him sing, and he does, and the people love him. Ashley, who was sitting in front of us, asked him how old he was, he's in eighth grade too. What is with this younger boy thing???  We walk back to the tent and who stops me? JAKE of course, along with his little buddy asking me for my wrist band. I GLADLY give it to him. and he walks away.  Any way Ashley Chels and I harrass some little kids, and they cancel the relay at 11:30, and i go home. thats about it.  WAHOO!  Around five, Chris, Lauren, and Jessica just HAVE to leave. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so micki wanted me to go to Hooters for dinner tonight. i was skeptical, but i agreed. so then i get there and our overly friendly skankoid waitress sat us down ect...so my salad came and i was disecting it, because that's what i do, and i found A  FREAKING GIANT MOTH  in my ceaser dressing. i was so grossed out, and then skankoid came and was all "oooh im SO sorry" but she was really like, haha stupid non-sluty girl.   So we went to Jan's and i got a nice chillidog instead  The end
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what the hell was i thinking last night?? This is not a good idea. in fact this is the dumbest thing i've ever heard. wow. sorry for my momentary lapse of stupidity.  Anyway I woke up at SEVEN then i went back to bed till ELEVEN and watched Dawson's creek and ate cheerios. I   previous posts have been removed because they made me sick. here are some non sickening things from them.  Taco bell has fun sauce. The show with Delia was good.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's thundering outside and it's freaking me out. Not because i'm scared of stoms...but because my power could go out if theres a storm. and when the power goes out there is the HORRID sound that comes from the basement, i think its the subpump or something. i dunno. but it's the most god awful sound ever. ok let me give you people an idea of what it kind of sounds like.  Lets say its three in the morning and you are SOUND asleep. Then your alarm clock makes that ungodly buzzing sound right in your ear! Thats what its like. Except much worse.  much much worse.  Anyway, it hasn't happened yet, but if it does you can be sure that i will not be in this house. i will be at laurens, or chelseas, or megans, or even...dun dun dun...my mom's.  SO Delia has decided to not talk to HWMNBN for a whole month. This should make it much easier to forget about him, because that's practically all she talks about. YAY.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my eye is twitching! its so uncomfortable i can hardly stand it. So today i was going to go see Harry Potter with Megan and Chels. Except Chelsea has to go to her brothers baseball game and won't be home until six. and the movie is like three hours long ish, and nobody will want to pick us up at nine, so we aren't seeing the movie today. THAT is why my eye is twitching. I'm feeling rather complainy today so i'm going to go mope in my room.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mick bought me the bracelet! but not the copper one...the silver one. YAY
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok i just got back from the art festival, and there was some AWESOME stuff. Like this native american girl was making these copper bracelets with turquoise stones in them, oh man i wanted one so bad but they were tres expensive. And like any great outdoor...er...festival thingie...there was my favorite kind of lemonade. you know? that kind thats mostly just water and sugar and theres like half a lemon squeezed in and then they shake it all up? Man, i drank a whole large one by myself and i had the hiccups for like ten minutes!   Hm, what else? Chelsea spent the night yesterday and we went Krogering. I  
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I missed the broomball meeting yesterday because I was hanging out with Delia. Lauren sounded pissed. But I just forgot, SOMETIMES people make mistakes. So now I have no idea what's going on with the team. :( But I had a good ol' time with Delia, we watched 10 things I hate about you...Which should actually be 12! Things I hate about you, and we went to Good Will and the head Shed, I bought a Marilyn Monroe poster that I cant hang anywhere cuz there's no space on my walls...So I had to put it REALLY low, so its like almost touching the carpet. And He-who-must-not-be-named put the X over my heart. Literally, and methophoricaly speaking.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, on the way to my dad's house, I saw crazy Ed on his lawn. he was standing in his yard playing croquette at six in the morning. as our car zoomed past him, he stopped and waved, although only for a second. at first glance you would probably think that its funny seeing somebody like crazy ed. I did. but day after day seeing him out there sometimes just sitting on an old wicker chair, watching the cars pass, you start to imagine what he's waiting for. why he isn’t out living his life like the rest of the world? mom says its because he's a loser- a bum who couldn’t amount to anything. I think he's just lonely. maybe he's waiting for a friend, somebody to wave back.  I arrived at school and was greeted by my friends at my locker. I gathered my books and together-yet separately, we walked to the commons area before class started. they were once pace ahead of me the whole way there. they sat down at our regular table where all of our other friends were seated and like always, there was an empty chair. the second chair in, that was my seat. everyday I sit down in that seat and everyday the girls at the table say "hello" to me, and I say "hi" back. they make mindless small talk and encourage me to join their conversations by asking "what do you think?". and I will politely respond giving them the opinion that they want to hear. but sometimes I really think, 'are you even listening to me?'. I know that they hear me, but do they listen, do they really care what I have to say? it would seem to the untrained eye, that if they didn’t care...they wouldn’t ask. but things are not always as they appear. nothing is black and white anymore, every area is just gray.  I go to all of my classes throughout the day, listening to our teachers drown us in facts about the 'real world'. and I wonder to myself...have we been living in the fake world? is your world any different than ours...at least you get paid to hate your life. we don't. the teachers here have no passion for what they teach. our history teacher might as well teach computer science, as long as they have a steady job, a paycheck. did they ever have strive to educate the young minds of tomorrow? to mold them into the adults they will become? Maybe...but I doubt it.  I get off the bus everyday at 2:45, get the mail from the rusty old box on the porch, and go inside. It’s my favorite time of day. I’m alone and there’s nobody around to crash my train of thought, nobody to interrogate me on whether or not I have a bathroom pass. my dad doesn’t come home until later, so I make popcorn and read by our electric fireplace. its sort of ironic, having the electric fireplace running in the early summer while the AC is going simultaneously. hey that’s America for you. I finish my homework by four and write my dad a note saying I went to bed early.  I slip off my jeans and crawl into my unmade bed in my messy room. I watch a spider walk cautiously across my wall towards the open window. it hypnotizes me and I cannot stop watching it. the next thing I know the garage door is opening and my father is walking through the door. he stops to read my note, and I hear him walking up the steps. an overwhelming sensation of dread and anxiety flushes over my body as I lie motionless in my bed. he knocks on my closed door and I say nothing. he walks away, avoiding confrontation for today-successful. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went out to see Rent with micki last night! it was wonderful and there were four of the original brodway castmates in it. I always forget how much i love the theater, i wish i had enough balls to get up on a stage an act. I think it would be so fun to be an actress. Anyway other notes from the play include: lots of cute rivers cuomo boys, lots of fancy nut mix being sold for three dollars, and me spilling coke on my purse. I had a good time.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There must be something wrong with me, I swear to god. Everybody LOVES my friends...A certain square loves Chelsea, Brandon loves Megan, Jeremy loves Jackie, Eric and Kyle and Ben love Delia, B2 love each other, I have no one. NO ONE. I should just take my computer and go live in a hole in the desert with Osama. He'd love me. OH NOOOOO the only person who loves me is Osama!!!!!! I mean, I really don't get it. I'm not really mean to people...Ok I'm kind of a smart-ass, but that's not SO bad is it?? I'm not terribly disfigured, I have boobs too! And it's not like I'm intellectually challenged...I'm taking THREE honors classes next year! UGGGGGGHHHHHHHHHHH. My life is in shambles and I am sad.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is Sean's live journal. He's my favorite person to admire from afar. He has lots of peircings and doesn't do drugs...he also happens to LIKE death cab. yay for sean! ahem copy and paste this in your own journal. With your own answers, not mine retard.  Top five bands: 5. Death Cab for Cutie 4. RHCP 3. Jason Mraz 2. Incubus 1. Weezer  Top Five CD's: 5.Audioslave-Audioslave 4.Incubus-Make Yourself 3.RHCP-Californication 2.OurLadyPeace-Happiness is not a fish and whatnot 1.Weezer-Pinkerton  Top 5 Songs: 5.Sex and Candy-Marcy Playground 4.MMMbop-Hanson...shut up i hate you all. 3.Sunburn-Fuel 2.Golden Years-David Bowie 1.El Scorcho-Weezer  Top 5 Live Bands I haven't been to many concerts but, heres what i know... 5.Smile Empty Soul 4.Magna-Fi 3.Fuel 2.Barenaked Ladies 1.Weezer (would be the ULTIMATE cool...but sadly i have not seen them)  Top 5 Bands you're embarassed you like: 5.Ace of Base 4.Dave Matthews 3.Dashboard Confessional 2.Brittney Spears 1.Justin timberlake  Ok i'm pretty sure i included everything. god, that was challenging...like spelling.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      all i can say is...Mary Peterson must see this movie.   and.   "Whenever god closes a door, he always opens a window...for you to throw yourself out of"
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      looky what i found!   urlLink  I adopted a cute lil' baby jesus fetus from Fetusmart! Hooray fetus!      urlLink  I adopted a cute lil' emo fetus from Fetusmart! Hooray fetus!    i love little emo fetus. jesus fetus is funny teehee
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   Your Years at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry        Name         Age         House     Gryffindor  Hufflepuff  Ravenclaw  Slytherin       Family Line     Muggleborn  Half-Blood  Pure-Blood        Dated      Ernie Macmillian        You are well known for      Always getting detentions       Percentage of student body you shagged -  76%                                                                             How do the staff and students feel about you      Will you Marry me?!?!!              This   fun quiz   by  urlLink  lady_ameily   - Taken 105452 Times.          New! Get Free  urlLink Daily Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so megan chels and i went to the strawberry festival last night, and i spent 20 bucks! each ride was like four dollars! it was crazy. we went on this really cool hang-glider ride, and there was this SUPER HOTT Australian hottie running it. he was amazing. and we went on another spinny ride and there was yet another hottie working the ride! it was hott carnie night. anyway, four rides later i was on the verge of ralphing my organs out and we went home. chelsea spent the night, we got some pizza and watched that howard stern movie, some guy gets hit in the face with a frisbee. its so funny. ok well im feeling good today, i just cleaned the WHOLE downstairs, so when the PUs get back from vacay, i will get tons o cash. yipee!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dudes i am at chelsea's house right now and it is craaazy! Her dad is yelling, the dog is barking, chels is vaccuming and nick is rambling! ahhhh! later we are going to la fete au fraises (strawberry fest 2004 baby WHOWHOO!) anyway, it should be a good time. i will also be home alllll night and if you wanna do something just ring me up. i guess thats all 4 now.   G.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its stopped raining! weeeee!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was my first day at grandma's house. yay we went shopping, because i needed bras. and i got five of them and a victoria secret credit card and a new prada backpack its pink.  i also saw my good bud Em today because she was in town from DC. we went for chinese, and it was tastey. yum  i guess thats all  oh yeah, how bout them pistons?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   Ultimate Highschool Quiz        Name         Favorite color     red  black  pink  blue  purple  green  yellow  orange  white       Sex         Favorite type of music     country  industrial  techno  pop  rock  metal  punk  pop  rap  none  other       Dorks are..     gay  losers  hella rad  diseased         Sporks are..     a kitchen utensil  awesome  stupid  lame  gay        Your classmates think you are..      a Skater        You will graduate at age 18.      FALSE        Will you get laid in highschool?     (8)  -  It is certain.   - (8)     What percentage of the student body hates you? -  1%                                                                             Largest amount of cash offered to you for sex      $222.57              This   QuickKwiz   by  urlLink  imabigburrito13   - Taken 39128 Times.          New - Kwiz.Biz  urlLink Astrology and Horoscopes  
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today has been blah. i am going to my grandma's later...my friend from D.C. is in town b/c her grandma died, so i thought i'd see her...try to cheer her up i guess. I'm sort of sad today, i'm not really sure why. I downloaded a new ringtone to make me feel better, its neat. Say it aint so-by the best band ever. its sort of quiet though, im scared i wont hear it if it rings.  anyway im off i guess, going to work on the novel for a bit, then take a nap. i hope everybody elses summer is going better than mine is  G
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i'm back from the cottage, but only for a short while (until 5:30). But when i go back, i will have my cell with me! yay! So yesterday, i was on the boat with Jason and he wanted to go skiiing, and i told him that i would drive the boat but he said no. so he asked Ian to do it. Ian is a guy who lives on the lake aussi. Hes 15. and a nice kid. BUT he's a redhead, so theres not even a tiny chance of me ever liking him. Anyway, so ian was walking over to the boat and then these girls who claim to be 15, but are actually 12-13 ask if they can come too. UGH it just made me so mad. those stupid skanky girls. god, why dont they just go home and get pregnant or something. we ended up taking them anyway and i was pissed. the end!  BACK AT THE COTTAGE.... the anti-christ, aka Devyn aka the nine year old was being annoying so i was forced to stay in my room until dark when she sleeps. its like HELL there when i dont have any friends to go with. I had a complete mental breakdown when i was sitting in my room because i'm a spoiled brat and it has to be my way, and its sad. i was angry at the world, and was being dark and moody in my room by myself. i also liked how nobody came in to check on me after FIVE hours. FIVE. i could've slit my wrists! but they wouldn't have known. i'm so sure. anyway, im better now that i am home away from the anti-christ.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      contact me at the cottage  2153541 thats my mothers celly...i forgot mine.  boohoo
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so heres the deal. my parents are on vaction in the UP so i have to stay with my mom allllll week, its a bummer. So right now i'm at Jason's parents' house. (jason=my mothers bf). on friday i DROVE up to the cottage. me, yes me, behind the wheel. and then i chilled for awhile before Jason invited us on a boat ride! whhoowhoo! but the boat is having issues, so we didnt get to ride in it for long. my evil stepsister is also here.  devyn shes nine. ewwwwwwww  anyway, then today me and my mom went to the movies and saw the stepford wives, it was ok. now we are here at jasons parents house and we might go on their new pontoon...although it is kind of chilly.   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we picked up chelsea on the way to mejer yesterday. we found some stupid sunglasses and some stupid hats and walked around the store with them on. then we picked up some stove-top sidedish and a fly swatter. we also bought giant gumballs. we had a good time. Then today we played some MarioParty and frolicked in the rain. we tried to have a rubber duckie race in the puddles, but the duckies werent moving. :( anywho life is dull and raining and i have to go to the cottage this weekend by myself. unless any of you would like to go? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         You are   29%   geek     You are a geek liaison, which means you go both ways. You can hang out with normal people or you can hang out with geeks which means you often have geeks as friends and/or have a job where you have to mediate between geeks and normal people. This is an important role and one of which you should be proud. In fact, you can make a good deal of money as a translator. 		  		 Normal:  Tell our geek we need him to work this weekend.   		 You [to Geek]:  We need more than that, Scotty. You'll have to stay until you can squeeze more outta them engines!   		 Geek [to You]:  I'm givin' her all she's got, Captain, but we need more dilithium crystals!   		 You [to Normal]:  He wants to know if he gets overtime.   		      urlLink Take the Polygeek Quiz at Thudfactor.com      I'm an Atheist!    urlLink     Which Enemy of the Christian Church Are You?     urlLink Take More of Robert & Tim's Quizzes   urlLink Watch Robert & Tim's Cartoons       you are either a record nerd or not a scenester at all. you are the coolest of the bunch. bravo, dude.    urlLink   what type of lame scenester are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, sorta. i got to sleep in for an hour and it was really nice, but then i took my english exam and it was hard! i am usually really good at english but i didnt even understand the essay question. then i went to chem and that test raped my in the ass. big time. i guessed on more than half of them. and the wierd thing is, they passed out quater grades, and i had a 100% in the class. so wtf? anyway it was the last day and all is right with the world. huzzah!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      x. i ____ Amanda x. Amanda is ____. x. if i were alone in a room with Amanda, i would _______. x. i think Amanda should _____. x. Amanda needs ______. x. i want to ____________ Amanda. x. someday Amanda will ________. x. Amanda reminds me of _______. x. without Amanda _______. x. memories of Amanda are ________. x. Amanda can be __________. x. __________ is how i describe meeting Amanda. x. worst thing about Amanda is _________. x. best thing about Amanda is _________ x. i am ________ with Amanda.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      depression.  i dont know what it is, but i am so bummed.  nothing is fun anymore im going to the doctors=extreme stress i wrote a song today my exams are f-ing hard and i have to go now
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just kidding.  today i got to wake up late because i had no exam first period, then my dad dropped me off at school. then i realised that i had nothing to do second period either! So i went to Chilis with Megan Kayla and Jessica...but it was closed, so then we went to Subway! But it was closed too. THEN we went to McD's and it was open yay! Jessica is scary in the car, she almost killed us.  THEN i had to go to my phys. ed exam. MAN it was tough. we walked a whole five feet to Krogers. Then i slept in a tanning bed for fifteen minutes. Then i went to Kroger to grab some grapefruit juice. yummy. then we walked the whole five feet back to school exams are awesome.  AFTER that i went to Jackie's house with her Delia, but while we were on the bus another bus totally rammed into us from behind. but i'm ok. dont worry! teehee and now, i am home trying to "study" for my chem exam.    its not working out.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just wish that everybody would just go away? like fall into a giant void in space for awhile?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so after i get home from chelsea's yesterday, i do some stuff, take a shower and get online. while online i find out a number of things: 1.Megan, Christine, Joanna, Jessica, and Lauren all go out to paint the rock. 2.I am not invited, neither is Chelsea. 3.Delia was going to do it with E.N. 4.I was getting picked up in 10 minutes.  Now, i am not mad about the rock thing, actaully, i couldn't care less. Chelsea was a wee bit angry. I was having a mini-stoke when i heard about 3. (im better now though)  So after i was picked up, we went to Max and Erma's and i was going to spend the night at megan's with her and delia. but then i didnt because of megans mom or something. SO THEN i spend the night at chelseas. Now, last weekend, megan and ryan and i were supossed to get tipsy at four in the morning, and i was excited. but then we decided that it was too late and that ryan was a violater. so we didnt get to do it. NOW delia is over at megan's and they are going to do it and i cant get out of chelsea's house because her parents are uber freaks and wake up and lock all the doors and windows and such ON THE HOUR!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    so i didnt get to do it. i texted megan and told her then she mentioned something about E.N. comming over, but i couldnt tell if she was serious or not. i was having a hard time because of the delia e.n. sex/hard drugs thing. so im not really sure what was happening. but what i do know is that i am really upset that megan would do this without me. because we were supossed to do this for the first time together, because thats what friends do. and i am not sure how long she has even been friends with delia, but i am not happy. at all. i dont even know if she went through with it or not because SHE TURNED OFF HER CELL PHONE AT 4:10 LAST NIGHT SO I COULDNT GET AHOLD OF HER. i dont know if shes mad, or what because i couldnt get of of Chelsea's house. ITS FREAKiNG imposible, and she probably thinks, "oh shes just too chicken to do it" but, i guess thats what she'll have to think because i REALLY wanted to do it. there was just no way. and if she did it with DELIA and not me, i will have a SHIT FIT.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thats saturday in french for you non-frenching people. frenching meaning speaking french. not sticking your tounge in someones mouth.  anyway   so today i was at paneras studing my little (actaully not really) butt of with stu and chels, and well, i actaully studied and thats all. then i went to chelsea's house and layed around on the deck for awhile.  micki's foot is broken or her ankle. i can't really remember. so she can't come upstairs. teehee. free computer usage for me. well, thats all i guess, i didnt wake up until 12:30 this morning. it was grandtastic. No rach, im not going to maxwells tomorrow, i will call you later and tell you of my adventures. sorry i didnt think to invite you to the thing. it wasnt that great. delia's friends hate me.  love amanda
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well today I went to see the uncertain 5 at the Masonic. They were pretty good, I'm not really into the whole punk-ska thing, but I enjoyed myself. Before, me Delia and Chelsea and megan were wandering around and I just feel super uncomfortable around that whole little group. I feel like they all hate me. MAN I JUST WANNA BE COOL.   ok I know that was lame, and I apologize. Anyway, so megan asks me to call kevo while we are there, and basically, it was not good. And I feel sad for her. Then, we were "backstage" its actually the ladies area leading into the bathroom, and e.n. came in looking all hott with his base and his cigarettes looking all nonchalant, and wondrous. uh, anyway, and he was literally, like four inches away from me when he was talking to Delia and he didn't even say one word to me, so I was like "whatever". So the show was fun and delia's mom picked us up, and now I am here, and updating for my blogging buddies.   yay
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just made up an awesome new solo for a weezer song i like. i love that i can solo now. its so fun to say. "yeah, i gotta work on my solo" heehee  anyway, the SITUTATION is sort of under controll i guess. i think i can handle it. somewhat. i dont really know. its really emotionally difficult for me to process.  "I wont worry my life away"- J Mraz
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how could somebody find out about that? i mean, it was all in good fun, but the only people who knew were : jessica, lauren, chels, megan, jackie, delia, rach, lauren m and stu. why would they say anything. UNLESS...people read this? do people read my blog? what the hell, dont they have better things to do than listen to me ramble on and on??
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my lifemy life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER  MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my lifmy life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER e MY LIFE IS Omy life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVERVER my life is over MY life imy life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER s OVER Over is my lifemy life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER  MY LIFE IS OVER my life is over MY life is OVER Over is my life MY LIFE IS OVER  please kill me now.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i must be one of the biggest losers of all time. i have went into a slightly red-headed infatuation with E.N. i was at his web-site and reading all about his hunky goodness and then i stopped and was like what the hell am i doing here? he doesn't even know who i am.  what am i supposed to do? there are only a select few days of school left. he MUST find out who i am but at the same time, no, he cannot, because if he did, he'd think i was a total freak. now, i've heard some talk about him "he smokes, he has a fondness for alcoholic bevs, he likes to do drugs, hes a man whore" and ive also heard that hes actually not that attractive up close. (this i have reason to doubt) anyway, i am just very confused and i shouldnt be because its not even a big deal. BECAUSE HE DOESNT KNOW WHO I AM i apparently need to get out of this dillusional state of mind where i think that life is a musical and that one day he'll come up to me in the hallway start singing "your song" by elton john and spin me around while im wearing a gorgeous red satin dress.  its simply not happening because i am a loser and he is not. sigh. any advice?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...a poem by Amanda  Tuesdays are crappy so today was not happy I played tennis 'til ten I accidently smacked Ben Mr Vens is a fox and I found a box i've developed west nile its cramping my style i didnt really find a box i could think of anything to rhyme with fox mrs michels still hates me   the end.   p.s. redheads are shifty 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On July 30th 2004, Katie Hodges was killed in a car accident. She wasn't my best friend, but she was always so considerate. So helpful and polite to anyone and everyone. We only had a few classes together, but I will always remember her just as she was...smiling and laughing, always pleasant. I will miss her and I hope that wherever she is now, that she is still smiling. We love you and will never forget you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My grandma is so cool. She just IMed me and told me that she had lunch with her old friend...who happens to be Adam Brody's Grandma. How SWEET is that? I love Adam Brody there is practically a bond between us already. His Grandma likes my Grandma...That's all you really need for a successful marriage right? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well looks as if i'm not going to see the movie after all. i wish i had more friends that didnt hate me. not that they do hate me. i mean some of them do but whatever you know what i mean 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So I was playing the Sims this morning and I totally think they should make teenager Sims. They could do everything that the adults do except they would have crappy jobs like fast food workers or bus boys/girls. They would also have the option to "sneak a drink" from the little mini-bars. hahah it would be most excellent. ANYWAY, all of my friends are busy cleaning and I feel that I should go clean too...Except I am terribly terribly lazy. But I did spray some windex on the TV. Tonight I think megan and I are going to go see that new M Night Shamalamadingdong movie...The Village. It should be good fun. Last time I saw a scary movie with megan she spilled popcorn allll over herself and it made me laugh. :D I think Lauren and Christine are mad at me, but I wish they weren't. I also hope that Lauren doesn't read my blog because I say things about certain people that live with her that I don't think she would like and would be totally grossed out about. The End PS my dad bought milk yesterday, so I got to have my raisin bran this morning. yay raisin bran!   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dammit. somebody just im'ed me and i thought it was somebody that i wanted to talk to that i haven't talked to in a long time...but it wasn't. it was Ian Kwasoski.   &nbsp;  &nbsp; (no offense Ian if you see this.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I haven't really had anything to do all day except  think . This is usually not a good thing for me to do for long periods of time. Either  bad things happen , or  bad things happen to other people , or  natural disasters occur . In this case though, nothing too horrid has happened. But I have come to realize that I will never catch my one   true love  . And I have found out why!  I am pure evil . Its totally true. I am going to hell and I know it. First of all this love of mine, I'm sure some of you know him,  he has a girlfriend  who is is in love with, he  doesn't know I exist anymore , and a lot of  very very pretty girls  have dated him and probably still want to date him. I had my chance...SURE it was awhile ago, but how would things be now if I had said something other than "  no, because I hate you  " THAT'S what I SAID. I'm so mean and heartless.&nbsp;&nbsp;I didn't hate him at all, in fact just the opposite of hate. I am so stupid sometimes. All I want is love, I mean, most people my age just want to get piss drunk, pass out, party some more, get laid... But I want  love ,  head-over-heels ,  can't eat, can't sleep ,  can't live-with-out-you love.  Is that so horrible? Am I a total freak for wanting that? I just don't know.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i signed up for drivers ed after i got back from Megan's and i have nobody in my class. Blakely Dye and the Jorlando twins are the only people that i would consider talking to.&nbsp; Blakely doesn't even like me for god's sake. and megan can't sign up because she has band camp. it sucks. shit! shit! shit!  But. i did have a good time with megan last night,&nbsp;i harassed her about brandon a little and we went on an early morning trampoline spree and took lots of quizes.  Yet, i am still super uber pissed that i have nobody in my class. and that lauren didnt invite me to Jessica's thing. SUPER PISSED. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me:  if you like pina coladas and gettin' caught in the rain...  Megan: Don't start that pina colada shit with me.  HAHAHAH 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're Soroity Slut Barbie!&nbsp; You're easy and you're really cheesy!&nbsp; Have fun with the entire football team.   urlLink  If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?    brought to you by   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that every female in my family has to smoke?  It's so unnecessary . Although, I'm not entirely sure that my grandma smoked...But I'm sure she did. Didn't everybody smoke in the fifties? Like the pinkladies all smoked in Grease. (except Sandy, but then she learned and got badass for Danny).  Anyway, I totally just found what I believe to be a joint in Micki's cig case. Now I have never seen a joint, but on TV this is what they look like. So I must break the family curse...I WILL NOT SMOKE EVER AGAIN.  Ok, I'm done with that now.  So later today I am supposed to see BOB but I really don't feel like it so I think that I will not go. And hang out with megan for a bit.  um, that's all I guess for today...Don't do drugs kiddles.       
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hmm. i am in the strangest mood today. i'm not sure what it is really...i haven't consumed any illegal substances in days, i slept for a good solid ten hours last night...i didn't eat anything blue yesterday or today. i'm not sure if i'm totally happy, or sad...but i'm not bored or tired. Maybe like i took a couple painkillers...minus the bendy woozy feeling. i've been disscussing it with megan, she says it's called "content". Content is a word&nbsp;we only see in books, like peaceful. this is the first time in a long long while that i have felt content with everything. i'm not anxious or stressed...not suffering from insatiable boredom. i have a sense of being, not here, nor there...just being.    &nbsp;  i am not feeling alone today  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So we arrived at the beauty Bar around the crack of dawn (or 10:45) and surprised Delia and got our manicures and pedicures. We also visited this store that had lipgloss that burned like fire...it was pretty cool. Then we got a limousine, except it was more like a  jankousine  and the driver happened to be a  wo-man-whoa  (Wo-man-whoa: A distinct gender that resembles a woman's body with a man head while showing both masculine and feminin tendencies)...so that was pretty scary. The ride was fun, then we ate at Zina's or something, some Italian restuarant where i had some brocollini. (Yes, brocollini). We then showed off the jankimo to some friends and went home and ate cake. It was glorious. (Except when Rachael smacked some cake in my face...that was TRES TRES upseting, and i could have&nbsp;killed her...but then her mother would have worried. By the way... RACHAELS A FOOL !!)&nbsp;Oh yes, how could i forget...TINY BABY! We set him ablaze a number of times and eventually melted him back in time. That's right, he is no longer Tiny Baby...he is now Tiny Fetus.&nbsp; I had fun.  "TINY BABY'S ON FIRE!!!"    &nbsp;  and today i almost killed people on airport highway...im never driving again.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  ever.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ann Arbor Art Fair in a Nutshell
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today i didn't do much of anything, my parents abandoned me at 8:00 am and so i was left with the pets until four. That's when deldo called me. She really wanted to go to ska fest, but i really didn't, and we were both poor, so we didn't go. Instead we went to her house and watched movies and made s'mores after deciding that setting up a tent in the back yard was too much work. AND then i went home and went to bed. And today should be fun. THE END  i hope you enjoyed my story. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday i ended up spending the night at Chels's house, we had a good time, watched some movies, played the sentence game, stayed up until 5:30...yeah, it was fun. Then today my dad couldn't get me for a long time so i hung out at their house for awhile and we went to Megan's to watch Big Fish. Anyway, now i am sort of in a wierd mood. I feel relaxed (which is odd, because i almost always have something to stress about or worry about) and happy. I'm hoping later Lauren will call and we can hang at her house. I suppose that's all for today.  Oh yes, Chelsea almost died last night when she took a straight shot of Creme de Menthe. It got all over her face, and she couldn't breathe. I couldn't breathe either...but only because i was laughing so hard.  aha. she makes me smile :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ooooh i  see blogger got all     grandtastically  fancy. i can  align paragraphs now, and add quotes and all kinds of fun stuff. Anywho, i am  home home again   . its awesome. i love my  house. so thats it i guess, i cleaned my gross    room so now it is sparkly clean  again. and now i am going to go clean the kictchen and the living room and the bathroom  because i am a  good  kid. THEN i have a lesson with BOB. I'm sure you are  all wondering why i always capitalize his name . Its  a mystery . Then  i think i am off  to buy deldo a  birthday present and then  maybe  hang ten with  laurie and stu. 
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i spent the day at Jan's pool it was nice, until it started thundering. I am absolutely freezing right now, and i might be getting a cold. which sucks. i'm getting some holes punched in my ears tomorrow and then im comming home. you can ring me up around nine if you wanna hang out. call the cell...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just got done spay-painting some lawn chairs...boy am i feeling goooooood! Hm, well i am coming home to lovey lovely Toledo tomorrow, and i am getting a hair cut. How does everybody feel about maroon highlights? If you think its a good idea write "splendid", if not then write "what the hell are you thinking" on my comments. And be sure to talk to me in my chatter box. YES my chatter box. its lovely. EVERYTHING right now, in this moment, is lovely. hooray to loveliness.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thats jewish talk. heh.  ok anyway, so i just got back from De-Lovely...it was so NOT lovely. It was more like Un-Lovely, well that wasn't as clever as it sounded in my head.  Well three more days.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i didn't get up until one today which was amazing, so i am in a super fantastic mood. here are some highlights and lowlights of yesterday  First we went to Jan's store because she was going to make me a toe ring-highlight:Got to give her my personal opinion and test her new line of monogramed rigns "love letters" lowlight:forgot to ask about toe ring  Then we went to Nordstoms to get shoes- highlight:got kick ass new tennis shoes. lowlight:couldn't find any pumps under 75 that i liked  After we went swimming at Jan's.  Next we went to some goddamed party. highlight:CHOCOLATE lowlight:children  Then we went out to dinner and there was excellent salad (HL) but we had a really shifty waiter-TED! (LL)  So it was a good day. OH and Chelsea came back from camp YAY!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah, i went to birmingham with Josh and Tatiana...we saw napoleon dynamite, it was pretty funny. then we walked the city aimlessly and josh found a soft sweater but didn't buy it. i'm glad i got to see them. So around five norbert picked me up and took me home so i could take a nap.  Jan and me were supposed to go to yoga at 7:45 but then she decided that she wanted to go to target instead, which is fine with me because i totally love target. Then at nine we met Mar and Ronelle for tai food. then we got some dairy queen.   Then i got home, and  i was tired. so i slept, and had the most awful dream ever. there was the abandoned building and me and megan had to stay there overnight for money. so we were up in the room with the little cots and we saw a bus pull into the driveway, and then all of these really sick people started getting off and they were like coughing and hacking all over the place. So then their flesh started like peeling of like in Cabin Fever, so Megan and i were freaking out, and i ended up calling my dad while we were hiding in the basement (we didnt want our flesh to peel off) and he came to rescue me. i was SO happy. but i left all of my stuff and my cell phone, so i was sort of sad.  ANYWHO. today i am going to Nordstoms to get some new tennis shoes and i'm having Jan make me a new toe-ring since mine snapped in half while trying to tighten it last week (tres upseting). MKAY well i love you all. toodles.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how could i forget...Today i found out that my mom's REAL name is Margarita. She changed it to Mari when she was 18. Her name WAS Margarita Martinez. Thats what happens when your mom is a full on Mexican and your father is a full on Italian. Thank god my dad is german. I wound up with a nice normal name...Italian+Mexican+German=norm.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well today i finally got my temps, and i look like a stoned arab in my picture. its hideous.  Then i got here, Detroit. And tomorrow I am going to Birmingham with Josh and Tatiana.  WhooWhoo
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hope i spelled that right... please everybody check out my buddy's new blogette, all the cool kids are doing it.  www.ogglethegoggles.blogspot.com  *cheer*
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I loved the 90's because everything in the 90's was simple. My biggest issue in the 90's was Mark...That horrible janitor with the mullet who made us sit in alphabetical order at lunch time. But now, nooooo everything is harder. It sort of sucks if you ask me. Well I haven't really been updating how I used to so here it goes, I am going to pour my heart and soul onto this entry...Dun dun dun   EARLIER  this week I found out that one of my good friends liked the guy that I had been jonesing for for months. Then she told him. I was crushed. But I am now getting over it and have discussed it with my friends and they all said to forget about him because he was an ass. So long Eric.   THEN , one day I was going over to Megan's house, but sadly I had no ride. So I called my parental units, and they were going to come and get me, and drop me off there. BUT INSTEAD, somebody else came to get me, somebody who was very special to me in the past. I was planning on going over to her house in my sweats and a dirty old ramones teeshirt, but I suddenly found my self getting into jeans and putting on my black lace underwear. Not that he would even see them, I mean he totally has a girlfriend. I even put on mascara. I don't know what the hell I was thinking, but it was very strange. So pulled into my driveway and I was SO nervous, and he was singing the pimp song you know, the dirt off your shoulder song? It was so cute. And the whole way to Megan's we hardly talked, but I said "thanks for the ride" when we got there and he was all "hey, no problem" and I was like...oh nooooo what am I doing? This can't be happening, because its HIM, and I was SO over him like three years ago. Not that anything DID happen, well things could have happened...But I was young and impressionable.   YESTERDAY , I went to the cottage, which is pretty much a party place, but thats besides the point. And Jason told me that my friend Ian (14) had OD'd on oxy-cotten. It was so strange to me that something like that could happen. I thought shit like that only happened in movies and in the ghetto. THis doesnt happen in Slyvania. Anyway, his older brother Dan (18) was with him when he did it, and Ian actually DIED for like two minutes and Dan was so strung out that he couldn't even do anything. I guess somebody called 911 or gave him CPR, he was taken away in cuffs in an ambulence. He also had quite a large stash of pot thats going on his record too. Chip (his dad) is sending him to a detox center in Lansing so I hope he'll be ok...he's such a nice kid.  Well, now that i have that all of my chest, maybe i can squeeze into a B cup. haha. I feel better, anyway, I am off to Detroit Rock City for the week so I'll try to keep updated from there. I'll be back on Monday though, so don't miss me too much.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      do you think i'm a strange ranger?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is Paul...he's my boyfriend! yay Paul!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AKA the DMV. Those bastards, i go in there to take my test and this stupid traffic officer guy is all YOU NEED YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY CARD! and i had the number, but I NEEDED THE SOCIAL SECURITY CARD and he just wouldn't shut up for like ten hours. Dane is right, they should just have somebody waiting at the door when you walk in punch you in the face.  THEN i was playing roller coaster tycoon for THREE hours and my F-ING computer has a virus so it like shut down and i didnt even get to save my park  :'(
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have a crush on a thirty year old.  Hes a red head. THEY ARE SO SHIFTY! He has a kid. its wierd. but he made me breakfast, it was so nice of him. but its still strange right?  Anyway, i just called Brando because Megan was too afraid to do it.  Lauren wanted to meet him and he can't come because his parents are mad at him :(  OK WELL my few days at the cottage were kickin' and i bought 3 new CDS while i was thurr. Franz Feridinand Velvet Revolver Magna-Fi....my lover is the drummer. He's only 28   just kidding hes not my lover...but at a show during a song called "Beautiful" he stopped playing the drums and pointed at me and winked. and i melted into a swooning plie of Magna-Fi love. IT was a defining moment in my life...I WILL MARRY A ROCKSTAR.  ok im all done now.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well my Dad finally rescured my report card from those dreadful office ladies and here goes nothing:  CALSS:                   QUARTER:                        EXAM:  art foundations             A                              A....yay, i'm not a failure phys ed                     A                              A.........i rule this school algerbra                    B                              C...at least its not a D world studies               A                              B...i hate your gross mole french                      A                              B...DIE MICHELS JUST DIE OK?!! english                     A                              A....I  Chemistry                   A                              B...whatever Thor is so creepy   The end. My GPA is 3.7ish. i wish i was smart like Rachael.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so today Megan Lauren and I went to Bob and Evan's...formally known as Bob Evans. And there was this crazy man in an electric wheel chair and he ran into Lauren and then he ran into the booth next to us and then ran into Lauren again, and i was trying soooo hard not to laugh, and so was Megan so she shoveld a bunch of salad into her mouth to keep from laughing then she dropped some onto her shirt, so i started laughing hysterically because i really needed to laugh at the man in the wheelchair. we laughed for like ten minutes at the man in the wheelchair. and lauren didnt even notice! Does this make me a horrible person??  Anyway so also we found a horoscope guide for next year and i am supposed to be a love match with a taurus! January horoscope "its a new year, and with the new moon in your sign on the 10th (my birthday!!), you will have an exciting secret crush. a good friend fills you in on need to know info, and you use it to impress him. your world is in order finally" Ok it also says that Jan 10 is my lucky day.   if you know what i mean...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      seemed like a fun thing to do... x. full name = Amanda Glynn Goldberg x. birthday = January 10th 1989 x. zodiac = Capricorn x. piercing = ears...for about a minute x. tattoos = on my 16th birthday baby! x. height = i'm taller than Delia but shorter than Chelsea. x. shoe size = 8 x. hair color = dark brown x. length = shoulder-ish x. siblings = none thank god x. pets = Bowie and Lola and Max. x. last movie you rented = Donnie Darrko x. last movie you bought = The Goonies x. last song you listened to = Everlong-The Foofighters x. last song that was stuck in your head = So Damn Hot-OK GO x. last cd you bought = OC Soundtrack x. last cd you listened to = Weezer's blue album x. last person you've called = My mommy x. last person that's called you = Megan x. last tv show you've watched = Faking the Video x. last person you were thinking of = My soul mate x. you have a bf or gf = nope sadly x. you have a crush on someone = of course! x. you wish you could live somewhere else = indeed x. you think about suicide = on rare occasion x. you want more piercings = yeah...my nose x. you want more tattoos = well I want some yes, dotn have any right now x. you drink = why not? x. you do drugs = nope x. you like cleaning = cleaning is hell. x. you like roller coasters = yea dude x. you write in cursive or print = a bit of both really x. you carry a donor card = not yet but when im 18 sure thing  for or against ... x. long distance relationships = if it can be done more power to you x. using someone = against x. suicide = not cool x. killing people = completely not cool x. teenage smoking = probably not a good idea x. doing drugs = no. x. premarital sex = psh i didnt think anyone cared about this anymore, or ever x. driving drunk = so so so dumb x. gay/lesbian relationships = do what makes u happy x. soap operas = so stupid...yet oddly catchy  favorite ... x. food = i'm rather fond of popcorn at the moment x. song = maybe Scar Tissue...or El Scorcho x. thing to do = anything but TV...guitar...blogging x. thing to talk about = religion...damn republicans...music x. sports = tennis baby or hockey x. drinks = Mountain Dew and water x. clothes = cargigans...and teeshirts x. movies = The count of monte christo donnie darko kevin smith movies x. bands = weezer (of course)incubus white stripes RHCP OK GO...im up for anything x. cars = I want a 69 mustang convertable but i'm gonna get my dads buick. yay  have you ... x. ever cried over a girl or boy = i think so yes x. ever lied to someone = er uh, no no never. x. ever been in a fist fight = no...but i'm trying REALLY hard x. ever been arrested = no, i think my dad would have a fit. or kill me.  what ... x. shampoo do you use = panteen Pro V x. perfume do you use = Pink by Gap  x. shoes do you wear = my adida flip flops or my nasty arse all stars x. are you scared of = blue foods. its so unnatural  number ... x. of times you have had your heart broken?: a few x. of hearts you have broken?: probably none  x. of continents you have lived in?: 1 x. of drugs you've taken illegally?: none x. of people you would classify as true, could trust with your life type friends?: 2 x. of people you consider your enemies?: Nebela...UGHHHHHHHHHH x. of people from high school that you stayed in contact with?: uh still here. x. cd's that you own?: many x. of things in your past that you regret?: lots and lots  Faves..  Class: english Friend: all of the weenies all seven of them Illegal thing: EXPLOSIVES yay! Candy: all green candy  Dessert: i like vanilla icecream with chocolate chips...does that make me dull? Color: of the moment...coral...for always green and pink Website: mine...i guess? Place to go for fun: anywhere but here TV show: That 70s show...NO i love the 80s er wait. i dont know. its a tie commercial: the one where the guy is like "is that your chair" dont remember? ah, what can you do? Clothing item: my adida flip flops with the little nubbie thingies Store: Gap and Urban Outfitters TV channel: Discovery Animal planet NG Radio station: 88.7 Celebrity: Dave Ghrol CD: Weezer Pinkerton Name: i'm an old fashion kinda girl...im going with Jack and Kate  Preferences.. Chocolate or vanilla: vanilla Pen or pencil: pencil Cold or hot weather: cold Cold or hot food: cold Sweet or sour: sweet Salt or sugar: sugar Dark or light: light Dogs or cats: cats Markers or crayons: crayons Board games or video games: neither...ZZzzZZZ McDonalds or Burger King: BK Starburst or Skittles: starburst  Do you.. Like painting: definitely Like boredom: oh its the worst! Like phonecalls: who doesnt! 419 283 9030 Like school: no. unless...no. Like music: Love it with everything in me Like food: of course shithead Like skating: iceskating? then hell yes i love my hockey skates but i cant skateboard. Like swimming: sure thing Like shopping: love it Like animals: sure why not? Like jewelry: yea Like pink: any time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cheesecake is delightful i feel so very insightful  the creamy goodness makes me smile the extra pounds are worth the while  The chocolatey chips are very tasty i had two peices i dont mean to be hasty  BUT Cheesecake is yummy. *snaps for manda*
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "OH MY GOD I CAUGHT A FISH WITH MY BARE HANDS!" teehee Ok so at Jackies party thing it was really funny because there was a pond with man-eating devil fish in it. SO naturally we wanted to pay delia to catch one of them and she did it. it was grandtastic. BUT. it we didnt give her the dollar.  THEN we went to Jackies house and watched Donnie Darrko. that movie is so good and i love jake. hes the best.  ps. eric and i are secret soulmates
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so i just dragged my dad to Taget. the coolest store on the planet, so i could buy a camcorder. I looked online first to see if they had some that i could afford...and they did. THEN i get to target and they are all like a  zillion bucks and i was crushed. So me and my dad looked online again, and actaully read the discriptions of the camcorders, and all the ones i can afford are CRAP. total and utter CRAP. its not fair. why is everything i own CRAP?   heres an update from my days away at the cottage: played UNO with Kianna for TWO HOURS. Not even kidding Joe made me breakfast Jason went skiing I got sunburned played more UNO with Kianna and Joe thats it.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so I was at the mall yesterday with Micki because I needed clothes. And there was this very creepy guy like following me and oogling me. I was tres tres violated. SO I didn't get jeans or shirts or anything else that I went to get, I bought some cute cargo pants and some really pretty lip gloss. I spent 55 dollars. ON TWO THINGS. I need a job.  Today ded (drivers ed) sucked. But I sat by some new people so that was ok. There is even one guy who I might have a teeeeeeny little crush on. I also met one of Delia's friends who is in my class. My ass hurts really bad because they have those damn metal folding chairs that make you want to die. I'm sorry I don't have anything excellent to write about I'm not feeling very creative today.  and i still need a job.   badly. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so sorry that I haven't updated in a year! No, no, I apologize, I'm sure you are all so distressed that you haven't seen anything new on my beloved blog. Well here's the what's new in the mind of a semi-psychotic fifteen year old. Drivers ed sucks beyond comparison to anything in the world. EXCEPT Mrs. Michels's (aka Stupid) class. I have to sit in a crappy metal chair that hurts my bum for FOUR HOURS. Yep, that's right. But I made a new friend. Who's a senior. I have senior friends! neenerneener! Um, anyway, Delia is home so that's fun. BOB got mad at me yesterday because I missed last weeks lesson. But I was all "whatever BOB". And he seemed to understand. YAY. Well I suppose that's all for now. I'm going to the mall to buy new clothes and such. I'll update later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This has officially been the worst year of my life. I haven't decided it was just because of Katie's death, but it did suck so bad. School is the most awful place ever. I know some people say that they hate it, but they really don't. Because there are always some classes that you liked or had fun it. I didn't. I hated most of my classes.  I mean sure there were some fun times, but the majority sucked. My home life sucked too. My mom moved away with her gross boyfriend and I never see her. My dad works all the time and i dont see him ever either, Micki is home sometimes, but when she is-she's sleeping. My friends are always there for me though. not. There has been more goddammed drama this year than in the past two summers combined. Sorry to bore you with my ranting and raving. But i have come to a conclusion, I can't just wait around for life to push me face down in the mud. I have to live dammit!  I am going to make this comming school year the best yet.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>