<Blog>


<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Revising my previous post:  I said that Marxism now has become a product. Scratch that. Marxism has always been and will always be a product. Also, it has  always  been about exploitation. No other idea created by mankind has caused more misery and destruction on this planet than Marxism. Nearly 100 million Russians were killed by Soviet communism. 100 million in less than a century!!! How can the human mind even fathom that? If the population of the Earth hasn't learned that mankind is fallen by now then they will never learn. There is no natural progression towards a strain of Marxism that will work. It will never,  ever  work. Redemption can only come from God, not from a political system. There is no such thing as a heaven on Earth forged by mankind. That is a ridiculous pipe dream. Yes, maybe a few individuals or families can make Marxism work, but for it to work on a worldwide level requires the elimination (either through murder or dehumanization) of everyone who can't make it work. Those who don't learn from history are doomed to repeat it. As a society we have brushed the horrors of communist Russia under the carpet and have tried to ignore it. That is damned foolish. Mysticism unbridled by reality and a belief that mankind is evolving into a society of superhuman beings is nothing more than a fuzzy dream. Nietzsche, Darwin and Marx. Those three may have never killed anybody with their own hands but they have killed millions with their pens. We must never forget that.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          The other afternoon I was walking around CD Warehouse and I saw something unusual. They were selling a red Mao t-shirt. I kind of felt a light sickness and laughed a little bit. The idea of a t-shirt with Mao Tse Tung on the front is about as ironic as a Karl Marx lunch box. But that's what Marxism is these days. It's a product. It failed miserably as cultural and economical system years ago. Now it's a prepackaged way to influence people who don't think. Brutal dictators and murderers are pop culture icons and heroes to people who have no idea of their atrocities against mankind. It's kind of funny and sleazy at the same time that the people selling the Mao shirts are exploiting the free market to further communism. Capitalism is far from perfect (like Churchill said, democracy is the worst system of government except for all the other ones), but it incorporates free will. Yes mankind is fallen and freedom is still a very fragile thing. People can become slaves to consumerism but its always within their power to free themselves. Marxism and communism leave no room for free will. A utopian system will never work because man can never be perfect. Anyone who believes that man can live peacefully in an ideal utopian system has a rather naive and childish view of mankind. All forms of government are man-made creations and inherently faulty. That's why free-will is paramount. Yes, free-will allows for exploitation, mankind has the freedom to choose good or evil. Marxism doesn't give mankind the freedom to choose good. Virtue is greater than freedom. As much as we'd like to, though, we can not legislate virtue. Without free-will virtue is not possible. Just because somebody exploits the free market doesn't mean that the free market is inherently evil. It means that the people selling Mao shirts, just as all of us, are fallen.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Akira Kurosawa's first collaboration with Toshiro Mifune (aka the greatest actor ever) is a doozy of a cop film. Murakami is a rookie homicide detective who loses his gun and must go on its trail trying to get it back. This is golden Kurosawa. A simple set up, but masterful execution. This a great, great film that puts modern cop movies to shame. For those new to Kurosawa this is well worth a rent. Kurosawa fanatics will need to pick this one up. Another superb effort from Criterion.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You're Tuesday night consists of:   Reading 75 pages of a Steven King fantasy serial   Failing miserbaly to pick up a little Italian   Watching a minor Marx brothers' film featuring a really bad actor who's going way out of his way to make, "Jumping Butterballs!" a popular catch phrase   Falling asleep while listening to conservative bloggers interview Michael J. Nelson on the radio   You enjoy all of the above mentioned things (except failing to learn Italian) 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Jumping Butterballs!  Bubba Ho-Tep  is perhaps the single greatest and most important American film ever made. Well, okay, maybe not, but look at the cover. Damn cool. And the movie is too. Bruce Campbell is as funny as heckfire as a decrepit, aging Elvis and the movie is just a blast. Plus the DVD has a commentary by Elvis!!! How can you not love that? Really, how? Buy it now, or you're a cinematic loser.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so not to toot my own horn, but I'm starting to get a handle on this whole food thing. Sure, maybe I'm not Wolfgang Puck, but I do alright. Last night I made honey teryaki porkchops. They were actually halfway decent. I had some rice and mixed vegetables as well. So last night I sat down with my dinner and a glass of Merlot while watching Looney Tunes (never underestimate the cultural sophistication of a good Chuck Jones short). Disc 3 of the Looney Tunes collection features the short where a mechanical female rabbit lures Bugs Bunny to the castle of that Peter Lorre-look alike mad scientist and he has to escape the clutches of the big orange monster. Classic stuff. After dinner I was still lazy and watched two movies: Rainer Werner Fassbinder's  Lola  and  Tender Mercies  starring Robert Duvall. Both were flawed, but good enough movies to strike my interest. This weekend should be better than last (see below). Going to Kim Q and Kelly's party on Friday night then going to see  Shrek 2  later on. Then Saturday is my seemingly ill-fated  Life of Brian  discussion at Max & Erma's. I guess this whole film discussion group thing is not something a lot of people want to do. I can't say that I'm not disappointed, because I am. I'm not sure if I expected it to go well or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Went to Monday Night Discussion at the Oaks last night to check out  Monty Python's Life of Brian  on the big screen. It's been a few years since I've seen the movie. It's just as funny, if not funnier than I remember. It really is a great comedy. Although I noticed that no one was laughing at the jokes about crucifixion. It's hard to laugh at something so inhuman and monstorous, especially after seeing it in bloody detail in  The Passion . The film also seemed a little more sinister to me this time around. It really is a cruel little film, although I would wager that the film spends more screen time making fun of left-wing revolutionaries than it does organized religion. The discussion was pretty lame. An icky veneer of political correctness covering an unspoken belief that conservativism and religion are tools of oppression. Although I didn't expect much different from a Pitt professor. Everything that she mentioned as research for her book on Monty Python, I already knew just from general net surfing. Hopefully we can hold a more substantive discussion on Saturday night.  Before the movie they had a trailer for  Seven Samurai , which will be shown during the Midnight Movie festival. I'm already excited!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I officially love iTunes. Officially. It could turn into a problem, though. I surf through the site and think, "Oh, here's a cool song, it's only 99 cents." At my current rate I will end up spending like $100 bucks a month on MP3's, which is coming a long way from the good 'ol college network days. So far I've gotten three Frou Frou songs, three Pretty Girls Make Graves songs, "Ophelia" by The Band, one of my favorite Velvet Undergroud songs "Pale Blue Eyes" and that techno combination of Bowie's "Rebel Rebel" and "Never Gonna Get Old." While I'm there I'm checking for any Wilco songs that I don't already own (alert, I own them all) and I find something interesting.    urlLink      Apparently before Martha Stewart got thrown in the slammer she made album compilations for KMart. This one is actually a damn good record. Don't believe me, click the album cover. Eva Cassidy, Emmylou Harris, Roseanne Cash, Sarah McLachlan, and "How to fight loneliness" which is one of my all-time favorite Wilco songs. Then I look through the other Marthapalooza albums on Amazon. Here is a just a smattering of artists appearing: Elvis Costello, Barenaked Ladies, Nickel Creek, Billy Bragg, Keb Mo, Paul Simon, The Pretenders, Ray Charles, David Bowie (!). Has the entire world been turned upside down!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No matter how cool I think I am there is no escaping the fact that I am anything but. At least I can accept that. I started Saturday by milling around the apartment for a while then taking a shower and heading out. I decided to finally drop off the two rolls of fully exposed film that have been sitting on my desk for weeks (I'm way too lax about getting photos developed). Afterwards I headed to Eat'n Park for a cheap lunch with book in hand. I'm not even going to begin to go into the ironies of a person sitting alone in Eat'n Park eating a barbecue burger and reading  Gravity's Rainbow  (I think it's all part of the paradox of a person that listens to public radio and reads  The Weekly Standard ). Anyway, I headed home and watched  Interview with the Vampire  for the first time. It's an interesting movie. I liked the way that it explores vampirism as a kind of festering disease (kind of like  Nosferatu ), but the movie just has so many cheesy parts and Kirsten Dunst is so, so awful (I know she was only 12, but still). Then I watched almost the whole Flyers-Lightning game. I hadn't watched a whole hockey game in a while. The game was okay not great. Mistakenly thinking that the film-developing place was same-day service, I went to pick up the film. When the guy at the counter told me that it was overnight service he kind of chuckled at me (which is a great way to keep customers mind you). I decided that driving out and coming home with nothing would be a waste, so I picked up a small mozzarella and basil pizza for dinner. I made the pizza and watched the Preakness Stakes. It was the first time that I made a conscious effort to actually sit and watch a horse race. It was really weird. The horse racing community is a whole group of people on TV who clearly have no idea how to be on TV. It's kind of funny. First off, the actual race lasts less than two minutes, but the broadcast must be over an hour so they have to fill it with all this dead air analysis, including comments about a man who has the grave misfortune of being named Chappy Chapman. One of the horses lost its shoe and it had to be re-shod (I learned a new term from watching horse racing!). A bunch of different people interviewed the trainer asking what happened and she gave the same uninteresting answer over and over. After the race a reporter asked the winning jockey what he was going to do with his share of the prize money. His answer was, "I'll save it in case I don't get old." What?!? What in the blue hell does that mean? It was a surreal experience. All of this confirms my suspicions that the gambling community is really stupid and has no clue of their own ineptness. After eating, I was tired of sitting in front of the TV, so I decided to head down to the Beehive with  Gravity's Rainbow  in hand. I ordered a mocha and sat down at the first seat I came across, which happened to be a bar stool at a wobbly table. There were six girls in the corner. Instead of looking silly and moving to a different seat I decided to stay there, ending up looking sillier than if I had moved. There are mainly two reactions that I usually get from girls, ignorance and laughter. I could kind of feel them laughing at me. I wasn't sure, but I didn't want to find out, so I just buried my face in the book and tried to concentrate (which is really hard to do in the Beehive, if you've ever tried, especially since they have this really cool radio station playing in there that I can never seem to find anywhere else in the freakin' world. The Cure, Depeche Mode, and Bowie were all on while I was there. The only Cure song I can ever seem to find on my car radio is that stupid 311 cover of "Love Song." They should be tarred and feathered for that piece of crap.). I finished the short chapter in the book and gave up on the reading plan. I got an Internet card for half an hour and did some general surfing (no net at home). When I backed out of chair I accidentally elbowed the girl sitting behind me that I had no idea was there. I stuttered "Sorry" at her and she kind of looked away disdainfully. As I walked out I went to drop some coins in the tip jar. I had a few quarters in my pocket and meant to drop them in there. I was so disheveled by my WWF move on the poor girl behind me that I accidentally grabbed the wrong coins and ended up only dropping 15¢ in the jar that clinked really loudly right in front of the clerk. I walked in feeling really hip and cool and left feeling totally cheap and uncool. To add to my general feeling of uncoolness, my attempts to find the mystery Beehive radio station in my car were futile and I ended up finding some kind of 80's cheese night on a Top 40 pop station. They were playing Rick Sprinfield's "Jessie's Girl." To my own consternation I actually like this song (it's my pathetic cell phone ring tone). The only reason I like the song is that crazy scene at the end of  Boogie Nights  when Alfred Molina's drug dealer character goes off on a rant about mix tapes featuring above-mentioned song and "Sister Christian" by Night Ranger. If you've never seen  Boogie Nights , this scene is well worth watching the movie surrounding it. I would like the scene even if the rest of the movie was really crappy. The rest of the movie is actually fairly good too, it's kind of a modern day retelling of the parable of the prodigal son, only, you know, about porno. Anyway, I drove my open windowed, "Jessie's Girl" cranking automobile to Barnes & Noble at the Waterfront to kill some more time. I walked around for a while picking up books that I've wanted to grab for along time: P.G. Wodehouse's  Picadilly Jim ,  The Great Gatsby  and  A Clockwork Orange . I also grabbed the latest David Byrne album which was fairly priced for B&N. (I felt obligated since the show was incredibly awesome.) The record is pretty good, except for the back cover that features the hairy-armed Byrne in a pair of denim overalls. It kind of looks like Deliverance-character-goes-to-New-York-art-school. Yeah, weird. Let the above be a warning. When you spend massive amounts of time on your own you have weekend days like the one I just had.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so going into the day I was little frustrated at having found no one to go to the David Byrne concert. Right before I left the apartment I was able to feel acceptance and just decided to go an have a good time. The concert was, at the risk of understatement, flippin' amazing. Literally one of the best five shows I've ever been at. Byrne played an eclectic mix of music, mixing in solo songs with well-placed Talking Heads classics and a few covers. The musical styles ranged from rock, Latin, opera, techno, etc. The performances were superb. The Tosca strings added a lot to the songs, especially a vamped up version of "Naive Melody (This Must Be The Place)" (my favorite Heads songs) and a richly layered version of "Psycho Killer." The show was incredible and makes me want to go back through some of Byrne's solo catalog. I think I'll be going if Byrne ever comes back to Pittsburgh. Just a fun and incredible night of music.  FYI, the four other shows in my top five (in no particular order):  Wilco @ Point State Park (summer 2003): A free outdoor show at the Point. The band came out and played some of their best atmospheric songs in their catalog, then reappeared for two hard-rocking encores. (they'll be back at the Point on June 6th and its free again).  Barenaked Ladies @ AJ Palumbo (fall 1998): My first encounter with BNL live. Your first BNL show is like a door opening to lifetime fandom of the band. It was right before the band got huge and they played in a cramped and sold-out AJ Palumbo. I was sitting fairly close to the band. They played all the songs I had wanted to hear and it was just such a fun show. For the first time I had realized how creative and funny the band truly was. I've been to two BNL shows since and have always enjoyed their live efforts.  Saves the Day/Dashboard Confessional @ Club Laga (summer 2001): A packed Laga rocked out to a just getting off of the ground Dashboard Confessional and a hard-rocking set by Saves the Day. It was sweltering hot and everybody was just drenched in sweat and into the music. The best punk rock show I've ever been at.  Ben Folds Five @ Amphitheatre at Station Square (summer 1999): Literally one of the last shows the Ben Folds Five played together. The band gracefully mixed hard rockers and heartfelt ballads while being funny at the same time. Ben Folds is such an enigmatic performer and he displayed it wonderfully here. I like Ben's solo work, but I do wish the band was still together.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you're ever buying me a present and have run out of ideas,  urlLink this  is always an option.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Disregard the mentioning of  Au hasard Balthazar  playing in Columbus in the previous post. It's going to be in Pittsburgh prior to that.  June 14-17 at the Harris Theater. That saves me at least one trip to Columbus.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was looking through the Columbia House website trying to find some adequate DVDs to fulfill my membership agreement when I stumbled upon the  urlLink Billy Wilder DVD Collection .       If you click the little link there, you'll see that the box set of nine Wilder films runs for over $100. Columbia House had (mistakenly, I'm guessing) labeled the set at $23.99! The special edition of   urlLink Some Like It Hot  , which is in the set, runs for about $17 at Amazon. I quickly gobbled it up and had it sent off. I got the set last night and it's actually the big box set seen above and they actually charged me $23.99. I checked the site yesterday and apparently somebody over there had figured out that they had made a goof. The set was marked around $93.00. I don't know if anyone else discovered this error or not, but I ended up getting 9 great Billy Wilder films for under $3 bucks a piece. Here's the kicker. In the set are   urlLink The Apartment   and   urlLink Some Like It Hot  , two films that I already own on DVD. So, I'm going to take them to CD Warehouse and pawn off my extra copies. I'll probably get somewhere in the range of $10-$15 for them. In the end I'll have paid about $10 for a $100 box set! Thank you Columbia House.  Also for those interested in art films and are in the tri-state area the  urlLink Wexner Center for the Arts  in Columbus, OH will be showing two landmark films.  On June 25-26 you can catch Robert Bresson's legendary   urlLink Au hasard Balthazar   playing in a double feature along side of Jacques Becker's   urlLink Touchez pas au grisbi  .  And the real highlight will be July 29-31. They'll be showing a new 70mm print of Jacques Tati's   urlLink Playtime  . The film was originally shot in 70mm and should look glorious in the new print.  That's enough to get you excited (at least me anyway).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've just realized that there's something truly profound about Daffy Duck. His plight is so unbelievably human that you can't help but sympathize with him. Does anyone remember the cartoon when Bugs and Daffy have a vaudeville show? There's the marquee that has Bugs Bunny's name in huge flashing lights and then Daffy's name in tiny letters. When Bugs walks on stage he gets roaring applause for doing nothing then Daffy comes out does a soft-shoe dance and then slides on his knees towards the audience and there's nothing but dead silence. Doesn't life just feel like that sometimes.   When Bugs walks on stage he gets roaring applause for doing nothing then Daffy comes out does a soft-shoe dance and then slides on his knees towards the audience and there's nothing but dead silence. Doesn't life just feel like that sometimes.  In all likelihood Daffy should be the star of Looney Tunes, but the people want Bugs. Don't get me wrong Bugs Bunny is funny, but he's no Daffy. It's like the animators knew Daffy was the star but Bugs would always be more popular, so Daffy is always sour about being in Bugs' shadow. Anyway, this is why Looney Tunes are so spectacular. The characters are so well-developed and creative. Almost all cartoons pale in comparison to the Looney Tunes. That's the end of my Daffy Duck rant, you may now go on to the less silly aspects of your day.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay. The Oaks just announced their Moonlit Matinee schedule for this summer and if you're into film you have to be psyched. Here are some of the highlights (I will be at these!!!).  June 19 & 20: Seven Samurai June 26 & 27: Evil Dead II July 3 & 4: Monty Python and the Holy Grail July 10 & 11: Network July 24 & 25: The Manchurian Candidate (The original, not the remake) August 21 & 22: A Clockwork Orange  Tickets are only $4. Saturday showtimes are Midnight, Sunday times are 10:00 PM.  So cool.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, here's the dilemma. I like going out to interesting and different films and concerts, but I can never ever find anybody that wants to go. It can get a little frustrating. I don't mind spending time by myself, but sometimes it really gets to me. And I don't want to slum it and just do regular things, every time I do it feels like I'm selling out. Sometimes I feel like an elitist. I hope that's not true of me, it's not who I want to be. I think I need to take a long, hard look at that. So I have two tickets to the David Byrne concert tomorrow night and, so far, only myself going. I can't even begin to tell you how many times this has happened. It sucks because now the concert is looming over my head instead of being something that I'm anticipating and something that should be fun.   "Last night ... I ... fell asleep watching  Black Narcissus . Uneventful but par for the course."  Last night was pretty regular. I went home and read a few articles in the Weekly Standard then made some dinner (which is going better than usual). Then I was wandering around Barnes & Noble not really knowing what to look for. I walked around for about 20 minutes and didn't get anything. I went home and fell asleep watching  Black Narcissus . Uneventful but par for the course. I want to write but have no motivation at the moment. Oh, well.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went down to the Harris theater last night to catch  Stop Making Sense , the Talking Heads concert film. It's literally one of the best movies ever and it only cost 30 cents to get in. The postage stamp sized theater was only about a quarter full, but hey why should people see a great movie for practically nothing when they've got drinking to do. Okay done venting. Anyway the movie was freakin' awesome on the big screen. Worth the effort to get out and see it.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That's right. I've been so busy that I haven't found a free minute or two to post. So much stuff to talk about. I watched virtually all of the Reagan funeral coverage on that Friday. Lots of great stuff. I felt Margaret Thatcher, Bryant Mulrony, and Michael Reagan were particularly eloquent. I was at Support Raising Bootcamp (just outside Philly) on Monday and Tuesday of last week. It was a tiring experience and I cam back beat. Then the very next morning I had a half-day meeting at work and spent the rest of the day flying through all the backed up work from being off for three work days. That night I had small group at Bellefield at got home late and crashed again. Thursday the Financial department went up to Geneva for CCO New Staff Training to meet and present financial info to the new staff. It was a lot of fun to see all the new staff (which now comprises probably at least a quarter of our total staff). That night I went to see  Au Hasard Balthazar  at the Harris. The movie was fantastic (watch for a future MinEx article) but the Harris is really a crappy movie theater. It has one of the worst layouts I've ever seen. Say what you will about R. Sq. and Melwood, but at least you can sit in the middle in those theaters. Got a call from Cooke on Friday night to go out and see  Dodgeball , which was nice since my  Bubba Ho-Tep  party didn't pan out.  Dodgeball  was okay I guess. After seeing something as beautiful as  Balthazar  the day before, it did make me lament the sorry state of mainstream cinema. In a continuation of my "Evan Does Lots of Stuff by Himself Series" I went and saw  Seven Samurai  at the Oaks on Saturday night at midnight. What an incredible cinematic experience! The movie is about ten times better on the big screen and it was already on my top five movies ever list. Would have been nice to share it with someone, but it their loss, whoever that nameless metaphorical whoever was. Sunday was just crappy. I just spent a lot of time thinking about the cool stuff that I want to do this summer and not a lot of people interested in doing those things. I went to Richard Thompson that night, which was a mistake really. Being in a crowd by myself was lousy and I didn't feel like being there. So before my self-confidence hit a complete low I decided to leave the show early and go home to watch MSTs on the couch. That brings things up to speed I think.  Evil Dead II  is at the Oaks this weekend, no one else is going yet. I was invited to the Dave Matthews concert this weekend, but its way too much money and I've totally just grown out of the music (it feels totally dead and boring to me). Normally I would just say hell with it and go to spend time with friends but I don't think I can afford to go even if I wanted too. In other concert news Modest Mouse will be playing in my hometown on Aug. 10th. It's totally weird, but heck, why look a gift horse in the mouth. MM is growing on me big time. I love their complex and layered sound and the vocals are flippin' amazing. That's all for now. Hopefully updates will be more frequent (not that this one was all that interesting).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My MST thirst is ever growing.  Now there is a new website for " urlLink The Film Crew " aka Mike Nelson, Kevin Murphy, Bill Corbett aka the guys behing MST3k. The whole site is devoted to movie humor and is a lot of fun. Make sure to check out their audio sketch from the pilot for a possible NPR show (I can't believe Mike would possibly be on NPR). If the show gets picked up I might have to violate my prinicples and actually listen to NPR (I'll do anything for more Nelson, Murphy, and Corbett).  My favorite line: "Jake Gyllenhall bolsters his reputation as the guy you get when Toby McGuire's busy."  My other favorite line: "A corrupt cop is killed by corn silage. It was doubly ironic, because he had always hated corn silage."
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went and hung out at the Arts Festival all day Sunday. I finished the book I was reading (P.G. Wodehouse's  Picadilly Jim ) and caught Wilco's sound check. The show was incredible. The new line-up sounded great. I think this years show was better than last years (no "Via Chicago" or "How to fight loneliness" though)  Here's the setlist (the parentheses contain the album from which the song comes):    Company in My Back (A Ghost is Born)   Hummingbird (A Ghost is Born)   Ashes of American Flags (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   Heavy Metal Drummer (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   I Am Trying to Break Your Heart (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   War on War (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   I'm Always in Love (Summerteeth)   Shot in the Arm (Summerteeth)   Hell is Chrome (A Ghost is Born)   Theologians (A Ghost is Born)   At Least That's What You Said (A Ghost is Born)   Muzzle of Bees (A Ghost is Born)   Poor Places (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   I'm the Man Who Loves You (Yankee Hotel Foxtrot)   The Late Greats (A Ghost is Born)    ---------- 1st Encore ----------   When The Roses Bloom Again (Chelsea Walls)   One by One (Mermaid Avenue)   Sunken Treasure (Being There)   Handshake Drugs (A Ghost is Born)   California Sun (Mermaid Avenue)    ---------- 2nd Encore ----------   Spiders [Kidsmoke] (A Ghost is Born)   I'm a Wheel (A Ghost is Born)    A great set. They pretty much played all of  A Ghost is Born  except for "Wishful Thinking" and "Less Than You Think". That's cool, because I was curious to hear the new songs live. "Company in My Back" was a pleasant surprise and better than the album version. "Theologians" was great live too. However, the new Wilco live standards from the new album will most definitely be "I'm a Wheel" and "Spiders (Kidsmoke)." "Spiders" was awesome with the live band. The sky had just turned dark and the stage was drenched in dark red lighting. The band and the crowd both got into it and maintained unbelievable intensity for a song that runs over ten minutes. The energy and pace of "I'm a Wheel" makes it a great song to sing along too. Some other highlights were "I'm Always in Love", which is a song that I wanted hear that they didn't play last year. Only one song off of  Being There  but if I had to pick only one it would be "Sunken Treasure." The inclusion of a  Chelsea Walls  track caught me off guard, but was a nice surprise. All in all, a fantastic show that confirmed my belief that Wilco is the best band in America. If you weren't there you should have been.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wilco .  They're not the best band you've never heard of (I feel sad if you've never heard of them). They're simply the best American band today. Period. Seriously, I can't understand how people can't go to a free concert by the best band in America. It's so damn confusing.  Also, if I don't find some friends with common interests soon I think I will literally go crazy.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is from the MST3k website:   MSTies are funny. They laugh easily and comedy is an important part of their lives. And, despite a culture that tends to discourage women from having and displaying a real sense of humor, female MSTies are every bit as funny as their male counterparts -- or more so.   MSTies are nice. The show itself has a very positive worldview -- one that BBI (Best Brains) says is intentional -- and it tends to attract people who are sweet, easy-going and easy to like. As friends, MSTies are loyal to a fault.   MSTies are smart. You'd have to be to love a show with references to everyone from Nietzsche to Heisenberg to Shakespeare, and they are invariably intelligent, well-read, thoughtful and erudite.   But MSTies are NOT all sweetness and light. They can be cynical, hyper-critical and impatient. They do not suffer fools easily, they tend to question authority and can be downright harsh when confronted with anyone or anything they deem mediocre, stupid and/or pompous. The flip side of their loyalty as friends is that they can be formidable enemies.   Seriously, that's me in a nutshell.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Haven't updated in a while. Mainly because I've been so tired. I was up late on Monday night burning an MST DVD (San Francisco International - a moderately funny episode). Speaking of MST, I'm on a big time kick. I watched Sidehackers last night and really enjoyed. The movie is so icky but the jokes are great, especially the Sidehackin' song (lyrics below).  Yeah, I'm trapped up in outer space. Sometimes my life feels like a big pile of nothing. So what? Word! I live with it, dig it? But now me and my bloods would like to wail out a song about our friends the Sidehackers and it goes like this.  Sidehackin' is the thing to do and it doesn't hurt to have a low I.Q. Take your (unintelligible) and a little luck Big-bang prize is twenty-five bucks. Sidehack'll quench your danger thirst the stupid ones always seem to come in first - yeah!  Sidehackin' is one big bash The favorite sport of cheap white trash When you're on your Sidehack make sure you don't slip You'll end up with five metal pins in your hip Lean way back till you'll scrape your butt Make it look like a quarter pound of ground chuck - yeah!  It's the sport that attracts a lot of racing fools A lot of people get hurt 'cause there are no rules All you need is a toxic land fill A cycle and a sidecar and an urge to kill Better get with the sport 'cause it won't last long The founders of the sport are laid at Forest Lawn.  So, yeah. Anytime I spend large amounts of time at  urlLink Ward E  I start to feel like a huge nerd. It's okay though. I'm glad that I'm a huge MSTie. In fact the world needs more MSTies, a lot more. I actually think MST is what I miss the most about college. Not the episodes, cause I can watch them now, but just having fun with friends watching the show. MST is really a community event, its just not the same by yourself. Anyway, at college I could always count on watching MSTs with friends at least once a month. It's so hard finding MSTies out of school. I'd like to start a group of people that just meets and watches an episode or two once in a while. So if you're a MSTie and in the vicinity of Pittsburgh, get in touch!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Back from vacation. Had a good time walking through Rome and seeing tons of amazing artwork. I definitely have a whole new appreciation for both Caravaggio and Bernini. Some of Bernini's sculptures are utterly breathtaking! My favorite day of the week was definitely when I got to explore Villa Borghese on my own.   The Villa Borghese is a gorgeous park in Northern Rome. Nestled in the far northeast corner of the park is the Galleria Borghese, a wonderful museum. I got an audio guide and spent just over two hours in awe of the sheer amount of amazing pieces including six Caravaggio paintings, four Bernini statues, Raphael's  Deposition , and numerous other masterpieces. There was also a pretty Italian girl who was walking through the Galleria on virtually my same schedule on the audio guide. Every once in a while we steal a glance at one another and then keep walking. We never really spoke and I kinda like that. Anyway it was a beautiful day.   After going through the museum I had lunch sitting next to the fountain at Piazza Navona (another Bernini masterpiece), had a little too much wine and walked back for one last look at St. Peter's. Awesome, awesome day.     Last night, I finally got caught up on home stuff and went to see  Before Sunset . I absolutely loved it. It's even more bittersweetly romantic than the first one and the ending is one of the most perfect movie endings I've seen in a long time. It's just over the halfway point in 2004 so it seems like a good time to evaluate the year in movies so far.           Miracle : Disney sports movie, but a damn good one. I'm probably biased though.      The Passion : Big controversy, beautifully crafted and powerful film. A visual masterpiece.      Starsky & Hutch : Saw it. Do I really care? No. Ben Stiller-Owen Wilson movies are now becoming stale and formulaic. Don't you just love movies that tread a sea of stupid jokes and retarded sexuality?      Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind : The pinnacle of Charlie Kaufman, Jim Carrey, and Kate Winslett's careers to date. The first of two romantic masterpieces this year.      The Ladykillers : More Coen bros. goodness. Tom Hanks' best performance in years. Very funny, very smart, very creative. Lot's of people don't like this movie (They were the ones who were first in line to see  Starsky & Hutch ).      Kill Bill, Vol. 2 : Just when I thought I couldn't dislike Quentin Tarantino anymore I saw this. Can we stop regarding him as a genius filmmaker please. Tarantino is a film god for pseudo cinephiles.  Kill Bill  may be a lot of things but it sure the hell isn't anything close to resembling art.      Shrek 2 : Kinda funny now, meaningless 15 years from now. Virtually the exact same plot as the first movie. Also I'm getting tired of kids movies made for adults and stupid reference humor.      Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban : The best Potter movie by far. Cuaron's visuals are amazing and the darkness fits wonderfully into the film. Michael Gambon grew on me very well as Dumbledore and Emma Thompson was fantastic. If you complain about this being too different from the book please get the hell out of my face. Can't wait for  Goblet .      Saved! : Could have been really good, ends up just being moral relativist bullshit. If you don't cringe when a character says, "Why would God give us feelings if he didn't want us to follow them?" then something is wrong.      Dodgeball : see  Starsky & Hutch  above. Same movie, more trash.      Fahrenheit 9/11 : I only saw it as a lark. Anyone who thinks Moore's hackneyed filmmaking is solid documentary is too blinded by political views to be objective. He's not a very good filmmaker, or writer, or groomer for that matter.      Spider-Man 2 : The first movie was mediocre, this was fantastic. I generally dislike comic book movies so this was a pleasant surprise. It's a real movie instead of a basement-dwelling geek's wet dream. I applaud Sam Raimi and Michael Chabon as well.      The Saddest Music in the World : Insane, above-average Guy Maddin freakfest. Kind of humorous and it almost works as a real movie (a stretch for Maddin). I'll catch flack for this, but I think it's a better post-modern musical than  Moulin Rouge!  (which I have soured on).      Dogville : A brilliant and infuriating Lars von Trier film. Very creative, original, and daring. I may not like his viewpoints but he's a heck of a filmmaker.      Coffee and Cigarettes : Jim Jarmusch, 'nuff said. Brilliant, offbeat, funny stuff.      Before Sunset : The second romantic masterpiece of the year, probably the best film so far this year.        
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Does anybody else think that the elevated stands that you use for gerunds when diagramming a sentence are cool?  Yeah, I'm almost positive that I'm alone on that one.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's just about less than 10 days until I leave for Rome and I'm starting to get fairly excited. I spent last night leafing through my guidebook trying to figure what I wanted to see. Today I bought foreign currency online! Amazing the things you can do nowadays. I haven't really been thinking about the trip at all and last night it sort of hit that in less than two weeks I'll be walking around the epicenter of the Renaissance. The weekend was pretty fun. The Pirates doubleheader was a blast. The first game featured an 11 strikeout performance by Oliver Perez, a grand slam, and an inside-the-park homerun (all by the Pirates nonetheless). The second game was another Pirates blowout followed by a cool fireworks show. One of the most fun times I've had at the ballpark in years. Saturday afternoon it was home for family stuff, which was exhausting. Then I got back to the apartment around 10 and got ready to go out again for the midnight screening of  Holy Grail . When I went to pick up Jen I couldn't remember which house was hers and was about 15 minutes late. Then on the way to the theater I didn't give a car crossing the train tracks the proper right of way. On the way home I almost ran a red light.  This brings me to a problem I have. Whenever I have a girl in the car, regardless of the context, my driving falls a few notches down the ladder. I must have messed up like 3 or 4 times when I went out with Meghan on Valentine's day '03. When Jaime and I went to see  Punch-Drunk Love  I was late because I couldn't find her place, I made the wrong turn trying to find the theater and I went out the wrong exit at the Waterfront. And, don't forget the infamous trip to the Dixon's house to watch  The Joy Luck Club  for Contemporary Lit class. I'm sure there are numerous other occasions that I can't think of because I've blocked them out of my memory. I don't think its nervousness, I just stop thinking for some reason. The movie was fun though, despite my lack of driving/thinking ability. I ended up being more tired then I thought I would be. The day at my parents' place really wore me out.  On a side note that has nothing to do with anything, my new favorite MST line is: "Never make light of  boing , son." I guess you kinda have to see it to get the joke.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night was surreal. I was really struggling with some guilt issues and then I watched a movie that Scott let me borrow called  The Addiction . It's a low budget vampire movie, but it's a low budget vampire movie about sin. Watching the movie was like having a spiritual revelation. It's a fairly incredible little movie. Try and check it out if you can find it. Also, I had virtually no plans for the weekend going into the day and now I have plans all weekend long. Neal is coming down tonight and we're going to the Pirates doubleheader/fireworks night. Then on Saturday I'm going home for a family cookout in the afternoon/evening. Then Jen and I are going to the midnight screening of  Holy Grail  at the Oaks. Sunday, I recover. Monday I catch up on my reading. Pretty darn good.  I am still recovering from seeing  Fahrenheit 9/11 . I'm glad I saw it for discussion purposes but I just felt guilt giving Michael Moore money. That said, I don't think the movie will have any effect on the election whatsoever. Most people with brains can see how Moore spins and contorts in his films. And I've found that the most passionate Moore defenders are often very closed-minded. I think it's because Moore paints his world in black and white. Either you believe everything he says or you're stupid, evil, or both. Sure the US is not free of corruption, what country is. Anyone who thinks America is an evil, racist nation just hasn't bothered to look or doesn't care about the history of the rest of the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Cast Adrift in a Sea of Blood & Cool   Consume and enjoy!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been seeing a lot of movies lately, but I feel fully up to date on this year in film so far. I caught  The Village  on Monday. It's not even close to being Shaymalan's best ( Unbreakable ), but its visually gorgeous and intriguing. It's politics are totally crap. This weekend will be full of movies that I'm excited about. Tonight (Thursday): I'll be checking out the new version of  The Manchurian Candidate , which I'm expecting to disappoint, but it should provide great article fodder. Friday: I'll be seeing the Director's Cut of  Donnie Darko  with some folks. I'm really excited about it.  Darko  is one of my favorite films of recent years. Saturday: I'll watch Luchino Visconti's  The Leopard  at home. Then I'm heading to a potluck dinner in the evening before the group goes out to see a double feature of  Psycho  and  The Birds . Hitchcock on the big screen is a revelation. Sunday: In between church services I'll be going to see  Collateral , which looks incredible. I'm a Michael Mann supporter and I've done a complete 180 on Tom Cruise. I now think he's a fantastic actor. Lot's of movies, lot's of fun 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>