<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        OUT here   It's funny, I've been talking lately with different groups of friends about the differences between guys and girls. One that seems to hold true with most guys is that they all think they're the best and coolest and everyone wants to know everything about them, while, girls like me think...Hmmm...who would ever care? However, here I am--blogging.   You see, thinking, writing, typing and hitting the send key is scary in a lot of ways. Once you do that, it's OUT there. There's no taking it back after that. There are no revisions, no changing your mind. It's not safe anymore because you are taking a risk.   Back to the girls/people like me. Being so OUT there can be terrifying for our kind because we fear that we'll be given a grade by those who see what we have to say. If we stink, we'll never know about it. We don't get a grade back that says, B+ or A-. We get nothing back. I'm shaking in my boots right now thinking about it.  That's my take today. I'll blog later about evil cell phones and why I just got one for the first time in my life, last October.  I'm out.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        We Are Getting Satellite Tomorrow    This is going to be my exciting story about getting out of the stone an into the 21st century.  Apparently there are other tv stations than local networks.  I know that sounds incredible, but it is true.  There are stations that are news all the time.  Can you believe 'dat?  I can't.    You need to check it out.  I will keep you posted.  I hear there are more than 10 stations.  What will I do?  I am thinking about quitting my job so that I will have more time to watch tv.  Peace.   --This Blog was created on behalf of Milton by the wonderfully creative mind behing the  urlLink MurDogBlog 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The First Blog    SO, this is my first blog EVER. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Good Times Had By All    You know when the weather is perfect and you're in a beautiful place camping with good friends after just having What-a-Burger for lunch? Could you just tell me, what is better than that for your birthday (except for Pizza Junction)? March 27th fell on a Saturday this year and we hopped in Vern, our car, and drove down to Petit Jean State Park for some camping, hiking, cooking on a campfire and S'mores.   We got there just about lunch time and as we were driving in, we passed a State Park EMT vehicle whizzing past us with its' sirens on. We thought, "huh..." So, we head out to campsite 16 to join our friends. Once we got there and got our gear all set up, we put on our hiking shorts, took our dog, Allie, and we all headed out to Cedar Falls.   So, we get to the main lodge and there are all these park rangers with their walky-talkies looking all serious and we all looked at each other and knew there had been an accident. Nuts. We took off down the Cedar Falls trail, 2.2 miles to the END ALL...the waterfall. Allie is "captain cutie" sniffing all the other dogs making friends, and lapping up water all along the trail. We're about a fourth of the way down the really steep part when we saw it, like out of a Stephen King book.  There was a guy on a stretcher with about a dozen EMT/hikers carrying him up the mountain. At first all I could do was stare, but then, I started to get that sick feeling. He had fallen 75 ft. off of Bear Cave. Everything was broken and bloody. Christian and Brian offered to carry him up the rest of the trail to give the guys a break. They had to have been carrying him over a mile. My friend, Meredith and I, just sat on the trail and watched them carry him until we couldn't see them anymore.   I feel like there is this specific dark black cloud that follows me sometimes. Like when the Lada outside my flat in Estonia was blown up by the Russian maffia, or like when I got Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever in Asheville, NC or when our cabbies in St. Petersburg, Russia got pulled over and arrested for DWI, and use and posession of cocaine after the scariest car ride and loudest techno experience of my life.   This stuff just happens and even when it's awkward, as morbid as that is, I always wish I had gotten a picture. So, sure enough, we heard about him on the news. He lived and they said that 1-2 people fall a year at Petit Jean.   Crazy, crazy birthday! It ended up awesome though. We made Hobo pockets on the fire, corn on the cob and S'mores! And oh ya, Christian got poisin ivy like a champ.     
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         there are no kangaroos in austria...   How great is that? It was on a tshirt i saw the other day. when i blogged last, we had just done the day part of salzburg...the night part was a blast. we went to the town and had dinner at an authentic austrian rest. we, once again, sat at a table with 4 straight up austrians. the restaurant had had the same owners for 50 years and they were retiring, so they had a band (a tuba and an accordian) and just like the stereotype, were drinking liters of beer and locking arms and rocking back and forth singing austrian folk songs...it was so hard not to laugh in amazement that we were really getting a chunk of this authenticity...so we of course joined in!!! we got Spiezl (a local brew) and raised our steins and sang away. it is times like those that we wish we had a video camera to take it back to our friends and fam to prove it actually happened. gotta run and make hotel resercations in london...more on vienna later...we went to the world famous opera. i have seen only a few operas in my life and this one was sang to perfection...more later...buh bie now...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Germany & Austria   were here in salzburg, austria and have had the most interesting supper encounters with foreigners. we got in last night at 8.00 and went out to grab a bite to eat at a local rest. we had to sit at another table (they just seat you there and everyones cool with it) and we sat with some Australians. they were so great...and so drunk. we talked about our president...the war...wal-mart...american thoughts and cultural questions...we had a blast. they took our picture and we took one too...they kissed us on the cheeks goodbye. today we visited mozarts home and another museum. this is the first rainy days weve had...later on
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Paris, Switzerland & on to Germany    I cant even begin to explain how amazing this all is so far. Paris was Paris...we had a freaking picnic with a bottle of wine at the base of t^he Eiffel Tower.   Gimmewald, Switzerland was the most beautiful place Ive been on Gods green earth...we saw the Schilthorn mountain at 10000 feet...  Were in Zurich right now waiting to catch a train to Munich and cant even begin to imagine what the rest of this trip will be like.  I gotta jet, im paying for this in swiss franks....and we have a train to catch....  Im out for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo dude. This is the stuff. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        EUROPE    5.4.04  Wow. We leave for Europe in 16 days. Ever since I lived overseas in 98-99 in Estonia, and my parents and I never got to take the 'tour of Europe trip' we planned, I've dreamed about going back and seeing all the things I had mapped out to see. I just have to be extremely thankful that the guy I married, Christian, has the same love to travel, explore and go on adventures.  Welp, we've been married 4 1/2 years and we're finally doing it. We leave May 20th to begin our romp on Europe. We'll be gone for three weeks in total. No worries...Kelsey Walker is keeping my dog and picking up the paper. We fly into Paris and will stay there for four days, we hop on a train and head to Switzerland where we'll travel to Interlocken, Gimmewald and Zurich. From Zurich, we head up to Munich where we'll spend a day and take a bus to Rothenburg, or as you might have heard it, The Romantic Road. Hubba hubba.  We stay there for a night or two, depending on how fast we can pry ourselves away, and then we hop on a train to Vienna and Salzburg. We stay there a couple days and then take a train to Prague. When I was in Estonia, all the Estonians said, "You must see Praha." That's Prague in American. :)   We'll stay in Prague for a few days and then fly to London. I'm extremely pumped that we're able to fly at $60 bucks a ticket to London...how cool is that? Then we stay in London for like four days, I think, and then head home.  It's going to be amazing. It's all I can think about. If you think about it, pray for our safety while we're there. There's all kinds of old European monsters, ya know? Oh, and also, stop by my garage sale on May 15th. We're selling everything but our souls so we can do more while we're there!   I'll try to give updates while we're there and as time permits.   Take care all, Milton
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         CURVEBALLS...   Well, all I have to report now is that life has high highs and low lows and you never know which is coming when. Lately, I've come to the knowledge that they can come back to back and one day can change the rest of your life. I've known this before today, but just wanted to shed some light on the last couple weeks.  From Europe to my little wreck that gave me the opportunity to receive letters from attorneys wanting to 'help' me with the small case of whiplash...to hardship dear friends are going through that makes me want to take their pain away...to NYC and what a blast that was...to a 13 year old girl stuck in ICU with a torn kidney and head trauma from a 4-wheeling accident...life gives us so much change.  I'm thankful that we have our health. I'm putting my trust in the hand of Jesus, asking me to step out of the boat onto stormy waters. Curveballs come from every direction. Trusting that God is in tomorrow is all we can do. Rest there sweet friends and family. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Birthday.... at Sassafrass&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I Took My First Bite of the Big Apple  I blogged this big blog about life since we got back from our last trip and went to publish it and it fizzled and died. I hate it when that happens. So, I'm missing some stuff that was probably blog-worthy, but I'm here now to tell the tales of NYC.  My mom, Dee (who we all call Momma Dee), came up from Little Rock last Thursday, June 17th, and after work we jotted up to XNA to fly to NYC. Christian has 40 mandatory hours of CPE classes as a CPA that he has to fulfill every year to keep his CPA current, so this year his firm sent him to The Big Apple. Not too bad at all!  So, with two nights of free hotels and one free plane ticket, the three of us got a little trip together to make a weekend out of it! Other than our plane being delayed five hours and getting into NYC at 3.00 am, our trip got off to a great start. We hit the ground running Friday morning and did Times Square, saw Biff Henderson of the David Letterman Show, saw a Broadway show, ate a $20 cheeseburger, etc.   The show was a blast. We saw "Thoroughly Modern Milly" on Broadway and it was so entertaining. Story line: it was about a girl who comes from Kansas to make it big and her pursuit of success, love, and life. It was great and we enjoyed the entire experience. The best of the best perform there and you could tell.  We saw the Brooklyn Bridge, Greenwich Village, went to the Metropolitan  Museum, took a horse and carriage ride through Central park (at mom's request of the two things she wanted to do while we were there), Empire State Building, Battery Park, Statue of Liberty, Ground Zero, yadda, yadda, yadda...we just went and went. We did stop, however for RCV to go to ESPN Zone to catch the last few innings of the College World Series for the AR/AZ game. I think it's safe to saw that we were definitely the only ones there to catch that game... Hey, a fan is a fan is a fan, right?   My mom got pulled aside by a cop when she was looking at buying a knock-off Gucci watch from a street vendor. She was mortified. It was so hard not to laugh because she was just to innocent about the whole thing. She bought it for $15 later! No worries.  We had reservations for Tavern on the Green for brunch on Sunday morning. That was good to do something special with mom on Father's Day. The last time she went to NY it was with my Dad, like over 10 years ago or something. So, I'm glad that worked out. It was special.  Welp, that's all I've got for now. I had a wreck last week and got a mad case of whiplash. No worries...I'm doing neck rolls and taking muscle relaxers so I'm actually doing great...  Love to all, Milton    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Home on the Range...  Welp, we made it in last night. Our house didn't burn down, we have like 45 thousand newpapers and a hee haw load of mail to go through. Ah, the joys of returning home from a three-week happy time. While we enjoyed our amazing and once-in-a-lifetime trip to Europe, I have to say that I'm glad to be home. Three weeks was perfect for our lifestyle. I think it would be different if we were students or jobless...homeless...dogless..friendless and familyless. But since we are not those things, coming home is sweet as well.  I honestly don't think you'll believe what I'm about to write...we saw a celebrity in London at Starbucks after an entire night's worth of food poisining from yummy Indian food that I got to taste not only at dinner, but again and again starting at 12.30 am, through the rest of the night. Curry...schmurry is all I have to say. Ick.  So, we had this big day trip in mind to see all this cool architecture and art...that actually got pushed back a day because I'd walk about ten steps and just about faint. So, we're in Leicester (pronounced Lester) square and going to Starbucks to get a hydrating beverage and sit for a spell, when lo and behold...the king of American television is two people behind us in line. Can you guess???? JERRY SPRINGER! No lie. I'm so for real. We got a picture with him...he's surprisingly an incredibly nice and cordial man. He spoke with us for about five minutes and then we got a pic and he shook our hands and wished us well. So, of all people to see in London, we see Jerry. It was a riot. We would be walking around later in London and just say, "we just met Jerry Springer."   London was great. The food stunk. I mean horribly stunk. I can make better food in my own kitchen than those Brits. We managed to make it to Starbucks daily and even twice daily, since they were literally at every 1/2 block. We also had Ben & Jerry's ice cream...twice. I had homemade Oatmeal Cookie once and A Piece of Cake another time. Both were so good they make you want to slap your momma.   Trying not to sound redundant, London was just so amazing. It has so much history. We saw the crown jewels at The Tower of London. We saw the London Bridge, the millenium bridge, the National Museum, The British White House where Tony Blaire lives, the Tate Modern Art museum, the changing of the guard at Buckingham palace, just everything. We were such tourists...it was great. We had an old Canon around our neck with a swanky rainbow strap and our new digital camera and everything. We snapped pictures like popparazi (sp?).  Now, we're at home and we had American coffee this morning and read the national and local newspapers. Life is good. Oh, last night Christian's parents took us to none other than La Huerta...they don't have Mexican food there so Mexican was a treat.  I have that funny feeling in the pit of my stomach and it's the feeling that you get when you're either a) homesick  b) in love  c) upon the revelation of something amazing that God's teaching you, or d)about to puke. I believe it's C mostly...maybe some B too (blushing...) Seriously though, the clarity and global picture that you're blessed with sometimes in life's pursuit is a blessing from God. It's like when you feel like you're about to burst. I know that God gave me little gifts all along this trip. They're not gifts that you can actually touch of feel physically, but the kind that are only from God. You know...the ones that just freeze you in time like a snapshot and make you feel that feeling, like, "this is my life..."   Christian and I had lunch today at Penguin Ed's...another very American delicacy. We made a promise to never forget what we saw and more importantly felt on this trip. That's all I have to say for now. Love to all...   Jerry Springer is our new favorite celebrity but I still won't watch his show, Milton
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So-Ho!   Welp, London is so fun. It's big and busy and we've had to figure out the Metro and lines will close without warning, but it's great! We've seen a whole lot...even Sherlock Holmes old haunts. I've had to get Christian to stop talking British...he thinks it's funny. We also saw someone get kicked off the Metro today for sticking his foot out in front of the train while it was coming. They straight up called him out on the loud speaker and what he was wearing and told everyone that we'd delay and just sit there until he got off. I got his picture. It's hilarious. After minutes of waiting for him to get his boots off the tubs...he got escorted off. Anway, since then, we keep saying, "Mind the Gap!" Which is what they say so you won't fall into the deep pits of subway hell and die. It's a service they provide, really.   We're just winding down and in disbelief that tomorrow we're on a plane back home and it's all over. Hmmmm...it's kind of sad just actually typing that. Wanka. Welp, I'll show you all the pix and my travel journal that I've kept everyday as soon as I see ya!   We love you all and still ask for your prayers for our safe return home tomorrow, Milton & Christian  P.S. We were so saddened to hear of President Reagan's passing. I know my family will miss him...we actually had his picture in our house growing up. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Pra HA!   Mmm Mmm Mmm. Words, words, words just can't explain this wicked cool town. Prague is a favorite. It's amazing and beautiful and has so much history. I'm SO glad we gave this place an extra day. Other than the hotels being pricey, everything else is cheap (or cheap if you can talk the vendors down). We have seen the biggest castle in the world here. We've gotten the history being the Christmas carol "Good King Wenceslas"... he's from here and there are tributes, town squares and statues in his honor all over. He's actually not a king.   The Charles Bridge is beautiful. It beats Paris' bridges hands down. I have a thing for bridges anyway...but this one is spectacular. All in all, we've eaten this place up. We got some original art that I'm so jazzed about. I have been saving my souvenir $$ just for the art here and I'm excited about the oil and the acrylics that we found.   We're headed to London tomorrow. I'm pretty worn out. It will be good to get to a place that speaks English. We're running ourselves ragged, but it's completely worth it.   We get home the first part of next week and I have to be at work on Wednesday...wanka.   Welp, Love to all and we'll see you soon, RCV & EMV
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       We're Going to Swim, Shop and See the Show    &nbsp;  Welp, we're headed out tonight to see Mr. John Mayer in concert in Dallas, TX. Hollie, Katie, Jill and I are loading up after work and making the trek to see a worthy show. We're meeting up&nbsp;with Penick and she's coming with us. She's also letting us bunk at her casa. (thanks Penny)    &nbsp;  We've got lawn seats&nbsp;so we'll be outside in the humid Dallas air with our crazy creeks, some snacks and good company. But, before the show, we're gunna make up syncronized swimming routines, then shop at like Urban Outfitters...Restoration Hardware...Eat some good supper...It will be good times had by all!    &nbsp;  More later on yo...    &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Africa Hot   For the longest time, we had been having a mild June filled with lots of rain and breezy days. Welp, now it's Africa hot here in Fayetteville. It's the drippy, nasty, singe your nose hairs hot. Love that...  Last weekend we went down to LR for some crazy busy wedding and baby showers and hoopla. Friday night we made it through a summer shower to get to Maumelle to stay with my sister. All my family was there and my cousin, aunt and neices and nephews. We ate pizza and my mom and I taught Braxton, my nephew how to play baseball. He's a riot. I just love that little monkey...I have to say, he loves his Ant Wizabith too.  A bunch of us gave a baby shower for one of my best friends, Allison Arrington Ridings. She's due in August and was very full of baby Ben. The shower was a blast...something like 90 people were invited and like 60 people showed up so we were glad for a good turn out! A bunch of us girls went swimming after that and then I had to go to another shower for Chase Keet. She's a long time friend whose getting married in Destin at the end of July.   Straight from there we came clear across town back to my Aunt Angie and Uncle Larry's house for a cookout with my brother and his wife, my sister and her husband, my nephew, my cousin Amy ard her husband Jason and their baby darlin, Sophia, my other cousin David and his wife Allison and their son Lawson..it was awesome. It's so fun to have cool family you like to hang out with!  More later on...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Corn shuckin'   Well, last Thursday after work, we came home packed up and went to Christian's folks in Tulsa. When we got there we went to eat with them and got to hang out with his Mamaw on Friday. It was good times with family. We came back and went to eat at Abuelo's with Cassie and Clay Dodson, and saw Spiderman II. It was good stuff... I dug it.  Sunday we went to church, out to lunch with Bryan & Erika Lewis, ran errands and went home to  'put up'  a bushel of Merit corn we'd gotten at this farmer's market in Bixby. Christian's Grandpa farmed corn up until his Alzheimer's got so bad he would forget what he planted where and would dig up cantaloupes, watermelons, and tear down bean plants and just try to start over in the middle of the summer. It was the saddest thing I've ever seen. Farming was like second nature to him and he couldn't remember what was where. He grew the best, sweetest corn you've ever put in your mouth and every year Christian's entire family would go there and put the corn up on a hot July day.   We shuck it, cut the ends off, silk it, give each ear a good rinsing in a bucket of water to get the worms and yuck off, and then we put it up. This entails taking each cob and cutting the precious sweet corn right off the cob, then going back with the back of your knife and scraping all the rest of the corn and sweet natural juices off, we measure it out by cups into 1 quart freezer bags that lasts us for most of the year. Now that I've had "Cecil corn" I just can't go back.   So afer that we cooked out at Scott & Amy McMurtrey's/Jonathan & Elizabeth Beasley's cul-de-sac for some good food and some mad home grown firework shows. Good times had by all. I love the fourth. I love summer foods...tomatoes, homemade strawberry jam, corn, canteloupes, cherries, snap peas...I'm going home and going to make BLT's tonight. Yum.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Big Florida Wedding...   Last Wednesday night after work, we did the first very short leg of our trip to Destin. We got to LR late and helped Momma Dee pack and got ready to wake up at 5 AM. It was brutal. My mom's best friend, Tami, got the new mid-size Cadillac SUV and it was pimpin. We thought..."this will be the best and easiest trip to Destin ever!" We were so wrong. Tami was a chatty Cathy and the worst driver I've ever ridden with in my life.  She would be talking to my mom, and jerk to the right, to the left...put on the brakes for a semi 345 yards ahead...I've never been so carsick in my life. We were literally plucking our eyebrows out one at a time. We did watch Two Towers in the car and could put a different CD in other than the best of Michael W. Smith they were playing up front.  Moms and their friends...they're the best worst. We did make it to Florida in  12  hours on the way down there. It should have been 9 1/2 or 10 at the most. But, we made it. Our cottage was great and it's location was even better. We did the bridesmaids' luncheon and a shrimp boil and everything...the wedding was a blast...so we got there Thursday and came back early Sunday morning. The good news about the make-you-wanna-vomit quick trip to Florida is that, on the way back, Christian got to drive the first half all the way to Jackson. Tami wanted to drive the last half and I got sick again...so I just slept...what else can you do?  We went to Outer Banks, NC last year, but of all the places we've been together, we have only been to the beach once...and it was cold. So, I was glad Christian got to come to Destin. I grew up going there every year so it's fun he got to see a surfer catch a live jellyfish and plop it in front of us so we could watch it die.  Love to all, Milton  P.S. I'm passing on the annual trip to Penick's lakehouse this weekend. I'm very sad. All my buds will be there, but next weekend we'll be out of town again...with RCV's Tulsa buddies at a cabin on the White River fishing. That'll be fun too yo. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>